<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-20T14:14:03.739Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T14:14:03.739Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominates, Crypto Markets Stand Firm: Binance H1 Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786179/Bitcoin-Dominates-Crypto-Markets-Stand-Firm-Binance-H1-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786179/Bitcoin-Dominates-Crypto-Markets-Stand-Firm-Binance-H1-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's mid-year review showcases that the crypto market, and Bitcoin are resilient, despite a turbulent 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance report shows crypto industry in “good health” in H1, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786174/Binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-H1-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786174/Binance-report-shows-crypto-industry-in-good-health-in-H1-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeways The crypto industry experienced growth across Bitcoin and other L1s, L2s, stablecoins, DeFi, and NFTs. Bitcoin network growth included trading volume, transaction count, fees and hashrate. Solana, BNB Chain led L1s, while Liquid staking emerged as a key DeFi component. Binance has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK financial regulator launching permanent Digital Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786184/UK-financial-regulator-launching-permanent-Digital-Sandbox</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786184/UK-financial-regulator-launching-permanent-Digital-Sandbox"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization and Investing: A Look at Tomorrow's Democratized Landscape]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561257731</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/tokenization-and-investing-a-look-at-tomorrows-democratized-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, the financial landscape has witnessed the  
rise of blockchain technology and its potential to revolutionize various  
industries. One of the most promising applications of blockchain is  
tokenization, a process that involves representing real-world assets as digital  
tokens on a blockchain network. This innovation has the power to democratize  
investing, providing new opportunities for a broader range of investors to  
participate in previously exclusive asset classes. In this article, we explore  
how tokenization is transforming the investment landscape, its benefits, and  
the potential challenges that lie ahead.
A Game-Changer for  
Investors: What is Tokenization? 
Tokenization is the process of converting physical or  
financial assets, such as real estate, fine …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FM Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startale Labs accepts CBDC Forum invitation from Bank of Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786180/Startale-Labs-accepts-CBDC-Forum-invitation-from-Bank-of-Japan</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786180/Startale-Labs-accepts-CBDC-Forum-invitation-from-Bank-of-Japan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Japan has selected Startale Labs Japan, a subsidiary of Startale Labs, to participate in its CBDC Forum. … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US law protects institutions and exposes retail investors — Rep. Torres]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786175/US-law-protects-institutions-and-exposes-retail-investors-Rep-Torres</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786175/US-law-protects-institutions-and-exposes-retail-investors-Rep-Torres"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Representative Ritchie Torres had an exclusive interview with Cointelegraph to discuss why retail investors are still at risk following the XRP court ruling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liquid staking claims top spot in DeFi: Binance report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786145/Liquid-staking-claims-top-spot-in-DeFi-Binance-report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786145/Liquid-staking-claims-top-spot-in-DeFi-Binance-report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonland Inches Closer to NFT Airdrop Following Early Access Announcement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561271d81</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/moonland-inches-closer-to-nft-airdrop-following-early-access-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. MoonLand, the groundbreaking social multiplayer metaverse game, is set to redefine the gaming industry with its revolutionary play-to-earn mechanism and immersive gameplay experience. By blending blockchain technology, web 3.0 principles, and the economy model of the metaverse, MoonLand aims to captivate a global audience of gaming enthusiasts.
 
Unlock Early Access with MoonLand’s NFT Airdrop
 
In a significant announcement, MoonLand unveiled its highly anticipated NFT airdrop. Aspiring players have the exclusive opportunity to sign the whitelist and secure their position among the first to receive coveted free NFTs. These unique tokens will not only grant early access to the game but also make participants eligible for a subsequent airdrop of 42 MTK (MoonLand Tokens).
 
MT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto whales targeted in wave of home invasions near Vancouver]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786139/Crypto-whales-targeted-in-wave-of-home-invasions-near-Vancouver</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786139/Crypto-whales-targeted-in-wave-of-home-invasions-near-Vancouver"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got a lot of crypto? Watch out for robbers posing as couriers, police say, as a pattern of crypto home invasions has emerged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tech Renaissance: AI And Big Data Push 300% Growth In 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756127eaeb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-ai-and-big-data-push-300-growth/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fusion of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and “Big Data” has emerged as a standout phenomenon in the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency. This dynamic sector has earned its place among the top 10 industries experiencing a remarkable market cap growth this year.
 
Revolutionizing the way data is processed and utilized, the AI and Big Data sector uses sophisticated algorithms and machine learning techniques to analyze vast datasets. 
 
By extracting invaluable insights, these domains play a pivotal role in reshaping various industries through data-driven decision-making, predictive analytics, and widespread automation. The result is a substantial boost in efficiency and innovation across sectors.
 
Big data is the term for the enormous, varied sets of information that multiply at an expon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Added Bitcoin Payments Back To Their Website: Rumor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756127eae6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tesla-added-bitcoin-payments-back-rumor/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the Bitcoin community was set abuzz with a tantalizing rumor suggesting that Tesla might be rekindling its love affair with BTC payments.The spark was ignited by a Twitter user who discovered that BTC can still be found in the source code of Tesla’s official website, alongside Apple Pay, Bancontact and other payment options.
 
 
The discovery that Bitcoin and Dogecoin payment options were still lingering in Tesla’s source code added fuel to the speculation that the electric vehicle giant might soon resume accepting BTC payments. Many enthusiasts were quick to interpret this as a possible signal of a Bitcoin comeback spearheaded by Elon Musk.
 
However, as the excitement escalated, the rumor was promptly debunked. Closer examination revealed that while the source code contained refer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin (FIL) Support Arrived from Bitcoin Mining Giant!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786143/Filecoin-FIL-Support-Arrived-from-Bitcoin-Mining-Giant</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786143/Filecoin-FIL-Support-Arrived-from-Bitcoin-Mining-Giant"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin mining device manufacturer and industry leader Bitmain has announced that it will produce mining devices for Filecoin. Continue Reading: Filecoin (FIL) Support Arrived from Bitcoin Mining Giant!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Who Replaces Do Kwon as Terraform Labs’ New CEO (Report)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786136/This-Is-Who-Replaces-Do-Kwon-as-Terraform-Labs-New-CEO-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786136/This-Is-Who-Replaces-Do-Kwon-as-Terraform-Labs-New-CEO-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Op-ed: US banks launch 24/7 Instant Payments – does FedNow reduce risk of CBDCs?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786132/Op-ed-US-banks-launch-247-Instant-Payments-does-FedNow-reduce-risk-of-CBDCs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786132/Op-ed-US-banks-launch-247-Instant-Payments-does-FedNow-reduce-risk-of-CBDCs"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Reserve’s (Fed) long-awaited instant payment service, FedNow, is set to launch imminently, promising a significant development in the country’s payment system. As reported by Reuters on July 20, with this service, everyday Americans will soon be able to send and receive funds in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tech Renaissance: AI And Big Data Push 300% Growth In 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786088/Crypto-Tech-Renaissance-AI-And-Big-Data-Push-300-Growth-In-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786088/Crypto-Tech-Renaissance-AI-And-Big-Data-Push-300-Growth-In-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimism among Binance professional investors about crypto predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786096/Optimism-among-Binance-professional-investors-about-crypto-predictions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786096/Optimism-among-Binance-professional-investors-about-crypto-predictions"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence in the long-term crypto trend among Binance investors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DEXs Account For 5% Of Global Stablecoin Trading: Kaiko]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786134/DEXs-Account-For-5-Of-Global-Stablecoin-Trading-Kaiko</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786134/DEXs-Account-For-5-Of-Global-Stablecoin-Trading-Kaiko"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken’s Crypto Facilities appoints hedge fund veteran as CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786102/Krakens-Crypto-Facilities-appoints-hedge-fund-veteran-as-CEO</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786102/Krakens-Crypto-Facilities-appoints-hedge-fund-veteran-as-CEO"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surpasses $30,000; Stellar Emerges As Top Gainer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786123/Bitcoin-Surpasses-30000-Stellar-Emerges-As-Top-Gainer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786123/Bitcoin-Surpasses-30000-Stellar-Emerges-As-Top-Gainer"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) traded higher, with the cryptocurrency prices rising above the key $30,000 level on Thursday. Ethereum (CRYPTO: ETH) also moved higher, trading above the key $1,900 mark this morning. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolf Of All Streets worries about a world where Bitcoin hits $1M: Hall of Flame]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786092/Wolf-Of-All-Streets-worries-about-a-world-where-Bitcoin-hits-1M-Hall-of-Flame</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786092/Wolf-Of-All-Streets-worries-about-a-world-where-Bitcoin-hits-1M-Hall-of-Flame"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former globe-trotting DJ Scott Melker — The Wolf Of All Streets — worries about the circumstances leading to Bitcoin topping $1 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP demand on Google hits a 1-year high]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786066/XRP-demand-on-Google-hits-a-1-year-high</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786066/XRP-demand-on-Google-hits-a-1-year-high"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unibot Leads Rise Of Telegram-Based Crypto Trading Bots, Facilitates $54M In Trades]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786124/Unibot-Leads-Rise-Of-Telegram-Based-Crypto-Trading-Bots-Facilitates-54M-In-Trades</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786124/Unibot-Leads-Rise-Of-Telegram-Based-Crypto-Trading-Bots-Facilitates-54M-In-Trades"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto traders are increasingly turning to Telegram-based trading bots, drawn by the convenience of executing transactions as simply as sending messages via the popular communication platform. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Rejects Proposal to Classify Crypto as Gambling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149343/uk-government-rejects-proposal-to-classify-crypto-as-gambling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government argued that classifying crypto asset trading as gambling would create a misalignment with global standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zeebu Inks Strategic Partnership with Hayo, Axistel and Qatama]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786058/Zeebu-Inks-Strategic-Partnership-with-Hayo-Axistel-and-Qatama</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786058/Zeebu-Inks-Strategic-Partnership-with-Hayo-Axistel-and-Qatama"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Zeebu Inks Strategic Partnership with Hayo, Axistel and Qatama Zeebu owns a revolutionary blockchain solution that tackles some of the unique problems faced in the telecom sector. Zeebu Inks Strategic Partnership with Hayo, Axistel and Qatama]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink (LINK) Jumps 19%, This Is Its Setup for New Levels]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786072/Chainlink-LINK-Jumps-19-This-Is-Its-Setup-for-New-Levels</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786072/Chainlink-LINK-Jumps-19-This-Is-Its-Setup-for-New-Levels"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink leading altcoin rally today]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: ETH Moves Past $1,900 as Traders End Losing Streak]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561231fc3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-eth-moves-past-1900-as-traders-end-losing-streak/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After six consecutive days trading in the red, ethereum bounced back on Thursday, once again climbing above the $1,900 mark. The move came as bitcoin also edged higher, after falling to a four-week low during Tuesday’s session. 
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) was marginally higher on Thursdays, as the cryptocurrency once again attempted to rebound from recent losses.
 
Following a low of $29,794.27 on Wednesday, BTC/USD rose to an intraday peak of $30,406.45 earlier in the day.
 
The move came as bitcoiners continued to move away from Tuesday’s fall below $30,000, which resulted in BTC hitting a four-week low.
 
 
Price stabilized as the relative strength index (RSI) found a firm floor at the 49.00 mark. It has now surged to a current reading of 53.60.
 
Traders are likely now targeting an upcoming ceiling at $30,800, which has historically been the last line of defense before entering the $31,000 zone.
 
Despite this target, momentum still appears to be bearish, as a result of the recent downwards crossover of the 10-day (red) and 25-day (blue) moving averages.
 
 
Ethereum
 
In addition to bitcoin, ethereum (ETH) rose back above $1,900 in today’s session, ending its own losing streak.
 
ETH/USD hit a high of $1,927.57 earlier in today’s session, which comes a day after edging to a low of $1,883.07.
 
Momentum has been largely bearish in the world’s second largest cryptocurrency in recent days, following last week’s rally.
 
 
Today’s move is the first day since last Thursday that ethereum has traded in the green, with traders still optimistic about future surges above $2,000.
 
A ceiling at $1,960 will likely be the main test for ethereum’s bull strength, and should it pass this level, it is highly likely the price will reach $2,000.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
What fundamentals are behind today’s price rebound? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Ritchie Torres: SEC Chair Gensler 'Intent on Sabotaging' Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149337</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149337/congressman-ritchie-torres-sec-chair-gensler-intent-on-sabotaging-crypto-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Ritchie Torres doubled down on his recent criticisms of Securities and Exchange Commission chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macro State of Crypto – Where It Has Been and What's Next]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75612dd98b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/20/macro-state-of-crypto-where-it-has-been-and-where-is-it-going/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analytics can offer insight into how recent and past crypto and regulatory events have affected prices and movement. Plus: A quick Q&A on retirement funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Morton, Greg Magadini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floor App Reveals Ethereum NFT Art Drops Exclusively on iOS and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149295/floor-app-reveals-ethereum-nft-art-drops-exclusively-on-ios-and-android"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Vinnie Hager will kickstart the series of drops so Floor can, in the CEO’s words, “meet people where they are—on their phone.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Labs Puts $10 Million Into Radiant Capital to Expand to Other Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149268/binance-radiant-capital-layer-2-cross-chain-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This investment will go toward enabling more Radiant users to move tokens across more chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: XRP Momentum Could Set Precedent for Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75612fe16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/20/first-mover-americas-xrp-momentum-could-set-precedent-for-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T12:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for July 20, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Gets Listed On Major Korean Exchange, Will It Impact SHIB Price?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561282518</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-shib-listed-on-major-korean-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T12:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) has scored a new listing: In the crypto space, fortunes can change overnight with a single exchange listing announcement. Riding the waves of its latest achievement, Shiba Inu (SHIB) has now secured a spot on Coinone, one of South Korea’s largest and most esteemed crypto exchanges. But the question on everyone’s mind is: Will this listing impact the SHIB price?
 
Shiba Inu Gets Listed On Coinone
 
The excitement is palpable as SHIB enthusiasts celebrate the news of its listing on Coinone. This strategic move marks a significant milestone for the meme-coin, allowing it to reinforce its presence in the heart of Asia and potentially attract an influx of new traders. Coinone, a well-established player in the South Korean market, has been in operation for an impressive nine yea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Govt. Rejects Lawmakers’ Push to Regulate Crypto Trading as Gambling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561285ee2</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/uk-govt-rejects-lawmakers-push-to-regulate-crypto-trading-as-gambling/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T12:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK Government has  
opposed the call by a panel of cross-party British lawmakers to regulate  
'unbacked' crypto assets such as Bitcoin and Ether as gambling. The executive arm argued  
that such treatment runs contrary to standards recommended by global bodies  
such as the G20 Financial Stability Board. 
‘Same Activity, Same Risk’
In a report published in May, the House of  
Commons' Treasury Committee argued that unbacked cryptocurrencies lack any intrinsic value or ‘discernible  
social good’ but instead carry ‘huge price volatility’. As a result, the Committee,  
which is headed by Harriet Baldwin MP, called for digital asset trading to be subjected to the same rules as gambling, Finance  
Magnates reported.
However, in  
a letter received by the House of Commons last Friday, Andr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX Get Spoofed in New Animated Comedy Starring T.J. Miller]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75612b6eba</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/web3/2023/07/20/sam-bankman-fried-and-ftx-get-spoofed-in-new-animated-comedy-starring-tj-miller/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T12:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An upstart Web3 studio satirizes the FTX saga in a new “interactive” series called "FORTUN3," debuting this fall.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Pachal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Regulatory Understanding, Bitcoin Mining Can Fuel Florida’s Energy Future]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561167cc5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-bitcoin-mining-can-fuel-the-future-of-florida"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Byron Donalds, the U.S. representative for Florida’s 19th congressional district, and Perianne Boring, founder and CEO of the Chamber Of Digital Commerce.
There are many reasons that businesses relocate to Florida, the welcoming regulatory and tax environments and the skilled and ready workforce among them. And these are certainly some of the reasons that many companies in the digital asset ecosystem — including Blockchain.com, Okcoin, Borderless Capital and BlockTower Capital — have moved out of such traditional tech regions as California, New York and the Pacific Northwest, for the friendlier sunshine and incentives of Florida.  
But there’s another reason digital asset firms are looking to Florida: the Sunshine State’s reliable energy grids and its increa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Byron Donalds,Perianne Boring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Financial Regulator to Introduce Digital Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756116e0da</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/20/uk-financial-regulator-to-introduce-digital-sandbox/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a pilot phase, the environment was used to test the eco-friendliness of decentralized ledgers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Trading in Japan Rises as Yen Turns Volatile]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756116e0d4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/20/bitcoin-trading-in-japan-rises-as-yen-turns-volatile/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The share of bitcoin trade volume on Japanese exchanges rose from 69% to 80% in the first six months of the year, data tracked by Kaiko show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDC: Chinese Digital Yuan Records $250 Billion In Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561109936</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cbdc-digital-yuan-records-250-billion-in-trans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China’s digital yuan has witnessed tremendous growth as the central bank ramps up its CBDC pilot in the last one-and-a-half year. According to the Chinese central bank governor, Yi Gang, within that period, the digital yuan has facilitated nearly $250 billion in transactions.
 
At a conference in Singapore held on July 19, Yi Gang disclosed that China’s central bank digital currency (CBDC) transacted 1.8 trillion yuan at the end of June. 
 
 
Digital Yuan Gains Traction, Records Nearly 1 Billion Transactions
 
According to the central bank governor, the digital yuan pilot recorded 950 million transactions from about 120 million wallets since its rollout in January 2022. That brought the average transaction amount to approximately $250 billion. Also, Yi claimed that about $2.3 billion (16.5…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Egyptian and Nigerian Central Banks Sign Agreement to Deepen Cross-Border Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75611139a9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/egyptian-and-nigerian-central-banks-sign-agreement-to-deepen-cross-border-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The central banks of Egypt and Nigeria have signed a fintech agreement to deepen the two institutions’ “cross-border regulatory collaboration” and information sharing. The London Institute of Banking & Finance, which also signed an MOU, will offer training programs, workshops, and courses to leaders in the Egyptian fintech sector.
 
MOU Agreement to Help Boost Innovation
 
On July 17, the Egyptian and Nigerian central banks announced the signing of a financial technology collaboration agreement. The signing of the memorandum of understanding (MOU) is expected to help “deepen cross-border regulatory collaboration” and information sharing between the two institutions.
 
Furthermore, the pact will help “boost innovation and grow regional technology investments.” The MOUs were signed on the si…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and NFTs Propel Crypto Market in H1 2023: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561125c8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitcoin-and-nfts-propel-crypto-market-in-h1-2023-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The digital asset website  
tracking the prices and trading volumes of cryptocurrencies, CoinMarketCap, has  
released a market analysis report for the first half of 2023. Although the  
report shows an increase in the cryptocurrency market capitalization year-to-date,  
the market cap for the first and the second quarter barely changed.
The global cryptocurrency market capitalization reached  
USD $1.17 trillion at the end of the second quarter, representing an increase of  
48% year-to-date. In the first quarter, the market capitalization was boosted by the rise in the price of Bitcoin and the heightened activity in the non-fungible tokens (NFT) market, CoinMarketCap noted.
Spot Trading Volumes
Additionally, according to CoinMarketCap, the  
trading of digital assets increased in the fir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's Bonds Have Skyrocketed Alongside Bitcoin in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149335</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149335/el-salvadors-bonds-have-skyrocketed-alongside-bitcoin-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the start of the year, both Bitcoin and El Salvador's government bonds have soared.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink’s LINK Climbs as Whales Add to Holdings Following Protocol Release]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75611d298a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/20/chainlinks-link-climbs-as-whales-add-to-holdings-following-protocol-release/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CCIP protocol is designed to help build cross-chain applications and services and went live for early access users on the Avalanche, Ethereum, Optimism and Polygon blockchains this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Myanmar Shadow Government to Start Neobank With Crypto Rails to Fund Fight Against Military Junta]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75611d2983</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/20/myanmar-shadow-govt-to-start-neobank-with-crypto-rails-to-fund-fight-against-military-junta/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Unity Government bank is set to run on Polygon and do currency swaps via Uniswap v3 pools and USDT stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavender Au</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Rejects Lawmaker Plan to Regulate Crypto as Gambling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75611d2977</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/20/uk-government-rejects-lawmaker-plan-to-regulate-crypto-as-gambling/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Treasury says it has learned lessons from FTX's collapse, and that gambling law doesn’t deal with crypto risks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Stuttering Litigation Strategy Draws Comment From France]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756118ee27</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/20/secs-stuttering-litigation-strategy-draws-comment-from-france/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T10:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French officials boast of crypto-ready laws that contrast with a stuttering enforcement campaign from the U.S. SEC – and are looking to the next generation of Web 3 gaming rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Bot Tokens Surge Toward $100M Market Cap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149313/telegram-bot-tokens-surge-toward-100m-market-cap"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T10:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sector has experienced massive growth in a short period, as projects such as Unibot and Ready Swap flood the markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Museums and Galleries Are Embracing Digital Art, Exploring AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149287/museums-and-galleries-are-embracing-digital-art-exploring-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T01:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of art, its accessibility, and its audience were explored at Christie’s Art+Tech Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT's Performance Is Slipping, New Study Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149272</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149272/chatgpts-performance-is-slipping-new-study-says"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UC Berkeley researchers found that ChatGPT has not improved over time, and in fact, may have gotten worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Billion People Will Go On-Chain Over the Next Decade: Coinbase Protocols Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149270/8-billion-people-onchain-blockchain-crypto-10-years-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Pollak is leading the exchange’s efforts on Base, its Ethereum-focused layer-2 network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orgasm NFTs? NARS Cosmetics Brand Reveals Eyebrow-Raising Art Auctions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149257</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149257/orgasm-nfts-nars-cosmetics-brand-reveals-eyebrow-raising-art-auctions"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NARS has teamed up with SuperRare and digital artists to drop NFTs for National Orgasm Day, continuing a trend for the beauty brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start Playing Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop'—Do You Need an NFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-start-playing-dr-disrespects-deadrop-do-you-need-an-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deadrop is currently in limited early access. Here’s how to unlock the first-person shooter game from Midnight Society.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Is Quietly Creating an AI Chatbot to Compete With ChatGPT: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149251/apple-is-quietly-creating-an-ai-chatbot-to-compete-with-chatgpt-report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike ChatGPT, Apple’s tool isn’t meant for public consumption, and the company has no plans to release it to consumers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia to Start Testing ‘Digital Ruble’ CBDC in August Barring Putin's Veto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149238</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149238/russia-to-start-testing-digital-ruble-cbdc-in-august-barring-putins-veto"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill still requires Vladimir Putin’s signature, but if approved, Russia will become one of the largest adopters of CBDCs to date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian Soccer Club AC Milan Extends Crypto Sponsorship With BitMEX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149241/italian-soccer-club-ac-milan-extends-crypto-sponsorship-bitmex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soccer giant AC Milan is sticking with BitMEX, two years after naming the exchange its official cryptocurrency trading partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Bill Would Give US Treasury Authority Over DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149234/bipartisan-bill-would-give-us-treasury-authority-over-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill’s sponsors highlighted DeFi and crypto ATMs as vectors for financial crime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Jackson Pollock’s Historic Paint-Splattered Floor Is Being Immortalized as NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149229/why-jackson-pollock-historic-paint-splattered-floor-being-immortalized-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An art collection from the Jackson Pollock Studio and Iconic Moments digitally preserves the famed painter's studio floor on Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Wants Bitcoin Backed U.S. Dollars and Tax Breaks for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149222/robert-f-kennedy-jr-wants-bitcoin-backed-u-s-dollars-and-tax-breaks-for-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Bitcoin is among the hardest currencies and the Kennedy administration is going to encourage its proliferation and propagation,” he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Won’t Replace Human Spies, Says Britain’s MI6 Chief]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149220</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149220/ai-wont-replace-human-spies-says-britains-mi6-chief"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of Britain’s SIS says ‘human factors’ important in intelligence gathering can’t yet be replicated by AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Delays Crypto Custody Until Regulatory Concerns Die Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149195/nasdaq-halts-crypto-custody-plans-citing-regulatory-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But Nasdaq CEO Adena Friedman said that the company would “remain committed to supporting the evolution of the digital asset ecosystem.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cymbal Launches 'Human Readable' Ethereum Blockchain Explorer—A Social Etherscan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149202/cymbal-human-readable-ethereum-blockchain-explorer-etherscan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike traditional explorers that can be difficult to understand, Cymbal is both visual and social—and aimed at the masses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is MiCA? What the EU Crypto Governing Framework Means for You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-mica-what-the-eu-crypto-governing-framework-means-for-you"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA does not cover most NFTs (except fractionalized NFTs and NFTs released as collections). Similarly, it does not cover DeFi apps that exist without an intermediary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Wants More Games—This Simple Tool Could Help Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149166/solana-wants-more-games-simple-tool-could-help-developers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameShift from Solana Labs aims to make blockchain game development easier for newcomers and traditional game studios alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ICO Whale Moves $116M in ETH to Kraken]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149142</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149142/ethereum-ico-whale-moves-116m-in-eth-to-kraken"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another dormant Ethereum wallet that participated in the project’s ICO has woken up after years of slumber.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles Launching Real World Play Experience in Chicago With Camp]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149147/doodles-launching-real-world-play-experience-chicago-camp"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pharrell Williams-backed NFT project Doodles is expanding further into the real world in partnership with “shop-and-play” retailer Camp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Société Générale’s Crypto Division Is First To Gain Full License From French Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149144</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149144/societe-generales-crypto-division-is-first-to-gain-full-license-from-french-regulator"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While more than 80 companies are registered with the AMF, SG Forge is the first to be licensed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Police Arrest 21 in $54M USDT Money Laundering Probe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149132/chinese-police-arrest-21-in-54m-usdt-money-laundering-probe"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The suspects allegedly purchased Tether’s stablecoin over-the-counter and sold it at inflated prices over WeChat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK Virtual Machine Developer RISC Zero Raises $40M in Series A]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149121/zk-virtual-machine-developer-risc-zero-raises-40m-in-series-a"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the new funding, the Seattle-based startup is getting closer to the launch of its computing platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev Team p0x Labs Raises $25M for Zero-Knowledge Ecosystem Manta Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149128/zero-knowledge-ecosystem-manta-network-raises-25-million-from-polychain-qiming"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T12:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding round for p0x labs — which has delivered a valuation of $500 million — was led by Polychain Capital and Qiming Venture Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Trading Saw 'Uptick' in Altcoin Activity After Ripple SEC Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149120/genesis-trading-saw-uptick-in-altcoin-activity-after-ripple-sec-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T10:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The institutional trading platform’s head of sales explains that the XRP ruling is the latest in a "series of bullish events" for crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Gains 6% on Possible SEC Settlement Conference, Ripple Metaverse Investment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149118/xrp-gains-6-on-possible-sec-settlement-conference-ripple-metaverse-investment"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T10:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP outperforms the crypto market as hopes of settlement with the SEC and metaverse investment boost buyer sentiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com Adds Reddit’s Moons Token as Kraken Listing Rumor Fades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149113/crypto-com-adds-reddits-moons-token-as-kraken-listing-rumor-fades"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T01:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The listing caused the token's value to double for the second day in a row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Assassin's Creed' Creator Ubisoft Throws Weight Behind Cronos Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149100</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149100/ubisoft-crypto-cronos-blockchain-validator"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T01:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gaming giant continues expanding across the blockchain space, this time as a Cronos blockchain validator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Donates $5 Million to the American Journalism Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149106</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149106/openai-donates-5-million-to-the-american-journalism-project"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T00:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ChatGPT creator previously inked a deal with the Associated Press and Shutterstock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Google Exec Predicts AI Sex Robots Could Replace Human Intimacy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149093</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149093/former-google-exec-predicts-ai-sex-robots-replace-humans"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T00:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could AI be taking over our jobs—and replacing our sex partners?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Neopets' Cancels NFT Game After Raising Money From Polygon, Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149074</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149074/neopets-cancels-nft-game-after-raising-money-from-polygon-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T22:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite $4 million in funding from crypto firms, Neopets is ditching NFTs—and making a game that can "better reflect our values and vision."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinfund Raises $158 Million to Boost Early-Stage Crypto, AI Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149062</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149062/coinfund-152-million-seed-early-stage-crypto-startups"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is launching a new fund after a tumultuous year where many players pulled back from cryptocurrency plays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Torres Tells SEC Chairman to End Crypto ‘Crusade’ After Ripple Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149079/end-sec-crusade-rep-ritchie-torres-annalisa-torres-doctrine"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The politician says it's time for the SEC to get comfortable with the “Torres Doctrine.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Decentralized Marketplaces?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=21404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-decentralized-marketplaces"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized marketplaces are what blockchains are all about. They allow people to interact and transact on a global, permission-less, and self-executing platform. Houses, hot sauce, and t-shirts can all be bought and sold without needing to trust a middleman.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are cryptocurrency wallets?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/wallets"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wallets are pieces of software that allow a user to hold cryptocurrency. The movement of cryptocurrencies to and from and wallets are controlled by public and private keys. There are several different types of wallets, characterised by their internet connectivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcardia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>