<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-11-17T08:19:00.270Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-11-17T08:19:00.270Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macro Expert Lyn Alden Says She’s Highly Convinced Bitcoin Will Go Up in Next Two Years – But There’s a Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044453/Macro-Expert-Lyn-Alden-Says-Shes-Highly-Convinced-Bitcoin-Will-Go-Up-in-Next-Two-Years-But-Theres-a-Catch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044453/Macro-Expert-Lyn-Alden-Says-Shes-Highly-Convinced-Bitcoin-Will-Go-Up-in-Next-Two-Years-But-Theres-a-Catch"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T08:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Macroeconomics commentator and author Lyn Alden is expressing bullish sentiment on Bitcoin (BTC) over the coming months. Alden says in a new interview with David Lin that in the next two years, she has a “pretty high conviction” that Bitcoin will appreciate in price. The macro expert, however,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressional Hearing Explores Blockchain’s Role in Combating Crypto Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044455/Congressional-Hearing-Explores-Blockchains-Role-in-Combating-Crypto-Crime</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044455/Congressional-Hearing-Explores-Blockchains-Role-in-Combating-Crypto-Crime"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T08:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States House Financial Services Subcommittee on Digital Assets, Financial Technology, and Inclusion gained...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asustek Plans Server Production Line in the U.S. to Capitalize on AI Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044448/Asustek-Plans-Server-Production-Line-in-the-US-to-Capitalize-on-AI-Opportunities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044448/Asustek-Plans-Server-Production-Line-in-the-US-to-Capitalize-on-AI-Opportunities"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T08:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asustek Computer Inc., a prominent Taiwan-based tech brand, has unveiled its plans to establish a production line in the United States, with mass production scheduled to commence in 2024. This move aligns with the global surge in opportunities stemming from advancements in artificial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin rallies by 10% this week: Will other meme coins follow suit?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044443/Dogecoin-rallies-by-10-this-week-Will-other-meme-coins-follow-suit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044443/Dogecoin-rallies-by-10-this-week-Will-other-meme-coins-follow-suit"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T08:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways Dogecoin is up by 10% over the last seven days, outperforming the broader market. Shiba Memu’s presale has officially crossed the $4.5 million mark. The cryptocurrency market has had a poor week so far, with Bitcoin and Ether both underperforming. However, DOGE has been one of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Tech Startups Thriving Despite European Tech Slump in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044449/Legal-Tech-Startups-Thriving-Despite-European-Tech-Slump-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044449/Legal-Tech-Startups-Thriving-Despite-European-Tech-Slump-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment in legal tech startups remains robust, outperforming the broader European tech sector in 2023. While European tech funding has declined by nearly half, legal tech startups have only seen a one-third decrease compared to 2022. The rise of AI in streamlining legal processes has piqued...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Announced It Added 5 New Altcoin Trading Pairs to Its Futures Trading Platform!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044412/Binance-Announced-It-Added-5-New-Altcoin-Trading-Pairs-to-Its-Futures-Trading-Platform</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044412/Binance-Announced-It-Added-5-New-Altcoin-Trading-Pairs-to-Its-Futures-Trading-Platform"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, announced the new altcoins that it will list on its margin platform on its blog. Continue Reading: Binance Announced It Added 5 New Altcoin Trading Pairs to Its Futures Trading Platform!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bullish or Bearish for Incoming Bitcoin 2024 Halving Year: We Asked Binance Blockchain Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044410/Bullish-or-Bearish-for-Incoming-Bitcoin-2024-Halving-Year-We-Asked-Binance-Blockchain-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044410/Bullish-or-Bearish-for-Incoming-Bitcoin-2024-Halving-Year-We-Asked-Binance-Blockchain-Week"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Why Do They Matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044408/Bitcoin-Spot-ETFs-Why-Do-They-Matter</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044408/Bitcoin-Spot-ETFs-Why-Do-They-Matter"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The approval window for spot Bitcoin ETFs is now open.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI of War is Redefining Conflict with Autonomous Killing Machines]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044409/AI-of-War-is-Redefining-Conflict-with-Autonomous-Killing-Machines</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044409/AI-of-War-is-Redefining-Conflict-with-Autonomous-Killing-Machines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of international relations and military strategy, the role of artificial intelligence (AI) has become a central point of discussion. The recent summit between Chinese President Xi Jinping and US President Joe Biden, amid the discussions on banning lethal autonomous...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada flags concern on AI-generated deepfake disinformation campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044407/Canada-flags-concern-on-AI-generated-deepfake-disinformation-campaigns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044407/Canada-flags-concern-on-AI-generated-deepfake-disinformation-campaigns"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:42:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sushi taps into ZetaChain to begin testing native Bitcoin DeFi swaps]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044393/Sushi-taps-into-ZetaChain-to-begin-testing-native-Bitcoin-DeFi-swaps</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044393/Sushi-taps-into-ZetaChain-to-begin-testing-native-Bitcoin-DeFi-swaps"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchange Sushi will test native Bitcoin DeFi functionality that promises to allow users to swap BTC across 30 blockchain networks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical  Shiba Inu (SHIB) Metric Skyrockets by 1,300%, Could It Propel Price Rally?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044394/Critical-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Metric-Skyrockets-by-1300-Could-It-Propel-Price-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044394/Critical-Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Metric-Skyrockets-by-1300-Could-It-Propel-Price-Rally"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approximately 105 million SHIB were burned over the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon: Reasons behind the massive hike in daily transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044390/Polygon-Reasons-behind-the-massive-hike-in-daily-transactions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044390/Polygon-Reasons-behind-the-massive-hike-in-daily-transactions"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon has reached a new high in daily transactions count. This was due to the activity around the Ordinals-inspired token standard on the network. Daily transactions count on leading Eth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German lawmaker Leads a Plan to Promote Bitcoin as legal tender.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044388/German-lawmaker-Leads-a-Plan-to-Promote-Bitcoin-as-legal-tender</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044388/German-lawmaker-Leads-a-Plan-to-Promote-Bitcoin-as-legal-tender"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tencent Bets on Chinese Suppliers to Fill GPU Gap Amid US Sanctions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044369/Tencent-Bets-on-Chinese-Suppliers-to-Fill-GPU-Gap-Amid-US-Sanctions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044369/Tencent-Bets-on-Chinese-Suppliers-to-Fill-GPU-Gap-Amid-US-Sanctions"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Generated Women Scam Thousands from Unsuspecting Men on Dating Apps and Social Media]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044370/AI-Generated-Women-Scam-Thousands-from-Unsuspecting-Men-on-Dating-Apps-and-Social-Media</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044370/AI-Generated-Women-Scam-Thousands-from-Unsuspecting-Men-on-Dating-Apps-and-Social-Media"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an age where technology continues to advance, the rise of artificial intelligence (AI) has given birth to a new breed of scammers who are preying on unsuspecting individuals looking for love on dating apps and social media. These scammers, utilizing AI-generated personas, have cost some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Looks to Capitalize on $7T Education Sector By Getting ChatGPT In Classrooms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044365/OpenAI-Looks-to-Capitalize-on-7T-Education-Sector-By-Getting-ChatGPT-In-Classrooms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044365/OpenAI-Looks-to-Capitalize-on-7T-Education-Sector-By-Getting-ChatGPT-In-Classrooms"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI is pivoting its focus towards the integration of its groundbreaking ChatGPT technology into educational settings. This strategic shift is not just a response to the initial uproar over potential cheating risks but a forward-thinking venture to harness AI’s vast potential in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore Announces Global Tokenization Initiative in Partnership With BNY Mellon, DBS, JPMorgan, and MUFG]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7499418a3d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/singapore-announces-global-tokenization-initiative-in-partnership-with-bny-mellon-dbs-jpmorgan-and-mufg/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T07:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has announced a global tokenization initiative that seeks to allow tokenized assets to be exchanged by different financial institutions across borders. The initiative, touted by MAS officials as the evolution of Project Guardian, a series of tokenization pilots carried by the institution, has the support of banking powerhouses like BNY Mellon, DBS, JPMorgan, and MUFG.
Monetary Authority of Singapore Announces Global Layer One Tokenization Project
The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) announced Global Layer One (Gl1), an initiative to integrate global tokenization activities under one interconnected network. The project, which has the involvement and support of banking behemoths like BNY Mellon, DBS, JPMorgan, and MUFG, seeks to “facilitate seam…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pioneering Genomic Tool Shields Trees from Global Pathogen Threat]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044331/Pioneering-Genomic-Tool-Shields-Trees-from-Global-Pathogen-Threat</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044331/Pioneering-Genomic-Tool-Shields-Trees-from-Global-Pathogen-Threat"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T06:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin (DOGE) Price in Green with Largest Transaction Volume in Months as SHIB, ADA, ETH, and Other Altcoins Slide]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044374/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-in-Green-with-Largest-Transaction-Volume-in-Months-as-SHIB-ADA-ETH-and-Other-Altcoins-Slide</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044374/Dogecoin-DOGE-Price-in-Green-with-Largest-Transaction-Volume-in-Months-as-SHIB-ADA-ETH-and-Other-Altcoins-Slide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T06:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the New Horizon: AI’s Pivotal Role in Shaping Human Behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044332/Navigating-the-New-Horizon-AIs-Pivotal-Role-in-Shaping-Human-Behavior</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19044332/Navigating-the-New-Horizon-AIs-Pivotal-Role-in-Shaping-Human-Behavior"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T06:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is no longer a futuristic fantasy but a present reality. Technology’s role in shaping human behavior and societal norms has become a subject of intense discussion and scrutiny. AI stands at the frontier of a technological revolution, offering unparalleled...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet StocksFC: The Football Stock Market Where Goals Earn You Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749948b279</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/meet-stocksfc-the-football-stock-market-where-goals-earn-you-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T06:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Amsterdam, Netherlands – StocksFC, the innovative football (soccer) stock market platform that runs on Ethereum, is proud to announce its astounding success since its inception six months ago. In this short span, StocksFC has redefined the sports investment landscape, presenting fans with an unprecedented opportunity to monetize their football acumen.
 
A Game-Changer in Sports and Finance
 
With its launch in May 2023, StocksFC offered fans the chance to buy, sell, and trade football player stocks with the potential to earn crypto rewards when players shine on the pitch. Fast forward six months, and the market cap has increased by 1350%, with over half a million stocks in circulation. This seismic shift in sports engagement mirrors the bullish trends of the most dynamic fin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX, NEAR Beat Ether and Bitcoin as Wall of Red Continues in Asia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74994ab44d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/17/avax-near-beat-ether-and-bitcoin-as-wall-of-red-continues-in-asia/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T05:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AVAX is up 8% in the last 24 hours, while bitcoin is trading below $36,500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Says JPM Coin Could Handle $10 Billion in Daily Transactions Next Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74993631bb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-says-jpm-coin-could-handle-10-billion-in-daily-transactions-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T05:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global investment bank JPMorgan expects its digital currency, JPM coin, to “start taking off.” The bank says JPM coin could handle $10 billion in daily transactions in the next year or two, according to its global head of financial institution payments. He emphasized that JPM coin transactions should grow at least five to tenfold.
 
JPMorgan’s JPM Coin Poised to Handle $10B Daily
 
Global investment bank JPMorgan’s global head of financial institution payments, Umar Farooq, discussed the bank’s own digital currency, JPM coin, on Wednesday in an interview with Bloomberg on the sidelines of the Singapore Fintech Festival.
 
Farooq expressed his optimism for JPM coin transactions to grow at least five to tenfold, emphasizing the potential for daily transactions with JPM coin to reach $10 bill…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nice: 69% Of Bitcoin Supply Now Locked Since 1 Year]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749931eff1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nice-69-of-bitcoin-supply-now-locked-since-1-year/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T04:32:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that the percentage of the Bitcoin supply inactive since at least one year ago has hit the 69% mark.
 
Bitcoin HODLing Grows As Supply Continues To Become Dormant
 
As pointed out by analyst Root in a new post on X, an all-time high (ATH) amount of the BTC supply hasn’t moved in over a year. The 1-year+ supply that’s of interest here is just a segment of a larger group called the “long-term holders” (LTHs).
 
The LTHs comprise one of the two main divisions of the Bitcoin investor base, with the other group being the “short-term holders” (STHs). Depending on the analytics platform, the cutoff between these cohorts is defined differently, but generally, five to six months is chosen as the boundary.
 
The investors carrying coins younger than this amount are put inside the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[58 US Lawmakers Probe Biden and Yellen on Hamas’ Crypto Operations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749939f084</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/58-us-lawmakers-probe-biden-and-yellen-on-hamas-crypto-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T03:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty-eight U.S. lawmakers have probed President Joe Biden and Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen regarding Hamas’ digital asset operations, as well as whether the U.S. has had success in seizing illicit cryptocurrencies. Despite reports that terrorist groups have raised millions in crypto, the lawmakers stressed: “It remains unclear how much, if any, of the publicly identified digital assets are accessible to or remains in the possession of Hamas.”
 
Lawmakers Want Answers From Biden, Yellen
 
Fifty-eight U.S. lawmakers sent a bipartisan letter to President Joe Biden and Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen on Wednesday seeking answers regarding Hamas’ crypto operations, including the group’s “ability to utilize digital assets to finance its operations.” The fact-finding letter aims to help Congr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Attracts 2X Solana’s Market Cap: Why Is ETH Struggling?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74993a3172</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-attracts-2x-solana-market-cap-eth-stalls/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T03:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to one crypto user on X, Ethereum is a different class from Solana, with the pioneer smart contract platform drawing much more capital from the community than the fourth-generation blockchain despite ETH price action being muted in the last month of trading. 
 
Ethereum Attracted $58 Billion, 2X Solana Market Cap
 
In a post on November 16, @litocoen, who describes himself as a creator, noted that with Ethereum prices rising above the resistance level to trade above $2,000 in November, the coin managed to attract $58 billion in the past 30 days. The creator added that the upsurge in liquidity is twice Solana’s total market cap, further highlighting that Ethereum is a “different asset class at this point,” and the path towards $10,000 looks inevitable.
 
 
Ethereum is in an uptren…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Big Moment: BlackRock Submits ETF Filing To US SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74992ddbfb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereums-big-moment-blackrock-submits-etf-filing/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T01:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, the world’s largest asset manager, has officially lodged an Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF) application with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). This notable step marks BlackRock’s deeper foray into the burgeoning digital asset market.
 
The proposed ‘iShares Ethereum Trust’ is structured to closely track the price performance of Ethereum (ETH), the second leading cryptocurrency, minus the Trust’s operational expenses and liabilities.
 
This development from BlackRock, a firm commanding over a trillion dollars in assets, has sent positive ripples through the crypto market. The announcement further underscores BlackRock’s commitment to expanding its portfolio offerings in the digital assets domain and reflects the growing institutional interest in cryp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vivek Ramaswamy Reveals Crypto Policy Framework — Plans to Roll Back Most of SEC Crypto Regulations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74992e0c5c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/vivek-ramaswamy-reveals-crypto-policy-framework-plans-to-roll-back-most-of-sec-crypto-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T01:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy has unveiled his “Three Freedoms of Crypto” policy framework. He stated that as President, he will ensure that innovative sectors, including crypto, are “liberated from the shackles of the unconstitutional shadow government.” He expects to rescind most, if not all, of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) regulations that apply to cryptocurrencies.
 
Vivek Ramaswamy’s Crypto Policy
 
U.S. presidential candidate Vivek Ramaswamy unveiled his cryptocurrency policy on Thursday. He wrote on social media platform X:
 

Rolling out my ‘Three Freedoms of Crypto’ policy framework at the North American Blockchain Summit this morning in Texas.
 
“Since the inception of crypto, the shadow government in the administrative state in Washington, D.C.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Is Making People ‘Question Their Own Reality’: Chelsea Manning]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206449</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206449/chelsea-manning-web-summit-ai-technology-privacy"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T01:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manning highlighted the clash between humans and technology at Lisbon's Web Summit, questioning AI's rapid development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emu Video and Emu Edit: Meta Debuts AI Models for Video and Images]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206440/emu-video-edit-meta-ai-video-generation-image-editing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-17T00:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social giant’s latest tools can conjure stunning visuals from text, setting up a generative AI showdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg Says He's Done Smoking Weed. Crypto Degens Are Betting He Isn't]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206425/snoop-dogg-says-done-smoking-weed-crypto-degens-betting-isnt"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T23:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new wager on Polymarket is offering crypto gamblers the chance to bet on whether iconic stoner Snoop Dogg will keep his word.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Lists Reasons Why The XRP Price Is Incredibly Bullish]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74991288ea</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-incredibly-bullish/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T23:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bullishness around the XRP price has still not waned even after an eventful week. As the asset has been able to maintain critical support levels, expectations surrounding its eventual resurgence remain, especially as crypto analysts give reasons why the altcoin is still very bullish.
 
Reasons Why The XRP Price Is Very Bullish
 
According to crypto analyst Tony The Bull, the XRP price is very bullish because of three major metrics. These include the Bollinger Bands Width (BBW), the Bollinger Bands %B, and the upper Bollinger Bands, all of which point to a continuation of the rally.
 
 
As Tony explains, the Bollinger Bands Width (BBW) is significant in the fact that the metric has reached its second tightest level ever for the XRP price. Moving forward, the Bollinger Bands %B has made …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Major Vulnerability Found in Early Crypto Wallet Software Risks Billions in Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749912b790</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/major-vulnerability-early-crypto-wallet-software-risks-billions-in-assets/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T23:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical vulnerability in early cryptocurrency wallets, identified by cybersecurity startup Unciphered, threatens billions of dollars in digital assets. Originating from a flaw in the BitcoinJS software used for wallet generation between 2011 and 2015, this issue exposes wallets to potential exploitation. Millions of users are being urged to transfer their assets to wallets generated with updated, secure software.
 
Report Shows Early Crypto Wallets Exposed to Billion-Dollar Vulnerability
 
Unciphered‘s exhaustive 22-month investigation has unearthed a significant flaw in BitcoinJS, a widely used browser-based cryptocurrency wallet generation tool. This flaw stems from the SecureRandom function in the JSBN javascript library, compounded by weaknesses in major browsers’ Math.random implem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Arrests Three Men in Alleged $10 Million Crypto Laundering Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206413</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206413/crypto-laundering-scheme-bank-transactions-china-taiwan"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T22:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The alleged scammers would create transactions and then claim they were unauthorized, converting bank refunds into crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Gaming Powers Up: Daily Active Wallets Hit a Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206392</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206392/crypto-gaming-powers-up-daily-active-wallets-hit-million"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T22:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DappRadar data shows growing blockchain gaming activity, but it arrives as more and more developers share how they're fighting off bots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California, Texas Among States Accusing GS Partners of Misleading Crypto Investors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74991f548b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/11/16/california-texas-among-states-accusing-gs-partners-of-misleading-crypto-investors/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T22:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple U.S. states have ordered GS Partners to halt operations, accusing the company of defrauding investors in a number of crypto schemes, including tokenized pieces of a Dubai skyscraper and stakes of metaverse property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Charts Strategic Course in Bitcoin Mining, Plans $500 Million Infusion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e749919c634</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tether-charts-strategic-course-in-bitcoin-mining-plans-500-million-infusion/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T22:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Holdings Ltd., the issuer of the leading stablecoin in terms of market value and trade volume, is poised to become a formidable player in the mining industry, as revealed by its CEO, Paolo Ardoino. On Thursday, Ardoino announced the company’s intention to channel approximately $500 million into its mining business over the next six months.
 
Tether’s Mining Ambition: A $500 Million Venture into Crypto’s Core
 

 
Under the strategic guidance of Paolo Ardoino, Tether is set to bolster its mining endeavors. The company is earmarking close to half a billion dollars for enhancing its mining facilities and acquiring stakes in other enterprises. Ardoino shared these insights during a Bloomberg interview conducted on Thursday.
 

 
Tether, at the helm of the largest stablecoin by market wo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips 5% to Under $36K as Crypto Rally Runs Into Wall, Liquidating $340M in 2 Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74991ae4e7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/11/16/bitcoin-dips-5-to-under-36k-as-crypto-rally-runs-into-wall-liquidating-340m-in-2-days/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC delaying decision about spot BTC ETFs could leave the market without a catalyst until early January, halting the crypto rally's momentum, K33 analysts said this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strike Rolls Out Bitcoin Purchases To Users Globally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74991ba706</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/11/16/strike-rolls-out-bitcoin-purchases-to-users-globally/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin payments firm Strike has expanded its services on a global scale, now allowing users in 36 countries (soon to be 65+) beyond the U.S. to buy bitcoin through the app, founder Jack Mallers announced in a blog post Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bitcoin ATHs In December Could Be A “Sure Thing”]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74990495ad</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/why-bitcoin-aths-in-december-could-be-a-sure-thing/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last two bear markets in Bitcoin were ended officially in the month of December. The confirmation signal came when the top cryptocurrency by market cap revisited its former all-time high.
 
With next month being December once again, and BTCUSD price action heating up, could revisiting all-time highs next month be a “sure thing?”
 
Bitcoin Know Sure Thing Could Cross Bullish Next Month
 
The idea that BTCUSD could be back at all-time highs next month might sound unrealistic. But each time the 1M Know Sure Thing indicator crossed bullish, Bitcoin was back at former record prices the same month.
 
 
This didn’t just happen once in December 2020 when BTCUSD surpassed the 2017 high of $20,000,. It also happened before that in December 2016, just prior to the one-year bull market that made B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot; Severino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Version of Bitcoin Ordinals Sends Gas Fees Skyrocketing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206415</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206415/polygon-version-of-bitcoin-ordinals-sends-gas-fees-skyrocketing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the drop, Polygon gas fees had increased 1,000% compared to the same time a day ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time Is Running Out for Crypto Leaders to Reason With the IRS]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7499069909</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/11/16/time-is-running-out-for-crypto-leaders-to-reason-with-the-irs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A united front is needed to oppose bad tax regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matan Doyich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Cathie Wood Is Bullish on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206390</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206390/why-cathie-wood-is-bullish-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["If you look at Ethereum it was faster and cheaper than Bitcoin in the day. Solana is faster and more cost-effective than Ethereum," Wood pointed out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xi Jinping Vows No Hegemony in China’s Approach to US, Aiming for Stable Ties]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7499010154</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/xi-jinping-vows-no-hegemony-in-chinas-approach-to-us-aiming-for-stable-ties/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Chinese President Xi Jinping delivered a speech emphasizing China’s aspiration for harmonious ties with the United States. The Chinese head of state conveyed his vision of an enhanced “friendship in the new era” between the two influential countries. He firmly declared that “China will never pursue hegemony or expansion.”
 
Despite Reported Tensions, China’s Xi Promises No Expansion, Seeks Harmonious U.S. Relationship
 
During this week’s San Francisco meeting between U.S. President Joe Biden and Chinese President Xi Jinping, topics of bilateral relations were at the forefront. President Xi underscored China’s intention to cultivate amity with the U.S., stating that China’s approach to the China-U.S. dynamic will be rooted in “mutual respect.” He reiterated the belief that a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taproot Wizards Raise $7.5 Million to Advance Ordinals, L2s, Zk-Snarks on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74990d9cac</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/taproot-wizards-raise-7-5-million-to-advance-ordinals-l2s-zk-snarks-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T20:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taproot Wizards, a Bitcoin Ordinals project focused on advancing Bitcoin's capabilities, has secured $7.5 million in funding to assemble a team of top tier developers to build on Bitcoin. 
The investment round was led by Standard Crypto, with Geometry, Collider Ventures, StarkWare, UTXO Management, Bitcoin Frontier Fund, Masterkey and Newman Capital participating in the raise as well.
"We went for a larger seed round of $7.5 million because we feel time is of the essence," said Taproot Wizards co-founder Udi Wertheimer. "We've been bullish on bitcoin for a decade but we genuinely believe that the best time to build in bitcoin is now."
Taproot Wizards aims to assemble a solid team of developers to further develop tools and applications that leverage the full potential of the open source pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Claim the Pyth Airdrop for Ethereum, Solana, Aptos Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206387</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206387/how-to-claim-the-pyth-airdrop-for-ethereum-solana-aptos-users"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T20:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users across 27 blockchains are eligible for the massive drop, which kicks off Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Brings ‘Great Promise and Great Risk' to Financial Markets: CFTC Commissioner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206378/artificial-intelligence-in-financial-markets-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T20:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Excessive reliance on a few AI models could lead to herd behavior," Christy Goldsmith warned today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Delays Bitcoin And Ethereum ETFs, Here Are The Next Deadline Dates]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74990f98a2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-bitcoin-ethereum-etfs-deadline/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T20:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US SEC has requested an extension of its decision to approve or reject spot Bitcoin and Ethereum ETFs. Presently, candidates for both ETFs are on standby as they await a final decision in 2024. 
 
SEC Extends ETF Review To 2024
 
The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has delayed its approval for Spot Bitcoin and Ethereum Futures ETF applications. The regulator filed for an extension on November 15 stating that it needed more time to properly review the issues of the application and its decision regarding ETFs. 
 
 
“The Commission finds it appropriate to designate a longer period within which to take action on the proposed rule change so that it has sufficient time to consider the proposed rule change and issues raised therein,” the SEC stated in the filing. 
 
Pre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft Will Give Away Free Ethereum NFTs for 'Champions Tactics' Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206381/ubisoft-free-ethereum-nft-giveaway-champions-tactics-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T19:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assassin’s Creed maker Ubisoft says it will host a free Ethereum NFT mint for Champions Tactics, its upcoming game on Oasys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDCs Could Replace Cash in Global Finance, Says IMF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206351</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206351/cbdcs-could-replace-cash-in-global-finance-says-imf"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T19:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IMF director is optimistic that CBDCs could replace cash in the global financial system—if central banks follow the org's handbook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heatbit Founder Alex Busarov on the Bitcoin Miner That Heats Your Home]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DJuHqcGT/heatbit-founder-alex-busarov-on-the-bitcoin-miner-that-heats-your-home"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T18:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Heatbit founder Alex Busarov at Web Summit for a walkthrough of the firm's flagship product, a Bitcoin miner that acts as a domestic space heater—aimed at the casual user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinShares Preps Move to US Market—Just in Time for a Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206359</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206359/coinshares-preps-move-to-us-market-just-in-time-for-a-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's an auspicious time for CoinShares to be eyeing a foothold in the states, as anticipation builds for a spot Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bazooka Tango Raises $5 Million to Revive 'Shardbound' as NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206135/bazooka-tango-raises-5-million-revive-shardbound-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T17:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game studio Bazooka Tango will use the funds to hire staff and bring the Immutable zkEVM game Shardbound closer to completion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Pumps 14% After JP Morgan Adoption, Bitcoin's ORDI Pops 16%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206343/avalanche-pumps-14-after-jp-morgan-adoption-dogecoin-rises"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T16:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche, Dogecoin, and Cardano have all made gains on Thursday, while BTC and ETH have slowed down their respective rallies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'Aurory' Expands With 'Seekers of Tokane' and Epic Games Store Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206262/solana-game-aurory-expands-seekers-tokane-epic-games-store"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is launching Seekers of Tokane and plans to take it beyond the browser with a desktop version in the works for the Epic Games Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why BlackRock Considers Tether a Risk for Its Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206303</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206303/blackrock-tether-usdt-fud-bitcoin-spot-etf-filing"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["There is a risk that a disorderly de-pegging or a run on Tether or USDC could lead to dramatic market volatility," the firm writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock Files Spot Ethereum ETF Application with SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206328</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206328/blackrock-files-for-spot-ethereum-etf-with-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T12:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase will serve as custodian for the iShares Ethereum Trust, according to BlackRock's form S-1 filing with the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's National Pension Service Invested $20M in Coinbase Shares in Q3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206314</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206314/south-koreas-national-pension-service-invested-20m-in-coinbase-shares-in-q3"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T09:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The national pension fund of South Korea has turned a 40% profit on its Q3 2023 purchase of Coinbase shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former VP Leaves Stability AI Over Copyright Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206307</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206307/former-vp-leaves-stability-ai-over-copyright-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T03:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ed Newton-Rex resigned from Stability AI, contesting the company's assertion that using copyrighted content in AI training is "fair use."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irregular Sleep More Harmful Than Shorter Sleep Sessions, Study Suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206297</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206297/irregular-sleep-more-harmful-than-shorter-sleep-sessions-study-suggests"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T01:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saying “I’ll sleep when I’m dead” is wrong in more ways than one, as better sleep is linked to greater longevity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Maia and Cobalt, Microsoft's New Custom Chips Designed for AI Supremacy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206286</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206286/microsoft-maia-cobolt-arm-chips-for-ai-datacenters"/>
        <updated>2023-11-16T00:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is shifting to an integrated strategy to grow both its AI and cloud computing portfolio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PancakeSwap Launches Crypto Gaming Hub—And You Can Earn CAKE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206281/pancakeswap-launches-crypto-gaming-hub-you-can-earn-cake"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T23:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-chain decentralized exchange (DEX) PancakeSwap is pushing into games, starting with a couple built around its CAKE token and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soccer Giant Paris Saint-Germain Drops NFTs for Blvck Paris Fashion Collab]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206237</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206237/soccer-giant-paris-saint-germain-drops-nfts-blvck-paris-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent soccer club Paris Saint-Germain is offering fans early entry to its fashion collaboration with Blvck Paris via a Crypto.com NFT drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dairy Queen Is Doing an NFT Thing in China Apparently]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206236</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206236/dairy-queen-doing-nft-thing-china-apparently"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T21:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American fast food brand has partnered with NFT project Weirdo Ghost Gang for a pop-up experience in Chengdu, China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Solar Storm Cycle Could Massively Disrupt the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206229/solar-activity-2024-disrupt-internet-gps-technology"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T21:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from two universities are sounding the alarm over solar activity that could disrupt most technologies, including blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Hate 'Call of Duty: Modern Warfare III'—What Went Wrong?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206223</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206223/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-iii-trashed-by-gamers-reviews"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T21:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Activision’s latest Call of Duty is getting slammed by critics and everyday gamers alike amid reports of rushed development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators Are Powerless to Prevent Another FTX, Says CFTC Chairman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206235</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206235/regulators-cant-prevent-another-ftx-cftc"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T20:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC isn't any better suited to stop a collapse like FTX today than it was a year ago, said commodities chief Rostin Behnam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Needs More Time on Grayscale Ethereum Futures ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206212</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206212/sec-needs-more-time-on-grayscale-ethereum-futures-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T19:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC gave itself a deadline extention on the Grayscale Ethereum Futures ETF application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Symbiogenesis Preview: Everything You Need to Know About Square Enix's NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206152/symbiogenesis-preview-everything-you-need-know-square-enix-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T19:26:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy maker Square Enix's first Ethereum game is called Symbiogenesis. From NFT characters to quests, here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Puts Paid Plan Signups on Pause as Systems Strain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206218/chatgpt-puts-paid-plan-signups-on-pause-as-systems-strain"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman said usage of its services has "exceeded our capacity."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Open Source AI Model from China Boasts Twice the Capacity of ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206195/new-open-source-ai-model-from-china-boasts-twice-the-capacity-of-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Yi series model takes a giant leap over its American competitors, at least by some metrics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manny Pacquiao Turns to Shiba Inu to Help His Foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206184</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206184/manny-pacquiao-shiba-inu-shib-shibarium"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manny Pacquaio's non-profit will use Shibarium for fundraising and operational activities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Wreck League' Preview: A Promising Fighting Game With Mechs and NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206009</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206009/wreck-league-preview-promising-fighting-game-mechs-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T18:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: In early access, Wreck League already packs a punch—but high Ethereum fees may K.O. some players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan’s Onyx Taps Avalanche for Tokenized Funds, AVAX Jumps 14%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206153/jp-morgan-onyx-avalanche-tokenized-funds-avax"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan's Onyx is using an Avalanche subnet to connect portfolios to tokenized assets offered by WisdomTree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pat Felder - The worst is over [Macro Deep Dive Episode]]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MdcKPVo0/pat-felder-the-worst-is-over-macro-deep-dive-episode"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first Markets Edition of This Time Will Be Different! In this episode we dive into the current macroeconomic conditions around crypto and look at the data behind the price action. 


Reza sits down with Pat Felder, founder of Prismatic Capital to discuss the current macro environment, and to answer the question on everyone's mind-- is the bear market really over?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple iPhone App Sideloading Could Increase Risk of Crypto Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=206156</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/206156/apple-iphone-app-sideloading-could-increase-risk-phishing-attacks"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Apple reportedly set to enable EU iPhone users to install apps from outside the App Store, crypto security firms warned of the risks of malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies Game Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205816/phantom-galaxies-game-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Head to the galactic frontier as the pilot of a transforming Starfighter in Blowfish Studios’ space-based battler. Here’s how to get started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox Co-Founder Sebastien Borget: 'We're Already Integrating AI']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HlARjhG1/the-sandbox-co-founder-sebastien-borget-were-already-integrating-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt sat down with The Sandbox co-founder Sebastien Borget at Web Summit to talk about AI, the open metaverse and the creative challenges of interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dacoco CEO Saro McKenna: How Alien Worlds is Creating an AI-Powered 'Lore DAO' with Kevin J Anderson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QrQTrsjH/dacoco-ceo-saro-mckenna-how-alien-worlds-is-creating-an-ai-powered-lore-dao-with-kevin-j-anderson"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt joined Dacoco CEO Sarojini McKenna at Web Summit 2023 to talk about Alien Worlds' new Lore DAO and its AI-powered collaboration with sci-fi author Kevin J Anderson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon's Jeffrey Butler on Designing a Metaverse MMO That Lets Players Co-Create]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XDz9vsvT/avalons-jeffrey-butler-on-designing-a-metaverse-mmo-that-lets-players-co-create"/>
        <updated>2023-11-15T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson and details his studio's new MMO game with interoperable assets—and how it will enable players to create and monetize their own content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gen Z Is Different: OTK Chief Strategy Officer Talks Creator Economy Shift and Rise of Kick]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PieshbpH/how-gen-z-is-different-otk-chief-strategy-officer-talks-creator-economy-shift-and-rise-of-kick"/>
        <updated>2023-11-10T18:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King, an esports and gaming lifestyle brand and media company, was founded by creators like Asmongold and Mizkif. OTK's Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz, who previously worked at TikTok and Twitch, shares with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the creator economy is changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moisés Zamora on Videomart and Bucking the Hollywood System]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kyjQCle8/moises-zamora-on-videomart-and-bucking-the-hollywood-system"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T17:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Selena: The Series" creator and co-showrunner Moisés Zamora joins Decrypt's Sander Lutz at the Film3 Summit 2023 to discuss why the Hollywood system is broken and why he founded the Videomart NFT digital film marketplace to give creators more power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OTK Is Making Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1NCV4Fk0/why-otk-is-making-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-11-09T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One True King (OTK) Chief Strategy Officer Zachary Diaz tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about OTK's long-term strategy and vision to become a content creator-powered media and video games company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: LoVid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E8BZZBWX/5-questions-with-scene-lovid"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T21:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artistic duo LoVid, aka Tali Hinkis and Kyle Lapidus, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer burning questions about art, lettuce, and the hellscape (in someone’s opinion) that is Miami.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Barney on DeFi, Privacy, and Vega]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hgDzjboU/barney-on-defi-privacy-and-vega"/>
        <updated>2023-11-08T18:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Barney the founder of Vega Protocol. 

They discuss the current state of DeFi, what's wrong with the apps being built today, whether or not privacy matters when its only applied to an L2, and most importantly-- which form of sales tax is the sexiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Phantom Galaxies Releasing Two Versions of Its Game?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QtnWGSSJ/why-is-phantom-galaxies-releasing-two-versions-of-its-game"/>
        <updated>2023-11-06T17:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands-owned Blowfish Studios is building a space mech pilot game called Phantom Galaxies. Blowfish Cofounder Ben Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his plans for the game's release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Maxx on NFTs, Augmented Reality, and Fashion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VByufHjn/sophie-maxx-on-nfts-augmented-reality-and-fashion"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T23:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Sophie Maxx (Web3Maxx) to discuss NFTs, augmented reality, the metaverse, how blockchain is sneaking into the fashion world, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Kevin Rose]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u9LDX8Vr/5-questions-with-scene-kevin-rose"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose, co-founder and CEO of PROOF and co-creator of the hit Moonbirds NFT collection, joins 5 Questions with SCENE to answer some hard-hitting questions about his childhood dreams, his wife’s candy preferences, and his undying love of rap music.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened to Atari's Token? Inside Atari's Blockchain Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7OtQIdqa/what-happened-to-ataris-token-inside-ataris-blockchain-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-11-01T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Atari X director Tyler Drewitz about what happened with Atari's token plans, whether a token is coming, and what Atari games might be getting the blockchain treatment. Oh, and there's lots of Easter eggs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch CEO Dan Clancy Is a 'Wild Card,' Says Marketing Director]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qCOCtPKe/twitch-ceo-dan-clancy-is-a-wild-card-says-marketing-director"/>
        <updated>2023-10-31T20:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Senior Director of Community Marketing Mary Kish speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Twitch CEO Dan Clancy, Ninja, Twitch's new simulcasting rules, the biggest differences between Twitch and rival platform Kick, and the role of esports on the streaming platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why NFT Paris has Launched a Loyalty Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/91tPVJff/why-nft-paris-has-launched-a-loyalty-token"/>
        <updated>2023-10-30T13:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Paris founder Alexandre Tsydenkov told Decrypt what to expect from the upcoming 2024 edition of the conference, the launch of its loyalty token and its plans to create a Web3 loyalty program that rewards the most engaged members of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review—Formula E: High Voltage Is a Fun Play-to-Earn Racer That Lacks Direction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/hzkx0TDg/game-reviewformula-e-high-voltage-is-a-fun-play-to-earn-racer-that-lacks-direction"/>
        <updated>2023-10-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Formula E: High Voltage is a play-to-earn racing game with a distinctive strategic approach. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin put Animoca's web-based game through its paces in this review, highlighting the unique gameplay design, the role of NFTs and crypto, and where the game currently comes up short.

Follow Decrypt's GG on Twitter: https://twitter.com/ggdecrypt 

Check out GG for daily gaming news: https://decrypt.co/gg 

Subscribe to our GG newsletter with over 50,000 subscribers: https://decrypt.co/newsletters/gg 

Join our official Discord: https://discord.com/invite/3bc4QpA57C]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Cassatt on Web3 Marketing and the early days of Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode, our host is joined by Amanda Cassatt! 

Amanda is the founder of Serotonin, a web3 marketing agency, the author of the first book ever published on web3 marketing, and led the marketing team that helped bring Ethereum to market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>