<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-26T09:19:17.231Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-26T09:19:17.231Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strike Expands Bitcoin and Lightning Services to the UK]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ec10a54</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/strike-expands-bitcoin-and-lightning-services-to-the-uk/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strike has announced its expansion into the United Kingdom. This move allows individuals and businesses in the UK to access Strike’s suite of Bitcoin and Lightning Network services. The features include buying, selling, sending, and withdrawing bitcoin, global payments, and more. The company’s founder, Jack Mallers, believes that bitcoin can solve some of the world’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 4th UK Election: A Turning Point for Crypto Regulations and Economic Stability?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625221/July-4th-UK-Election-A-Turning-Point-for-Crypto-Regulations-and-Economic-Stability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625221/July-4th-UK-Election-A-Turning-Point-for-Crypto-Regulations-and-Economic-Stability"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 4, the United Kingdom will hold a general election, one that could redefine the nation’s approach to economic policy and cryptocurrency regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Light Ahead For Ethereum ETF, States SEC Chair Gensler]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ec1d4ca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/green-light-ahead-for-ethereum-etf-gary-gensler/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The approval process for the Spot Ethereum ETF is progressing smoothly, according to the US Securities and Exchange Commission Chair, Gary Gensler. Speaking at the Bloomberg Invest Summit, Gensler expressed optimism for the new investment product, which is anticipated to launch as early as July. This development marks a significant milestone for the cryptocurrency market, as Ethereum prepares to follow in the footsteps of its Bitcoin counterpart.
 
 
Ethereum ETF: Smooth Sailing Towards Approval?
 
Gensler emphasized the positive trajectory of the Spot Ethereum ETF approval process in his remarks. “The registration process is working smoothly,” he said, echoing statements made earlier this month before the US Senate Appropriations Subcommittee on Financial Services.
 
The SEC is actively w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack O’Holleran, CEO of SKALE Labs, on the State of Web3 Gaming and Meme Coins vs. NFTs | Ep. 346]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625220/Jack-OHolleran-CEO-of-SKALE-Labs-on-the-State-of-Web3-Gaming-and-Meme-Coins-vs-NFTs-Ep-346</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625220/Jack-OHolleran-CEO-of-SKALE-Labs-on-the-State-of-Web3-Gaming-and-Meme-Coins-vs-NFTs-Ep-346"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jack O’Holleran, the co-founder and CEO of SKALE Labs, discusses Web3 gaming, its path to a “massive breakout,” social apps as a way to reach millions of players, and SKALE’s major partnerships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stacks(STX) Rises 8 % In 24 Ho, Will The L2 Crypto Remain Bullish?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625215/StacksSTX-Rises-8-In-24-Ho-Will-The-L2-Crypto-Remain-Bullish</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625215/StacksSTX-Rises-8-In-24-Ho-Will-The-L2-Crypto-Remain-Bullish"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stacks (STX) makes a strong movement upward, resilient to its downward trend Stacks registered massive growth in its network activity. Experts predict STX to be back to its monthly high of $2.48 Stacks(STX), the Layer2 blockchain network comes to attention with a 24-hour growth of 8% and volume...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Light Ahead For Ethereum ETF, States SEC Chair Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625180/Green-Light-Ahead-For-Ethereum-ETF-States-SEC-Chair-Gensler</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625180/Green-Light-Ahead-For-Ethereum-ETF-States-SEC-Chair-Gensler"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The approval process for the Spot Ethereum ETF is progressing smoothly, according to the US Securities and Exchange Commission Chair, Gary Gensler. Speaking at the Bloomberg Invest Summit, Gensler expressed optimism for the new investment product, which is anticipated to launch as early as July....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong targets DeFi, metaverse for fintech expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625181/Hong-Kong-targets-DeFi-metaverse-for-fintech-expansion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625181/Hong-Kong-targets-DeFi-metaverse-for-fintech-expansion"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite challenges in the current DeFi and metaverse landscape, the reports highlight potential growth and innovation in these emerging sectors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Reasons Why Ethereum (ETH) Is Much Stronger Than Bitcoin (BTC) Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625158/5-Reasons-Why-Ethereum-ETH-Is-Much-Stronger-Than-Bitcoin-BTC-Right-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625158/5-Reasons-Why-Ethereum-ETH-Is-Much-Stronger-Than-Bitcoin-BTC-Right-Now"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum might be stronger option for investors compared to Bitcoin, and there are good reasons for it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany Continues Where It Left Off in Bitcoin: Here's Its New Million Dollar Move!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625147/Germany-Continues-Where-It-Left-Off-in-Bitcoin-Heres-Its-New-Million-Dollar-Move</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625147/Germany-Continues-Where-It-Left-Off-in-Bitcoin-Heres-Its-New-Million-Dollar-Move"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the data, the address belonging to the German government moved 750 Bitcoins worth $46 million in about an hour. Continue Reading: Germany Continues Where It Left Off in Bitcoin: Here's Its New Million Dollar Move!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Protocol acquires Openstory amid team expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625122/Ava-Protocol-acquires-Openstory-amid-team-expansion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625122/Ava-Protocol-acquires-Openstory-amid-team-expansion"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Protocol, a Web3 automation platform, has acquired Openstory, a leading data streaming platform specializing in on-chain data and analytics, … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Accumulating More BTC Amid Price Dip To $60k]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625111/Bitcoin-Investors-Accumulating-More-BTC-Amid-Price-Dip-To-60k</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625111/Bitcoin-Investors-Accumulating-More-BTC-Amid-Price-Dip-To-60k"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin recently experienced a notable price drop, falling below $60,000 briefly after peaking near $70,000 earlier in June. As Bitcoin’s price fluctuates, there’s also been a noticeable change in how investors are buying and holding Bitcoin. Analysts have pointed out that many are increasing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemz vs. Hamster Kombat: Two Crypto Games, Two Different Paths]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625170/Gemz-vs-Hamster-Kombat-Two-Crypto-Games-Two-Different-Paths</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625170/Gemz-vs-Hamster-Kombat-Two-Crypto-Games-Two-Different-Paths"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Telegram games, Gemz and Hamster Kombat, are making waves in the crypto community, but for vastly different reasons. Gemz lures players with the promise of free coins, while Hamster Kombat has become a surprising tool for political expression and faces legal challenges in some countries....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Largest Holder of dogwifhat Buys 2.3 Million WIF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625091/Largest-Holder-of-dogwifhat-Buys-23-Million-WIF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625091/Largest-Holder-of-dogwifhat-Buys-23-Million-WIF"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the latest post on X by blockchain analytical firm Lookonchain, the largest holder of WIF recently spent 4.65 Million USDC to purchase 2.3 Million WIF at a price of $2.03. At the time of writing this holder currently possesses 23.39 Million WIF ($49.6M) with a profit of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SushiSwap (SUSHI) Targets $0.85 as Demand Picks Up]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625156/SushiSwap-SUSHI-Targets-085-as-Demand-Picks-Up</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625156/SushiSwap-SUSHI-Targets-085-as-Demand-Picks-Up"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUSHI, the token that powers SushiSwap, an automated market maker (AMM), witnessed a price decline between June 6 and 23. The altcoin’s value decreased by 42% during that period to form a descending channel. By June 23, selling pressure had weakened, paving the way for the bulls to re-enter....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delist Announcement for 7 Altcoins from Bitcoin Exchange Binance!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625077/Delist-Announcement-for-7-Altcoins-from-Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625077/Delist-Announcement-for-7-Altcoins-from-Bitcoin-Exchange-Binance"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the Bitcoin exchange that announced Delist, stated that the affected altcoins are BLUR, LINK, MEME, METIS, NFP, OSMO and SHIB. Continue Reading: Delist Announcement for 7 Altcoins from Bitcoin Exchange Binance!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pendle price prediction 2024-2030: Is PENDLE a good investment?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625075/Pendle-price-prediction-2024-2030-Is-PENDLE-a-good-investment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625075/Pendle-price-prediction-2024-2030-Is-PENDLE-a-good-investment"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key takeaways Pendle (PENDLE) is innovating the DeFi space by enabling the trading of future yields. This unique approach helps users maximize returns through advanced smart contracts and seamless integration with other DeFi platforms. The recent progress of Pendle such as smart contract...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[R. Kiyosaki: Hang on tight as Bitcoin lifts off into the ‘Banana Zone’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625067/R-Kiyosaki-Hang-on-tight-as-Bitcoin-lifts-off-into-the-Banana-Zone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625067/R-Kiyosaki-Hang-on-tight-as-Bitcoin-lifts-off-into-the-Banana-Zone"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although Bitcoin (BTC) has lately been correcting way below its this year’s and all-time highs (ATH), popular investor and best-selling … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Inflation Concerns Rise After 73 Consecutive Days of Supply Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625058/Ethereum-Inflation-Concerns-Rise-After-73-Consecutive-Days-of-Supply-Growth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625058/Ethereum-Inflation-Concerns-Rise-After-73-Consecutive-Days-of-Supply-Growth"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Ethereum Inflation Concerns Rise After 73 Consecutive Days of Supply Growth It appears that Ethereum might be losing its “deflation dream” after seeing its longest inflationary spell since transitioning to PoS model. Ethereum Inflation Concerns Rise After 73 Consecutive Days of Supply Growth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WinDAO DApp Staking is Now Live! Unlock Rewards and Grow Your Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625061/WinDAO-DApp-Staking-is-Now-Live-Unlock-Rewards-and-Grow-Your-Digital-Assets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625061/WinDAO-DApp-Staking-is-Now-Live-Unlock-Rewards-and-Grow-Your-Digital-Assets"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:19:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is WinDAO? WinDAO is a pioneering digital asset venture platform that embraces a community-centred approach. Since its inception in 2018, WinDAO has focused on high-quality projects and decentralized governance, providing comprehensive support and services for investors. Our native token,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spot Bitcoin ETFs reverse 7-day outflow streak]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625055/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-reverse-7-day-outflow-streak</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625055/Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-reverse-7-day-outflow-streak"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of June 25, the 11 spot Bitcoin funds that debuted in January have seen net inflows of $14.42 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe Soars 9% Daily, Bitcoin Price Eyes $62K After Recent Crash (Market Watch)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625048/Pepe-Soars-9-Daily-Bitcoin-Price-Eyes-62K-After-Recent-Crash-Market-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625048/Pepe-Soars-9-Daily-Bitcoin-Price-Eyes-62K-After-Recent-Crash-Market-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:16:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NOT is today's top performer from the larger-cap alts, followed by PEPE and ENS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[George Latimer defeats anti-crypto Jamaal Bowman in NY primary with crypto PAC support]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625039/George-Latimer-defeats-anti-crypto-Jamaal-Bowman-in-NY-primary-with-crypto-PAC-support</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19625039/George-Latimer-defeats-anti-crypto-Jamaal-Bowman-in-NY-primary-with-crypto-PAC-support"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Representative Jamaal Bowman, one of the anti-crypto Congressmen who voted against the FIT 21 bill, lost to Democratic George Latimer in the New York primary, according to Fox Business journalist Eleanor Terrett. The victory was partially influenced by the pro-crypto lobby group FairShake,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoQuant Integrates TRON Data to Empower Users with Enhanced Blockchain Analytics]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ecb358f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cryptoquant-integrates-tron-data-to-empower-users-with-enhanced-blockchain-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Seoul, South Korea, June 26, 2024 – CryptoQuant, a leader in blockchain analytics, is excited to announce the integration of TRON data into its comprehensive analytical platform. This development is set to revolutionize how users interact with and derive insights from the TRON network. CryptoQuant’s enhanced platform now offers expanded capabilities for both […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous Bitcoin Donor Foots Bill For Julian Assange’s Flight Into Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740eb6a4b3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-donor-julian-assange-flight/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An anonymous donor has significantly contributed to the cause of Julian Assange, the founder of WikiLeaks, by covering almost the entire cost of his travel expenses as he transitioned from detainment to freedom. This donation of 8 Bitcoin (BTC), valued at nearly $497,000 at current market rates, nearly fulfills the total appeal of $520,000 outlined by Assange’s family.
 
Bitcoin Donor Covers Assange’s Private Jet
 
On Tuesday, Assange’s wife Stella posted via X: “URGENT: Emergency appeal for donations to cover massive $520,000 debt for jet. Julian’s travel to freedom comes at a massive cost: Julian will owe $520,000 which he is obligated to pay back to the Australian government for charter Flight VJ199. He was not permitted to fly commercial airlines or routes to Saipan and onward to Austr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renewed Bullishness Expected After Bitcoin, Ether's $10B Options Expiry on Friday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740eb0dfbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/26/renewed-bullishness-expected-after-bitcoin-ethers-10b-options-expiry-on-friday/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 25% of options are set to expire "in the money," Deribit's Luuk Strijers told CoinDesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA Is Already Here: Binance Restricts EU Users from Copy Trading and Many Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740eb2152b</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/mica-is-already-here-binance-restricts-eu-users-from-copy-trading-and-many-stablecoins/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European  
Binance users logging into their mobile app on Wednesday were greeted with an unsettling message indicating that certain services were no longer available in  
their region. This sudden change comes as new cryptocurrency regulations on the  
Old Continent officially take effect at the end of June. 
Binance,  
acting proactively, has already blocked access to some services, including copy  
trading, starting from June 26.
Binance Users in Europe  
Face Significant Restrictions
A year ago,  
the European Union introduced the Markets in Crypto-assets (MiCA) regulation  
package, governing the digital assets industry across Europe and within the  
European Economic Area (EEA). 
The MiCA regulations concerning stablecoins will significantly impact the products and services of Europea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damian Chmiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Execution-Only Platform Crossover Markets Raises $12M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740eb225c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/06/26/crypto-execution-only-platform-crossover-markets-raises-12m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Series A round was led by Illuminate Financial and DRW Venture Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donor Gifts 8 BTC to Aid Julian Assange’s Journey to Freedom]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740eb3615c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/donor-gifts-8-btc-to-aid-julian-assanges-journey-to-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julian Assange, the founder of Wikileaks, has finally embarked on his journey to freedom. The actual flight, however, comes with a hefty price tag of $520,000, which Assange is obligated to repay to the Australian government for the charter flight to Saipan and onward to Australia. After enduring 14 years of detention, including five years […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Duo Gets Prison Time for Manipulating Crypto Price]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ebdddec</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/american-duo-gets-prison-time-for-manipulating-crypto-price/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Kane and Shane Hampton have received jail terms for manipulating the price of a cryptocurrency of their company, Hydrogen Technologies, with wash and spoof trading, thus defrauding investors.
Jail For Market Manipulation  

According to the announcement by the Department of Justice yesterday (Tuesday), Kane, co-founder and CEO of the company, received three years and nine months in prison, while Hampton, the Head of Financial Engineering, received two years and 11 months. 
The sentencing came after Kane pled guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit securities price manipulation, one count of conspiracy to commit wire fraud, and two counts of wire fraud last November. Hampton, on the other hand, was convicted in February for one count of conspiracy to commit securities price mani…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu And PEPE Whales Deposit 1.8 Trillion Tokens To Binance, Are They Selling?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ebe0f1e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-pepe-whales-binance/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu and PEPE whales have begun to make their move in a market currently rocked with uncertainty. This time around, these prominent investors are sending large amounts of tokens to centralized exchanges like Binance, suggesting that they could be looking at dumping the meme coins. Such a move would put undue pressure on both the Shiba Inu and PEPE prices at a time when they’re struggling to find their footing.
 
Shiba Inu Whale Sends 1.8 Trillion Exchanges
 
Spot On Chain, an on-chain data tracking and aggregation platform, reported a transaction carrying significant amounts of SHIB. While these large transactions are not new, this one stood out due to the destination of the coins, which was the Binance crypto exchange.
 
 
As the data tracker reports, the whale transaction was most n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Unfazed By Failed DDoS Attack Targeting Staked ADA]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ebff48f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/06/26/cardano-unfazed-by-failed-ddos-attack-targeting-staked-ada/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No downtime was observed as a Cardano developer managed to attack the attacker and take back some funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ron Wyden on FISA Reform and Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ea4bb69</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/26/ron-wyden-on-fisa-reform-and-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) has been a long-standing member of the U.S. Senate, and was a sponsor or co-sponsor of several key pieces of legislation enabling broad adoption of the internet. More recently, he voted in favor of a House Resolution overturning the Securities and Exchange Commission's Staff Accounting Bulletin 121, and questioned threats to personal and financial privacy online. Last month, he spoke at CoinDesk's Consensus 2024 conference. As with previous versions of this newsletter, my questions have been shortened but the Senator's responses. have only been edited lightly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit Surpasses Coinbase's Crypto Trading Market Share]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ea4cce7</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bybit-surpasses-coinbases-crypto-trading-market-share/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit has surpassed Coinbase to become the second-largest cryptocurrency exchange in terms of volume, according to a recent report published by Kaiko. It is now only behind Binance, which dominates the market.
Second-Largest Crypto Exchange  

The report outlined that Bybit’s market share surged from 8 percent in October 2023 to 16 percent in June 2024, the highest growth rate among the top exchanges. Coinbase also improved its market share by merely a single percentage point, from 7 percent to 8 percent in the same period. The demand on Bybit surpassed the volume handled by Coinbase last March.  

However, Binance lost market share, as its dominance declined to 54 percent of the total volume in June, compared to 60 percent last October.
Bybit's spot trading offering has been driven by Bitcoin and Ethereum, the two largest cryptocurrencies by market capitalisation. The share of these two cryptocurrencies on the exchange jumped to 53 percent from merely 17 percent last year.  

Market leader Binance, on the other hand, witnessed declining demand for Bitcoin and Ethereum, which dropped to 43 percent from 59 percent a year ago. However, it saw a stronger increase in altcoin volume.
Finance Magnates earlier reported that the number of registered users on Bybit surpassed 30 million recently, as the exchange increased its customer base by 10 million over the last six months.
Low-Fee Is a Factor  

Kaiko pointed out that one factor that could have benefited Bybit “could be its competitive fees, which are among the lowest in the industry.” Indeed, the exchange introduced zero-fee trading for Circle’s USD (USDC) stablecoin in February.
“However, other offshore exchanges like Binance and OKX also offer low fees, and many exchanges have ongoing zero-fee promotions and reward campaigns… This suggests that while low fees contribute to Bybit's competitive edge, they are not the only reason for its rise,” the report added.
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Arnab Shome at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian Stock Exchange B3 Mulls Offering Ether Futures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ea61cc4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brazilian-stock-exchange-b3-mulls-offering-ether-futures/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[B3, the Brazilian stock exchange, is considering extending its native cryptocurrency trading options to offer ether futures contracts to its customers. The exchange, which has been a pioneer in Latam offering crypto-related trading products, would be focusing on institutional investors who want to diversify their traditional or crypto portfolios with more options. Brazilian Stock Exchange […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Protocol Alex Lab $4 Million Hack Linked To Lazarus Group]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740ea0d32f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/defi-protocol-alex-lab-4-million-hack-linked-to-lazarus-group/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Lab, a Bitcoin-based DeFi protocol, revealed new details about the hack it suffered in May. The project announced it had potentially identified the attacker with the help of a blockchain sleuth while the police continued to investigate the incident.
 
 
DeFi Protocol Loses Millions To Phishing Attack
 
On May 15, the Alex Lab Foundation fell victim to an exploit that took millions in users’ funds. The DeFi protocol unveiled that the attacker obtained private keys via a phishing attack, granting them full access to the funds.
 
The attacker used the compromised keys to access one of the vaults associated with the Alex Liquidity Pool, which compromised all assets in the vault.
 
The affected asset list includes aBTC, sUSDT, XBTC, xUSD, ALEX, atALEX, LiSTX, SKO, CHAX, $B20, ORDG, ORMM, O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea’s Lazarus Group Exploited Defi Protocol Alex Lab for $4.3 Million, Probe Reveals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740eaf4f6f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/north-koreas-lazarus-group-exploited-defi-protocol-alex-lab-for-4-3-million-probe-reveals/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T04:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin layer-two developer Alex Lab revealed that an investigation linked the North Korea-linked Lazarus Group to the $4.3 million exploit that occurred on May 16. Alex Lab has facilitated communication between the Singapore Police Force and relevant cryptocurrency exchanges as part of the ongoing investigation. Alex Lab Collaborates With Law Enforcement in $4.3M Hack Investigation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin As Federal Tax Payment Method? Congressman Presents New Legislation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740eafceaa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-as-federal-tax-payment-method/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T04:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for the crypto industry, Republican Congressman Matt Gaetz is set to introduce a new bill allowing federal income tax payments to be made using Bitcoin (BTC). 
 
Gaetz believes that by allowing taxpayers to utilize Bitcoin for their federal tax obligations, the country can foster innovation, enhance efficiency, and provide greater flexibility to American citizens. 
 
The proposed legislation aims to amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986, directing the Treasury secretary to establish a framework for accepting Bitcoin as a valid form of payment.
 
Inspiration From El Salvador?
 
In a statement to The Daily Wire, Gaetz expressed his belief that this step is crucial in shaping a future where digital currencies play a significant role in the financial system, ensu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Quietly Buy $439 Million In BTC While Market Panics]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740e95f854</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-whales-quietly-buy-439-btc-market-panics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T03:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that large investors in the Bitcoin network have been buying while the market has been in a panic state about the latest crash.
 
Bitcoin Large Holders Netflow Has Been Positive Recently
 
According to data from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, the largest wallets on the Bitcoin blockchain have been making some large net inflows recently.
 
The on-chain indicator of interest here is the “Large Holders Netflow,” which keeps track of the net amount of the cryptocurrency entering into or exiting the wallets associated with the “Large Holders.”
 
IntoTheBlock defines Large Holders as those investors who own at least 0.1% of the entire circulating supply of the asset. There are over 19.7 million BTC tokens in circulation, so this figure would be equivalent to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metallica Joins Growing List of Hacked Celebs Promoting Scam Crypto Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=237057</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/237057/metallica-hacked-celebs-promoting-scam-crypto-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T02:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter account for the heavy-metal titans was used to promote the METAL Solana meme coin, which spiked—and then swiftly collapsed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Digital Rupee Usage Drops Drastically After Initial Surge]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740e907e93</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/indias-digital-rupee-usage-drops-drastically-after-initial-surge/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T02:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s central bank digital currency (CBDC), the digital rupee, has experienced a significant decline in usage, decreasing to a tenth of its peak in December 2023, according to sources involved in the pilot project. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) initially reached 1 million daily retail transactions with the digital rupee by incentivizing banks and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Investors Embrace Crypto: Majority of Institutions Ready to Invest, Survey Finds]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740e93fb3b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/japanese-investors-crypto-majority-of-institutions/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T02:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent insights from a survey conducted by Nomura Holdings and Laser Digital Holdings shed light on the evolving attitudes of Japanese institutional investors towards cryptocurrency.
 
The survey, which included responses from 547 investment managers across various sectors such as family offices and public interest corporations, suggested a big embrace of cryptocurrency from these respective fields.
 
 
YES to Crypto
 
A striking 54% of these investors expressed intentions to venture into the cryptocurrency market within the next three years, highlighting a shift towards diversifying investment portfolios with digital assets.
 
The findings suggest a significant inclination towards using cryptocurrencies as speculative instruments and as substantial components of diverse investment strateg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Cancer Detector Boasts 98% Accuracy Across 13 Types: Study]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=237007</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/237007/ai-cancer-detection-98-percent-accurate-cambridge"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T00:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new machine learning model could speed early detection, diagnosis, and treatment, Cambridge researchers say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tor Constantino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Rebound Sees Shorts Rekt as Crypto Market Recovers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=237052</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/237052/bitcoin-price-rebound-short-position-liquidations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T23:49:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than $92 million in liquidations landed in the last day, most of it hitting short positions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toys‘R’Us Ad Made With AI Ignites Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=237017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/237017/ai-film-toys-r-us-sora-controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T23:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One actor called the 60-second production, created using Sora from OpenAI, an “abomination.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is 'Catizen'? The Telegram Swipe-to-Earn Game and Airdrop Details]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=237036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-catizen-telegram-crypto-game-airdrop-details"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T23:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catizen, the latest Telegram game to blow up, has you combining felines to increase your cat café earnings—and it’s a little more involved than others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Stubbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blast’s Token Airdrop Is Tomorrow—Here’s Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=237026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/237026/blasts-token-airdrop-everything-you-need-know"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of this year’s most hyped crypto giveaways is finally here as Ethereum layer-2 network Blast is set to conduct its long-awaited airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Did OpenAI Just Acquire a Screen-Sharing Startup?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236978/openai-acquires-multi-screen-sharing-startup"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “multiplayer” collaboration software firm is shutting down its app to join the ChatGPT desktop project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Gensler's War on Crypto Hurt Biden? ‘I Don't Speak About Elections’, SEC Chair Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=237014</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/237014/gary-gensler-war-on-crypto-biden-election-ethereum-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T21:43:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler also said that the process for launching Ethereum spot ETFs is “going smoothly.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 145 - WE SURVIVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/812Lhy0g/fomo-hour-145-we-survived</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/812Lhy0g/fomo-hour-145-we-survived"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T21:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces back above $61k after nosedive. SOL leads majors, BTC dominance falls. BTC RSI hit 18, largest net selling day in over a year. $174m ETF outflow led by GBTC. German government sells $24m more more BTC. Mt Gox info probably ‘leaked to insiders’. Mr 100 buys dip for first time in 34 days. SOL leads Moonpay transactions for 5th week. Trump may speak at Bitcoin Nashville. Biden rehires crypto advisor. Crypto & AI complement each other: Balaji. Bitcoin will protect AI’s wealth: Pomp. Tether stops minting on Algorand & EOS. Jupiter launches v3 swaps. ETH Foundation mailing list gets leaked. Jump CEO resigns after CFTC investigation. 54% of Japanese institutional investors want BTC. Strike launches in UK. MiCA approved EUR stablecoins coming in 6 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Hamster Kombat? The Telegram Crypto Game and Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-hamster-kombat-telegram-game-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat is the latest Telegram-based crypto game to go viral, just like Notcoin. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netmarble’s Marblex Migrating to Ethereum L2 Immutable zkEVM With $20 Million Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236984</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236984/netmarble-marblex-ethereum-immutable-zkevm"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean mobile gaming giant Netmarble is shifting its Marblex ecosystem from Klaytn to the Ethereum layer-2, with three games set to make the leap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayFi Launches the PlayFi Airdrop Platform to Enhance Community Engagement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236989/playfi-launches-the-playfi-airdrop-platform-to-enhance-community-engagement"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City, New York, 25th June 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GolfN Tees Up Play-to-Earn Golf Following $1.3M Pre-Seed Raise]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236977/golfn-tees-up-play-to-earn-golf-following-1-3m-pre-seed-raise"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T19:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago, United States, 25th June 2024, Chainwire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chainwire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Bitcoin Bottom In? Here's What Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236953</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236953/is-the-bitcoin-bottom-in-heres-what-experts-say"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T18:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot ETFs, Mt. Gox creditors, and the German government have recently hit Bitcoin’s price. But not everything on the horizon is dour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck Filing Suggests Ethereum ETFs Are Only One Week Away]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236951</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236951/vaneck-filing-suggests-ethereum-etfs-one-week-away"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T18:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When VanEck published this filing for their Bitcoin ETF, the product launched seven days later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Matt Gaetz Introduces Bill to Allow Federal Tax Payments in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236945</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236945/rep-matt-gaetz-bill-federal-tax-payments-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T17:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paying taxes with Bitcoin? Republican House Representative wants to make it so in the U.S. as crypto becomes a key election year issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Has Shed All of Last Month’s Gains as Roaring Kitty Disappears]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236943</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236943/gamestop-shed-last-months-gains-roaring-kitty-disappears"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GME’s latest losing streak continues as GameStop’s stock price turns negative over the past month with Roaring Kitty quiet again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany Selling More Bitcoin After Dumping $170 Million: Arkham]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236936</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236936/germany-selling-bitcoin-dumping-170-million-arkham"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German authorities have moved even more seized Bitcoin to exchanges, apparently liquidating more of its BTC billions in the weakened market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidirim Ndeche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Art Mile ‘Bridges Worlds’ Between Traditional and Electronic Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236872/digital-art-mile-bridges-worlds-between-traditional-and-electronic-art"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T13:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The art fair in Basel showcased contemporary and historical digital art, alongside a programme of talks and screenings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation Launches Social Media Features Aimed at 'Putting Crypto Back in Crypto Twitter']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236854</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236854/solana-foundation-launches-new-feature-social-media"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T13:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Actions and Blinks features are aimed at "putting the crypto back into crypto Twitter," Solana Foundation head of engineering told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Gemz’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn 5 Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/gemz-daily-combo-guide-free-coins-telegram-game"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like Hamster Kombat, rising Telegram game Gemz offers players a massive daily haul of free coins. Here’s how to get it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonshot Rising: DexScreener's Pump.fun Competitor Already Has 7,000 Solana Meme Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236904</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236904/dexscreeners-pump-fun-competitor-moonshot-solana-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DEX Screener says that its launchpad ensures that all smart contracts launched on the platform are fully audited.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Minsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘PixelTap’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn Millions of Free Coins in the Pixelverse Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/pixeltap-daily-combo-guide-earn-free-coins-pixelverse-telegram-game"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game PixelTap lets you battle robots to earn coins ahead of a token airdrop—and you can earn way more with this easy bonus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Sweeping Bitcoin and Ethereum Liquidations, Analysts Are Watching for Accumulation Whales]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236887</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236887/after-sweeping-bitcoin-and-ethereum-liquidations-analysts-are-watching-for-accumulation-whales"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“This is time when accumulation whales are likely to respond to market fear, indicating a potential V-shaped rebound," said a CryptoQuant analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidirim Ndeche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptopia Announces Increased Airdrop Allocation and Beta Tester Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236902</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236902/cryptopia-announces-increased-airdrop-allocation-and-beta-tester-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands, 25th June 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Lost $174 Million After Confirmation of Mt. Gox Repayments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236855/bitcoin-etfs-lost-174-million-mt-gox-repayments"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T10:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past five trading sessions, Bitcoin ETFs have seen net outflows of $714 million, according to data analytics platform SoSovalue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake Has Lost Over $1 Million in Bitcoin Betting on Stanley Cup and NBA Finals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236856/rapper-drake-lost-1-million-bitcoin-betting-on-stanley-cup"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T08:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapper's fate was sealed when the Florida Panthers beat the Edmonton Oilers in Game 7 to secure their first ever championship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Minsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Shares How to Send and Receive Crypto Using Kraken Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Dg5Xjel7/mika-shares-how-to-send-and-receive-crypto-using-kraken-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Dg5Xjel7/mika-shares-how-to-send-and-receive-crypto-using-kraken-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T07:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Rug Radio creator and crypto influencer Mika as she guides you through the process of sending and receiving cryptocurrency using the Kraken wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Doom’ Creator Says AI Can Do a Lot of Things—Except Be Original]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236845</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236845/doom-creator-john-romero-ai-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T00:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ID Software co-founder John Romero said using AI is “problematic” as it is based on existing material.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI Gets New CEO, Restructuring Amid Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236829</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236829/stability-ai-ceo-bailout-departures-license-controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T23:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Weta Digital CEO Prem Akkaraju takes the helm of the company as it deals with debt, departures, and a controversial release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Deadrop' Game Studio Drops Founder Dr. Disrespect After Alleged Misconduct]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236839</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236839/deadrop-game-studio-drops-founder-dr-disrespect"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T22:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society co-founder and streamer Dr. Disrespect is out following accusations that went viral over the weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Music Industry Giants Sue AI Music Services Udio and Suno]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236809</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236809/ai-music-riaa-lawsuit-suno-udio-industry-copyright"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T21:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Recording Industry Association of America accuses the generative music services of “unlicensed copying of sound recordings on a massive scale.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Firm MicroStrategy's Price Target Cut—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236800</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236800/microstrategy-bitcoin-stock-price-target-cut-canaccord-genuity"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T20:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canaccord Genuity said Bitcoin price volatility played a part in its revision, but still gives MSTR a buy rating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Slammed by Iran Official as Telegram Game Claims 200 Million Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236798</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236798/hamster-kombat-slammed-iran-telegram-game-200-million-players"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A military general said that crypto game Hamster Kombat is part of the West’s “soft war” against Iran as state-run media also weighs in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 144 - A VERY RED DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tDG5cHBN/fomo-hour-144-a-very-red-day</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tDG5cHBN/fomo-hour-144-a-very-red-day"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 6-week lows, $215m liquidations in fall. Mt Gox set to start BTC repayments in July. Fear & Greed index nears 2024 lows. Bitfinex whales’ long positioning rebounds. Open Interest rises as shorts grow, funding negative. BTC is economic immortality, going to $10m: Saylor. Moment of truth for BTC to rebound: Ansem. Expect $61-62k BTC to hold: Emperor BTC. SOL upgrade is big step-change: Raoul Pal. Expect slow melt-up from ETH ETF: DC Investor. MKR falls 11% as delegate gets phished. TON ecosystem sees phishing attacks spread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Riot Attempts to Purge Bitfarms Board as Hostile Takeover Bid Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236765</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236765/bitcoin-miner-riot-purge-bitfarms-board-hostile-takeover-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T19:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riot has abandoned a proposal to absorb Canadian Bitcoin mining firm Bitfarms for $2.30 a share. But Riot is not giving up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Administration Rehires Crypto Advisor Critical of the SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236794</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236794/biden-admin-rehires-crypto-advisor-critical-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the White House's stance on crypto changing ahead of the election? A past advisor has returned to a post on the National Security Council.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japan's MicroStrategy Pops 9% After Announcing $6.2 Million Bond Sale to Buy Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236774</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236774/metaplanet-stock-japan-microstrategy-bond-sale-buy-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplanet could soon scoop up another 100 BTC thanks to the latest price dip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Falls Further as Crypto Liquidations Top $330 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236775/bitcoin-price-falls-further-crypto-liquidations-330-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Mt. Gox creditors are promised their Bitcoin back, the market panics on fears that they’ll dump it all into the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 143 - CRYPTO TRENDS LOWER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dvJof6CV/fomo-hour-143-crypto-trends-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dvJof6CV/fomo-hour-143-crypto-trends-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto sinks, ETFs see another $140m outflow. German government likely sells $195m more BTC. 100 day BTC break-out coming: Don Alt. SOL ETF applied for in Canada. Rumours SEC case vs Coinbase also dropped. Standard Chatered setup spot trading desk. ARB has record daily revenue on LayerZero claims. CFTC investigating Jump Crypto. FTM outperforms ahead of Sonic upgrade. Binance integrates USDT on TON. Onchain prediction market TVL continues to soar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 142 - ETH LEADS THE RALLY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH continues to lead gains, SOL underperforms. BTC may rebound as Fed liquidity rips higher. ETH sees large amount of bullish call activity. LayerZero launches today, 25% unlock. Funding level the lowest in 3 months. German government sends 1000 BTC to exchanges. Stablecoins to become 10% of money: Circle CEO. Stabelcoin transfers up 16x in 4 years. BTC exchanges balances hit 3 year low. SOL again flips ETH for DEX volumes. Kraken reports $3m bug exploit found by CertiK. Debate about whether CertiK were whitehats. Jump Crypto gives $10m to crypto PAC. Binance launches HODLer airdrops. TipLink allows SOL transfers by email. ETHFI proposes 50% revenue for buybacks. JTO teases LSD backed stablecoin. JUP team proposes to reduce 30% of supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Robotics Company Aims to Solve a Labor Shortage in Manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrayMatter Robotics Co-founder and CEO Ariyan Kabir explains the origin of the company, the need for artificial intelligence and robotics to offset a growing labor shortage, and takes Decrypt on a tour of its AI-powered facility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 141 - SEC DROPS ETH PROBE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 65.4k (0%), ETH: 3545 (+3%), SOL: 139 (+2%). Top Gainers: LDO, BRETT, PEPE, AR. ETH & beta lead gains after SEC headline. SEC drops probe into ETH as a security. BTC ETFs see another $152m outflow. Pantera show $100m buying interest in ETH ETF. Pantera aims to raise new $1bn fund. Lack of staking won’t harm ETH ETF: 21 Shares. LayerZero airdrop coming June 20th. SEC concerns on USDC may delay Circle IPO. Hayes increasing PENDLE & DOGE positions. Fox News to build L2 with Polygon. EIGEN trades at $10bn pre-market. Drift & Ondo partner on RWAs. Commercial real estate coming on-chain: KPMG.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 140 - MARKETS DOWN BAD]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC touches 1-month lows, dominance hits 56%. $500m of liquidations in fall, $146m ETF outflows. VanEck to launch first ETF in Australia. Coinbase to launch pre-market trading. 56% of Fortune 500 building in web3. Uphold to delist USDT in EU due to MiCA. TON flips DOGE in sell-off. Base DEX users now 2nd place after SOL. Ethena launches staking & restaking with Symbiotic. Lens aiming to raise $50m at $500m valuation. Two ‘crazy’ MATIC announcements coming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 139 - WHATS THE NEXT META?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC again breaks $66k, dominance rises. Fear & Greed index hits 3 month low. Whales continue to be in accumulation mode. Miners 33 days into capitulation, average 41 days. Financial advisors not buying BTC yet: BlackRock. Crypto funds saw $600m outflows last week. ZKsync airdrop live, prices at $5bn FDV. ZKsync defend sybil measures. Low float, high FDV coins get hammered again. Tether launches product backed by Gold. Korean exchanges reviewing 600 coins for delisting. ETH ETF ‘sell the rumour, buy the news event’. BTC ETF basis buyers roughly 15% of demand. CVX bounces 100% after loan liquidation. TON sees fastest user growth in crypto history. APT may flip SOL in 1-3 years: Hayes. Crypto lifetime funding eclipses $100bn. SEC claims $876m Ripple fine still fair. Gensler could cost Biden election: Cuban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 138 - MORE CELEB COINS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed out heavy, BTC dominance rises towards 60%. Miners continue to be large BTC sellers, whales accumulate. ETF inflows slow, hedge fund allocations point to basis trades. ETH ETFs approvals see little movement, coming 'in the summer’. Stocks continue to hit ATHs as CPI & PPI both come in soft. TON performs best in L1s, active wallets eclipse ETH. Andrew Tate joins celebrity memecoin meta, DADDY hits $350m. SOL DEX volumes eclipse ETH in memecoin frenzy. Curve founder defaults on CRV debt as DeFi coins tumble. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon to pay $4.5bn fine to SEC. BAMK hits $350m in Runes as it issues BTC stablecoin. Gaming tokens face huge sell-off, PRIME changes tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 137 - CRYPTO DIPS FURTHER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls after slightly hawkish Fed speech. BTC whales buy $1.4bn in 24hrs. Miners continue to be large sellers of BTC. BTC ETFs see $100m inflows. MicroStrategy to raise $500m to buy BTC. Egorov CRV debt positions begin to liquidate  . Circle to support SOL for wallets. 4% of Turkey GDP used to buy stablecoins. QuantMatter say $11m stolen from OKX account. Biden to use Coinbase for crypto donations. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon set to pay $4.5bn fine. Franklin Templeton write report on SOL DePin. TON flips ETH for active addresses. Moonpay & Paypal integration goes live in EU & UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 136 - FIRST MOTHER, NOW DADDY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see another $200m outflows. Another $190m of liquidations in volatility. $1.2bn BTC leaves exchanges in a day. ETF flows largely driven by basis trades: Pal. ‘Perfect setup’ for longs into macro news today. ETH ETF approvals ‘expected this month’. Crypto in best place it has ever been: Circle CEO. China’s ICBC calls ETH ‘digital oil’. Trump wants ‘made in the USA’ BTC. Crypto hacks $19bn since 2011. Symbiotic restaking protocol sees $150m inflows. Polygon launches $720m grants program. ZKsync accused of insider allocations. CRV drop leaves $90m loans at risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>