<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-06T21:12:44.271Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-06T21:12:44.271Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP News: Why The January 11 Court Hearing Is Critical For Ripple And The Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbdc139d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-january-11-ripple-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T21:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January 11 has been set as the day for the court hearing in the case between Ripple and a class of XRP investors in what has been a long-running legal battle. The outcome of the case is of huge significance as another precedent could be laid for the crypto industry and its stakeholders. 
 
Why This Ripple Case Is Important
 
The class of XRP investors led by Vladi Zakinov are accusing Ripple of selling XRP as an unregistered security. As such, any ruling made by Judge Phyllis Hamilton could have several ripple effects throughout the crypto industry. For one, it could lead to other class actions being instituted against other crypto firms. 
 
 
The case is also significant considering that it borders on issues that are in focus in the legal battle between the Securities and Exchange Commiss…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin (LTC) Flashing Bullish Signal Amid Rising Address Activity: Crypto Analytics Firm Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155398/Litecoin-LTC-Flashing-Bullish-Signal-Amid-Rising-Address-Activity-Crypto-Analytics-Firm-Santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155398/Litecoin-LTC-Flashing-Bullish-Signal-Amid-Rising-Address-Activity-Crypto-Analytics-Firm-Santiment"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T21:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analytics firm Santiment says that peer-to-peer payments network Litecoin (LTC) is flashing readings that could lead to a price surge. Santiment notes that Litecoin, decentralized finance (DeFi) protocol Maker (MKR) and liquid-staking service provider Lido DAO (LDO) are all witnessing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP News: Why The January 11 Court Hearing Is Critical For Ripple And The Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155407/XRP-News-Why-The-January-11-Court-Hearing-Is-Critical-For-Ripple-And-The-Crypto-Industry</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155407/XRP-News-Why-The-January-11-Court-Hearing-Is-Critical-For-Ripple-And-The-Crypto-Industry"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T21:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Mega Whales Continue Buying Spree; Signals of Optimism or Hidden Warnings?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155400/Ethereum-Mega-Whales-Continue-Buying-Spree-Signals-of-Optimism-or-Hidden-Warnings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155400/Ethereum-Mega-Whales-Continue-Buying-Spree-Signals-of-Optimism-or-Hidden-Warnings"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the recent market recovery, Ethereum (ETH) has attracted attention as prominent whales embarked on a sizable accumulation of the crypto asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CertiK briefly loses its account to a Forbes impersonator]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155395/CertiK-briefly-loses-its-account-to-a-Forbes-impersonator</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155395/CertiK-briefly-loses-its-account-to-a-Forbes-impersonator"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. interest rate cut bets for 2024 see massive decline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155396/US-interest-rate-cut-bets-for-2024-see-massive-decline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155396/US-interest-rate-cut-bets-for-2024-see-massive-decline"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment world is recalibrating its expectations for U.S. interest rate cuts in 2024. This shift comes in the wake of recent economic data and comments from Federal Reserve officials, which suggest a more hawkish stance than previously anticipated. Last year, the market was overly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Spot Bitcoin ETFs might not cut it]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155397/Why-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-might-not-cut-it</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155397/Why-Spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-might-not-cut-it"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment world is on the cusp of a potentially historic moment with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) poised to possibly approve the first spot Bitcoin ETFs. Despite the fervor, there’s a growing sentiment that these financial instruments might not be the panacea for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2.15 Million Ethereum Poured Into Liquid Staking Protocols in 6 Months]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbde1745</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/2-15-million-ethereum-poured-into-liquid-staking-protocols-in-6-months/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent statistics indicate that in the past six months, a substantial 2.15 million ethereum has been allocated to liquid staking derivatives protocols. As of Jan. 6, 2024, Lido Finance holds a dominant share, exceeding 75% of the total deposited ether, with a massive addition of 1.7 million ethereum deposited since July 5, 2023.
 
Liquid Staking Protocols Surge, Locking More Than $27B of Ethereum
 
The arena of liquid staking protocols has witnessed significant expansion, both in the volume of ether deposits and ETH’s overall value increase, during the last half-year. Archived records from defillama.com on July 5, 2023, reveal that 10.16 million ether, valued at $19.69 billion, were locked in these protocols. Presently, the combined total has surged to 12.31 million ether, now worth $27.49…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia wants BRICS to have more power in the IMF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155382/Russia-wants-BRICS-to-have-more-power-in-the-IMF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155382/Russia-wants-BRICS-to-have-more-power-in-the-IMF"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a bold move marking the beginning of its chairmanship, Russia has set its sights on elevating the BRICS alliance’s influence within the International Monetary Fund (IMF). This initiative, driven by Russian President Vladimir Putin, aligns with the bloc’s growing ambition to reshape the global...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon: Can high network activity push MATIC north]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155380/Polygon-Can-high-network-activity-push-MATIC-north</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155380/Polygon-Can-high-network-activity-push-MATIC-north"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock expects spot Bitcoin ETF approval next Wednesday: Fox Business]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155377/BlackRock-expects-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-approval-next-Wednesday-Fox-Business</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155377/BlackRock-expects-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-approval-next-Wednesday-Fox-Business"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wait for the government to approve a spot Bitcoin ETF may be over by the middle of next week, according to BlackRock's prediction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Satoshi JUST USE BINANCE?!?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155373/Did-Satoshi-JUST-USE-BINANCE</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155373/Did-Satoshi-JUST-USE-BINANCE"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCG Successfully Repays All Genesis Short-Term Loans]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155365/DCG-Successfully-Repays-All-Genesis-Short-Term-Loans</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155365/DCG-Successfully-Repays-All-Genesis-Short-Term-Loans"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Predicts Dramatic Rise In Cardano (ADA) Price, Here’s The Target]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155354/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-Dramatic-Rise-In-Cardano-ADA-Price-Heres-The-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155354/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-Dramatic-Rise-In-Cardano-ADA-Price-Heres-The-Target"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whopping 9.25 Trillion SHIB May Be Burned This Month, Shiba Inu Rep States]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155366/Whopping-925-Trillion-SHIB-May-Be-Burned-This-Month-Shiba-Inu-Rep-States</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155366/Whopping-925-Trillion-SHIB-May-Be-Burned-This-Month-Shiba-Inu-Rep-States"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu representative stated that SHIB team may potentially remove almost 10 trillion SHIB from circulation this month]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC instructs ETF participants to submit updated filings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155353/SEC-instructs-ETF-participants-to-submit-updated-filings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155353/SEC-instructs-ETF-participants-to-submit-updated-filings"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T19:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has directed several participants in the Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) market to submit revised filings, according to Bloomberg’s report on January 5. The SEC has specifically instructed exchanges and issuers to provide final versions of their 19b-4...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price correction predicted by BitMEX co-founder Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155340/Bitcoin-price-correction-predicted-by-BitMEX-co-founder-Arthur-Hayes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155340/Bitcoin-price-correction-predicted-by-BitMEX-co-founder-Arthur-Hayes"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T19:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great Sword: Craft and Upgrade Your Weapon in Monster Hunter World]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155332/Great-Sword-Craft-and-Upgrade-Your-Weapon-in-Monster-Hunter-World</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155332/Great-Sword-Craft-and-Upgrade-Your-Weapon-in-Monster-Hunter-World"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T19:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon’s 2023 Bitcoin Production Surpasses $563 Million, Tripling 2022 Output: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155322/Marathons-2023-Bitcoin-Production-Surpasses-563-Million-Tripling-2022-Output-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155322/Marathons-2023-Bitcoin-Production-Surpasses-563-Million-Tripling-2022-Output-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T19:06:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase Freezes, Eliminates Bank Account Without Warning, Explanation or Redemption: New Accusations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155325/JPMorgan-Chase-Freezes-Eliminates-Bank-Account-Without-Warning-Explanation-or-Redemption-New-Accusations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155325/JPMorgan-Chase-Freezes-Eliminates-Bank-Account-Without-Warning-Explanation-or-Redemption-New-Accusations"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T19:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Corrupt is The World Economic Forum From Insider?!? #Bitcoin #Crypto #Shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155333/How-Corrupt-is-The-World-Economic-Forum-From-Insider-Bitcoin-Crypto-Shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155333/How-Corrupt-is-The-World-Economic-Forum-From-Insider-Bitcoin-Crypto-Shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T19:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Whales Going Crazy On ADA Buys As Pundits Predict $4 ADA Price Explosion In 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155302/Cardano-Whales-Going-Crazy-On-ADA-Buys-As-Pundits-Predict-4-ADA-Price-Explosion-In-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19155302/Cardano-Whales-Going-Crazy-On-ADA-Buys-As-Pundits-Predict-4-ADA-Price-Explosion-In-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T18:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Rocky Start to 2024 — SOL’s Value Dips Over 6% Amidst Previous Year’s Highs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbc7f3d6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/solanas-rocky-start-to-2024-sols-value-dips-over-6-amidst-previous-years-highs/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T18:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the initial week of 2024, the digital currency solana experienced a sharp decline, shedding over 6% in value. This downturn has relegated the crypto asset to the fifth position in market rank, as it oscillates beneath the $100 threshold on Saturday, Jan. 6, 2024.
 
2024 Brings Chill to Solana’s Market Performance
 
After surging by over 700% in 2023, solana (SOL) has experienced a cool-off period. In the last week, SOL dipped slightly more than 6%, yet it still boasts a 46% increase against the U.S. dollar over the preceding month.
 
As of Jan. 6, 2024, SOL’s intraday value fluctuated between a high near $100 and a low of $92.23, trading at $96.75 per unit at 12:51 p.m. Eastern Time. Notably, SOL commands significant influence in South Korea’s market, trading at $99 on Upbit and $98.81 on Bithumb, surpassing the global average of $96 per unit as noted on aggregate market sites.
 

 
Tether (USDT) is SOL’s primary pair, constituting over 67% of all solana trades, followed by the U.S. dollar and Korean won, contributing 14% and 8% of SOL’s trade volume respectively, according to data from cryptocompare.com.
 
Behind them, BTC and the stablecoin FDUSD represent 3.35% and 2.68% of SOL’s trading activity. Currently, Solana ranks fifth in global trade volume, reaching $2.287 billion in the last 24 hours, though this figure has dipped over 30% from the previous day.
 
 
SOL’s market capitalization stands at $41.30 billion, accounting for 2.387% of the total $1.73 trillion crypto market value. Despite a commendable 621% rise over the past year, SOL is still trailing more than 63% below its peak of $259 per unit on Nov. 6, 2021.
 
As the crypto asset navigates the volatile market, its future trajectory remains uncertain, leaving investors to wonder if it will continue as a leading performer in 2024.
 
What do you think about solana’s market performance this week? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low Turnout: 39% Predict Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval By SEC In 2024, Survey Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbc8ac35</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/39-predict-spot-bitcoin-etf-approval-by-sec/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T17:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, the spot Bitcoin ETF approval by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) is deemed certain by just 39% of financial advisors, according to a recent survey.
 
The survey’s findings demonstrate that financial advisors are generally skeptical of the commission’s decision to approve a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF).
 
There are several reasons for this lack of assurance. The SEC’s cautious and conservative past handling of cryptocurrency-related items is the first and most important factor.
 
Advisors Skeptical: SEC’s Bitcoin ETF Fate
 
Financial advisors appear pessimistic about the SEC’s approval of the spot Bitcoin ETF this year, based a survey conducted by Bitwise and VettaFi.
 
 
LESS THAN HALF OF ALL ADVISORS EXPECT A SPOT BITCOIN ETF IN 2024…
 
In a surprisin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuna Rin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly NFT Sales Record Minor Ebb While Bitcoin Maintains Dominance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbcb1602</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/weekly-nft-sales-record-minor-ebb-while-bitcoin-maintains-dominance/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T16:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to recent data, sales of non-fungible tokens (NFTs) over the last week declined by 1.31% to $308.23 million, a decrease of $4.09 million from the prior week’s $312.32 million. NFTs centered around Bitcoin remained at the forefront among 21 distinct blockchain networks, experiencing a 4.10% uptick in sales this week.
 
RBX Voucher Sale Leads the Pack in Priciest NFTs, as Uncategorized Ordinals Compilation Dominates This Week’s Collections
 
This week saw 873,268 NFT buyers and 619,949 sellers engaging in transactions worth $308.23 million in NFT sales. Despite the buyer and seller counts each surging over 20%, sales dipped slightly by 1.31% over the course of the week.
 
 
The priciest NFT, an Ethereum-based “RBX Vesting Voucher #42,” fetched $741,910, equivalent to over 328 ether…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Founder Predicts 30% To 40% Bitcoin Price Correction If SEC Approves ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbbcca8a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-founder-predicts-30-to-40-bitcoin-price-correction-if-sec-approves-etf/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T15:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX co-founder, Arthur Hayes, has published a blog post predicting a specific price correction for Bitcoin following the introduction of the highly anticipated Spot Bitcoin ETF. 
 
Bitcoin Price Correction Forecast
 
The former chief executive officer of BitMEX, Hayes has shared valuable insights on the potential price impact for Bitcoin following the approval of Spot Bitcoin ETFs by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
 
According to Hayes’s analysis, Bitcoin is projected to experience a 20% to 30% price correction by March 2024. The crypto exchange founder warned that the correction phase could be relatively steep if there is a substantial surge in traders’ interest in Spot Bitcoin ETFs. 
 
“I expect Bitcoin to experience a healthy 20% to 30% correction from w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Spot Bitcoin ETFs Inch Closer to Approval — Analyst Says It’s ‘Basically Done’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbbfe146</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/11-spot-bitcoin-etfs-inch-closer-to-approval-analyst-says-its-basically-done/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T14:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eleven spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) are moving closer to approval by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Proposed rule changes to list and trade all 11 spot bitcoin ETFs on stock exchanges have been filed with the SEC. “It’s basically done,” an ETF analyst said, adding that the securities regulator is “trying to line everyone up for Jan 11th launch.”
 
Bitcoin ETF Decisions Loom: Analyst Says ‘It’s Basically Done’
 
Proposals to list and trade 11 spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) flooded for the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Friday amid heightened speculation regarding the imminent approval of spot bitcoin ETFs by the securities regulator.
 
“The [SEC] staff had no additional feedback on the paperwork for several of the firms after the la…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn To Be Automated Through Shibarium – How Much SHIB Will Be Destroyed Monthly?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fba1cc2e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-to-be-automated-through-shibarium/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T12:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the announcement of an automated Shib burn mechanism, speculations have been flying concerning the total number of SHIB tokens slated to be burnt every month in 2024. 
 
9.25 Trillion SHIB Set To Burn Monthly 
 
According to a 2022 publication, a Shiba Inu community member, ‘Queenie’ on X (formerly Twitter) created a hypothetical estimation of the total amount of Shiba Inu tokens that could be burned through the burn portal in a year. According to Queenie, SHIB’s total supply could be reduced by over 111 trillion in a “bad” year.
 
 
Anyone can run hypotheticals from current data :) 
I did this just now: pic.twitter.com/iSeKJeB9V9
 
— Queenie (@Web3Queenie) March 31, 2022
 

 
 
This hypothetical analysis has given rise to rumors, suggesting a potential burn of 9.25 trillion SHIB…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mystery Transfer — Unidentified Wallet Sends $1.19 Million in Bitcoin to Satoshi Nakamoto’s Genesis Address]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fba391ab</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/mystery-transfer-unidentified-wallet-sends-1-19-million-in-bitcoin-to-satoshi-nakamotos-genesis-address/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T12:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two days after Bitcoin’s 15th anniversary, an unidentified wallet transferred roughly 26.917 bitcoin, valued at $1.19 million, into Satoshi Nakamoto’s Genesis wallet. Originating on Jan. 3, 2009, this wallet has primarily accumulated nominal dust transactions. Including the hard-coded block reward, minor dust transactions, and the recent 26.917 bitcoin deposit, the total now stands at 99.676 bitcoin, equivalent to $4.35 million. 
 
Satoshi’s Genesis Wallet Receives $1.19 Million Boost: A Cryptic Bitcoin Anniversary Gift
 
An anonymous sender dispatched $1.19 million in bitcoin (BTC) to the “1A1zP” wallet of Satoshi Nakamoto. Originating from the “bc1q9” address, this substantial sum of 26.917 BTC was confirmed at block height 824,513. The motivation behind sending these funds to the Genesi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ark Invest Continues to Sell Coinbase Shares]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fbab77ba</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ark-invest-continues-to-sell-coinbase-shares/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T11:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a strategic move, Ark Invest has offloaded another portion of its Coinbase holdings, selling over $29 million worth of COIN shares from its ETFs. This decision aligns with Ark’s target weighting policy and follows Coinbase’s strong performance in the last quarter of 2023.
 
Ark Invest Sells Over $29 Million in Coinbase Shares Amid Portfolio Rebalancing
 
Ark Invest, led by CEO Cathie Wood, has been actively selling shares of Coinbase (Nasdaq: COIN), further reducing its stake in the crypto exchange, although Coinbase still is one of the most significant assets of Ark’s portfolio.
 
On Jan. 3, Ark sold a total of 166,183 COIN shares from its Innovation ETF (ARKK) and Next Generation Internet ETF (ARKW) for a value of $25.3 million at the closing price for the day. The following day, Jan.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EVM Chains See Slump In Inscriptions – What’s Behind The Drought?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb95dc38</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/evm-chains-see-slump-in-inscriptions/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T10:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been a noticeable surge in transaction activity on the main Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM) chains as of late. Around 95% of these transactions have inscriptions, according to blockchain analytics tool Etherscan.
 
Ordinals inscriptions have gained favor as a direct means of creating non-fungible tokens (NFTs) on the blockchain by embedding unique data in transaction call data.
 
Imagine tiny capsules, embedded within Bitcoin itself, holding images, text, or even videos. That’s what Ordinals Inscriptions are: digital artifacts etched permanently onto the Bitcoin blockchain. Each inscription sits on a single Satoshi, the smallest unit of Bitcoin, creating unique, indestructible assets. Think of them as NFTs forged within the Bitcoin network itself.
 
 
Decoding The Drop In Inscript…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq-Listed Bitcoin Miner Cleanspark to Launch in-House Trading Desk, CEO States It ‘Makes Financial Sense’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb9c0d23</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nasdaq-listed-bitcoin-miner-cleanspark-to-launch-in-house-trading-desk-ceo-states-it-makes-financial-sense/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T09:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cleanspark, a Nasdaq-listed Bitcoin mining company, has announced that it will launch an in-house trading desk to maximize the return on its cryptocurrency holdings. Cleanspark CEO Zachary Bradford explained that organizing their trading desk made “financial sense,” given the high volume of Bitcoin reserves the company handles.
Cleanspark Announces in-House Crypto Trading Desk
Cleanspark is moving to utilize its bitcoin to generate more revenue. The U.S.-based public mining company will launch an in-house cryptocurrency trading desk to take advantage of its bitcoin holdings later this year. According to Bloomberg, the company is seeking to put its more than 2,500 BTC to work amidst a surge in cryptocurrency prices due to the expectation of the upcoming approval of a Bitcoin ETF.
The compan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF Applicants Submit 19b-4 Amendment Forms – Approval Imminent?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb9811ad</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-applicants-submit-19b-4-amendment/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T08:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the latest development, about a dozen Bitcoin spot ETF (exchange-traded fund) applicants have submitted 19b-4 amendment documents. These submissions come with the deadline for the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to approve the investment product just days away. 
 
Will Bitcoin Spot ETF Be Approved Next Week?
 
On Friday, January 5, 11 asset management firms looking to offer Bitcoin spot ETF in the US filed 19b-4 amendments for their applications. These companies include BlackRock, Grayscale, Valkyrie, ARK 21shares, Hashdex, Biteise, Invesco Galaxy, Fidelity, VanEck, WisdomTree, and Franklin Templeton.
 
These submissions are one of the defining last steps in the SEC approval process for an exchange-traded fund. However, S-1 filings still need to be completed and a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvesting the Digital Skies: The Controversial Practice of Airdrop Farming]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb842c0d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/harvesting-the-digital-skies-the-controversial-practice-of-airdrop-farming/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T08:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the crypto economy burgeons, a new trend called airdrop farming is taking root, offering both promise and pitfalls. The following is an exploration of this emerging practice, unraveling its intricacies, potential rewards, and the controversies it stirs.
 
The Double-Edged Sword of Airdrop Farming: Boon for Some, Bane for Others
 
In recent years, airdrops have surged in prominence, with individuals involved in decentralized finance (defi) discovering rewarding opportunities, and defi initiatives innovating ways to disburse their native cryptocurrencies. As the appeal of airdrops has grown, a trend of widespread farming has emerged within the sector.
 
Although this strategy has proven profitable for a handful, others contend it manipulates the system unjustly. Fundamentally, airdrop far…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better Markets CEO Opposes Bitcoin Spot ETF Approval – Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb829e2c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/better-markets-opposes-bitcoin-spot-etf-approval/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T06:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a stern warning to the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Dennis M. Kelleher, Co-Founder and CEO of Better Markets, a non-profit organization that focuses on advancing public financial interest, has issued a statement vehemently opposing the approval of Bitcoin spot ETFs. 
 
This development comes amidst widespread optimism among market analysts that the SEC will, in the next few days, greenlight several applications by asset managers vying to launch a Bitcoin spot ETF in the United States.
 
 
Approving Bitcoin Spot ETF Would Be A ‘Historic Mistake’ – Kelleher
 
On Friday, December 6, Better Markets submitted a Supplemental Comment Letter to the SEC in response to proposed rule changes by national securities exchanges looking to list and trade shares in Bitcoin spot ETFs. 
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamma Heist — Over $3M in Digital Assets Drained, 1,000 ETH Moved to Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb83d361</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gamma-heist-over-3m-in-digital-assets-drained-1000-eth-moved-to-tornado-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T06:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Jan. 4, the decentralized finance protocol Gamma Strategies was a victim of a hacking attack which saw criminals make off with digital assets worth over $3 million. To pre-empt further attacks, Gamma Strategies said it has shut off all deposits on any of its “public-facing vaults.”
 
Hacker Transfers 1,000 Ethereum to Crypto Tumbler Tornado Cash
 
On Jan. 4, 2023, the decentralized finance (defi) protocol Gamma announced its platform had been breached in a cyber attack, resulting in the theft of digital assets valued at several million dollars. In response to thwart additional security breaches, Gamma reported it has ceased all deposits into its “public-facing vaults.”
 
According to a series of alerts issued by the blockchain security company Peckshield, the exploiter-labeled address h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Assigns Monitoring Tag to Privacy Coins, Including Monero and Zcash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb7574c4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-assigns-monitoring-tag-to-privacy-coins-including-monero-and-zcash/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T04:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the largest cryptocurrency exchange, has recently announced that it will start monitoring ten new projects, including privacy blockchains like Monero, Firo, Mobilecoin, and Zcash. Binance reported that these projects might be delisted in the future, failing to meet the criteria required by the exchange to keep being traded on its platform.
Binance Might Delist Several Privacy Coins, Including Monero and Zcash
Binance might be moving to delist privacy coins in the future. In a recent announcement, the exchange reported that it will assign the monitoring tag to ten different cryptocurrency projects, of which several are privacy-focused.
Firo, Mobilecoin, Monero, and Zcash are now part of the assets that Binance states present “notably higher volatility and risks compared to other li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asset Manager Vaneck Pledges to Donate 5% of Spot Bitcoin ETF Profits to Bitcoin Core Developers for 10 Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb7c70a9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/asset-manager-vaneck-pledges-to-donate-5-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-profits-to-bitcoin-core-developers-for-10-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T03:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset management firm Vaneck has pledged to donate 5% of its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) profits to support Bitcoin Core developers for at least 10 years. The company is currently awaiting approval from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to launch its spot bitcoin ETF. The securities regulator is expected to approve multiple applications early next week.
 
Vaneck to Donate 5% of Spot Bitcoin ETF Profits
 
Asset manager Vaneck pledged financial support for Bitcoin Core developers on Friday, ahead of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s decision on its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application. Vaneck is one of 11 companies vying to launch the first U.S. spot bitcoin ETFs.
 
“We’re not Bitcoin tourists at Vaneck. We’re in it for the long ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Institutional Investors Buying In ETF Anticipation? This Metric Suggests So]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb7ce79d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-institutional-buying-etf-anticipation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T03:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows the Bitcoin Coinbase Premium has remained positive since the start of the year, a sign that institutional traders may be buying.
 
Bitcoin Coinbase Premium Gap Is Still At Positive Levels
 
CryptoQuant community manager Maartunn explained in a Quicktake post that there has been significant demand for Coinbase since the start of 2024.
 
The indicator of interest here is the “Coinbase Premium Gap,” which keeps track of the difference in the Bitcoin prices listed on cryptocurrency exchanges Coinbase and Binance. This metric can tell us how buying and selling behaviors differ between the two platforms.
 
 
When the value of this indicator is positive, it means that the price listed on Coinbase is greater than that on Binance right now. Such a trend implies the former is either recei…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layer 2 On Solana? Possible But Irrelevant, Says Co-founder – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74fb79257f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/layer-2-solana-possible-irrelevant-says-co-founder/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-06T02:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, a prominent player in crypto, has been a subject of much discussion, particularly regarding adopting Layer2 (L2) solutions. Anatoly Yakovenko, the co-founder of Solana, recently clarified this topic, emphasizing the blockchain’s core mission and its stance on Layer2 solutions.
 
Solana’s Focus: Enhancing Layer1 Over Layer2 Solutions
 
Yakovenko, in a definitive statement, dismissed the necessity of Layer2 solutions for SOL, labeling them irrelevant to the blockchain’s primary objective.
 
 
 
 
According to Yakovenko, the blockchain aims to expand its atomic global state machine – a sophisticated system designed to increase efficiency and scalability.
 
Yakovenko pointed out that while Layer2 solutions like side chains and zero-knowledge proofs are ‘innovative and welcomed,” they d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Take a Big Step Toward Approval, Analysts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211876</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211876/bitcoin-spot-etf-applications-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T23:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's application led the way on Friday, as an ETF analyst predicted that we could see a $100 billion Bitcoin ETF in as little as five years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report Crypto Trades Over $10K to IRS or Face Jail? It’s Complicated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211843</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211843/crypto-trades-10k-irs-jail-complicated"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T21:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new tax law appears to have massive implications for crypto users. But who it might affect, and when, is not so straightforward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pixels Game Airdrop Announced—Here’s How to Get Pixel Tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211855/pixels-game-airdrop-announced-heres-how-to-get-pixel-tokens"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T18:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrops continue to keep crypto believers enthralled, further fueled by Pixels’ latest announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Says It Won’t Use Your Private Data to Train Its AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211846</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211846/anthropic-says-it-wont-use-your-private-data-to-train-its-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T18:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI companies hungrily consume every trove of data they can find, the makers of Claude.AI say they won’t their its own customers' work to improve its chatbot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin's Time Has Arrived': ETF Hopefuls Eagerly Await SEC Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211839</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211839/whats-happening-with-the-bitcoin-etf-today"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETF hopeful Hashdex releases a Bitcoin advert as analysts speculate that the SEC’s decision on Bitcoin ETFs may be imminent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius to Unstake $466 Million Ethereum Holdings, 'Ensure Ample Liquidity' for Creditors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211799</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211799/celsius-to-unstake-466-million-ethereum-holdings-ensure-ample-liquidity-for-creditors"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T10:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celsius accounts for almost a third of ETH awaiting withdrawal, as it begins "recalling and rebalancing assets" ahead of asset distributions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Airdrop Coming Ahead of Blockchain Launch—Here’s Who Is Eligible]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211794</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211794/who-is-eligible-for-the-saga-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Polygon, Avalanche, Cosmos, and Celestia users will be included in Saga’s community token airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’re Not Here to Sell You Another ChatGPT’: Perplexity AI CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211784/perplexity-ai-answer-engine-not-another-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder Aravind Srinivas wants to change the perception of generative AI through a trustworthy "answer engine."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s LFG Token Lures Ethereum Users, Plans Second Airdrop and Grants Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211778</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211778/solana-lfg-ethereum-users-second-airdrop-grants-program"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's “Less Fn Gas” airdropped LFG tokens to Ethereum users who spent over $4,269 in gas over the last year. It doesn't want to stop there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logan Paul Launches CryptoZoo NFT ‘Buyback,’ Files Countersuit As Legal Battles Rage On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211776/logan-paul-launches-cryptozoo-nft-buyback-files-countersuit-as-legal-battles-rage-on"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The famous YouTuber and influencer alleges two of his CryptoZoo co-creators engaged in “nefarious trading activity.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blame Human Lawyers, Not Tech, for Courtroom Blunders: Robin AI Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211764/uk-startup-raises-26-million-to-build-law-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robin AI is taking on hallucinations and other thorny issues to ensure tech is an effective courtroom partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Advisors Are Still Skeptical SEC Approves Bitcoin ETF, Bitwise Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211770/financial-advisors-are-still-skeptical-sec-approves-bitcoin-etf-bitwise-says"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only 39% of 437 financial advisors polled said they think we'll see a Bitcoin ETF available to U.S. investors in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beam Token Up 36% as Merit Circle Network Transactions Hit All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211737/beam-token-up-merit-circle-transactions-hit-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche subnet token is climbing back toward its highest price ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Adds Dedicated AI Key to Windows 11 Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211739/microsoft-copilot-keyboard-dedicated-key"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cortana didn’t fare much better than Clippy, but the Redmond-based tech giant is betting that Copilot will finally earn its spot at our fingertips.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nikon, Sony, and Canon Pitch a New Way to Fight Deepfakes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211744</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211744/nikon-sony-and-canon-pitch-a-new-way-to-fight-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of watermarking AI images, top cameramakers propose encoding signatures into real photos instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale, VanEck and ARK Bitcoin ETFs Register to Trade on Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211735</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211735/grayscale-and-vaneck-bitcoin-etfs-register-to-trade-on-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T18:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more Bitcoin ETF applicants have gotten the green light to have their funds listed on exchanges—but it's all pending SEC approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rebounds From Flash Crash as Market Fixates on ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211732/bitcoin-rebounds-flash-crash-btc-etf-price"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC has recovered losses after slipping briefly yesterday on fears that Bitcoin ETFs might again be denied or delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Coins Monero, Zcash, Horizen 'At Risk' of Delisting by Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211717/privacy-coins-monero-zcash-horizen-at-risk-of-delisting-by-binance"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T11:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has flagged several privacy coins with a "monitoring tag" indicating that they are at risk of being delisted from its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's What's Coming to Xbox Game Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208162/heres-whats-coming-xbox-game-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Xbox Game Pass is adding more indie games to its subscription service, as well as a few big names. Here's a look at the lineup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: Is It Priced In?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211708</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211708/bitcoin-etf-priced-in"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T22:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts are split on whether the long-awaited approval of a Bitcoin ETF will halt BTC’s momentum, or pump the cryptocurrency even higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Bitcoin ETF Set to Trade on CBOE—But No Word From SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211702/fidelity-bitcoin-etf-set-to-trade-on-cboe-but-no-word-from-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T20:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust got the ok to trade on the CBOE under the FBTC ticker, but there's still no word from the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Justice Ponders Impact of AI on Law]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211696</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211696/supreme-court-justice-warns-of-ais-impact-on-legal-system"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T20:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justice Roberts emphasized AI's ability to aid people, but also 'dehumanize' the legal processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Before AI Puts Us Out of Work, AI Jobs Could Pay Well]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211675/before-ai-puts-us-out-of-work-ai-jobs-could-pay-well"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI jobs are paying on average 77% more than other jobs, with entry-level positions paying more than twice the average salary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Possible Scenarios for Bitcoin ETFs in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211560</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211560/three-possible-scenarios-bitcoin-etf-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will they or won’t they? The SEC is on the clock and crypto markets eagerly await its decision on a Bitcoin ETF. Here’s what could happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Tokens IMX, SAND and AXS Plunge Following Bitcoin Flash Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211671/gaming-tokens-imx-sand-and-axs-plunge-following-bitcoin-flash-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T18:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable, The Sandbox, Axie Infinity, and Gala tokens dropped 8-15%, facing deeper losses after Bitcoin’s dip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Upgrade Could Create a Centralized Fork, Says BRC-20 Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211665/bitcoin-ordinals-upgrade-could-be-unsafe-create-centralized-fork"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T18:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest drama in Bitcoin inscriptions swirls around the BRC-20 protocol, which allows the creation of meme coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearish Bitcoin ETF Report Spooks Market—But Analysts Say Denial Is Unlikely]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211658/bearish-bitcoin-etf-report-spooks-market-analysts-say-denial-unlikely"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A line about approval by Q2 2024 didn’t calm fears. The suggestion that none of the ETF applications will be approved in January panicked the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's MixMob Launches 'Race-to-Earn' Game Ahead of Airdrop, Saga Phone Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211637</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211637/solanas-mixmob-launches-race-earn-game-ahead-airdrop-saga-phone-perks"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MixMob's Racer 1 lets players gamble on races or earn crypto for wins. An airdrop is coming, along with benefits for Solana Saga owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges 7% to $42,000 in Flash Crash as Bull Run Falters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211634/bitcoin-plunges-7-to-42000-in-flash-crash-as-bull-run-falters"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin plunged by over 7% in the past 24 hours, erasing the past week's gains in a matter of minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor to Sell $216 Million in MicroStrategy Stock Options, Buy More Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211626/michael-saylor-to-sell-216-million-in-microstrategy-stock-options-buy-more-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T11:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy co-founder Michael Saylor plans to "acquire additional Bitcoin" for his personal holdings with some of the proceeds of the sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Powered Cybercrime Will Explode in 2024: CrowdStrike Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211596</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211596/ai-powered-cybercrime-will-explode-in-2024-crowdstrike-executive"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T02:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security exec Shawn Henry says the capability of AI to deceive and misinform is coming of age just in time for the 2024 elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midjourney Leaps into AI Video Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211583/midjourney-leaps-into-ai-video-creation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T01:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI image generator MidJourney will begin training its video model in the upcoming days and they expect to release a final product "in a few months"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s When to Expect the Jupiter JUP Airdrop for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211576/heres-when-expect-jupiter-jup-airdrop-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T00:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter’s airdrop draws nearer and nearer. Here’s when the Solana DEX aggregator plans to launch JUP to the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source or OpenAI: What's the Best Path to Advanced AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211563/open-source-or-openai-whats-the-best-path-to-advanced-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T23:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long tweet went viral among AI enthusiasts, revisiting a decades-long debate over how AI will best evolve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Traders Flock to Sei and Its Dragon Ball-Inspired Meme Coin—Will It Last?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211551/crypto-traders-flock-to-sei-and-its-dragon-ball-inspired-meme-coin-will-it-last"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dragon Ball-themed SEIYAN meme coin has been gathering energy—and gains—on the Sei Network's Layer 1 blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFT Sales Skyrocket, Topping Ethereum in Monthly Volume for First Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211547/solana-nft-sales-skyrocket-ethereum-monthly-volume"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T21:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising momentum around Solana catapulted NFT sales above Ethereum in December, according to data from CryptoSlam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sell Signal? Jim Cramer Pulls U-Turn on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211530/sell-signal-jim-cramer-pulls-u-turn-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infamous crypto skeptic admits Bitcoin's resilience in the face of government pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake Reveals Crypto Casino Stake's Rebranded F1 Racing Team]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211523/drake-reveals-crypto-casino-stakes-rebranded-f1-racing-team"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sauber's F1 team is now officially the Stake team. Rapper, spokesperson, and frequent bettor Drake took to social media to share the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dymension Is the Latest Airdrop for Solana, Ethereum, and Cosmos Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211515/dymension-latest-airdrop-solana-ethereum-cosmos-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than a million crypto users and NFT owners across chains can now claim DYM tokens in Dymension’s airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson Explains His Quest for Immortality and Why He Started with the Penis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire biohacker Bryan Johnson shared with Decrypt's Jason Nelson why he began his longevity quest and how technology has shaped the endeavor. Johnson also discusses some of his controversial experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>