<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-08-20T10:13:14.452Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-08-20T10:13:14.452Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Judge rules in favor of human ingenuity, denies copyright for AI art]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848440/US-Judge-rules-in-favor-of-human-ingenuity-denies-copyright-for-AI-art</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848440/US-Judge-rules-in-favor-of-human-ingenuity-denies-copyright-for-AI-art"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T10:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This ruling shifts the conversation on AI and copyright and underscores the significance of human creativity in intellectual property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Shows Promoter of Binance FUD Adam Cochran Is An FTX Affiliate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848424/Data-Shows-Promoter-of-Binance-FUD-Adam-Cochran-Is-An-FTX-Affiliate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848424/Data-Shows-Promoter-of-Binance-FUD-Adam-Cochran-Is-An-FTX-Affiliate"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critics spread FUD about Binance, arguing that it may be about to crumble like FTX. One of the FUD promoters is an FTX affiliate, Adam Cochran. Cochran raised concerns about the Binance SAFU Fund. Some prominent crypto community figures are again spreading fear, uncertainty, and doubt FUD about...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When This Coin Does A 10x People Will Be SAD They Don't Own Any]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848422/When-This-Coin-Does-A-10x-People-Will-Be-SAD-They-Dont-Own-Any</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848422/When-This-Coin-Does-A-10x-People-Will-Be-SAD-They-Dont-Own-Any"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Possible Futures ETF Approval: How Will Price React?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848439/Ethereums-Possible-Futures-ETF-Approval-How-Will-Price-React</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848439/Ethereums-Possible-Futures-ETF-Approval-How-Will-Price-React"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins Flashing Bullish Signal After Last Week’s Bloodbath, According to Analytics Firm Santiment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848400/Altcoins-Flashing-Bullish-Signal-After-Last-Weeks-Bloodbath-According-to-Analytics-Firm-Santiment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848400/Altcoins-Flashing-Bullish-Signal-After-Last-Weeks-Bloodbath-According-to-Analytics-Firm-Santiment"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:15:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New data from market intelligence firm Santiment suggests that altcoins may recoup some of their losses from the crypto market’s sharp downturn last week. According to the crypto analytics platform, altcoins are “overwhelmingly showing undervaluation” after last week’s bloodbath, leaving...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto downturn sinks ALGO price to all-time low]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848390/Crypto-downturn-sinks-ALGO-price-to-all-time-low</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848390/Crypto-downturn-sinks-ALGO-price-to-all-time-low"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Files a Reply Memorandum Against SEC To Dismiss LawsuitÂ]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848394/Gemini-Files-a-Reply-Memorandum-Against-SEC-To-Dismiss-LawsuitA</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848394/Gemini-Files-a-Reply-Memorandum-Against-SEC-To-Dismiss-LawsuitA"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T09:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Trust Company files a reply brief requesting the court to dismiss the SEC lawsuit against the exchange. The lawsuit claimed that the platform traded unregistered securities and amassed billions worth of crypto assets from investors. The exchange asserts that the SEC has failed to produce...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BAYC NFT Sells for 153 ETH Just 11 Months After 777 ETH Purchase – Seller Loses 80%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848389/BAYC-NFT-Sells-for-153-ETH-Just-11-Months-After-777-ETH-Purchase-Seller-Loses-80</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848389/BAYC-NFT-Sells-for-153-ETH-Just-11-Months-After-777-ETH-Purchase-Seller-Loses-80"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape NFT Sells for 153 ETH Just 11 Months After 777 ETH Purchase – Seller Loses 80% A Bored Ape Yacht Club (BAYC) NFT that was the most valuable Trippy Bored Ape on record when it sold for 777 ETH in November 2022 has exchanged hands for 153 ETH. Thanks to rare attributes, including trippy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canaan Cuts Bitcoin Mining Power by 2 EH/s Amid US, Kazakhstan Challenges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75501f8c39</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/canaan-cuts-bitcoin-mining-power-by-2-eh-s-amid-us-kazakhstan-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canaan, a leading high-performance computing firm and mining rig producer, recently disclosed hurdles set to dent its bitcoin mining activities and revenue from Q3 2023 onward. These setbacks primarily stem from diminished operational hours of their mining devices. This revelation comes hot on the heels of Canaan’s teaser about their “groundbreaking” mining innovation slated for a September debut.
 
Canaan Forced to Trim Mining Power by 2 EH/s
 
In Kazakhstan, regulatory changes forced Canaan’s hand, making them curtail 2 exahash per second (EH/s) of their mining prowess since July. That’s a significant chunk, amounting to half of their mining power across Central Asia and North America. To paint a clearer picture, Canaan’s overall hashrate stood at 4 EH/s as Q1 2023 wrapped up.
 
While gr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JUST IN: Binance Announces a New Altcoin to List on Futures]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848354/JUST-IN-Binance-Announces-a-New-Altcoin-to-List-on-Futures</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848354/JUST-IN-Binance-Announces-a-New-Altcoin-to-List-on-Futures"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T08:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO clarifies on SEC appeal, highlights case complexity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848342/Ripple-CTO-clarifies-on-SEC-appeal-highlights-case-complexity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848342/Ripple-CTO-clarifies-on-SEC-appeal-highlights-case-complexity"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to David Schwartz, the SEC is seeking an appeal at this specific point based on its interpretation that the legal case has not yet concluded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RUNE Defies Market Sentiment With 30% Weekly Surge, BTC Uncertain at $26K: Market Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848330/RUNE-Defies-Market-Sentiment-With-30-Weekly-Surge-BTC-Uncertain-at-26K-Market-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848330/RUNE-Defies-Market-Sentiment-With-30-Weekly-Surge-BTC-Uncertain-at-26K-Market-Watch"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legendary Trader Peter Brandt Warns Bitcoin at Risk of Doing Damage Amid ‘Highly Suspect’ Price Action]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848323/Legendary-Trader-Peter-Brandt-Warns-Bitcoin-at-Risk-of-Doing-Damage-Amid-Highly-Suspect-Price-Action</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848323/Legendary-Trader-Peter-Brandt-Warns-Bitcoin-at-Risk-of-Doing-Damage-Amid-Highly-Suspect-Price-Action"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T07:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran trader Peter Brandt is warning that Bitcoin (BTC) is on the verge of losing all bullish momentum following the marketwide crypto correction. Brandt, who gained legendary status after calling the crypto king’s meltdown in 2017, tells his 698,500 X followers that Bitcoin is now at risk of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morocco Denies South Africa’s Claim That It Has Applied to Join BRICS: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7550003dd0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/morocco-denies-south-africas-claim-that-it-has-applied-to-join-brics/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Morocco has reportedly denied the claim made by South Africa, the host of the BRICS summit this year, that it has formally applied to join the economic bloc. According to South African officials, over 40 countries are interested in joining the BRICS group, including 23 nations that have formally applied.
 
Morocco Maintains Good Relations With 4 BRICS Countries, Will Not Attend Summit
 
South Africa, the host of the BRICS summit this year, claimed last week that 23 countries have formally applied to join the economic bloc. According to South Africa’s Minister of International Relations and Cooperation, Naledi Pandor, they are Algeria, Argentina, Bangladesh, Bahrain, Belarus, Bolivia, Venezuela, Vietnam, Cuba, Honduras, Egypt, Indonesia, Iran, Kazakhstan, Kuwait, Morocco, Nigeria, State of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the crypto SEI project airdrop: check to see if you are eligible]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848303/A-look-at-the-crypto-SEI-project-airdrop-check-to-see-if-you-are-eligible</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848303/A-look-at-the-crypto-SEI-project-airdrop-check-to-see-if-you-are-eligible"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Integrates with Copper’s ClearLoop to Offer Institutional Clients Innovative Off-Exchange Settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848300/Bitget-Integrates-with-Coppers-ClearLoop-to-Offer-Institutional-Clients-Innovative-Off-Exchange-Settlement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848300/Bitget-Integrates-with-Coppers-ClearLoop-to-Offer-Institutional-Clients-Innovative-Off-Exchange-Settlement"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Horoscope from 21 to 27 August]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848301/Crypto-Horoscope-from-21-to-27-August</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848301/Crypto-Horoscope-from-21-to-27-August"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SingularityNET: in-depth interview with the crypto-related AI project]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848302/SingularityNET-in-depth-interview-with-the-crypto-related-AI-project</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848302/SingularityNET-in-depth-interview-with-the-crypto-related-AI-project"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini files brief in lawsuit against SEC, requests to keep it simple]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848272/Gemini-files-brief-in-lawsuit-against-SEC-requests-to-keep-it-simple</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848272/Gemini-files-brief-in-lawsuit-against-SEC-requests-to-keep-it-simple"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T05:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dollarization Can Lead to ‘Economic Contraction and Collapse’ of Argentine Economy — Former US Treasury Official]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75500fe3de</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dollarization-can-lead-to-economic-contraction-and-collapse-of-argentine-economy-former-us-treasury-official/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T04:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. chairperson of the Official Monetary and Financial Institutions Forum (OMFIF) has characterized the Argentinian presidential hopeful’s plan to fully dollarize the economy as “a far too risky gamble.” Mark Sobel said full dollarization without an exit policy “could well lead to a far more serious economic contraction and collapse.”
 
Javier Milei’s Unconventional Policy Proposals
 
Argentinian presidential hopeful Javier Milei’s plan to dollarize the economy of the South American country is “a far too risky gamble,” Mark Sobel, the U.S. chairperson of the Official Monetary and Financial Institutions Forum (OMFIF), has said. According to Sobel, only “hard work” and austerity measures can extricate Argentina from its current problems.
 
During his campaigns, Milei has repeatedly tout…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Optimism L2 moving towards displacing Arbitrum?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848230/Is-Optimism-L2-moving-towards-displacing-Arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848230/Is-Optimism-L2-moving-towards-displacing-Arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T03:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Expansion Will Speed Up De-Dollarization, Chinese Expert Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551f6bbc4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-expansion-will-speed-up-de-dollarization-chinese-expert-says/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T02:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more countries join the BRICS economic bloc, there will be a significant increase in settlements using national currencies, leading to an acceleration in the de-dollarization process, a Chinese expert says. “For most developing countries, development is a top priority. That is why the BRICS cooperation mechanism is attractive to these countries,” he added.
 

 
BRICS and De-Dollarization
 
Sun Qi, executive director of the Center for Russian and Central Asian Studies at the Shanghai Academy of Social Sciences, told Russian news outlet Tass Friday that more countries joining the BRICS economic bloc will increase the use of national currencies in settlements significantly, which will help accelerate de-dollarization. The BRICS nations comprise Brazil, Russia, India, China, and South Afric…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Wants To Be In Jail Only On Weekends]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551f71309</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-sam-bankman-fried-jail/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T02:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 11, a Judge ruled that disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) be remanded in the Brooklyn Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC) after he was found guilty of violating his bail conditions. However, just a week after, SBF is asking to be released under special circumstances. 
 
SBF Asking For Weekday Bail
 
In a letter dated August 18, sent to US District Judge Lewis Kaplan, SBF’s lawyers ask that SBF be released on weekdays to enable them to prepare for his defense adequately. This comes after the lawyers rejected the prosecutors’ initial plan on how SBF would prepare for his trial, which begins on October 2. 
 
 
Federal Prosecutors reportedly gave SBF two days a week without adequate tools to handle the voluminosity of his case files. SBF’s lawyers have tagged this prep tim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX’s Sam Bankman-Fried Wants To Be In Jail Only On Weekends]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848203/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Wants-To-Be-In-Jail-Only-On-Weekends</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848203/FTXs-Sam-Bankman-Fried-Wants-To-Be-In-Jail-Only-On-Weekends"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T02:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 11, a Judge ruled that disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) be remanded in the Brooklyn Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC) after he was found guilty of violating his bail conditions. However, just a week after, SBF is asking to be released under special circumstances. SBF...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpaceX's Bitcoin Exit, Trump's Ethereum Stash And Floki's Meme Coin Love: Top Crypto Stories This Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848206/SpaceXs-Bitcoin-Exit-Trumps-Ethereum-Stash-And-Flokis-Meme-Coin-Love-Top-Crypto-Stories-This-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18848206/SpaceXs-Bitcoin-Exit-Trumps-Ethereum-Stash-And-Flokis-Meme-Coin-Love-Top-Crypto-Stories-This-Week"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T02:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economist Lord Jim O’Neill Calls BRICS Currency Idea ‘Ridiculous’ — Says China and India Never Agree on Anything]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551fd2b85</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/economist-lord-jim-oneill-calls-brics-currency-idea-ridiculous-says-china-and-india-never-agree-on-anything/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-20T00:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lord Jim O’Neill, the British economist credited with coining the acronym BRIC, calls the creation of a common BRICS currency “ridiculous,” emphasizing that the BRICS nations have “never achieved anything since they first started meeting.” He added: “It’s a good job for the West that China and India never agree on anything, because if they did the dominance of the dollar would be a lot more vulnerable.”
 
Lord Jim O’Neill Slams Common BRICS Currency Idea
 
British economist Lord Jim O’Neill shared his view on the proposed single BRICS currency in an interview with the Financial Times this week. The BRICS leaders are set to meet at the economic bloc’s 15th summit on Aug. 22-24 in Johannesburg. South Africa is the host of the BRICS summit this year. However, there are mixed reports on whethe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea Will No Longer Support NFTs Minted On This Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551f91c1a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/opensea-nfts-bsc/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T23:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November last year, NFT marketplace Opensea announced that the Binance Smart Chain Chain (BSC) was one of the several blockchains it was adding support for. However, that collaboration seems to be ending less than a year after.
 
OpenSea To End Support For BSC NFTs
 
In an announcement on the X (formerly Twitter) platform on August 17, the NFT marketplace stated that users would no longer be able to list or buy NFTs minted on the BSC chain. However, users “will still be able to view, discover, and transfer BSC NFTs” on the platform. 
 
 
According to OpenSea, this decision was made as part of its cost-reduction efforts. Apparently, the cost of maintaining BSC NFTs “outweighs” the company’s profits from this venture. 
 
This decision will undoubtedly surprise many, considering that Binan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankman-Fried Wants to See His Lawyers Outside Jail Five Days a Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551fb84ac</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bankman-fried-wants-to-see-his-lawyers-outside-jail-five-days-a-week/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T22:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF) is asking to be released from jail five days a week to work on his defense for the fraud trial against him set to begin in October. On Friday, Bankman-Fried’s lawyers complained to a judge in Manhattan that the currently proposed preparation time and regime for his case is “inadequate.”
 
SBF Seeks Daily Meetings With Lawyers at Courthouse and Laptop With Internet
 
Disgraced crypto mogul Sam Bankman-Fried is asking to be allowed to leave the Metropolitan Detention Center (MDC) in Brooklyn, New York, five days a week in order to meet with the members of his defense team at the federal courthouse in Manhattan.
 
The request comes just days after the 31-year-old founder and former chief executive of the failed cryptocurrency exchange FTX was jailed in the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Gears Up for ‘Holesky’ Testnet Launch With 1.6 Billion Testnet Ether]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551e2e429</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-gears-up-for-holesky-testnet-launch-with-1-6-billion-testnet-ether/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T20:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum developers plan to roll out a new testnet named Holesky, intending to bring 1.6 billion Holesky testnet ether to the network. The core devs of Ethereum highlighted that 1.4 million validators were evaluated for Holesky, with the aim of enhancing the blockchain’s comprehensive development.
 
Ethereum’s Holesky Set to Replace Goerli Testnet in 2023
 
As reported by Tim Beiko, a core developer, during the Ethereum Execution Layer Meeting 168, Parithosh Jayanthi shared an update on the recently launched devnet-8. Beiko mentioned that while some clients faced challenges, most have been addressed or are being fixed. Notably, Lighthouse encountered a problem due to nplex support removal – an issue they plan to resolve.
 
Furthermore, Beiko revealed that Ethereum JS rectified a bug relate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC And South Korea Are Tag-Teaming Against Terraform Labs, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551ec0af2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-and-south-korea-terraform-labs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T20:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has doubled its investigation efforts on Terraform Labs by teaming up with the South Korean government to gather more evidence into Terraform Labs’ operations. 
 
SEC And South Korea Against Terraform Labs
 
Terraform Labs, the company behind Terra blockchain and Terra USD stablecoin has been under scrutiny after investigations of its collapse revealed crypto market manipulation and fraudulent transactions. 
 
Given the breadth of the case, the SEC has been granted a motion by District Judge Jed Rakoff to join forces with South Korea to probe further into Terraform Labs and question Daniel Shin, Terraform Labs’ Co-founder. 
 
 
The decision to align with South Korea follows a recent report by Bloomberg which highlighted the SEC’s i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Believe In God? You Might Believe In AI, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153068/believe-in-god-you-might-believe-in-ai-too"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T19:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A joint university study suggests that people with a strong belief in God are more willing to trust advice from AI over humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Uncover Biological Echoes in Powerful AI Transformer Models]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153069/scientists-uncover-biological-echoes-in-powerful-ai-transformer-models"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T19:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unassuming astrocytes, thought to merely be helper brain cells, are more than meets the eye.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Court Classifies Tornado Cash as ‘Person’ in Verdict Echoing Ooki DAO Designation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551ea4a43</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-court-classifies-tornado-cash-as-person-in-verdict-echoing-ooki-dao-designation/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T18:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent ruling by a U.S. judge declared that Tornado Cash holds the legal status of a “person.” This development came on the heels of a previous verdict in June, which recognized the decentralized autonomous organization Ooki DAO in a similar manner.
 
U.S. Judiciary Designates Tornado Cash as ‘Person’ in OFAC Case
 
In a legal face-off with the U.S. government, specifically the OFAC, the plaintiffs posited that Tornado Cash is simply decentralized software. On the contrary, the government viewed it as an organization facilitating cryptocurrency mixing. Central to the dispute was whether the OFAC held the power to impose sanctions on Tornado Cash, and if such an action infringes on the plaintiffs’ freedom of speech.
 
Yet, the court dismissed the plaintiffs’ stance, recognizing Tornado Ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Have Stolen $200 Million So Far This Year: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153063/north-korean-hackers-stolen-over-200-million-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T18:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals have raked in over $2 Billion over the last five years, TRM Labs says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interlocutory Filing Sheds Light On SEC’s Stance Regarding XRP’s Security Status]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551d4375b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-stance-xrp-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T18:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the SEC vs Ripple case, the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has filed an interlocutory appeal on XRP’s security status and has made an inquiry from the US District Court in the Southern District of New York (SDNY) to certify its appeal against Ripple Labs.
 
This significant step in the SEC vs Ripple case originated due to a federal judge’s ruling that said on XRP sales conducted through exchanges did not breach securities law.
 
The judge in charge of the SEC vs Ripple case, Judge Torres Analisa then said the agency could proceed to file a motion for leave for an interlocutory appeal, this prompted the SEC to request for an interlocutory appeal.
 
SEC’s Interlocutory Appeal On Ripple Case
 
The SEC has been granted permission to file a motion for leave to file …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Flash Crash! Bitcoin and Ethereum Shed 10% as Altcoins Tumble]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153053/this-week-in-coins-flash-crash-bitcoin-ethereum-altcoins-down"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T17:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A major selloff this week sent the prices of all leading cryptocurrencies spiraling down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opensea Phases Out BNB Smart Chain Support, Citing Resource Alignment With Promising Efforts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551dcb8a5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/opensea-phases-out-bnb-smart-chain-support-citing-resource-alignment-with-promising-efforts/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T16:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the largest non-fungible token (NFT) platforms, Opensea, has declared its decision to withdraw BNB Smart Chain (BSC) support. Opensea revealed that the “cost to continue supporting BSC outweighs the impact.”
 
Opensea Pivots Away From BNB Smart Chain in Strategy Re-evaluation
 
On August 18, 2023, Opensea proclaimed that they would cease BSC support after incorporating multiple blockchains over recent years. This announcement coincides with Opensea’s strategy to phase out the enforcement of NFT royalties. Concerning BSC support, Opensea stated that as the industry advances, the company needs to “align resources with the most promising efforts.”
 
“We’ve decided the cost to continue supporting BSC outweighs the impact,” Opensea said. “Starting today, you will no longer be able to create new listings for or make new offers on BSC NFTs. However, you will still be able to view, discover, and transfer BSC NFTs on our site.”
 
 
In response to Opensea’s X thread publication, some individuals claimed they were unaware of BSC support’s existence. Others seized this chance to voice their grievances about the royalty ruling. One individual commented, “IDK what kind of system you guys are running over there but it’s not that expensive to run BSC if you do it right.”
 
Opensea concluded by asserting their continued optimism regarding a multi-chain future and shared that they recently added support for layer two (L2) blockchains Base and Zora. “We’re confident this decision will help us direct resources to keep pace with the rapid innovation in our ecosystem,” added Opensea.
 
What do you think about Opensea dropping BSC support? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender Helio Faces Regulatory Penalties In Australia For False License Claims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551db214b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/helio-faces-regulatory-sentencing-in-australia/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T15:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne-based cryptocurrency lending firm Helio has been subjected to penalties by the Australian Securities and Investment Commission (ASIC) for making false claims about holding an Australian credit license (ACL).
 
Enforced since 2009 through the National Consumer Credit Protection Bill, the ACL mandates strict criteria for entities offering financial services to consumers, extending to crypto lenders like Helio.
 
Helio, a subsidiary of US-based Cyios Corporation, which also owns the NFT platform Randomly, falsely publicized its possession of an ACL 391330 credit license in an August 2019 news article.
 
 
Helio: False Claims And ASIC’s Action
 
However, subsequent investigations by Australian regulators uncovered the anomalies of claims made by Helio. The lender’s assertion of obtai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuna Rin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s Turbulent Debut: Down 53% From Peak With 85% WLD Held in Just 6 Wallets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551c678e4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoins-turbulent-debut-down-53-from-peak-with-85-wld-held-in-just-6-wallets/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T14:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In just over 25 days since its listing debut on July 24, 2023, the cryptocurrency known as worldcoin (WLD) has experienced a notable decline of 29% when measured against the U.S. dollar. Notably, within the last week alone, it saw a decrease of more than 11%. Interestingly, within the past 24 hours, WLD showcased a rise of more than 15% against the greenback. Furthermore, four days prior, the count of distinct wallets containing WLD surpassed the 500,000 mark.
 
Worldcoin Plummets Over 50% Since Its All-Time High
 
According to statistics, the iris-scanning crypto project Worldcoin‘s native token, WLD, has increased 15% in the last 24 hours. Data from July 24 to August 18, 2023, shows WLD has declined 29.1% against the U.S. dollar. Currently, WLD ranks 156 out of more than 10,000 crypto as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypher Protocol Freezes Over $600,000 Of Stolen Funds On CEXs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551c03a63</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cypher-protocol-freezes-600000-stolen-funds-on-cexs/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T14:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cypher Protocol, a decentralized exchange (DEX) based on the Solana network, has disclosed that more than half of the funds stolen from its platform have been frozen across various centralized exchanges (CEXs). This comes as the latest development in the $1 million exploit of the protocol.
 
On August 7, 2023, Cypher Protocol reported a breach of its security, which caused the unauthorized withdrawal of 38,530 Solana and $123,184 USDC tokens. This attack prompted the protocol to halt its smart contract to prevent further unauthorized access.
 
Bitcoinist reported that the hacker tried to immediately cash out the stolen funds via centralized exchanges, transferring 30,000 USDC to Binance’s Solana USDC address in one transaction. However, it appears that most of these funds will not be leavi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: XLM, DOGE Rebound on Saturday, Following Recent Market Sell Off]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551c3968b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-xlm-doge-rebound-on-saturday-following-recent-market-sell-off/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T13:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar was a notable mover during Saturday’s session, as the token returned to the green to start the weekend. Prices recently fell lower for six straight days, however, bulls have reentered the market snapping this streak in the process. Dogecoin also rebounded today. 
 
Stellar (XLM)
 
Stellar (XLM) rose higher on Saturday, following a recent six-day losing streak which pushed the price to a multi-month low.
 
XLM/USD climbed to an intraday peak at $0.12 earlier in today’s session, which comes following a low of $0.1115 the day prior.
 
The move comes as stellar continued to move away from a support point at $0.110, which was hit on Thursday.
 
 
This was the first time the price collided with this floor since mid-June, and comes as the relative strength index (RSI) hit its own floor at 30.00.
 
At the time of writing this, the index has also rebounded and is now tracking at 34.84, which is marginally below a ceiling at 36.00.
 
Should it push past this point, the next likely price target will be around a ceiling of $0.1340.
 
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
In addition to XLM, dogecoin (DOGE) was also in the green to start the weekend, as it bounced from a floor of its own.
 
After trading at a low of $0.06079 during Friday’s session, DOGE/USD surged to a peak of $0.06385 earlier in the day.
 
The jump in price came as the meme coin moved away from a support point of $0.0600, which is near a recent two-month low.
 
 
Similar to XLM, the RSI on the dogecoin chart has bounced from a support point at the 30.00 mark, and is now tracking at 34.13.
 
The next visible point of resistance is at the 44.00 mark, and should this point be hit, DOGE will likely be near $0.06600.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will sentiment continue to shift this weekend? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Ethereum Whale Sells $41 Million ETH Before Market Crash: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551cd2d2e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-whale-sells-41-million-eth-market-crash/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T13:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last week, CoinMarketCap reports that Ethereum (ETH) has lost 10.31% of its value marking a highly negative performance for the prominent altcoin. However, most of this price loss was driven by a general market crash on Thursday, which saw about $1 billion wiped out from the total crypto market cap. 
 
Interestingly, prominent on-chain analytics firm, Lookonchain reports that a particular “smart” whale was able to avoid this market turmoil by liquidating a substantial amount of ETH right before the market crashed. 
 
 
Ethereum Whale Dumps 22,341 ETH Ahead Of Major Market Loss
 
According to a social media post on Friday by Lookonchain, a certain crypto whale sold 22,341 ETH, valued at roughly $41 million, just prior to the crypto market downturn this week. Lauding this liquidation …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC, ETH Seek Support Level, Following Worst Selloff Since FTX Crisis]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551ce4510</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-eth-seek-support-level-following-worst-selloff-since-ftx-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T13:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin started the weekend trading below $26,000, as the cryptocurrency had its worst week since the collapse of FTX. Market sentiment was bearish following reports that Spacex liquidated its bitcoin holdings. Ethereum remains below $1,700.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bears continued to circle bitcoin (BTC) to start the weekend, as the cryptocurrency had its biggest one-day decline since the collapse of FTX.
 
BTC/USD dropped to a low of $25,668.92 on Saturday, which comes less than 24 hours after trading at a high of $26,598.65.
 
As a result of today’s move, bitcoin remains close to a two-month low, with some traders targeting a breakout below $25,000.
 
 
Overall, the relative strength index (RSI) is deep in bearish territory, with a current reading of 18.56.
 
Price strength hasn’t tracked below 20.00 since January last year, which for some was the beginning of the so-called “crypto winter”.
 
Should there be further declines this weekend, the target will likely be a support point of $24,900.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) was marginally higher on Saturday, as the price rebounded from a recent move below $1,600.
 
Following a high of $1,695.45 on Friday, ETH/USD fell to a bottom of $1,644.93 to start the weekend.
 
On Thursday, ethereum dropped to a low of $1,540, which was its weakest point since March 12, when the price was trading below the $1,459 level.
 
 
The 10-day (red) moving average is now firmly on a downward trend, after appearing as though it was nearing an upwards cross earlier in the week.
 
As of writing, ethereum seems to have found a firm floor around the $1,660 level.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect ethereum to rebound in the coming week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto's Oldest Use Case Is Back in the Spotlight. But Why Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152936</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152936/cryptos-oldest-use-case-is-back-spotlight-why-now"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization is back in a big way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zetachain Raises $27 Million to Develop a ‘Chain to Manage Them All’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7551b35041</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/zetachain-raises-27-million-to-develop-a-chain-to-manage-them-all/"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T10:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zetachain, a project that seeks to build one chain to interoperate with all other blockchains, announced it raised $27 million in a Series A funding round. Blockchain.com, Human Capital, Vy Capital, Sky9 Capital, and Jane Street Capital, among others, participated in the funding round. Zetachain will use the funds to launch its solution on mainnet and grow its app ecosystem.
Zetachain Raises $27 Million in Series A Funding Round
Zetachain, an interoperability-focused blockchain project, has raised $27 million in a Series A funding round. Blockchain.com, Human Capital, Vy Capital, Sky9 Capital, Jane Street Capital, VistaLabs, CMT Digital, Foundation Capital, Lingfeng Capital, GSR, and others participated in the round. Funds will be used to launch the mainnet of the chain and also to grow it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban, Yuga Labs Lead Backlash Over OpenSea's NFT Royalties Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153043</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153043/mark-cuban-yuga-labs-lead-backlash-over-opensea-nft-royalties-change"/>
        <updated>2023-08-19T00:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea investor Mark Cuban expressed disappointment in the marketplace's move as creators plot potential boycotts and restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Down Bad Again—Here's Why and What Comes Next]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=153024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/153024/bitcoin-down-bad-again-why-what-comes-next"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T22:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon or Evergrande—or something else entirely? Experts share what caused Bitcoin's flash crash Thursday, and what to expect ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Enables 'Illicit Gambling' for Kids, Lawsuit Alleges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152990</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152990/roblox-enables-illicit-gambling-kids-lawsuit-alleges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T22:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox is being blamed for third-party online casinos that use its currency, Robux, and facilitate underage gambling. Will the case stick?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says He's Killing Twitter's Block Feature, Sparking Outcry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152980</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152980/elon-musk-says-hes-killing-twitters-block-feature-sparking-outcry"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T20:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Twitter owner revealed plans to axe the block feature, igniting swift backlash among users citing safety concerns on the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Crypto Bridge Collapses as DeFi Lender on Optimism Suffers $7 Million Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152966</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152966/defi-lender-optimism-exactly-suffers-7-million-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T20:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly, a credit market on the Optimism network, was hacked on Friday as thieves exploited its bridge to swipe a stash of ETH.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the DJ Who Wears a CryptoPunk Helmet While He Spins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152947</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152947/meet-seedphrase-dj-who-wears-cryptopunk-helmet"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T19:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With his debut single "Angels" out today, Seedphrase says he understands skepticism but wants to "let the music do the talking."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Biohacker Who Wants to Live Forever Just Started 'Penis Rejuvenation' Therapy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152950</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152950/billionaire-biohacker-wants-live-forever-just-started-penis-rejuvenation-therapy"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 45-year-old Bryan Johnson is undergoing therapy using sound waves to help him attempt to achieve the erections of a healthy 18-year-old.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s a DAO to Do? Gitcoin Backlash Shows Crypto Governance Is More Than a Meme]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152934/whats-dao-do-gitcoin-backlash-shows-crypto-governance-is-more-than-meme"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T18:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another DAO, another controversy. The latest Gitcoin debacle has revived an age-old question: Are DAOs really better than the firm?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 Arbitrum Sees Ongoing ‘Influx’ of New Users After ARB Airdrop: Nansen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152918</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152918/ethereum-layer-2-arbitrum-sees-ongoing-influx-new-users-after-arb-airdrop-nansen"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T13:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum has enjoyed continued growth even after the ARB airdrop, as new users pile into the speedy layer-2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[40% of Workers Will Need New Job Training Due to AI: IBM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152914</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152914/40-of-workers-will-need-new-job-training-due-ai-ibm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T11:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The re-skilling needs are varied, said researchers, but executives think employee roles will be augmented rather than replaced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorand Hits New All-Time Low Amid Market Downturn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152910</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152910/algorand-hits-new-all-time-low-amid-market-downturn"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T10:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The layer-1 blockchain Algorand, already in regulators’ crosshairs, suffered yet another breakdown during the latest market crash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Expected to Approve Ethereum Futures ETFs by October: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152903/sec-expected-to-approve-ethereum-futures-etfs-by-october-report"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T09:36:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With at least a dozen Ethereum futures ETF applications already submitted, this October could be a big one for the markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securitize Acquires $40B Crypto Fund Manager Onramp Invest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152794</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152794/securitize-acquires-40b-crypto-fund-manager-onramp-invest"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T08:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The undisclosed acquisition means that RIAs from Onramp Invest will be able to turn to Securitize's tokenization offering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Associated Press Limits How Journalists Can Use Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152873</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152873/associated-press-limits-how-journalists-use-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T02:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AP releases guidelines on using generative AI, as the storied news agency emphasizes the role of human oversight in journalism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea Will Make Creator Royalties Optional for NFT Trades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152878</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152878/opensea-make-creator-royalties-optional-nft-trades"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T02:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once the largest NFT marketplace by trading volume, OpenSea has revealed plans to stop enforcing creator royalty fees on secondary trades.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeGods Co-Founder Departs Amid Falling NFT Prices and Pushback]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152866</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152866/degods-co-founder-departs-amid-falling-nft-prices"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T23:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As one of DeGod’s co-founders stepped away, a known NFT whale pressured the collection’s floor price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Flash Crash Triggers $800 Million in Liquidations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152872/bitcoin-ethereum-flash-crash-triggers-800-million-liquidations"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T22:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin crashed hard on Thursday afternoon, dipping below $26,000. The rest of the crypto market followed suit—as did the liquidations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX and Genesis Reach $175 Million Settlement After $4 Billion Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152852</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152852/ftx-genesis-reach-175-million-settlement-after-4-billion-demand"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX has reached a settlement agreement with Genesis over claims tied to Alameda, though it must still be approved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Is Testing a New AI Life Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152843</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152843/google-ai-life-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is using the power of AI to help you figure out your life. How soon before the machines replace human wisdom?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Modern Warfare III Revealed—5 Things You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152839</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152839/call-of-duty-modern-warfare-iii-things-you-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Warfare III will offer a new campaign, upgraded maps from 2009's Modern Warfare 2, and the largest Zombies map to date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Suspends Tether Trading in Canada]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152847</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152847/coinbase-suspends-tether-trading-canada"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T19:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is also suspending trading for DAI and RAI, claiming they no longer meet listing standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Returns: Pixelmon's 'Horrible Mistake' Reborn as Base NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152831</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152831/kevin-returns-pixelmons-horrible-mistake-reborn-base-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T18:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blocky, meme-fueling creature is back as a $2 NFT on Base, offering perks to holders while celebrating Pixelmon’s disastrous reveal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Boosts Bitcoin ETF Team as Potential Ruling in SEC Lawsuit Nears]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152818</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152818/grayscale-bitcoin-etf-job-opening-sec-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T17:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale sued the SEC last June after its bid to convert its Bitcoin Trust into an ETF was denied.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China GPT? Tencent to Unleash Homegrown AI as Big Tech Races for Supremacy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152815</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152815/china-tencent-ai-big-tech-chatgpt"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not one to be left out, the Chinese tech giant is coming for AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges Below $28,000 for First Time in Two Months]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152809</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152809/bitcoin-plunges-below-28000-first-time-two-months"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T16:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has dropped to its lowest level since mid-June, likely because of investors fed up of the SEC's delay in approving a spot ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Still Lacks ‘Real Economic Activity’, Says Generative Ventures Partner Lex Sokolin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152793/web3-still-lacks-real-economic-activity-says-generative-ventures-partner-lex-sokolin"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T15:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the next phase of the latest tech convergence will mean keeping users safe in a digital economy dominated by bots, said Sokolin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian Expansion Part of ‘2-Pronged International Strategy’, Says Coinbase Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152792</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152792/canadian-expansion-part-2-pronged-international-strategy-says-coinbase-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike the crackdown the exchange is facing in the U.S., a Coinbase exec said authorities in Canada offer “regulation by engagement.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Philippine National Police Issues Warning Against Play-to-Earn Crypto Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152787</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152787/philippine-national-police-issues-warning-against-play-to-earn-crypto-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T12:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides scams and hacks, Philippines' authorities have also warned of the expensive barrier to entry for some play-to-earn crypto games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$1.7M of Ethereum 'Stuck' in SHIB Layer-2 Network Shibarium]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152773</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152773/1-7m-ethereum-stuck-shib-layer-2-network-shibarium"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated Shibarium layer-2 network has been marred by a key technical issue with its bridge contract.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum Are Now Less Volatile Than Oil: Kaiko Research]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152771</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152771/bitcoin-ethereum-are-now-less-volatile-oil-kaiko-research"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T09:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer doldrums are hitting Bitcoin and Ethereum hard, dampening the assets’ historic volatility to multi-year lows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Dip After Fed Hints at More Rate Hikes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152767</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152767/bitcoin-ethereum-dip-after-fed-hints-more-rate-hikes"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T08:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and stocks saw a decline after the U.S. Federal Reserve reaffirmed its aims to bring inflation down to its 2% target.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Just Bought a Game Studio—But Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=152757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/152757/openai-just-bought-a-game-studio-but-why"/>
        <updated>2023-08-17T02:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ChatGPT creator acquired Global Illumination for an undisclosed amount.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Games Need to Compete with All Games, Says Solana Foundation GM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ud9wTd4s/web3-games-need-to-compete-with-all-games-says-solana-foundation-gm"/>
        <updated>2023-08-09T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about Solana's PlayGG conference and shares his take on crypto gaming and the "play-to-earn" concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Early Blockchain Games Were 'Cash Grabs,' Says Twitch Streamer Alliestrasza]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BA4yE45A/many-early-blockchain-games-were-cash-grabs-says-twitch-streamer-alliestrasza"/>
        <updated>2023-08-07T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I wrote them off," Twitch streamer Alliestrasza said of her initial thoughts on many early blockchain games. She tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how her perspective on Web3 games has evolved over time and now sees blockchain games getting significantly better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['MetalCore' Game Preview: Hands-on With the 'Titanfall' Meets 'Destiny' NFT Mashup]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/tjK6i7lv/metalcore-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-titanfall-meets-destiny-nft-mashup"/>
        <updated>2023-08-04T19:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MetalCore is an upcoming mech shooter developed by Studio 369, and it's being developed on Ethereum scaling network Immutable zkEVM. Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin played through the prologue and tested out the recent Alpha 3 online experience to get a sense of the NFT-infused mashup of Titanfall and Destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Give Projects a Chance,' Says Aurory's Michael Natoli on NFT Game Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nBNKKZdK/give-projects-a-chance-says-aurorys-michael-natoli-on-nft-game-challenges"/>
        <updated>2023-08-02T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory is an NFT-driven game franchise that started life on Solana and is expanding to other chains. Decrypt's Jason Nelson spoke with Aurory Head of Marketing Michael Natoli at Solana's PlayGG event, where Natoli shared his thoughts on the challenges that blockchain games face in reaching players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Is Only Network Ready for Gaming: Solana Foundation's Johnny Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5OvV3ZXn/solana-is-only-network-ready-for-gaming-solana-foundations-johnny-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-31T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation General Manager Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Solana network will tackle the scaling problem that blockchain games pose for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Com2uS Is Going "Full Speed" on Crypto Gaming: Kyu Lee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pYMZRoYy/com2us-is-going-full-speed-on-crypto-gaming-kyu-lee"/>
        <updated>2023-07-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyu Lee is the President of game studio Com2uS USA. In an interview, he shares the studio's approach to Web3 and crypto gaming with Decrypt GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Discord Game with AI and Blockchain: 'Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos' Creative Lead Alex Finden]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mF18GHGo/building-a-discord-game-with-ai-and-blockchain-alchemy-battle-for-ankhos-creative-lead-alex-finden"/>
        <updated>2023-07-26T21:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson interviews Alchemy: Battle for Ankhos Creative Director Alex Finden at the Solana PlayGG event in San Diego, California.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Big Respect Between Ethereum and Cosmos Developer Communities': dYdX Foundation CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XU5MbCGE/big-respect-between-ethereum-and-cosmos-developer-communities-dydx-foundation-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of the dYdX Foundation Charles d'Haussy unpacks the decision behind moving one of the largest decentralized exchange protocol's over to its very own chain built on Cosmos. A key driver, he told Decrypt at this year's EthCC event, was that instead of launching on a rollup or another layer-1, launching a fully customized chain will allow dYdX to fine tune the network for its product's needs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Solution Lido 'Had Perfect Product Market Fit' at Launch, Says DAO's Biz Dev Contributor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/fUHhelhV/ethereum-staking-solution-lido-had-perfect-product-market-fit-at-launch-says-daos-biz-dev-contributor"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marin Tvrdić, a business development contributor to the Lido DAO, sat down with Decrypt during this year's EthCC to break down how the liquid staking protocol has managed such a massive lead, how it plans to keep that lead, and the protocol's new dual-governance tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Going to Stop All the DeFi Hacks? 'Standards,' Says OpenZepplin Security Architect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/aYNuFdAi/whats-going-to-stop-all-the-defi-hacks-standards-says-openzepplin-security-architect"/>
        <updated>2023-07-25T08:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenZeppelin's security solutions architect Michael Lewellen sat down with Decrypt to discuss how the industry can become a little safer for users at this year's EthCC Paris. The key? Introducing security standards across the industry so folks know what an audit actually means and where risks lie, be it bad faith actors or poor implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ev.io' Game Review: Earn Solana While Blasting Enemies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2ZmkuhL2/evio-game-review-earn-solana-while-blasting-enemies"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T22:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ev.io is a web-based first-person shooter that's free to play, but lets NFT holders earn in-game currency that can be redeemed for Solana (SOL). Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin shares his review of the fun throwback to Quake-style blasting, albeit with a modern crypto twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Moving Fast and Breaking Things Isn't the Web3 Ethos': MetaMask Product Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/l1EbLgl3/moving-fast-and-breaking-things-isnt-the-web3-ethos-metamask-product-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T15:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction this, smart wallets that. Discussions at EthCC Paris about improving user experience have pointed at industry leader MetaMask as an example of what not to do. But that may soon change, with a host of updates and optimizations coming to crypto's number one wallet, said its product lead Alex Jupiter. It still may take some time, though, before these changes take effect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Smart Wallets on Starknet 'Was The Winning Combination', Says Argent Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gnBsxw4D/scaling-smart-wallets-on-starknet-was-the-winning-combination-says-argent-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-24T07:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argent co-founder Julien Niset told Decrypt at EthCC Paris that he wants to make crypto wallets disappear. Or at least how they're currently conceived. From clunky seed phrases to a stiff user experience, Argent hopes to make using crypto a little less intimidating and a whole lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>