<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-20T02:27:43.671Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-20T02:27:43.671Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bitcoin Won The Heart Of This Financial Giant]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189644/How-Bitcoin-Won-The-Heart-Of-This-Financial-Giant</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189644/How-Bitcoin-Won-The-Heart-Of-This-Financial-Giant"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T02:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton President and CEO Jenny Johnson joined CNBC’s ‘Squawk Box’ to discuss the firm’s spot Bitcoin Exchange-Traded Fund (ETF) offering in the US. In this interview, Johnson shared the reasons for investing in Bitcoin. Related Reading: Trillion-Dollar Franklin Templeton Shares High...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Debiex faces romance scam allegations, CFTC claims $2.3M in losses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189635/Crypto-exchange-Debiex-faces-romance-scam-allegations-CFTC-claims-23M-in-losses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189635/Crypto-exchange-Debiex-faces-romance-scam-allegations-CFTC-claims-23M-in-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States watchdog labeled Debiex a "bogus digital asset platform," amid filing civil charges against the exchange for the alleged misappropriation of funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Analyst Lists Everything You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f249c045</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etfs-analyst-everything-need-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days since the Bitcoin spot ETFs have gone live, here are the winners and losers in the space, as an analyst broke down.
 
Blackrock’s iShares Bitcoin ETF Is The Biggest Winner So Far
 
Earlier in the month, the much-anticipated Bitcoin spot ETFs finally gained approval from the US SEC. The BTC spot ETFs are financial instruments that allow investors to gain indirect exposure to the cryptocurrency’s price movements.
 
This means that, with the spot ETF, traders don’t need to own the asset itself to gain exposure to it. ETFs trade on traditional exchanges, so they may be a preferable option for traditional investors.
 
 
For some investors, navigating cryptocurrency exchanges and learning how wallets work may be a market entry barrier. Still, with the ETFs, such traders should also be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Pledges No CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189637/Trump-Pledges-No-CBDCs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189637/Trump-Pledges-No-CBDCs"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CBDCs have officially hit the big time as a political issue with presumptive Republican nominee Donald Trump hammering the topic at a New Hampshire campaign event. Some see the fingerprints of former candidate Vivek Ramaswamy. Enjoying this content?SUBSCRIBE to the Podcast:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETFs: Analyst Lists Everything You Need To Know]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189634/Bitcoin-Spot-ETFs-Analyst-Lists-Everything-You-Need-To-Know</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189634/Bitcoin-Spot-ETFs-Analyst-Lists-Everything-You-Need-To-Know"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days since the Bitcoin spot ETFs have gone live, here are the winners and losers in the space, as an analyst broke down. Blackrock’s iShares Bitcoin ETF Is The Biggest Winner So Far Earlier in the month, the much-anticipated Bitcoin spot ETFs finally gained approval from the US SEC. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Faces Potential 38% Drop IF Key Support Level Fails, Analyst Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189619/XRP-Price-Faces-Potential-38-Drop-IF-Key-Support-Level-Fails-Analyst-Warns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189619/XRP-Price-Faces-Potential-38-Drop-IF-Key-Support-Level-Fails-Analyst-Warns"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of the native token of the XRP Ledger, XRP, could soon face a significant sell-off scenario where its price plunges by around 38% to $0.34, if a key support level that is currently holding eventually gives in. That’s according to popular cryptocurrency analyst Ali Martinez, who shared...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S15 E16: Paul Sztorc Talks Bitcoin Scaling, But Can't Say "Drivechains"]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189604/S15-E16-Paul-Sztorc-Talks-Bitcoin-Scaling-But-Cant-Say-Drivechains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189604/S15-E16-Paul-Sztorc-Talks-Bitcoin-Scaling-But-Cant-Say-Drivechains"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Sztorc returns with a twist: he's talking about sidechains, rollups, BitVM, Lightning, and ever other scaling solution... but can't say the words "Drivechain" or "BIP 300". If he breaks the rule, he must send a Lightning transaction and drink vodka.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Rights Bill Introduced in Virginia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f23401b2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cryptocurrency-rights-bill-introduced-in-virginia/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:06:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill that seeks to safeguard the cryptocurrency rights of the citizens has been introduced to the Senate of Virginia. The bill, sponsored by State Sen. Saddam Azlan Salim, would guarantee that citizens can self-custody, transact, mine, and pay with cryptocurrency, also exempting cryptocurrency transactions of less than $200 from paying state capital gains tax.
Virginia State Senator Introduces Cryptocurrency Rights Bill
Saddam Azlan Salim, a state senator in Virginia, has introduced a bill that aims to impede state authorities from blocking its citizens from exerting different cryptocurrency and bitcoin-linked activities. Senate Bill 339 (SB 339), introduced on January 9, establishes that citizens will not require a money-transferring license to operate staking or mining equipment at the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase Doing Nothing After $10,000 Exits Customer’s Account in Sophisticated Scam: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189612/JPMorgan-Chase-Doing-Nothing-After-10000-Exits-Customers-Account-in-Sophisticated-Scam-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189612/JPMorgan-Chase-Doing-Nothing-After-10000-Exits-Customers-Account-in-Sophisticated-Scam-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A JPMorgan Chase customer says the bank has decided not to rectify or even investigate the theft of $10,000 from a primary checking account. Arizona customer Cate Dutler says she mailed a check to a relative in Chicago that never arrived, reports the CBS-affiliated news station WTOC. Instead,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Be SCARED of Bitcoin's 'Volatility'!! #bitcoin #crypto #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189626/Dont-Be-SCARED-of-Bitcoins-Volatility-bitcoin-crypto-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189626/Dont-Be-SCARED-of-Bitcoins-Volatility-bitcoin-crypto-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T01:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is the true stable coin - 1 btc=1btc - it's not that bitcoin si volatile its that paper money is volatile against bitcoin!!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP On The Brink: Urgent Call For Bulls As Analysts Predict Dire Correction Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189570/XRP-On-The-Brink-Urgent-Call-For-Bulls-As-Analysts-Predict-Dire-Correction-Ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189570/XRP-On-The-Brink-Urgent-Call-For-Bulls-As-Analysts-Predict-Dire-Correction-Ahead"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T00:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB) Rapidly Breaks Down, Ethereum (ETH) Loses Traction, While Solana (SOL) Presents Hidden Opportunity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189576/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Rapidly-Breaks-Down-Ethereum-ETH-Loses-Traction-While-Solana-SOL-Presents-Hidden-Opportunity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189576/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Rapidly-Breaks-Down-Ethereum-ETH-Loses-Traction-While-Solana-SOL-Presents-Hidden-Opportunity"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Makes $6.7 Million In 3 Hours With Ethereum Token, Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2316eb5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-trader-6-7-million-ethereum/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T00:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One crypto trader has been making the rounds on social media after making more than $6 million in profit on the Ethereum blockchain. This incredible trade took place in less than a day, translating to an almost 600% gain for the whale trade. So how did they do this?
 
Crypto Trader Makes $6.7 Million In 3 Hours
 
According to Lookonchain, an on-chain data tracker, a single wallet has made almost $7 million off a particularly hyped launch in the last day. The project, Satoshi VM which is a Layer 2 network for the Bitcoin blockchain, launched on Thursday amid much fanfare as it was shilled by some notable influencers in the space.
 
 
One wallet, in particular, took advantage of this hyped launch and paid a premium fee to snipe the launch. As Lookonchain reports, the trader paid a bribe fee …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hottest Altcoin Gem in Crypto DEPIN]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189562/The-Hottest-Altcoin-Gem-in-Crypto-DEPIN</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189562/The-Hottest-Altcoin-Gem-in-Crypto-DEPIN"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T00:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://bit.ly/Free-Decentralized-StorageSerenity Shield and its StrongBox service has everything you want in a decentralized storage app and MORE! More like privacy, multi-signature setups for security, and added nominees to use for financial controls in business or beneficiary access for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Makes $6.7 Million In 3 Hours With Ethereum Token, Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189556/Crypto-Trader-Makes-67-Million-In-3-Hours-With-Ethereum-Token-Heres-How</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189556/Crypto-Trader-Makes-67-Million-In-3-Hours-With-Ethereum-Token-Heres-How"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T00:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One crypto trader has been making the rounds on social media after making more than $6 million in profit on the Ethereum blockchain. This incredible trade took place in less than a day, translating to an almost 600% gain for the whale trade. So how did they do this? Crypto Trader Makes $6.7...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experienced crypto devs pool size grew 16% in 2023: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189550/Experienced-crypto-devs-pool-size-grew-16-in-2023-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189550/Experienced-crypto-devs-pool-size-grew-16-in-2023-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost 2,000 developers (devs) completed more than one year deploying blockchain smart contracts in 2023, with a yearly growth of 16%, according to the 2023 Crypto Developer Report published by Electric Capital on Jan. 17. The report highlights this group of developers as experienced, which is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s New Study Reveals Emerging Synergy Between AI and Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f233e9c8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/grayscales-new-study-reveals-emerging-synergy-between-ai-and-cryptocurrency/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of artificial intelligence (AI) and cryptocurrency is heralding a new era of technological advancement, as highlighted in a recent Grayscale Investments report by Will Ogden Moore. Grayscale’s latest report says this synergy, marked by the impressive performance of AI-related crypto assets, is expanding the scope of blockchain applications beyond traditional payment systems. 
 
Grayscale Research Report Illuminates the Collaborative Future of AI and Cryptocurrency
 
Grayscale Investments’ research report emphasizes the potential of this intersection to address future AI-related societal challenges, including concerns over data privacy and the centralization of power. According to the Grayscale researcher, Will Ogden Moore, AI-adjacent cryptocurrencies have shown significant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Faces Price Dip Amidst Criticism from JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189544/Bitcoin-Faces-Price-Dip-Amidst-Criticism-from-JPMorgan-CEO-Jamie-Dimon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189544/Bitcoin-Faces-Price-Dip-Amidst-Criticism-from-JPMorgan-CEO-Jamie-Dimon"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$ADA: Analyst Forecasts 1,300% Price Rise for Cardano, Citing Historical Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189541/ADA-Analyst-Forecasts-1300-Price-Rise-for-Cardano-Citing-Historical-Pattern</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189541/ADA-Analyst-Forecasts-1300-Price-Rise-for-Cardano-Citing-Historical-Pattern"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Church Allegedly Issued Crypto Token Backed by Nothing But God's Word]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213592</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213592/church-allegedly-issued-crypto-token-backed-nothing-but-gods-word"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Colorado couple had their assets frozen by a state judge after making millions on a cryptocurrency they say they created at God’s command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Church Allegedly Issued Crypto Token Backed by Nothing But God's Word]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189527/Church-Allegedly-Issued-Crypto-Token-Backed-by-Nothing-But-Gods-Word</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189527/Church-Allegedly-Issued-Crypto-Token-Backed-by-Nothing-But-Gods-Word"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Colorado couple had their assets frozen by a state judge after making millions on a cryptocurrency they say they created at God’s command.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton CEO says ETF has shown ‘demand’ for Bitcoin is ‘everywhere’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189504/Franklin-Templeton-CEO-says-ETF-has-shown-demand-for-Bitcoin-is-everywhere</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189504/Franklin-Templeton-CEO-says-ETF-has-shown-demand-for-Bitcoin-is-everywhere"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s Legal Defense Against US Securities Regulator Pushed Back to Next Week Due to Snow: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189507/Binances-Legal-Defense-Against-US-Securities-Regulator-Pushed-Back-to-Next-Week-Due-to-Snow-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189507/Binances-Legal-Defense-Against-US-Securities-Regulator-Pushed-Back-to-Next-Week-Due-to-Snow-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Accumulation: USDT Issuer Tether Goes On Massive 8,888 BTC Buying Spree]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189494/Bitcoin-Accumulation-USDT-Issuer-Tether-Goes-On-Massive-8888-BTC-Buying-Spree</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189494/Bitcoin-Accumulation-USDT-Issuer-Tether-Goes-On-Massive-8888-BTC-Buying-Spree"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T23:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an encouraging development for the crypto space, Tether, the issuer of the world’s largest stablecoin USDT, has doubled down on its Bitcoin investment momentum by acquiring a staggering 8,888 BTC, further diversifying its portfolio.  Tether Increases Its Bitcoin Holdings Tether has recently...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck to Liquidate Bitcoin Strategy ETF as Focus Shifts to Spot Bitcoin Investment Vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189497/VanEck-to-Liquidate-Bitcoin-Strategy-ETF-as-Focus-Shifts-to-Spot-Bitcoin-Investment-Vehicles</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19189497/VanEck-to-Liquidate-Bitcoin-Strategy-ETF-as-Focus-Shifts-to-Spot-Bitcoin-Investment-Vehicles"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T22:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It True That Cardano Needs A “USD-Backed Stablecoin” Like USDT To Rally?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f23997cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-usd-backed-stablecoin-like-usdt-to-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T22:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a post on X, analyst Cardano Yoda believes that a USD-pegged stablecoin is crucial for ADA’s future success, suggesting that its integration could trigger a bull run sometime in 2025.
 
A stablecoin, a token that’s “stable” since its price is pegged to a fiat currency like the USD or Euro, will ignite activity, driving decentralized finance (DeFi) and even non-fungible token (NFT) activities even higher. With a popular stablecoin like USDT or USDC deployed on the proof-of-stake blockchain, the number of users interacting with Cardano dapps will likely spike, catalyzing demand since ADA is used for paying fees.
 
Stablecoins, Input Endorsers, And Hydra Might Prop Up Cardano In The Long-Term
 
The presence of a high market cap stablecoin can facilitate seamless value transfers and reduce …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times Still Doesn’t Get Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f23b76a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/01/19/the-new-york-times-still-doesnt-get-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T22:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Response to the latest article misunderstanding bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Definition at the Core of Coinbase v SEC First Scuffle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f224da5b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/security-definition-at-the-core-of-coinbase-v-sec-first-scuffle/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T22:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, a U.S based cryptocurrency exchange, and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) had their first scuffle as New York’s Judge Katherine Polk Failla weighted in on a motion to dismiss the case in which the regulator alleges the exchange was involved in facilitating the trade of unregistered securities. Judge Failla will decide on the subject in the coming weeks.
Coinbase and SEC Face at Court
What might become the most significant case to define the classification of cryptocurrencies as securities finished its first chapter without a clear winner. This Wednesday, Coinbase and the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) met for the first time in court to discuss if the case should be thrown based on the arguments presented by the exchange in a document filed in Augus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Is Sending Bitcoin to Coinbase in $500 Million Clips—Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213564/grayscale-sending-bitcoin-coinbase-500-million-why"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cash continues to flow out from Grayscale's Bitcoin ETF, while other funds see gains. Here's what's going on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ubisoft, Xbox, and Blizzard Are Using AI to Make Next-Generation Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=147436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/147436/ai-game-development-ubisoft-roblox-blizzard"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Final Fantasy maker Square Enix says it used AI tools for its big new game, plus Ubisoft is tapping Nvidia's gaming tech for NPCs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Coinbase Win Dismissal of SEC Lawsuit? Legal Experts Weigh In]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213566</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213566/will-coinbase-win-dismissal-sec-lawsuit-legal-experts-weigh-in"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawyers were impressed by Coinbase's oral arguments, and say full dismissal of the SEC's suit is a realistic possibility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil Stock Exchange to Open After Hours Trading, Give Bitcoin a Boost]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213568</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213568/brazil-stock-exchange-to-open-after-hours-trading-give-bitcoin-a-boost"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin was the only asset besides the country’s own Ibovespa index approved for late night trading sessions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Secures Another Listing On Major Indian Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f22303b3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-listing-crypto-exchange/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular dog-themed meme coin Dogecoin, has recently achieved a new milestone by getting officially listed on one of India’s top cryptocurrency exchanges.
 
New Dogecoin Listing
 
On Thursday, January 18, Indian cryptocurrency exchange Flitpay announced Dogecoin as the new addition to its extensive portfolio of cryptocurrencies. The news was communicated via the crypto exchange’s official X (formerly Twitter) account.
 
According to Flitpay, users can now make deposits and withdrawals using Dogecoin’s native DOGE token on its platform. This move underscores the growing acceptance and recognition of Dogecoin in the cryptocurrency market. 
 
 
Additionally, the crypto exchange has introduced an exclusive incentive for new users aiming to trade and utilize Dogecoin for daily transactions. As h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Eclipse Silver, Claiming Second Spot Behind Gold in US ETF Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f22edfee</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-etfs-eclipse-silver-claiming-second-spot-behind-gold-in-u-s-etf-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin ETFs, after a phenomenal market debut, have claimed the second-largest commodity position in the U.S. ETF market, growing larger than silver and trailing only behind gold, in a clear sign of the the mainstream appetite for the digital asset.
 
Bitcoin ETFs Outshine Silver, Secure Second Place in U.S. ETF Commodities
 
Spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) have overtaken silver to become the second-largest commodity in the U.S. ETF market, trailing only gold.
 
The recent approval of spot bitcoin ETFs by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission has catalyzed this shift. Bitcoin ETFs, including the newly converted Grayscale Bitcoin Trust ETF (GBTC), command nearly $28 billion in assets under management (AUM). This figure starkly contrasts with the $11 billion AUM of silve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Gaming airdrops are heating up, with Nifty Island, Nyan Heroes, and Apeiron revealing plans after the buzzy XAI token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Gift Cards Are Like Crypto – and Not in a Good Way]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f22901c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/01/19/gaming-gift-cards-are-like-crypto-and-not-in-a-good-way/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In-game tokens, like V-Bucks on Fortnite, face UX problems like many Web3 platforms. Is there a role an open, shared “trust layer” for gaming payments?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Galen Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Voices Awe Over Bitcoin – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f22a89a4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/elon-musk-voices-awe-over-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a notable exchange on the social media platform X (formerly Twitter), Tesla and SpaceX CEO Elon Musk voiced his astonishment about Bitcoin in reaction to a tweet from Cathie Wood, CEO of Ark Invest. Wood’s tweet, which resonated with Musk, shed light on the extraordinary statistics characterizing the Bitcoin network, eliciting a simple yet profound response from Musk: “Wow.”
 
Wood’s message on X emphasized the unmatched magnitude of the Bitcoin network, stating, “Bitcoin is backed by the largest computer network in the world, a network orders of magnitude larger than the combined size of the clouds that Amazon, Google, and Microsoft have built over the last 15-20 years.”
 
 
Wow
 
— Elon Musk (@elonmusk) January 19, 2024
 

 
Bitcoin Is 500x More Powerful Than Supercomputers
 
This bol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX's Bankruptcy Crisis Deepens: Appeals Court Orders Appointment of Independent Examiner]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2166447</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftxs-bankruptcy-crisis-deepens-appeals-court-orders-appointment-of-independent-examiner/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US federal appeals court has ordered the  
appointment of an independent bankruptcy examiner to investigate the collapse  
of FTX, the cryptocurrency exchange once headed by the now-convicted Sam  
Bankman-Fried. 
This decision, reversing a prior ruling, followed  
the alleged misappropriation of a staggering $10 billion in customer assets,  
bringing to light a case with profound implications for FTX's global investors  
and the volatile cryptocurrency industry.
According to a report by Reuters, the 3rd US Circuit  
Court of Appeals in Philadelphia justified this decision, mentioning that the  
appointment of an independent examiner is mandatory under the US Bankruptcy Code. This step was attributed to the significant scale of  
FTX's case, alongside allegations of misappropriation of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘You Can See the Demand Out There for Bitcoin’: Franklin Templeton CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213537/you-can-see-the-demand-out-there-for-bitcoin-franklin-templeton-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global asset manager’s Bitcoin ETF is the latest in blockchain-related investment opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin Gaming Wallet Now Supports Ethereum, Polygon, and BNB Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213540/ronin-gaming-wallet-now-supports-ethereum-polygon-bnb-chain"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin’s mobile wallet for iOS and Android will see a new security feature as well as a refreshed design that lets users view more data about their crypto and NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Eyes Broad Crypto Expansion Beyond Bitcoin, Foresees More ETP Filings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2114c1c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/franklin-templeton-eyes-broad-crypto-expansion-beyond-bitcoin-foresees-more-etp-filings/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton’s Head of Digital Assets, Sandy Kaul, foresees an increase in filings following the recent approval of 11 new spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds. Kaul highlighted that the firm, managing $1.5 trillion in assets, recognizes the “potential of this whole crypto domain.”
 
Franklin Templeton Sets Sights on Expanding Crypto Horizons
 

 
On social media this past week, the investment management giant Franklin Templeton discussed ethereum (ETH) and solana (SOL) in a series of tweets about crypto and blockchain technology. The company just launched its spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) and presently the fund commands 1,160 BTC worth around $47 million. In an interview with Bloomberg’s Kailey Leinz and Sonali Basak, the asset manager’s digital assets sector chief Sandy Kau…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Vs. SEC: Crypto Exchange Heads To Court Seeking Lawsuit Dismissal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f211efd7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-vs-sec-crypto-exchange-heads-to-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T19:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant legal showdown, Binance, the world’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, is set to go head-to-head with the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in a Washington courtroom. 
 
The hearing, scheduled for Friday, marks the second high-profile legal battle this week involving the SEC and a top crypto exchange, following a similar case against Coinbase.
 
Binance Challenges SEC Lawsuit
 
According to a Reuters report, Binance intends to request a federal judge to dismiss the lawsuit filed by the SEC in June. 
 
The regulatory body accused Binance, its former CEO Changpeng Zhao (CZ), and the operator of Binance.US of various infractions, including “artificially inflating” trading volumes, diverting customer funds, failure to restrict US customers, and misleading investors ab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Hundreds of developers admit in a major industry survey that they're working on Nintendo Switch 2 games. Here's everything we know so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Expands Airdrop Rewards to Solana, Polygon, and Avalanche Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213528/saga-expands-airdrop-rewards-solana-polygon-avalanche-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming gaming network Saga is bringing its play-to-airdrop push to games like Parallel, Shrapnel, and Gas Hero on other chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bit.Store Unveils Comprehensive B2B Offerings, Empowering Crypto Projects with Custom Solutions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f219349c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bit-store-unveils-comprehensive-b2b-offerings-empowering-crypto-projects-with-custom-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:05:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. [VILNIUS, Lithuania, Jan. 19, 2024] BitStore is making significant strides in the cryptocurrency card sector, offering a suite of services that blend traditional financial ease with the cutting-edge world of digital currencies tailor made for projects or brands. Our card services support multiple card BINs from different countries, including the US and Hong Kong, catering to a global audience. What sets us apart is our commitment to user convenience, underscored by flexible registration processes for our virtual Visa and MasterCard offerings. This approach ensures a swift, minimal-information-required setup, ideal for users who value speed and privacy.
 
In line with our vision to continually enhance user experience, we’re excited to announce the imminent launch of the $STOR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Worry About Bitcoin: Glassnode Predicts When The Bull Market Will Begin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f219deaf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bull-market-glassnode/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T18:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several crypto analysts have weighed in on when the next bull run is likely to begin. A majority of them pinpointed the Bitcoin Halving as what will trigger this next cycle. With this in mind, crypto analytics firm Glassnode has provided insights as to when to expect the next bull market. 
 
Bitcoin Halving Now 100 Days Away
 
In a post on their X (formerly Twitter) platform, Glassnode estimated that the Halving event is now 100 days away based on their calculation using the current average block interval. They highlighted how the fourth halving is pre-determined to occur at block height 840,000. However, the exact date cannot be ascertained due to the “natural variability and probabilistic nature of mining blocks.”
 
 
The reason why these analysts predict that the Bitcoin Halving could m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Avalanche Tumble as Bitcoin Slides Towards $40,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213511</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213511/solana-avalanche-tumble-bitcoin-slides-towards-40000"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T17:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is down bad—but major altcoins like Solana, Avalanche, and Cardano are also experiencing a brutal selloff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-President Trump Launches Limited Edition Cards on Bitcoin Blockchain via Ordinal Technology]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f205edaa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ex-president-trump-launches-limited-edition-cards-on-bitcoin-blockchain-via-ordinal-technology/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T17:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ex-45th President of the United States has been engaged in the sale of digital trading cards for a considerable period. On Thursday, the official account for the trading card enterprise announced the launch of Trump cards that are crafted using the Bitcoin blockchain’s Ordinal inscription technology. The creators of this venture have stated that a mere 200 units of the Trump Digital Trading Cards Mugshot Edition Bitcoin Ordinals “will ever exist in the world.”
 
Trump Reveals Exclusive Bitcoin Ordinal Inscribed NFT Trading Cards
 
Trump’s collectible non-fungible token (NFT) trading cards are set to debut on Bitcoin. This news comes from the official X account, known as ‘Collect Trump Cards,’ which shared this information on Thursday afternoon. “Trump Digital Trading Cards on Bitcoin O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US CEO Slams SEC's Approach to Digital Asset Regulation in Op-Ed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f2029bda</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binanceus-ceo-slams-secs-approach-to-digital-asset-regulation-in-op-ed/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Norman Reed, Interim CEO of Binance.US, has launched a  
scathing critique of the Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) strategy  
for regulating digital assets, characterizing it as fundamentally flawed and  
harmful to the US economy. Reed, a former SEC employee, has articulated his  
concerns in a strongly worded op-ed for Fortune, pointing out the agency's  
departure from core principles such as transparency, fairness, and stable  
regulation in its management of the rapidly evolving digital asset landscape.
SEC's Approach: A Regulatory Overreach According to  
Binance.US CEO
In his editorial, Reed emphasizes the crucial role of  
regulatory frameworks in maintaining a healthy financial ecosystem and  
protecting the interests of investors. Drawing on his background as a former  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins Record $4 Billion Inflows: What It Means For Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f20df229</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/stablecoins-record-4-billion-inflows-means-bitcoin/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows stablecoins have recorded more than $4 billion in inflows in the past month. Here’s why this could be relevant for Bitcoin.
 
Stablecoin Market Cap Has Enjoyed Some Notable Growth Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the aggregate supply of stablecoins has been going through an expansion since October of last year.
 
The relevant indicator here is the “aggregated market cap net position change,” which keeps track of the monthly changes happening in the total stablecoin supply (or market cap, as they are equivalent in the case of these assets tied to the USD).
 
 
When the value of this metric is positive, it means that the supply of the stables has gone up during the last 30 days. On the other hand, negative values imply a decline has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will A Spot Bitcoin ETF Launch In Hong Kong In The First Quarter?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74f20ae110</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/will-a-spot-bitcoin-etf-launch-in-hong-kong-in-the-first-quarter/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This month’s spot Bitcoin ETF (Exchange Traded Fund) approval by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) marked a significant and historic moment for BTC and crypto adoption.
 
The event opened new investment possibilities for firms and traditional investors, leading several asset managers worldwide to assess their possibilities for launching Bitcoin ETFs in their specific regulatory landscapes.
 
 
 
 
Hong Kong Firm Aims For Spot Bitcoin ETF Approval
 
Following the approval of these investment products in the US, Hong Kong’s Securities and Futures Commission (SFC) published guidelines for spot crypto fund approvals for the first time, potentially advancing their efforts to develop a “digital-asset hub” more accessible.
 
Since the release of the SFC’s circular in December 2023, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Dips Into Bitcoin Ordinals as His NFT Ambitions Fizzle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213478</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213478/trump-is-doing-bitcoin-ordinals-as-he-tries-to-revive-flailing-nft-drop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 presidential hopeful’s latest project involves 200 NFTs inscribed on the Bitcoin blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Punts Fidelty Spot Ethereum ETF Decision to March]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213480/sec-punts-fidelty-spot-ethereum-etf-decision-to-march"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T11:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has stated it needs "sufficient time to consider the proposed rule change and the issues raised therein."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crime Down 29% in 2023: Chainalysis Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213470/crypto-crime-down-29-percent-in-2023-chainalysis-report"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T01:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX tipped the scales in the amount of illicit cryptocurrency reported after the conviction of Sam Bankman-Fried.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Nifty Island' Is Already Better Than Most NFT Sandbox Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213423</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213423/nifty-island-already-better-most-nft-sandbox-games"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: Our first hands-on playtest of Nifty Island’s public beta was surprisingly addicting, allowing tons of room for imagination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Microwaved a Solana Saga Phone—Now Degens Are Buying Meme NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213457</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213457/someone-microwaved-solana-saga-phone-now-degens-buying-meme-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T23:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s one less Solana Saga in the world after a viral experiment... but 3,333 more NFTs commemorating it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Coming for Gold's Global Market, Says Cathie Wood]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213442/bitcoin-is-coming-for-golds-global-market-says-cathie-wood"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T22:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ARK Invest CEO says financial investors should go with crypto over the precious metal, and tech investors should stick with software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenSea Exec Argues NFT Insider Trading Conviction Violated Law]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213440</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213440/former-opensea-exec-argues-nft-insider-trading-conviction-violated-law"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T22:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nathaniel Chastain was convicted last year for profiting off of information he was privy to as an executive at NFT marketplace OpenSea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges 12% in 7 Days as BlackRock Collects $1.1 Billion From ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213422</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213422/bitcoin-price-down-blackrock-1-billion-etf"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T21:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock's Bitcoin ETF has broken records—but BTC's price is down bad since the historic launch of the long-awaited investment vehicles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Crypto Unicorns’ Game Ditching Polygon for Arbitrum’s Xai Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213416</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213416/crypto-unicorns-game-ditching-polygon-arbitrum-xai-network"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following last week’s XAI token airdrop, Arbitrum gaming network Xai will add Crypto Unicorns and related NFT games from Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Half of Game Devs Use AI, But Creatives Are Wary: Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213411</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213411/half-game-developers-use-ai-designers-worried-jobs"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T20:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[84% of developers raise ethical concerns, with AAA studios more likely to have AI policies, according to Game Developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Vision Pro Preorders Begin Friday—What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213404/apple-vision-pro-preorders-begin-friday-what-need-know"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T19:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got $3,499 burning a hole in your pocket? The Apple Vision Pro is nearly here, and the first wave of orders are set to begin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Snaps Up More Bitcoin, Brings Holdings to $2.8 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213393</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213393/tether-buys-more-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T18:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stablecoin issuer continues to load up on Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Exchange dYdX Dethrones Ethereum's Uniswap as Token Outpaces the Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213380</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213380/defi-exchange-dydx-dethrones-ethereums-uniswap-as-token-outpaces-the-market"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized cryptocurrency exchange dYdX is hotter than ever, beating Uniswap v3 Ethereum in volume—and the charts back the hype.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PIXEL Token Launch 'Very Close' as Pixels Game Sets Play-to-Airdrop End]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213348</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213348/pixel-token-launch-very-close-pixels-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T16:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Ronin farming and social game Pixels is nearing its token launch as the current airdrop campaign winds down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Provisionally Agrees Tougher AML Rules for Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213327/eu-provisionally-agrees-tougher-aml-rules-for-crypto-firms"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T13:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the new rules, crypto firms in the European Union would need to conduct due diligence checks on transactions over €1,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Celestia (TIA)? The Coin Created by a CIA Hacker Spikes 800%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213312</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213312/what-is-celestia-tia-the-coin-created-by-a-cia-hacker-spiked-800-in-3-months"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A modular blockchain with a notorious founder is the new obsession among crypto enthusiasts, its token value up 40% since December 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Vows to 'Never Allow' U.S. CBDC if Reelected]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213324/trump-vows-to-never-allow-u-s-cbdc-if-reelected"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T10:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a campaign speech in New Hampshire, the former U.S. President called central bank digital currencies "government tyranny."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laser-Eyed Franklin Templeton Sets Sights on Ethereum, Solana After Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213281/franklin-templeton-layer-one-ethereum-solana-after-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T03:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The investment giant highlighted Solana's vision and Ethereum's ecosystem in its bullish Twitter thread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Apeiron’ God Game Begins Airdrop Rewards on Ethereum Scaler Ronin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213295/apeiron-god-game-begins-airdrop-rewards-ethereum-scaler-ronin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:34:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin’s latest big game has launched a play-to-airdrop campaign, letting users earn while playing and engaging online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Nifty Island' NFT Game Launches Open Beta With Airdrop Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213275</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213275/nifty-island-nft-game-launches-open-beta-airdrop-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nifty Island, the create-an-island game with NFTs, is offering future token perks to active players who mint NFTs and create experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Case Judge Asks If SEC Is ‘Sweeping Too Broadly’ as She Weighs Dismissal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213288</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213288/coinbase-case-judge-asks-if-sec-is-sweeping-too-broadly-as-she-weighs-dismissal"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T23:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. District Judge Katherine Polk Failla will decide whether to dismiss the SEC’s lawsuit against the crypto exchange for alleged securities violations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hash Rate Tumbles as Halving Approaches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213274/bitcoin-hash-rate-tumbles-halving-approaches"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T23:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners in Texas are curtailing power to ensure the stability of the state’s power grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Dogwifhat Spikes 257% as SOL Reclaims $100]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213268/solana-meme-coin-dogwifhat-spikes-257-sol-reclaims-100"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T21:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONK isn’t the hottest Solana meme coin at the moment: WIF has more than doubled in price this week alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft CEO: Rabbit R1 AI Gadget Was ‘Most Impressive’ Demo Since Steve Jobs’ iPhone Unveiling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213244</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213244/microsoft-ceo-rabbit-r1-ai-gadget-was-most-impressive-demo-since-steve-jobs-iphone-unveiling"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T20:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satya Nadella sees a future where AI agents acting on our behalf are at the core of our interactions with computers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$2 Billion in 'Dormant' Bitcoin Just Moved—Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=213243</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/213243/2-billion-dormant-bitcoin-moved-why"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T20:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 50,000 BTC just moved after sitting still for years. One lucky whale? Unlikely, analysts say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you the one being farmed? w/ Frisson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Frisson from Tallyx.xyz

They reflect on:
- building in the bear market
- the points system meta
- will zoomers care about decentralization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Look Touch Own': OONA Discusses Her Performance Art Exhibition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptual artist OONA joins moderator Raina Marie to discuss "Look Touch Own," her performance art exhibition featuring her own former breast implants, which have been tokenized. This conversation was recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genius Marketing by Genius Marketers: How Crypto Builders Can Reach the Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio founder Farokh Sarmad moderates a conversation between 9dcc founder and CEO Gmoney and Serotonin founder and CEO Amanda Cassatt about the challenges and opportunities in Web3 marketing and how they're navigating the ever-evolving space. Recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: This Is the 'Calm Before the Storm', Says ETF Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VOX04ytt/bitcoin-etf-this-is-the-calm-before-the-storm-says-etf-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T20:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bloomberg Senior ETF Analyst Eric Balchunas joins Farokh Sarmad, Michael Anderson, and Ovie Faruq on the FOMO Hour to share the latest intel on the looming approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF, what might happen when the very different worlds of TradFi and crypto collide, and his insights on “Genslish,” the unique and strategic language of SEC chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bryan Johnson Explains His Quest for Immortality and Why He Started with the Penis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tAwP55g9/bryan-johnson-explains-his-quest-for-immortality-and-why-he-started-with-the-penis"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire biohacker Bryan Johnson shared with Decrypt's Jason Nelson why he began his longevity quest and how technology has shaped the endeavor. Johnson also discusses some of his controversial experiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>