<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-11T02:49:31.789Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-11T02:49:31.789Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Nations to Expand Use of National Currencies Through New Financial Platform]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443f15257</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-nations-to-expand-use-of-national-currencies-through-new-financial-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T02:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian presidential aide Yury Ushakov announced new BRICS initiatives to increase the use of national currencies in trade, backed by financial infrastructure developments like a BRICS-wide platform and special clearing systems. This move aims to simplify transactions between member nations and reduce trade costs. Meanwhile, Russian Deputy Foreign Minister Sergey Ryabkov highlighted ongoing Western efforts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heavy Sell-Off Pushes Bitcoin to $58.8K, Cautious Buying Fuels Modest Recovery]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443f15255</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/heavy-sell-off-pushes-bitcoin-to-58-8k-cautious-buying-fuels-modest-recovery/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T02:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of bitcoin dipped to $58,867 on Thursday, around 2 p.m. Eastern Time, but by 8:50 p.m. it had climbed back above $60,000. The initial drop reflected heavy selling pressure, but the later rebound—though slow—suggests a potential recovery might be on the horizon. Bitcoin Reclaims $60K After Market Dips: Traders Face $191M in Losses […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitnomial SEC Lawsuit Causes Disagreement Among Agencies]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992231/Bitnomial-SEC-Lawsuit-Causes-Disagreement-Among-Agencies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992231/Bitnomial-SEC-Lawsuit-Causes-Disagreement-Among-Agencies"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T02:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitnomial SEC lawsuit follows the agency's recent appeal in the Ripple case and is the second legal challenge this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI shows signs of exhaustion after 98% gain – Fall ahead?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992228/SUI-shows-signs-of-exhaustion-after-98-gain-Fall-ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992228/SUI-shows-signs-of-exhaustion-after-98-gain-Fall-ahead"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T02:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If buying activity remains scanty, SUI will likely drop to test support at $1.70.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cumberland DRW Lawsuit Initiated by SEC for Securities Law Violations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992188/Cumberland-DRW-Lawsuit-Initiated-by-SEC-for-Securities-Law-Violations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992188/Cumberland-DRW-Lawsuit-Initiated-by-SEC-for-Securities-Law-Violations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T02:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Cumberland DRW lawsuit, the SEC seeks to recover profits from these trades and impose penalties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Holds Steady Despite SEC's Case Against Market Maker Cumberland DRW]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285754/bitcoin-price-holds-steady-despite-secs-case-against-market-maker-cumberland-drw"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, the SEC charged Cumberland DRW with various securities allegations, though bellwether Bitcoin has so far shrugged it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Holds Steady Despite SEC's Case Against Market Maker Cumberland DRW]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992181/Bitcoin-Price-Holds-Steady-Despite-SECs-Case-Against-Market-Maker-Cumberland-DRW</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992181/Bitcoin-Price-Holds-Steady-Despite-SECs-Case-Against-Market-Maker-Cumberland-DRW"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, the SEC charged Cumberland DRW with various securities allegations, though bellwether Bitcoin has so far shrugged it off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Widens Lead Over Harris In Betting Odds On Prediction Markets —Sets A New High On Crypto-Based Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992164/Trump-Widens-Lead-Over-Harris-In-Betting-Odds-On-Prediction-Markets-Sets-A-New-High-On-Crypto-Based-Polymarket</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992164/Trump-Widens-Lead-Over-Harris-In-Betting-Odds-On-Prediction-Markets-Sets-A-New-High-On-Crypto-Based-Polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump set an all-time high in presidential betting odds against Vice President Kamala Harris on Polymarket. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Shatters All-Time Hashrate Record at 698 EH/s as Miners Defy Market Challenges – Mining Bitcoin News]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992138/Bitcoin-Shatters-All-Time-Hashrate-Record-at-698-EHs-as-Miners-Defy-Market-Challenges-Mining-Bitcoin-News</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992138/Bitcoin-Shatters-All-Time-Hashrate-Record-at-698-EHs-as-Miners-Defy-Market-Challenges-Mining-Bitcoin-News"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by   /u/ShivayBodana [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Seeks Crypto Fraud Victims in Major Market Manipulation Case]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443fe91a4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fbi-seeks-crypto-fraud-victims-in-major-market-manipulation-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) is urging potential victims of cryptocurrency fraud to come forward as it investigates market manipulation involving several cryptocurrency companies. Accusations include “wash-trading” and artificially inflating trading volumes to deceive investors. FBI Seeks Victims in Major Cryptocurrency Fraud Investigation The Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)’s Boston Division is calling on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Millionaire Picks the Best Altcoins To Get Rich, RCOF Leads the Pack With Upcoming 6000% Run In 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443f80ee1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-millionaire-picks-the-best-altcoins-to-get-rich-rcof-leads-the-pack-with-upcoming-6000-run-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who became insanely wealthy off of tokens like Dogecoin (DOGE) are now seen bidding on the RCO Finance (RCOF) presale. Moves like this show that many seasoned crypto investors believe that RCOF is one of the best altcoins for getting rich in 2025.
 
Crypto experts and analysts support this sentiment and add that RCO Finance can revolutionize the crypto space, ushering in utility like we’ve never seen before. 
 
Thus, not only does RCOF have the ability to generate massive ROI, but it also has everything to become a powerful long-term player in the market. This only adds further to its bullish thesis and to the list of reasons why experts deem this project one of the best altcoins to get rich off of in 2025.
 
Are Dogecoin Investors Losing Confidence? 
Dogecoin is one of the most pop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US DoJ Getting Rid Of This Meme Coin Market Maker Boosts Trading Confidence]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443f80ed8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-doj-meme-coin-market-maker-trading-confidence/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin industry is undoubtedly one of the fastest-growing sub-sectors in crypto. As of October 10, CoinMarketCap data shows that the total market cap of all meme coins exceeds $47 billion. Dogecoin, Shiba Inu, and Pepe top the list, commanding billions and, in some instances, hundreds of millions.
 
United States DoJ Cracks Down On Meme Coin Wash Traders And GoBit
 
Bullish as the industry might be, it is rife with pump-and-dump schemes and even rug pulls. Traders have lost millions through rug pulls. There are hundreds of millions more lost through pump-and-dump schemes.
 
 
On October 9, the United States Department of Justice (DoJ) announced the arrest and prosecution of four crypto firms and 14 individuals. Detectives also recovered over $25 million of diverse crypto assets. 
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Launches Bank-Grade Crypto Custody Solution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443f80ed2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-bank-grade-crypto-custody-solution/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple has announced a major upgrade to its Ripple Custody service, aiming to deliver bank-grade crypto custody solutions to fintech firms and crypto businesses. The enhancements include integration with compliance tools, expanded hardware security module (HSM) options, support for tokenizing real-world assets on the XRP Ledger (XRPL), pre-configured policy frameworks, and an improved user interface, according to the official press release.
 
“Ripple’s custody technology provides a unified platform for securing and managing digital assets, built with the security and compliance standards that global banks and financial institutions rely on. With these new features, Ripple Custody is expanding its capabilities to better serve high-growth crypto and fintech businesses with secure and scalabl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETFSwap (ETFS) Is The Leading Contender To Beat Out Shiba Inu And XRP Price For 88x Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443f80ecf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/etfswap-etfs-is-the-leading-contender-to-beat-out-shiba-inu-and-xrp-price-for-88x-gains/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As investors seek the next big opportunity in the cryptocurrency space, ETFSwap (ETFS) is a strong challenger that could outperform Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Ripple (XRP) owing to its innovative approach and robust features.
 
ETFSwap (ETFS): The Next Big Opportunity For 88x Gains In The Cryptocurrency Market 
ETFSwap (ETFS) is currently in Stage 3 of its presale, capturing the interest of savvy investors eager for high returns. This phase allows early adopters to secure their positions before the anticipated price surge. ETFSwap (ETFS) offers unique market-making and perpetual trading services that let users trade assets continuously, ensuring liquidity and flexibility. With the ability to take positions up to 50x, traders can maximize their potential profits without the constraints typical of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC settles with trading firm over $4M ‘AI-washing’ scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992113/SEC-settles-with-trading-firm-over-4M-AI-washing-scheme</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992113/SEC-settles-with-trading-firm-over-4M-AI-washing-scheme"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC alleged that Rimar LLC’s executives overstated the AI capabilites of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) Price Soars Over 10% Following Unichain Announcement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992157/Uniswap-UNI-Price-Soars-Over-10-Following-Unichain-Announcement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992157/Uniswap-UNI-Price-Soars-Over-10-Following-Unichain-Announcement"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) price raised more than 10% after Uniswap Labs announced the launch of its own Layer-2, Unichain. This surge in price has driven the Relative Strength Index (RSI) to overbought levels, suggesting strong buying momentum. The rapid increase has brought caution to the market, as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple files for a cross-appeal to the U.S. Court of Appeals in its U.S. SEC vs. Ripple lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992080/Ripple-files-for-a-cross-appeal-to-the-US-Court-of-Appeals-in-its-US-SEC-vs-Ripple-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992080/Ripple-files-for-a-cross-appeal-to-the-US-Court-of-Appeals-in-its-US-SEC-vs-Ripple-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple announced on October 10 that it would file a cross-appeal with the U.S. Court of Appeals for the U.S. SEC vs. Ripple lawsuit. The decision came after the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission filed a notice for appeal to Judge Torres’s final judgment in August of this year. Ripple filed...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whales Redistribute 30,000 BTC Worth $1.8 Billion in Major Sell-Off]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992082/Bitcoin-Whales-Redistribute-30000-BTC-Worth-18-Billion-in-Major-Sell-Off</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992082/Bitcoin-Whales-Redistribute-30000-BTC-Worth-18-Billion-in-Major-Sell-Off"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past three days large Bitcoin holders, colloquially referred to as whales, have “sold or redistributed” around 30,000 BTC, the equivalent to more than $1.8 billion worth of the flagship cryptocurrency. That’s according to data from on-chain analytics firm Santiment first shared by...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I hold $Tsuki]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992056/Why-I-hold-Tsuki</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992056/Why-I-hold-Tsuki"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn’t about 10x or 100x returns—it’s about being part of something bigger. Tsuki is more than just a meme; it’s a project with deep connections that span across industries, gaming, and blockchain. If you’ve been paying attention, you’ll notice the links—subtle ties to Roaring Kitty, Elon,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s Volatility Increases: Token Down 35% by Volume as Selloffs Continue]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992058/Worldcoins-Volatility-Increases-Token-Down-35-by-Volume-as-Selloffs-Continue</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992058/Worldcoins-Volatility-Increases-Token-Down-35-by-Volume-as-Selloffs-Continue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin is trading at $1.82, with a 35% volume decrease and a drop of 6.4% in the last 24 hours. Technical analysis shows a bearish rising wedge pattern emerging. Worldcoin focuses on Asia and Latin America amidst regulatory challenges in Europe. Alameda Research’s Continued Selloffs With a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Could Surge 400% Under Trump Presidency, Standard Chartered Predicts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443fb5bc3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/solana-could-surge-400-under-trump-presidency-standard-chartered-predicts/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banking giant Standard Chartered predicts that solana could experience a significant surge of up to 400% if Donald Trump wins the 2024 U.S. presidential election. The bank’s head of digital assets suggests that solana’s faster transaction speed and support for decentralized applications position it well in a crypto-friendly environment. Standard Chartered Predicts Solana Surge if […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s Custody Product Expands Its Offering with RWA Tokenization Features]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992044/Ripples-Custody-Product-Expands-Its-Offering-with-RWA-Tokenization-Features</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992044/Ripples-Custody-Product-Expands-Its-Offering-with-RWA-Tokenization-Features"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A range of new features for Ripple Custody are now available for institutional clients to cater to the demand for robust and secure custodial solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Lifelike Zoom Clone May Soon be Taking Meetings For You. Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285732/your-lifelike-zoom-clone-may-soon-be-taking-meetings-for-you-heres-how"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Zoom prepares to launch lifelike AI clones in 2025, the company is banking on a rethink to workplace communication—for better or worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Lifelike Zoom Clone May Soon be Taking Meetings For You. Here's How]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992018/Your-Lifelike-Zoom-Clone-May-Soon-be-Taking-Meetings-For-You-Heres-How</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992018/Your-Lifelike-Zoom-Clone-May-Soon-be-Taking-Meetings-For-You-Heres-How"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Zoom prepares to launch lifelike AI clones in 2025, the company is banking on a rethink to workplace communication—for better or worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Exec Stuns Community With 1,000% Surge Prediction In 2-3 Days]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443e4c86f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-exec-1000-surge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:19:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current Shiba Inu price trajectory might be unsure at the moment, but fervent investors continue to stand strong. Lucie, Shiba Inu’s marketing lead, recently dropped an interesting take on the meme coin’s potential in the near future. In a stunning post on social media platform X, Lucie noted that if everything works out well, Shiba Inu has the potential to perform a 1000% increase in its price within two to three days. As expected, this projection has sparked excitement among some members of the Shiba Inu community.
 
Current Price Action Is Irrelevant
 
Lucie’s bold assertion of a massive Shiba Inu surge came hand-in-hand with her candid assessment of the token’s current price movement. In a recent post on the social media platform X, she reflected on the meme coin’s price trajectory…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Cumberland, the SEC's Latest Big Crypto Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285729/what-is-cumberland-sec-lawsuit-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's latest target isn't exactly a household name. Yet, as a critical liquidity provider, Cumberland is one of crypto’s major players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Cumberland, the SEC's Latest Big Crypto Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991991/Who-is-Cumberland-the-SECs-Latest-Big-Crypto-Target</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991991/Who-is-Cumberland-the-SECs-Latest-Big-Crypto-Target"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC's latest target isn't exactly a household name. Yet, as a critical liquidity provider, Cumberland is one of crypto’s major players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Reasons Why Dogwifhat (WIF) Return to $3 May Be Delayed]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992054/2-Reasons-Why-Dogwifhat-WIF-Return-to-3-May-Be-Delayed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992054/2-Reasons-Why-Dogwifhat-WIF-Return-to-3-May-Be-Delayed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogwifhat (WIF) has surged 42% over the past 30 days, but sustaining this momentum and reaching $3 again remains uncertain. The bullish trend appears to be weakening, as indicators like the Relative Strength Index (RSI) and Average Directional Index (ADX) show diminishing trend strength,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's (BTC) Suffering Continues, Solana (SOL) at Crucial Support Level: What's Next? Ethereum (ETH) to Dive Below $2,000?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991994/Bitcoins-BTC-Suffering-Continues-Solana-SOL-at-Crucial-Support-Level-Whats-Next-Ethereum-ETH-to-Dive-Below-2000</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991994/Bitcoins-BTC-Suffering-Continues-Solana-SOL-at-Crucial-Support-Level-Whats-Next-Ethereum-ETH-to-Dive-Below-2000"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin might not be in trouble, but it is still not getting enough confidence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Says ‘That’s Often Where Opportunities Lie’ As Cardano Lingers in ‘Deep Depression Phase’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991986/Analyst-Says-Thats-Often-Where-Opportunities-Lie-As-Cardano-Lingers-in-Deep-Depression-Phase</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991986/Analyst-Says-Thats-Often-Where-Opportunities-Lie-As-Cardano-Lingers-in-Deep-Depression-Phase"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T00:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano’s (ADA) longstanding price woes have dampened crypto traders’ enthusiasm about the smart contract platform’s future, but one analyst thinks that lack of enthusiasm indicates a potential opportunity. Ali Martinez tells his 73,700 followers on the social media platform X that he thinks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Charges Cumberland DRW for Unregistered $2 Billion Crypto Securities Dealings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443e05781</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-charges-cumberland-drw-for-unregistered-2-billion-crypto-securities-dealings/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has charged Cumberland DRW LLC, a Chicago-based firm, for operating as an unregistered dealer in over $2 billion of crypto assets classified as securities. The SEC claims that Cumberland violated federal securities laws by failing to register, raising concerns over investor protection. The charges seek injunctive relief and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Lawmaker: Regulators Playing Squid Game With Domestic Crypto Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991945/South-Korean-Lawmaker-Regulators-Playing-Squid-Game-With-Domestic-Crypto-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19991945/South-Korean-Lawmaker-Regulators-Playing-Squid-Game-With-Domestic-Crypto-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A South Korean lawmaker has accused the nation’s top regulator of “playing Squid Game” with domestic crypto exchanges – allowing Upbit to thrive at the expense of its rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC sues Cumberland DRW for acting as an unregistered securities broker, Solana ETFs at risk]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992046/SEC-sues-Cumberland-DRW-for-acting-as-an-unregistered-securities-broker-Solana-ETFs-at-risk</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19992046/SEC-sues-Cumberland-DRW-for-acting-as-an-unregistered-securities-broker-Solana-ETFs-at-risk"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities & Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a lawsuit on Thursday against Chicago-based trading firm Cumberland DRW for operating as an unregistered securities dealer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun Is Now Prime Minister of Liberland—What Does That Even Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285717/justin-sun-prime-minister-liberland"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T23:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liberland is an imagined libertarian utopia on the Danube, where every system lives on-chain and the age of consent is 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ETFs Still Hot, With Nearly 50% of U.S. Investors Planning to Buy: Charles Schwab]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285715</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285715/crypto-etfs-still-hot-nearly-50-u-s-investors-planning-buy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Charles Schwab survey shows that there’s massive demand for new American Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deribit Launches US Yield Coin (USYC) as New Yield-Bearing Cross-Margin Collateral Option]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443ef0b31</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/deribit-launches-us-yield-coin-usyc-as-new-yield-bearing-cross-margin-collateral-option/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deribit has announced the launch of the US Yield Coin (USYC) from Hashnote as a new yield-bearing cross-margin collateral option. USYC, an ERC-20 token backed by reverse repurchase agreements on U.S. Government Securities, provides traders with a stable and flexible collateral option that generates daily yield. The assets are secured in a segregated account at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian Authorities Launch Operation Targeting Entities Facilitating Crypto Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443ef0b30</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brazilian-authorities-launch-operation-targeting-entities-facilitating-crypto-money-laundering/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brazilian Federal Police launched Operation Alcacaria this Wednesday, aiming to thwart the action of a network focused on providing money laundering services using cryptocurrency. The operation involved 62 search warrants, 13 arrest warrants, and the seizure of funds of the involved entities in banks. Brazilian Authorities Execute Operation Alcacaria Against Crypto Money Laundering Actors […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs Files Cross-Appeal as Battle With SEC Rages On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285714</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285714/ripple-labs-cross-appeal-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Labs moved to file a cross-appeal in its years-long legal battle with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission over XRP sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Designer Susan Kare Brings NFT 'Esc Keys' to Asprey Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285439</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285439/apple-designer-susan-kare-nft-esc-keys-asprey-studio"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designer Susan Kare's iconic pixel art style is gracing a new collection of physical and digital artworks unveiled during Frieze London.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Falls Under $60,000 as $150 Million in Crypto Longs Get Rekt]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=284560</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/284560/bitcoin-falls-60000-150m-longs-rekt"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin dipped below the $60,000 mark Thursday after three weeks above that line. What's to blame for the latest cooldown?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT Faces Downward Pressure as Investors Pivot to Stocks in China]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443d53fe8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/usdt-faces-downward-pressure-as-investors-pivot-to-stocks-in-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USDT, the largest stablecoin in the crypto market, has marginally lost its peg to the U.S. dollar, trading at less than $1 since September 30. Analysts believe this is a byproduct of large outflows from China as crypto investors turn to the national stock market to participate in the bull run following the announcement of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dubai Tightens Grip On Crypto, Issues Cease And Desist Orders To 7 VASP Operators]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443d6261f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dubai-tightens-grip-on-crypto-issues-cease-and-desist-orders-to-7-vasp-operators/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Virtual Assets Regulatory Authority (VARA) in Dubai has moved decisively, slapping cease-and-desist orders on seven VASPs. This is all a part of VARA’s continued attempts to make sure everyone follows its rules, especially when it comes to crypto marketing and licensing. The fines imposed can reach up to AED 100,000 (around $27,000), underscoring the gravity of these infractions.
 
 
VARA’s Commitment To Regulation
 
Founded in 2022, VARA seeks to establish Dubai as a worldwide center for virtual assets while safeguarding investor interests. The regulator supervises all operations concerning virtual assets, encompassing trading, management, and marketing.
 
According to VARA, the recent cease and desist orders are intended for organizations in Dubai to avoid illegal activities and be g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's Lead Over Harris Widens on Polymarket's Prediction Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443d64bc5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/10/trumps-lead-over-harris-widens-on-polymarkets-prediction-market/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His odds of winning the U.S. presidential election have soared to a more than two-month high.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Settles Charges With Trading Firm It Says Tricked Investors With AI 'Buzzwords']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285680/sec-trading-firm-tricked-investors-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has hit trading firm Rimar Capital with civil charges for allegedly lying to investors about its use of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto ETFs Take Center Stage: Nearly Half of Charles Schwab Investors Eye Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443d3eb2e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-etfs-take-center-stage-nearly-half-of-charles-schwab-investors-eye-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent survey conducted by American financial powerhouse Charles Schwab revealed that nearly half of the respondents (45%) are gearing up to invest in cryptocurrency exchange-traded funds (ETFs). Millennials Lead the Crypto ETF Charge, Expert Puzzled by Schwab’s Slow Move Charles Schwab, a major player in the finance world, rolled out a new asset management […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Set For Explosive Growth As BTC Enters Early Stages Of Mega Bull]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443dcae4c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-enters-early-stages-of-mega-bull/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite recent fluctuations in the general crypto market, Bitcoin, the flagship digital asset is showing signs of an impending major rally, possibly to a new peak, which indicates a potential positive shift in price movement to the upside.
 
Bitcoin’s Mega Bull Run Begins To Unfold
 
Bitcoin is reportedly set for explosive growth as the crypto asset draws closer to the much-anticipated pivotal moment that will send BTC to unprecedented heights. Market expert and trader, Ether Nasyonal identified the positive development, capturing the attention of the crypto community.
 
 
According to the market expert, Bitcoin appears to be entering the early stage of a mega bull run, marking a significant moment for the crypto asset. This forecast is consistent with the rising belief that BTC is poised …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Made a Profit From Ethereum Token Created to Catch Fraudsters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285701</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285701/fbi-made-profit-ethereum-token"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Ethereum token created by the FBI to foil market manipulators netted investigators around $14,500 in profit, on-chain data shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Pushes Back: Cross-Appeal Notice Filed Against SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443d8236c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-cross-appeal-notice-filed-against-sec/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T19:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development in the ongoing litigation between Ripple Labs and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Ripple announced the filing of a cross-appeal against the regulator. 
 
This move follows the SEC’s recent appeal of a 2023 ruling by Judge Analisa Torres, which determined that the XRP token, sold by Ripple on public exchanges, does not qualify as a security under current laws.
 
Alderoty Highlights SEC’s Struggles And Cross-Appeal Rationale
 
Stuart Alderoty, Ripple’s Chief Legal Officer, took to social media platform X (formerly Twitter) to explain the company’s position. He emphasized that the SEC lost on all the critical points in the case, which is why they are appealing. Alderoty said: 
 

Today, Ripple filed a cross-appeal to ensure nothing’s left  on the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Reasons Ether ETFs Have Underperformed]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443d89f4d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/10/10/four-reasons-ether-etfs-have-underperformed/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T19:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs haven't gained the same traction as BTC ETFs, even seeing net outflows this week. Tom Carreras investigates why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Carreras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Takes Significant Lead Over Harris in Polymarket Odds for 2024 Election Win]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7443daf9e3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/trump-takes-significant-lead-over-harris-in-polymarket-odds-for-2024-election-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T19:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, betting activity on Polymarket indicated that former President Donald Trump has pulled ahead of Vice President Kamala Harris in the race for the 2024 election. As of press time, Trump’s odds stand at 55.8%, with Harris trailing at 43.7%. This shift in favor of Trump has been observed since around Oct. 5, approximately […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Sues Crypto Trading Firm Cumberland, Again Alleges Solana and Polygon Are Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285688/sec-sues-cumberland-solana-polygon"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC continued its crypto crackdown Thursday with charges against Cumberland, again calling Solana and other assets securities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Holders Top 100 Million Following 'Hamster Kombat' Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285674</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285674/ton-holders-100-million-hamster-kombat-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100 million wallets now hold TON as the Telegram-linked network has surged via tap-to-earn games like Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol is Reinventing Decentralized Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285471</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285471/how-walrus-protocol-is-reinventing-decentralized-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized storage protocol’s novel data encoding algorithm will unlock applications across AI, websites and social media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Thursday, October 10.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo, Riddle, and Rebus Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and rebus solution for Thursday, October 10? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tap-to-Earn Gaming Expands From Telegram to TikTok via Solana's Sonic SVM]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285619</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285619/tap-to-earn-gaming-expands-from-telegram-to-tiktok-via-solanas-sonic-svm"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana gaming ecosystem has launched Sonic X, a tap-to-earn game based natively inside TikTok as it aims to be the next ‘Notcoin.’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Reveals Plans to Launch Ethereum Layer-2 Network Unichain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285616/uniswap-ethereum-layer-2-unichain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap will launch an Ethereum layer-2 network called Unichain in an effort to cut fees, boost liquidity, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubisoft Reveals Release Date for ‘Champions Tactics’ NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285608/ubisoft-champions-tactics-release-date"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Tactics: Grimoria Chronicles will debut on the Oasys network on October 23, gaming giant Ubisoft announced Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ronin Gaming Network Adopts Chainlink Protocol to Increase Security on Ethereum Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285606</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285606/ronin-network-adopts-chainlink-cross-chain-protocol-to-increase-security-on-its-ethereum-bridge"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Security was the number one most important factor," said Phuc Thai, Head Researcher at Ronin developer Sky Mavis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Iris Energy Accused of Overstating Data Center Capacity in Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285600</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285600/bitcoin-miner-iris-energy-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The lawsuit claims that Iris Energy "knew or should have known" that its Childress County site in Texas was a poor fit for high-performance computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Jitters Intensify as Investors Brace for Inflation Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285598</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285598/bitcoin-price-jitters-inflation-report"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["While these outflows are still relatively modest, they signal waning institutional support as bullish momentum fades,” an analyst said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe Follows Through on Crypto Payment Support in USDC Following Six-Year Hiatus]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285581</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285581/stripe-crypto-payment-support-usdc-following-six-year-hiatus"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T06:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe’s reintroduction to crypto comes after a decision to end support for Bitcoin in 2018, where it cited market volatility concerns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thai SEC Proposes New Rules for Crypto Investment in Mutual and Private Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285578</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285578/thai-sec-proposes-new-rules-digital-asset-investment-mutual-private-funds"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T03:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand's SEC is trying to update domestic regulations to reflect the changes and opportunities in crypto investing globally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Kamala Harris' VP Pick Just Twitch Streamed a Rally Alongside World of Warcraft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285567</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285567/kamala-harris-vp-pick-twitch-streamed-rally-alongside-world-of-warcraft"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T00:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It marks the first time the Harris campaign has integrated live gaming with political content on its Twitch account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Crypto Project Submits Proposal to Ethereum DeFi Giant Aave]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285548</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285548/trump-crypto-world-liberty-proposal-ethereum-defi-aave"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T22:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's World Liberty Financial plans to operate as an Aave instance, and AaveDAO stands to gain substantial fees from the deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Can Now Beam Cat Videos to Mars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285512</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285512/nasa-can-now-beam-cat-videos-mars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T22:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good news for outer space colonizers: The next step for space telecommunications may be using light beams to stream data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Asks Judge to Dismiss Elon Musk Lawsuit as 'Blusterous' Harassment Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285528/openai-dismiss-elon-musk-lawsuit-blusterous-harassment"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The motion filed in federal court argues that Musk's claims lack a legal basis and merely aim to give him a competitive edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Doxx or Not to Doxx: Crypto Sleuth Reignites Fiery Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285530/to-doxx-or-not-zachxbt-murad"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain investigator ZachXBT sparked a robust debate about doxxing wallets after divulging a meme coin booster's associated addresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Charge Meme Coin ‘Market Maker’ Gotbit, Three Others With Crypto Market Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285503</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285503/feds-charge-gotbit-others-market-manipulation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T19:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feds on Wednesday unsealed indictments against Gotbit, ZM Quant, CLS Global and MyTrade for alleged crypto market manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Use Booms in Argentina as Inflation Skyrockets: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285491</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285491/argentina-stablecoin-use-booms-inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T19:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina still suffers from hyperinflation and citizens in the country are using stablecoins as a result, according to a new report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latest Way to Catch a Virus: AI-Driven Porn Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285455/the-latest-way-to-catch-a-virus-ai-driven-porn-sites"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Russian hacker group is using AI “deepnude” websites to spread malware, continuing a classic trend with a modern twist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins No ‘Safe Haven’ From US Monetary Policy, Says European Central Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285473/stablecoins-no-safe-haven-us-policy-ecb"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ECB says that stablecoins are vulnerable to both shocks coming from within the crypto world and the decisions of U.S. central bankers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Island Nation Palau Puts Digital Savings Bonds on Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285467</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285467/palau-digital-savings-bonds-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The island nation is planning to fully launch the digital bond system next year to raise funds for critical infrastructure projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ready Player One-Inspired 'The Readyverse' Launches Generative AI Building Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285211</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285211/ready-player-one-readyverse-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readyverse Studios has introduced Promptopia, enabling real-time, in-game creativity for all players via simple text prompts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why This Colombian Neobank is Switching From Ethereum to Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285233</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285233/why-colombian-neobank-switching-ethereum-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To scale with growing demand, Littio said it would transition its holdings from OpenTrade's vaults on Ethereum to those on Avalanche.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Still Undervalued and That Presents a Buying Opportunity, Say Analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285423</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285423/bitcoin-undervalued-buying-opportunity-analysts"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Historically, when [Bitcoin] active addresses surge like this, it often precedes or accompanies price increases," an analyst told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Settlement Requires Caroline Ellison to Give Up 'All of Her Assets']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285363</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285363/ftx-settlement-caroline-ellison-assets"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T14:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company noted that pursuing a lawsuit would deplete Ellison's remaining resources and incur additional costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rep. Tom Emmer Is Confident Crypto Laws Are Coming Soon—No Matter Who Wins the Election]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qWDybFgM/rep-tom-emmer-is-confident-crypto-laws-are-coming-soonno-matter-who-wins-the-election"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Majority Whip Tom Emmer sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano to discuss the state of crypto legislation, Kamala Harris, Fairshake, and more at Messari Mainnet 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 209 - LET UPTOBER BEGIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DdOpex2X/fomo-hour-209-let-uptober-begin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see inflows for 8 straight days. SUI enters top 20, $110m of unlocks today. SOL weekly DEX volume flips ETH. Firedancer sees very fast TPS on Testnet. ETH gas up 500% in 2 weeks. EIGEN opens at $7bn FDV. FTX creditors vote in favour of restructuring plan. Dell to sell another $1.2bn Dell stock. Metaplanet buys another 107 BTC.Grayscale opens decentralised AI fund to investors. Robinhood allows crypto transfer in EU. Pollak to head Coinbase Wallet & join exec team. Gemini to close in Canada. Japan considers lower cap gains tax on crypto. Ohio bill would make it legal to pay taxes in crypto. Trump project opens whitelist to non-US users. CZ pledges to invest in blockchain companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng Talks Progress on Exchange's Global Regulatory Goals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DNhZEWGn/binance-ceo-richard-teng-talks-progress-on-exchanges-global-regulatory-goals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T22:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Reporters Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano spoke with Binance CEO Richard Teng about the crypto exchange's progress on establishing a global headquarters, improving its relationships with regulators, and expanding its global presence in the wake of founder Changpeng "CZ" Zhao's jailing in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 207 - WELCOME BACK TO THE BULL!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2OVTsv7N/fomo-hour-207-welcome-back-to-the-bull"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T18:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala signals support for crypto. Top memecoins all soar, add $10bn in value in a week. MOODENG hits $180m, does 11x in a week. SUI & SEI continue to lead L1s for price & TVL growth. Revolut & Robinhood are considering stablecoin. Visa launches new tokenisation platform for banks. PayPal to allow business accounts to hold crypto Hamster kombat's HMSTER disappoints on launch. Biden admin may have forced Silvergate’s closure. Court rules crypto mining boxes ‘are securities’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 206 - MEMES ARE PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Uc5GOy50/fomo-hour-206-memes-are-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T15:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC nears $65k key resistance level. Kamala makes positive comments about crypto. PayPal allows businesses to hold crypto. Visa allows banks to test RWAs & smart contracts. Cuban wants to be head of SEC. Silvergate claims about ‘Chokepoint 2.0’ grow. Truflation hacked for $5m. Telegram Wallet blocked in UK & US. Court rules crypto mining boxes are securities. Infinex DeFi platform raises $65m. Ethena announces new stablecoin linked to BUIDL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 205 - ALTCOINS CONTINUE TO RALLY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mtR8OATG/fomo-hour-205-altcoins-continue-to-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUI leads L1 gains as TVL crosses $1bn. Altcoin market cap close to breaking downtrend. SEI becomes top chain for 1 month TVL growth. ETH ETFs sees 3rd largest inflow ever. SEC delays ETH ETF options decision. SOL took most of ETH outflows over last 3 months. SOLETH continues to be trading at resistance. $8.1bn BTC options to expire this week. BTC heading to $500k-$1m in a year: PlanB. Stablecoin supply hits new ATH. Caroline Ellison sentenced to 2 years in jail. SBF & Diddy in the same jail. SEC settles against TUSD for not being collateralised. Gensler gets derided for crypto approach. Hester Pierce admits flaws in SEC crypto policy. Harris against regulation by litigation: Cuban. Golem claims ETH move to CEXs due to staking. Binance refutes data leak claims. Next Y combinator batch has ‘no crypto companies’. Celo overtakes Tron for stablecoin addresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 204 - MOODENG MOO-NING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g2yV7DjU/fomo-hour-204-moodeng-moo-ning"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC needs to top $65.2k to put in a higher high. ETH ETFs see biggest outflow since July. ETH outperformance could be start of ‘alt season’. BlackRock gets 12hr BTC withdrawal from Coinbase. cbBTC only wrapped BTC to not show reserves. Telegram to share user data upon legal requests. EIGEN non-transferability to be removed Sep 30th. TIA announces $100m funding round. TIA deal was OTC token sale ‘done months ago’. Polymarket considers token, trying $50m raise. Maybe we will pay off debt with crypto: Trump. Harris unlikely to give full crypto policy pre-election. 13m Binance users’ data may have been leaked. Caroline Ellison likely won’t serve time in jail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 203 - KAMALA GOES PRO-CRYPTO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZIgJfh06/fomo-hour-203-kamala-goes-pro-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T16:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds saw $321m inflows last week. Kamala commits to crypto & AI expansion. TAO leads gains in AI hype, does 2x in 2 weeks. SUI TVL breaks $900m. Average Q4 returns for BTC is 88%. BTC Google searches down 75% since 2021. BTC 161 days from halving, when it rallied in 2020. Crypto VCs raised $2.2bn this year, well below 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 202 - SOL STARTS TO SEND IT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kMr0ptrw/fomo-hour-202-sol-starts-to-send-it"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors as Breakpoint begins. SOL launches Frankendancer on mainnet. Helio Pay allows Shopify items to sell on X. Franklin Templeton to launch fund on SOL. BTC short term holders fall at fastest rate in 12 years. MicroStrategy upsizes convertible note raise to $1bn. BingX loses $52m in hack. $243m crypto heist exposed by ZachXBT. Supreme Court of India hacked on X, shills scam. SocGen launches Euro stablecoin on SOL. Sky agrees to stop using WBTC. Germany shuts down 47 crypto exchanges. Stablecoin’s now 18th biggest holder of treasuries. Consensys lawsuit against SEC dismissed. Partisanship will stop Trump crypto plans: Hoskinson. Scaramucci working with Kamala on crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>