<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-01T02:34:20.503Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-01T02:34:20.503Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Bitcoin Replace Gold For National Reserves? Expert Weighs In]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe59772</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/could-bitcoin-replace-gold-for-national-reserves/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T02:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gabor Gurbacs, a strategic advisor at Tether, the issuer of USDT, recently spotlighted Bitcoin’s potential in “revolutionizing” how central banks handle and secure national reserves, using India’s logistical challenges with gold as a prime example.
 
A Digital Solution For Traditional Gold Logistics
 
India’s decision to relocate a significant portion of its gold reserves from the UK back to domestic vaults has reignited discussions about the logistical challenges of physical gold. A report from the Economic Times particularly noted:
 

India’s central bank has moved around a 100 tonnes, or 1 lakh kilograms of gold from the United Kingdom back to its vaults in India, and intends to move more in coming months.
 
Leveraging this scenario, Gurbacs suggested that cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Releases First-Ever Risk Assessment on NFTs, Highlighting Potential Illicit Uses and Investor Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545468/US-Treasury-Releases-First-Ever-Risk-Assessment-on-NFTs-Highlighting-Potential-Illicit-Uses-and-Investor-Risks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545468/US-Treasury-Releases-First-Ever-Risk-Assessment-on-NFTs-Highlighting-Potential-Illicit-Uses-and-Investor-Risks"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T02:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Treasury Department has published its inaugural finance risk assessment for nonfungible tokens...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Bitcoin Replace Gold For National Reserves? Expert Weighs In]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545464/Could-Bitcoin-Replace-Gold-For-National-Reserves-Expert-Weighs-In</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545464/Could-Bitcoin-Replace-Gold-For-National-Reserves-Expert-Weighs-In"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T02:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gabor Gurbacs, a strategic advisor at Tether, the issuer of USDT, recently spotlighted Bitcoin’s potential in “revolutionizing” how central banks handle and secure national reserves, using India’s logistical challenges with gold as a prime example. A Digital Solution For Traditional Gold...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Board Defends CEO Sam Altman Amid ‘Toxic Culture’ Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233372</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233372/openai-toxic-culture-former-current-board-members-argue"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenAI board members claimed there was “psychological abuse,” but their replacements say Altman was “consistently collegial.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Board Defends CEO Sam Altman Amid ‘Toxic Culture’ Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545442/OpenAI-Board-Defends-CEO-Sam-Altman-Amid-Toxic-Culture-Claims</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545442/OpenAI-Board-Defends-CEO-Sam-Altman-Amid-Toxic-Culture-Claims"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenAI board members claimed there was “psychological abuse,” but their replacements say Altman was “consistently collegial.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Vetoes Bill That Would Have Eliminated Controversial SEC Crypto Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545425/President-Biden-Vetoes-Bill-That-Would-Have-Eliminated-Controversial-SEC-Crypto-Policy</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545425/President-Biden-Vetoes-Bill-That-Would-Have-Eliminated-Controversial-SEC-Crypto-Policy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:35:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden has followed through on a promise to veto SEC-related crypto legislation that recently passed the House and Senate. The bill would have reversed guidance from the SEC that says certain companies should label crypto assets as liabilities on their balance sheet, even if they are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pepe Whale (PEPEWHALE) Coin Will Rally 14,000% Ahead of KuCoin Listing, While Shiba Inu, Bonk and Dogecoin Lag]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545414/Pepe-Whale-PEPEWHALE-Coin-Will-Rally-14000-Ahead-of-KuCoin-Listing-While-Shiba-Inu-Bonk-and-Dogecoin-Lag</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545414/Pepe-Whale-PEPEWHALE-Coin-Will-Rally-14000-Ahead-of-KuCoin-Listing-While-Shiba-Inu-Bonk-and-Dogecoin-Lag"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early investors in memecoins like Shiba Inu (SHIB), Bonk (BONK) and Dogecoin (DOGE) made astronomical...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Crypto Ownership Reaches 562 Million: 6.8% of World Population Now Own and Use Digital Currencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe1522e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/global-crypto-ownership-reaches-562-million-6-8-of-world-population-now-own-and-use-digital-currencies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report reveals that 562 million people globally now own digital currencies, an increase from 420 million in 2023, making up 6.8% of the world’s population. Asia is at the forefront of this growth, with North America close behind. Overall, cryptocurrency adoption is rising worldwide, with notable increases seen across all continents. ‘562 Million […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Exchange DMM Bitcoin Falls Victim To $305 Million Hack]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe290e1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dmm-bitcoin-falls-victim-to-305-million-hack/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DMM Bitcoin, one of Japan’s largest cryptocurrency exchanges, recently suffered a major setback when it reported a loss of 48 billion yen ($305 million) in Bitcoin (BTC) due to a security breach. 
 
The incident, discovered on May 31, 2024, revealed the illegal leakage of BTC from a DMM Bitcoin wallet. As a result, several services have been temporarily suspended to address the situation and protect customer assets. 
 
Unauthorized Access Incident Hits DMM Bitcoin
 
According to local media reports, on May 31, DMM Bitcoin detected an unauthorized access incident resulting in the illegal leakage of 4,502.9 BTC, equivalent to approximately 48.2 billion yen. The exchange then took measures to prevent further unauthorized outflows. 
 
 
In response to the security breach, DMM Bitcoin suspended…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOT prices react in THIS way to Polkadot’s new milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545392/DOT-prices-react-in-THIS-way-to-Polkadots-new-milestone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545392/DOT-prices-react-in-THIS-way-to-Polkadots-new-milestone"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot becomes the most decentralized blockchain, but its price action continues to remain bearish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Meow (TRUMPMEO) Coin Will Surge 13,000% Ahead of KuCoin Listing, While Shiba Inu, Bonk and Dogecoin Lag]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545368/Trump-Meow-TRUMPMEO-Coin-Will-Surge-13000-Ahead-of-KuCoin-Listing-While-Shiba-Inu-Bonk-and-Dogecoin-Lag</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545368/Trump-Meow-TRUMPMEO-Coin-Will-Surge-13000-Ahead-of-KuCoin-Listing-While-Shiba-Inu-Bonk-and-Dogecoin-Lag"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early investors in memecoins like Shiba Inu (SHIB), Bonk (BONK) and Dogecoin (DOGE) made astronomical...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Estonian Nationals Extradited to US for $575M Crypto Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fec9794</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/estonian-nationals-extradited-to-us-for-575m-crypto-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Estonian nationals have been extradited from Estonia to the U.S. to face charges for their roles in “a massive multi-faceted cryptocurrency Ponzi scheme,” according to an announcement by the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ). Sergei Potapenko and Ivan Turõgin are accused of operating a $575 million Ponzi scheme involving the fraudulent cryptocurrency mining service […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Turns $3,200 into $350,000 by Snagging Huge Chunk of Celebrity Token]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545377/Crypto-Trader-Turns-3200-into-350000-by-Snagging-Huge-Chunk-of-Celebrity-Token</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545377/Crypto-Trader-Turns-3200-into-350000-by-Snagging-Huge-Chunk-of-Celebrity-Token"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cryptocurrency trader has managed to take advantage of the launch of a red-hot celebrity-themed token to capture a large percentage of its total supply, which they used to turn less than 1 ETH into over $350,000. According to available blockchain data, the trader took advantage of the launch...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Reversal Could Be Closer Than You Think, Crucial Solana (SOL) Support Level Is Here, Ethereum (ETH) on Verge]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545366/XRP-Reversal-Could-Be-Closer-Than-You-Think-Crucial-Solana-SOL-Support-Level-Is-Here-Ethereum-ETH-on-Verge</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545366/XRP-Reversal-Could-Be-Closer-Than-You-Think-Crucial-Solana-SOL-Support-Level-Is-Here-Ethereum-ETH-on-Verge"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite some bullishness, market is still far from full recovery]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$30,000 Drained From Wells Fargo Account in Seconds – Bank Refuses To Reimburse, Charges $1,184 in Fees To Hacked Customers: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545329/30000-Drained-From-Wells-Fargo-Account-in-Seconds-Bank-Refuses-To-Reimburse-Charges-1184-in-Fees-To-Hacked-Customers-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545329/30000-Drained-From-Wells-Fargo-Account-in-Seconds-Bank-Refuses-To-Reimburse-Charges-1184-in-Fees-To-Hacked-Customers-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple in California says Wells Fargo failed to protect $30,000 that was lost to hackers in a heartbeat. Ron Scott and his wife Jan say criminals recently logged into their Wells Fargo account after managing to hack one of their email passwords, reports CBS 8. The Scotts say the bank should...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Prediction: Machine Learning Algorithm Reveals Where Price Will Be In June]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fefb48d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-prediction-june/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is among the altcoins that continue to command a large following even after putting on a poor performance for the last few years. At the same time, expectations for the altcoin have fluctuated between bullish and bearish, especially in the long term. However, in the short term at least, the machine learning algorithm at CoinCodex predicts some level of bullishness for XRP.
 
XRP To Jump 20% In June
 
As the month of May draws to an end and June swims into view, there are varying expectations for the crypto market and where it could go from here. For XRP, the CoinCodex machine learning algorithm predicts that the month of June will be bullish for it.
 
The one-month prediction timeframe on the website shows that the price would rise as high as $0.627709, and from the current price of XR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Vetoes SEC SAB 121 Repeal Resolution]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fe80b3d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/president-biden-vetoes-sec-sab-121-repeal-resolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden issued a veto against H.J.Res. 109, a resolution that would disapprove of the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin No. 121 (SAB 121). In its veto document, Bides states that the approval of this Republican-led resolution would “inappropriately constrain the SEC’s ability to set forth appropriate guardrails and address […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden vetoes resolution overturning SEC’s controversial crypto guidance, says repeal would ‘jeopardize’ consumers]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545323/Biden-vetoes-resolution-overturning-SECs-controversial-crypto-guidance-says-repeal-would-jeopardize-consumers</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545323/Biden-vetoes-resolution-overturning-SECs-controversial-crypto-guidance-says-repeal-would-jeopardize-consumers"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Joe Biden has vetoed a bipartisan resolution that aimed to overturn the Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin 121 (SAB 121), a controversial piece of guidance that establishes accounting standards for firms that custody crypto assets.The resolution had...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Gaming Token Notcoin (NOT) Surges Nearly 160% This Week To Reach a New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545316/Telegram-Gaming-Token-Notcoin-NOT-Surges-Nearly-160-This-Week-To-Reach-a-New-All-Time-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545316/Telegram-Gaming-Token-Notcoin-NOT-Surges-Nearly-160-This-Week-To-Reach-a-New-All-Time-High"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new altcoin connected to a viral game on the encrypted messaging platform Telegram printed fresh all-time highs this week after surging by nearly 160%. NOT is a community token for the popular Telegram-based tap-to-earn mining game Notcoin that began trading on May 16th when Binance rolled out...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market blues? Not for Bitcoin Runes! DOG, CATS hit new highs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545320/Market-blues-Not-for-Bitcoin-Runes-DOG-CATS-hit-new-highs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545320/Market-blues-Not-for-Bitcoin-Runes-DOG-CATS-hit-new-highs"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The prices of Bitcoin Runes tokens such as MAGA•THE•DONALD•TRUMP and CATS•IN•THE•SATS have climbed by triple digits in the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Prediction: Machine Learning Algorithm Reveals Where Price Will Be In June]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545322/XRP-Price-Prediction-Machine-Learning-Algorithm-Reveals-Where-Price-Will-Be-In-June</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545322/XRP-Price-Prediction-Machine-Learning-Algorithm-Reveals-Where-Price-Will-Be-In-June"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T00:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is among the altcoins that continue to command a large following even after putting on a poor performance for the last few years. At the same time, expectations for the altcoin have fluctuated between bullish and bearish, especially in the long term. However, in the short term at least, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US President Joe Biden vetoes SAB 121 repeal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545298/US-President-Joe-Biden-vetoes-SAB-121-repeal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545298/US-President-Joe-Biden-vetoes-SAB-121-repeal"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden said he vetoed the resolution because "he will not support measures that jeopardize the well-being of consumers and investors."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Biden Vetoes Resolution Overturning SEC Guidance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fea6d13</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/31/us-president-biden-vetoes-resolution-overturning-sec-guidance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S President Joe Biden signed a veto of a House Joint Resolution that would have repealed the Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin 121.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Holders Flock to New DOGE Alternative, Betting on Huge 1000x Returns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545296/Dogecoin-Holders-Flock-to-New-DOGE-Alternative-Betting-on-Huge-1000x-Returns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545296/Dogecoin-Holders-Flock-to-New-DOGE-Alternative-Betting-on-Huge-1000x-Returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Dogecoin (DOGE) price struggles just to the north of its 21 and 50DMAs,holders are flocking to a new DOGE alternative called Dogeverse (DV) as they bet on potential 100x returns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Vetoes Pro-Crypto Resolution, Defends SEC's Judgement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233358</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233358/biden-veto-sab-121-resolution"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House said the bipartisan-passed bill would “jeopardize the well-being of consumers and investors.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21Shares drops Ark from ETH ETF as remaining applicants meet SEC deadline]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545274/21Shares-drops-Ark-from-ETH-ETF-as-remaining-applicants-meet-SEC-deadline</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545274/21Shares-drops-Ark-from-ETH-ETF-as-remaining-applicants-meet-SEC-deadline"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six companies updated their spot Ethereum ETF S-1 registration statements on May 31, with 21 Shares notably dropping Ark Invest from its filing. The relevant filing renames the “Ark 21Shares Ethereum ETF” to the “21Shares Core Ethereum ETF.” It also removes all mention of Ark Invest from its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Tightens Customer Service Regulations for Crypto Companies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fd4dced</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-york-tightens-customer-service-regulations-for-crypto-companies/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York State Department of Financial Services (DFS) has introduced new guidance mandating regulated cryptocurrency entities to implement customer service policies and procedures. Crypto entities must collect data to ensure timely and fair resolution of issues, maintain records for regulatory review, and provide quarterly analyses. New York Regulator Requires Crypto Firms to Adopt New […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Citizens of Consensus]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fd50996</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/31/meet-the-citizens-of-consensus/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at some of the people who attended the conference this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Biden Vetoes Resolution Overturning SEC Guidance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545273/US-President-Biden-Vetoes-Resolution-Overturning-SEC-Guidance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545273/US-President-Biden-Vetoes-Resolution-Overturning-SEC-Guidance"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S President Joe Biden signed a veto of a House Joint Resolution that would have repealed the Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) Staff Accounting Bulletin 121.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Shuts Out Unlicensed Exchanges as Deadline Expires]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545257/Hong-Kong-Shuts-Out-Unlicensed-Exchanges-as-Deadline-Expires</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545257/Hong-Kong-Shuts-Out-Unlicensed-Exchanges-as-Deadline-Expires"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All unlicensed exchanges will no longer be permitted to offer services within the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Penguiana Doubles Market Cap to Over $2.5 Million Ahead of GUIANA NFT Mint]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fd5e605</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/penguiana-doubles-market-cap-to-over-2-5-million-ahead-of-guiana-nft-mint/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Penguiana, the distinctive penguin-themed meme coin on the Solana blockchain, continues to captivate the crypto community, achieving a new milestone by doubling its market cap to over $2.5 million according to Dexscreener. This surge in valuation underscores the strong investor confidence and community enthusiasm surrounding the project, especially with the impending launch of the GUIANA […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink takes a bearish turn: Is a $20 price target still possible?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545250/Chainlink-takes-a-bearish-turn-Is-a-20-price-target-still-possible</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19545250/Chainlink-takes-a-bearish-turn-Is-a-20-price-target-still-possible"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T23:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LINK sheds all of its monthly gains in a stunning bearish reversal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Firm And University Of Austin Partner For $5 Million Endowment Fund]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fd036b2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-firm-and-university-of-austin-partner-for-5-million-endowment-fund/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T22:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin firm Unchained partnered with the University of Austin (UATX) to launch the first long-term endowment fund held in the flagship cryptocurrency. The partnership seeks to create a strong relationship between the firm and the university to benefit both communities.
 
 
First Long-Term Bitcoin Endowment Fund
 
On Thursday, Unchained and UATX announced their collaboration to launch an endowment fund. The partnership aims to raise $5 million for the fund, which would remain invested in Bitcoin (BTC) for at least five years.
 
The Bitcoin firm will offer a collaborative custody vault to store the endowment. Additionally, it will ensure the fund’s security and safeguard the BTC holdings, providing UATX “with a reliable and secure investment vehicle.”
 
According to the press release, Uncha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Re-Staking Platform Attracts $18.8 Billion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fd30a8d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-re-staking-platform-attracts-18-8-billion/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T22:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rising trend of “re-staking” has driven significant cryptocurrency investments into platforms that reward users for locking up their tokens. Leading this movement is Seattle-based startup Eigenlayer, which secured $100 million in funding from Andreessen Horowitz’s crypto arm in February. Eigenlayer has attracted $18.8 billion worth of crypto to its platform from less than $400 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Explains Why ‘Big Blockers’ Lost the Bitcoin Scaling Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233339</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233339/vitalik-buterin-on-why-big-blockers-lost-the-bitcoin-scaling-wars"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T22:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s creator says the best way to prevent future disputes will require new technologies like ZK-SNARKs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street Asks Biden Not to Veto Congress' Rejection of SEC Crypto Policy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fddcafe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/31/wall-street-asks-biden-not-to-veto-congress-rejection-of-sec-crypto-policy/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T21:47:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a rare lobbying overlap with crypto world, Wall Street banks and members of Congress are asking President Joe Biden to reverse course on his vow to veto the U.S. congressional resolution to overturn the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission's (SEC) crypto accounting policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton, Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Reveals Ethereum ETF Fee]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233336</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233336/franklin-templeton-reveals-ethereum-etf-fee"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T21:14:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global asset manager will charge investors 0.19%, in line with the low fees in the competitive spot Bitcoin ETF race.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplex Announces Introduction of Hybrid Defi Protocol for Solana]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fd9e5f7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/metaplex-announces-introduction-of-hybrid-defi-protocol-for-solana/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T21:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaplex, a Solana-based protocol that allows for the easy deployment of NFTs across applications, has introduced MPL-404, a hybrid decentralized finance standard. MPL-404 leans on SPL-404, a protocol that allows for the exchange of an NFT for a fixed number of tokens assigned by the designers of each artistic collection. Metaplex Aims to Extend Hybrid […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Won’t Believe How Many Bitcoin Millionaires Are Being Created Every Day]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fda9434</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-millionaires-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T21:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has seen a notable price increase since the start of the year, largely thanks to 2024 ushering in the bull run for this market cycle. This surge in Bitcoin’s price has led to an impressive amount of Bitcoin millionaire wallets being created daily. 
 
Almost 2,000 Bitcoin Millionaire Wallets Created Daily
 
According to data from research firm Kaiko, just under 2,000 Bitcoin millionaire wallets are created daily. Interestingly, this figure is still way lower than the 2021 Bull run when over 4,000 wallets hit the million-dollar mark daily, according to Kaiko. The research firm also claimed over 2,000 wallets reached $10 million daily in the last bull run.  
 
 
Kaiko noted that the slowdown in this market cycle is likely because new capital has yet to enter the market in full force. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlyn Jenner Releasing a Meme Coin Is Riskier Than Kim Kardashian Shilling Ethereum Max, Legal Experts Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233315</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233315/caitlyn-jenner-meme-coin-risk-kim-kardashian-ethereum-max"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T20:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week wasn’t the first time a Kardashian-linked token turned heads in crypto, but the stakes could be higher this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Betrayal In The Force: How An Indian Officer’s Bitcoin Theft Could Change Crypto Policing Forever]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fc1a4a1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/how-indian-officers-bitcoin-theft-crypto-policing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T20:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a striking crypto breach of trust, an Indian police officer, Chandrahar SR, was recently arrested for illicitly siphoning off Bitcoin worth approximately INR 1.8 crores ($216,000).
 
This misconduct occurred amid an investigation into a major cryptocurrency scam that dates back to 2017.
 
 
The Scam And The Breach
 
Chandrahar, a former inspector with the Central Crime Branch (CCB), exploited his position to access and transfer Bitcoin from the digital wallet of a hacker involved in the scam.
 
This wallet was supposed to be secure evidence in an ongoing probe into illicit activities encompassing several high-profile hacks of cryptocurrency exchanges, including Bitfinex and Unocoin, orchestrated by the hacker Srikrishna Ramesh and his accomplice Robin Khandelwal.
 
Despite the duo amass…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Are Back? Meme Coin Surge Pushes Market Cap Over $2 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233318/bitcoin-runes-back-meme-coin-surge-2-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last week, the value of assets on the Runes protocol for Bitcoin meme coins has doubled—and DOG is leading the charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dragonfly-Backed Stablecoin, Agora, to Launch Natively on Sui]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fcc925d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/dragonfly-backed-stablecoin-agora-to-launch-natively-on-sui/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:41:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agora, a stablecoin company that recently raised $12 million in its Series A funding round led by Dragonfly, has announced that it will launch its AUSD token natively on Sui. The company aims to produce a better stablecoin focusing on emerging markets, and sharing the revenue obtained with partners integrating AUSD in their services platforms. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Should Join UK in ‘Blockchain Sandbox’ Free of Regulatory Meddling, SEC Commissioner Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233170</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233170/blockchain-regulatory-sandbox-us-uk-hester-peirce-unikely"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Commissioner Hester Peirce says a safe space for blockchain experimentation could foster better crypto regulations—but experts doubt it will happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Whales Just Went On A 700 Million DOGE Shopping Spree]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fc934f7</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-whales-700-million-doge-shopping-spree/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data reveals the Dogecoin whales have participated in a significant amount of net buying during the last three days.
 
Dogecoin Whales Have Seen Their Holdings Rise Recently
 
As explained by analyst Ali Martinez in a post on X, DOGE whales have just shown a large amount of accumulation. The on-chain metric of interest here is the “Supply Distribution” from the analytics firm Santiment, which keeps track of the total amount of the Dogecoin supply that the various wallet groups are holding right now.
 
The addresses or investors are divided into these cohorts based on the number of coins that they are carrying in their balance currently. The 1 to 10 coins group, for example, includes all addresses that own between 1 and 10 DOGE. If the Supply Distribution is applied to this group, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian Artist Davido’s Meme Coin Plummets Shortly After He Pockets $474,000 From Token Sale]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fcb0f40</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerian-artist-davidos-meme-coin-plummets-shortly-after-he-pockets-474000-from-token-sale/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigerian artist Davido has been accused of perpetrating an “outright scam” after pocketing over $468,000 from selling his recently launched meme coin. A prominent Nigerian crypto enthusiast claims Davido’s actions create problems for many legitimate crypto businesses and startups operating in good faith. Davido Offloads Meme Coin Hours After Promoting It to Followers The Nigerian […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Ethereum Meme Coin Price Hits New High After Post-Verdict Dip]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233310</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233310/trump-ethereum-meme-coin-price-new-high"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Donald Trump-themed MAGA meme coin surged late Thursday after a short-lived crash prompted by his “hush money” trial verdict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Postpones Protocol Upgrade Vote; UNI Tumbles 9%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741fb6cb1c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/31/uniswap-postpones-protocol-upgrade-vote-uni-tumbles-9/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "fee-switch" vote was supposed to take place today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Bitcoin Game Boy’ Gets a Runes Makeover—Here’s How to Win One]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233296</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233296/bitcoin-game-boy-runes-makeover-giveaway"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BitBoy One is a Bitcoin-centric gaming handheld, and a new limited-edition Runes model gives it a sleek overhaul.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Notcoin? Telegram-Based Game ‘Hamster Kombat’ to Launch Token on TON]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233287/next-notcoin-telegram-game-hamster-kombat-open-network-token"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat, another tap-to-earn game akin to Notcoin—and based around a hamster CEO—is launching a token on The Open Network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Meta Disclose Their AI Tools Were Used for Political Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233249</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233249/openai-meta-disclose-ai-tools-political-disinformation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T16:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI giants both revealed this week how their tools have been enlisted in China, Israel, Russia, and Iran to spread political disinformation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Accuses SEC of 'Purposeful Effort to Destroy' Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233279</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233279/coinbase-accuses-sec-purposeful-effort-destroy-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a legal filing on Friday, America's leading crypto exchange accused the SEC of trying to snuff out crypto by refusing to make new rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Exchange DMM Bitcoin Hacked for $308 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233283</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233283/japanese-exchange-dmm-bitcoin-hacked-308-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exploit against Japanese exchange DMM Bitcoin is one of the largest to hit the crypto industry in years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: JAM Upgrade Passes in Near-Unanimous Vote]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233042</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233042/the-week-in-polkadot-jam-upgrade-passes-in-near-unanimous-vote"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Polkadot community has spoken, with the network's proposed JAM upgrade getting an almost unanimous vote of approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK Trademark Fight: Competitors Demand Matter Labs Withdraw Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233226/zk-trademark-fight-competitors-demand-matter-labs-withdraw-application"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matter Labs, developer of zkSync technology, has faced criticism for its attempt to register the term "ZK" as a trademark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum Is About to Unlock $250 Million in Funds for Ethereum Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233082</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233082/arbitrum-unlock-250-million-funds-ethereum-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T14:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum holders are strongly supporting a program that’s devised to boost gaming on Ethereum layer-2 network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, JasmyCoin Does Not Have a Partnership With Apple—But Its Token Is Still Pumping]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233229/no-jasmycoin-does-not-have-a-partnership-with-apple-but-its-token-is-still-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T12:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Apple announced it’ll be integrating Japan’s My Number feature into its iPhones, investors believed JasmyCoin was part of the deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra Coins LUNA and LUNC Rise After Do Kwon SEC Settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233218/terra-luna-lunc-rise-do-kwon-sec-settlement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Terra founder Do Kwon and Terraform Labs reached a tentative settlement with the SEC in their civil fraud case Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trial Begins for $575 Million HashFlare Crypto Mining Fraud Defendants]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233217/trial-begins-for-575-million-hashflare-crypto-mining-fraud-defendants"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two men linked to $575 Million HashFlare crypto mining fraud had their first court appearance yesterday in Seattle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. ‘Delighted’ Trump Is Now Pro Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233155</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233155/robert-f-kennedy-jr-delighted-trump-is-now-pro-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T23:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I’m not a fan of Trump’s,” Kennedy noted after the Trump trial verdict was announced, but said blockchain can defend Americans against “dystopian” AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Still Favored by Crypto Bettors to Win Election, Despite Guilty Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233148</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233148/trump-verdict-election-win-odds-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People putting money on Trump's political future on Polymarket don't seem to think much has changed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON Market Cap Plunges by Billions After Fixing Inflated Supply Data]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233113/ton-market-cap-plunges-billions-fixing-inflated-supply-data"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market capitalization of Toncoin (TON) dropped by billions of dollars after The Open Network updated its circulating supply data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Meme Coins Plunge After He's Found Guilty on 34 Felony Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233146</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233146/trump-meme-coins-plunge-after-hes-found-guilty-on-34-felony-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T21:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MAGA (TRUMP) and other tokens inspired by Donald Trump are down bad after the former U.S. president's "hush money" trial ended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Enthusiasts Are ‘Not Psychopaths’, New Research Concludes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233091/bitcoin-investors-not-psychopaths-canadian-research-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T19:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A forthcoming study of 500 Canadian Bitcoin investors found them to be financially literate and emotionally stable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlyn Jenner Solana Meme Coin Crashes After Launching Ethereum Token to Support Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233084</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233084/caitlyn-jenner-solana-meme-coin-crashes-ethereum-donald-trump"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T19:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Caitlyn Jenner token on Ethereum takes a fee to support Donald Trump's presidential ambitions—but the Solana coin has plummeted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Superfan Elon Musk Says He ‘Never Discussed Crypto With Trump’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233063/elon-musk-donald-trump-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T18:28:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the former president’s pivot to embrace cryptocurrency, the Tesla CEO denies a report that they’ve talked about crypto policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Final Fantasy’ Maker Square Enix Moves to Arbitrum for Ethereum Game NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233069/symbiogenesis-square-enix-arbitrum-ethereum-game-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T17:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix is jumping to Ethereum layer-2 Arbitrum for the next NFT character mint for its Symbiogenesis blockchain game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Pay? Every Good Thing About OpenAI's GPT-4o Is Now Free]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233032</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233032/why-pay-every-good-thing-about-gpt-4o-free"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T17:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plus and Free are now equally capable. Does it make any sense for you to keep a paid subscription?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Startup Babylon Raises $70 Million to Bring BTC Staking to Ethereum and Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233029/bitcoin-startup-babylon-raises-70-million-btc-staking-ethereum-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Babylon, a startup working to enable native Bitcoin staking on chains like Ethereum and Solana, just raised $70 million towards that goal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Kwon and Terraform Labs Settle With SEC Over LUNA, TerraUSD Fraud Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233039</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233039/do-kwon-terraform-labs-settle-sec-luna-terrausd-fraud"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup behind the collapsed LUNA and TerraUSD coins is settling with the SEC over fraud charges, a court filing revealed Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Meme Coins Surge as DOG's 85% Jump Calms Fears That 'Runes Are Dead']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233027/bitcoin-meme-coins-surge-calms-fears-runes-dead"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As some Bitcoin-based meme coins glitter with gains, a dog-themed token pushes back on claims that Runes hype has faded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pudgy Penguins Mobile Game Coming to Mythos Chain on Polkadot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233026/pudgy-penguins-mobile-game-polkadot-mythos-chain"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFL Rivals and Blankos Block Party creator Mythical Games is developing the Pudgy Penguins mobile game to launch in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink and Circle Want to Help Institutions Use Stablecoins and DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233024</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233024/chainlink-circle-institutions-defi-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership is aimed at "moving the industry forward and growing the adoption of tokenized assets," a Chainlink exec told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DeFi Projects Still Favorite Target for Hackers, But Stolen Funds Down 28% in May: Immunefi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233016</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233016/ethereum-defi-projects-still-favorite-target-for-hackers-but-stolen-funds-down-28-in-may-immunefi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors have lost $473 million since the beginning of the year to hacks and frauds, a decrease of 20% from last year during the same period.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 122 - ETH ETF MOVES CLOSER!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs move closer to approval, drop staking. Blackrock ETF see biggest inflow in 6 weeks. Grayscale ETH discount narrows under 10%. BTC & ETH heading for ATH: StanChart. Banana zone squared coming for ETH: Raoul Pal. Trump accepts crypto donations including DOGE. Pelosi mulls support of crypto bill. Farcaster raises $150M, DEGEN up 20%. Coinbase to launch gold & oil futures trading. Uniswap ‘ready to fight’ against SEC. Vitalik proposes solutions to MEV problems. Phantom may soon support email sign-up. Jupiter announces initiative to tokenise RWAs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 120 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL again leads majors, DEX volume dwarfs others. BTC whales buys $106M in 24hrs. ETH ETF decision on Thursday or Friday. 5 of 7 onchain indicators ‘point to bull-run’. ETH ETF may be rejected due to weak link to futures. AI coins in focus ahead of Nvidia earnings. Cobie inks new article on low float, high FDV coins. ETH foundation staff reveal links to EigenLayer. 12 L2 & L3s controlled by single multisig. Layer Zero pauses sybil rewards. Aevo to airdrop pre-launch tokens on platform. FTM to migrate one-to-one to Sonic S coin. UK judge rules Craig Wright is not Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 119 - GOOD MORNING BULLS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher again, BTC stable. ETFs see $257M inflow, volumes hit 2 month high. 414 holders of BlackRock ETF ‘blows away record’. SOL continues to be fastest blockage despite usage. Pump. fun exploited for $1.9M by ex-employee. LINK up 20% after partnership with top banks. Senate also repeals SEC crypto rule. US Senator uses laser eyes PFP. Tether mints another $1B USDT. Bitcoin production costs now $45K: JP Morgan. Pink Drainer retires after stealing $85m assets. PancakeSwap to reimburse fees on Uniswap. TON & Tether partnership on payment solution. Trabucco writes character defence of Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 118 - ARE THE ETFS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has best day in 2 months after dovish CPI. ETFs see $300M inflow, highest in weeks. ETH continues to underperform ahead of ETF ruling. Millennium buys $2B of BTC ETF. CME group to launch BTC spot trading. Fed’s Kashkari compares BTC to beanie babies. Tate says he will buy $100M BTC. El Salvador now owns 5750 BTC. Binance creates ‘antidote’ to address poisoning. Tornado Cash developer appeals conviction. China busts $1.9B USDT banking racket. MEV bot operators charged with fraud by DoJ. Swiss to adopt global crypto tax rules. FTX repayments create ‘bullish overhang’ for crypto. SEI up 30% after proposing v2 upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 117 - BITCOIN GAINS ON CPI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces driven by spot buying. US ETF sees $100M+ inflow for first time in weeks. State of Wisconsin buys $170M of BTC ETF. Vanguard appoints Bitcoin friendly CEO. Coinbase sees billions of BTC leave exchange. BTC to consolidate between $55-75K: Novogratz. SOL beats ETH TEV for first time ever. ETH may be labelled a security by SEC next week. AI & memes the only two positive sectors this week. Crypto hostility led by TradFi: Lubin. Tornado Cash developer guilty of money laundering. Circle shifts legal hope to US ahead of IPO. Cypher developer gambled $300K of customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 116 - ROARING KITTY RETURNS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, stays in range ahead of CPI tomorrow. US ETFs see small net inflow led by Fidelity HK ETFs wipe 2 weeks of inflows in a single day. Bracebridge bought $363m of BTC ETFs. Coinbase has system wide outage. Poloniex hacker sends funds to Tornado Cash. Brazil biggest in LATAM for crypto trading. Biden removes China BTC miner near military base. CertiK patches $5m flaw in Aptos bridge. LayerZero sees 100k bot accounts self-report. DYDX CEO set to leave. Tate sells $500k BTC to buy GME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With  Roger Dickerman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T14:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and founder of the 24 Hours of Art, Roger Dickerman. We dive into Roger’s background in trading and fitness, his love of art, founding Artifex and 24 Hours of Art, the power of routines, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Funghi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and co-founder of Shillr, Funghibull. Funghi is one of our favorite collectors, builders and overall people in the space. 

We dive into Funghi’s background playing rugby, going to medical school in Scotland, 10 gram mushroom trips, finding punks, forming Shillr, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Breaks Down Solana Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains what happened during Solana's Q1 2024 network congestion through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Explains the Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains the recent Bitcoin halving and how you can build your understanding through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Neighbor Alice Season 1 Beta Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator Orangie plays the new season of multiplayer builder-game My Neighbor Alice and tries out all its features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>