<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-22T07:16:14.788Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-22T07:16:14.788Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin To Hit $90,000 ‘Sooner Rather Than Later’ if This Happens, Says Crypto Analyst Kevin Svenson]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612922/Bitcoin-To-Hit-90000-Sooner-Rather-Than-Later-if-This-Happens-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Kevin-Svenson</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612922/Bitcoin-To-Hit-90000-Sooner-Rather-Than-Later-if-This-Happens-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Kevin-Svenson"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T07:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Kevin Svenson is outlining a path forward for Bitcoin (BTC) amid the flagship cryptocurrency correcting by around 11% over the past two weeks from the June high of around $72,000. In a new video, Svenson tells his 78,400 YouTube subscribers that even though the price of Bitcoin has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21 Million Chainlink Worth $295M Unlocked From Its Non-Circulating Supply]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612901/21-Million-Chainlink-Worth-295M-Unlocked-From-Its-Non-Circulating-Supply</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612901/21-Million-Chainlink-Worth-295M-Unlocked-From-Its-Non-Circulating-Supply"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Spot On Chain monitoring, 21 Million LINK was unlocked from Chainlink’s non-circulating supply contract worth $295 million. 18.25 million LINK worth $264 million was transferred to Binance and 2.25 million LINK worth $31.3 million was transferred to a multi-signature wallet address...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pantera Raising Funds For New Investment In TON]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612900/Pantera-Raising-Funds-For-New-Investment-In-TON</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612900/Pantera-Raising-Funds-For-New-Investment-In-TON"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto venture capital firm Pantera Capital is raising funds for a new investment in The Open Network’s Toncoin. Dubbed the ‘Pantera TON Investment Opportunity’, it is aimed at purchasing more TON tokens. Pantera is inviting potential investors to participate in the funding round. Investors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU and Beyond: How MiCA Can Balance Innovation, Compliance, and Crypto’s Future]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612888/The-EU-and-Beyond-How-MiCA-Can-Balance-Innovation-Compliance-and-Cryptos-Future</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612888/The-EU-and-Beyond-How-MiCA-Can-Balance-Innovation-Compliance-and-Cryptos-Future"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Markets in Crypto-Assets (MiCA) regulation marks a significant turning point for the crypto industry within the European Union (EU). As these new regulations come into force, crypto companies are poised to navigate both challenges and opportunities. In an exclusive interview with BeInCrypto,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins’ $2M Bitcoin Bet on Trump Hits Legal Limit, Partial Refund Issued]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612898/Winklevoss-Twins-2M-Bitcoin-Bet-on-Trump-Hits-Legal-Limit-Partial-Refund-Issued</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612898/Winklevoss-Twins-2M-Bitcoin-Bet-on-Trump-Hits-Legal-Limit-Partial-Refund-Issued"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a recent Bloomberg report by Stephanie Lai and Bill Allison, Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, the billionaire twins known for their cryptocurrency ventures, have made substantial Bitcoin donations to Donald Trump’s presidential campaign. Bloomberg notes that these donations exceeded...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Monthly Active Addresses Hit Record High Amid ETF Buzz]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612885/Solanas-Monthly-Active-Addresses-Hit-Record-High-Amid-ETF-Buzz</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612885/Solanas-Monthly-Active-Addresses-Hit-Record-High-Amid-ETF-Buzz"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana has achieved a major milestone with over 30 million monthly active addresses, setting a new all-time high. This surge coincides with digital asset manager 3iQ’s groundbreaking application to list a Solana-based exchange-traded fund (ETF) on the Toronto Stock Exchange (TSE). This potential...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could See 18% Decline, Predicts Crypto Analyst: Plunge 'More Likely Now' With $54K A Possibility]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612902/Bitcoin-Could-See-18-Decline-Predicts-Crypto-Analyst-Plunge-More-Likely-Now-With-54K-A-Possibility</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612902/Bitcoin-Could-See-18-Decline-Predicts-Crypto-Analyst-Plunge-More-Likely-Now-With-54K-A-Possibility"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Justin Bennett has cautioned that Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) could potentially plummet to significantly lower levels. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Development in Ethereum ETFs: They’re About to Begin Trading – Here’s the Latest Information]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612873/Critical-Development-in-Ethereum-ETFs-Theyre-About-to-Begin-Trading-Heres-the-Latest-Information</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612873/Critical-Development-in-Ethereum-ETFs-Theyre-About-to-Begin-Trading-Heres-the-Latest-Information"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the developments required for Ethereum ETFs to be opened for trading is finally over. Here are the analysts' statements. Continue Reading: Critical Development in Ethereum ETFs: They’re About to Begin Trading – Here’s the Latest Information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Disputes Ruling, Reasserts XRP’s Non-Security Status]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612884/Ripple-CEO-Disputes-Ruling-Reasserts-XRPs-Non-Security-Status</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612884/Ripple-CEO-Disputes-Ruling-Reasserts-XRPs-Non-Security-Status"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Brad Garlinghouse countered the most recent court ruling which questioned XRP’s status as a non-security, reaffirming his stance and clarifying the implications for the ongoing lawsuit. In a recent development in the Ripple lawsuit, Judge Hamilton allowed the charge of “misleading...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perplexity’s AI Chatbot: Why Wired Magazine Calls It a ‘BS Machine’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612860/Perplexitys-AI-Chatbot-Why-Wired-Magazine-Calls-It-a-BS-Machine</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612860/Perplexitys-AI-Chatbot-Why-Wired-Magazine-Calls-It-a-BS-Machine"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 21, 2024, Katie Drummond, Wired’s global editorial director, joined CNBC’s “Squawk Box” to discuss the magazine’s recent in-depth investigation into the AI search startup Perplexity. The conversation shed light on some troubling aspects of Perplexity’s operations and raised important...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogwifhat (WIF) Memecoin Plunges 50% In Valuation This Month!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612854/Dogwifhat-WIF-Memecoin-Plunges-50-In-Valuation-This-Month</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612854/Dogwifhat-WIF-Memecoin-Plunges-50-In-Valuation-This-Month"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana-based memecoin started the month of June with a price tag of around $3.8. Reportedly, the WIF coin price has recorded a correction of approximately 50% to its portfolio over the past three weeks, resulting in it hovering close to its important support level of $1.80. Further, with its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Discussion, June 22, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612849/Daily-Discussion-June-22-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612849/Daily-Discussion-June-22-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:04:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please utilize this sticky thread for all general Bitcoin discussions! If you see posts on the front page or /r/Bitcoin/new which are better suited for this daily discussion thread, please help out by directing the OP to this thread instead. Thank you! If you don't get an answer to your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto News Today: Mixed Signals as Market Volatility Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612817/Crypto-News-Today-Mixed-Signals-as-Market-Volatility-Surges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612817/Crypto-News-Today-Mixed-Signals-as-Market-Volatility-Surges"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Fidelity, and six others amended S-1 filings for Ethereum ETFs, awaiting SEC approval. The Winklevoss brothers returned $311,400 to Trump's campaign, surpassing the legal limit with their $1 million Bitcoin donation. Crypto Fear and Greed Index:Crypto Fear and Greed Indicator shows 53...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview with David Schwartz, Chief Technology Officer at Ripple, the crypto company behind XRP]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612826/Interview-with-David-Schwartz-Chief-Technology-Officer-at-Ripple-the-crypto-company-behind-XRP</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612826/Interview-with-David-Schwartz-Chief-Technology-Officer-at-Ripple-the-crypto-company-behind-XRP"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cryptonomist interviewed the CTO on the occasion of the APEX conference held in Amsterdam in June a few weeks ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RemindMe! 9 months]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612833/RemindMe-9-months</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612833/RemindMe-9-months"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by   /u/cocoon_eclosion_moth [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Falls to Lowest Level in a Month – Where is the Next Support?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612866/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-as-BTC-Falls-to-Lowest-Level-in-a-Month-Where-is-the-Next-Support</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612866/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-as-BTC-Falls-to-Lowest-Level-in-a-Month-Where-is-the-Next-Support"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price prediction focuses on BTC's fall to $64,295, with recent ETF outflows and economic data influencing support levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNNY.COM: Impact of Regulatory Changes on Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612723/DNNYCOM-Impact-of-Regulatory-Changes-on-Crypto-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612723/DNNYCOM-Impact-of-Regulatory-Changes-on-Crypto-Market"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once the speciality of a tech fan, digital currency has made considerable progress to where it is now a worldwide pervasion in financial impact, taking everything into account from funds to craftsmanship. As it grows, the crypto market captures the imagination of governments and regulatory...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Vs Nigeria: US Lawmakers Call For Release Of Detained Exec After Prison Visit]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740822618f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-vs-nigeria-us-lawmakers-call-for-release-of-detained-exec-after-prison-visit/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US lawmakers continue to call for the release of the detained Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan. The ongoing saga between the crypto exchange and the Nigerian authorities intensified when several US Congress members sent a letter urging the Biden administration to take action.
 
 
This week, two US representatives visited Gamabaryan in prison during their trip to Nigeria. The politicians shared details about the executive’s alarming condition and urged for his “humanitarian release.”
 
US Lawmakers Continue To Call For Action
 
On Thursday, US representatives French Hill and Chrissy Houlahan called for the immediate liberation of former federal agent Tigran Gambaryan. Gambaryan was detained, alongside his colleague Nadeem Anjarwalla, by Nigerian authorities on February 26 and was accused …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington State Regulator Warns Investors of Pig Butchering Crypto Scheme]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7408227cc0</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/washington-state-regulator-warns-investors-of-pig-butchering-crypto-scheme/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington State Department of Financial Institutions (DFI) issued a warning on Thursday after it received a complaint from a Washington investor about Fameex, now offline. The investor, a real estate agent, met scammer “Jackson Qie” via an unsolicited text. Qie convinced him to invest over $113,000 in ether (ETH) and tether (USDT) on Fameex. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will There Be an Altcoin Season in 2024? Expert Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612714/Will-There-Be-an-Altcoin-Season-in-2024-Expert-Analysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612714/Will-There-Be-an-Altcoin-Season-in-2024-Expert-Analysis"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sentiment around altcoins remains cautious. Despite Bitcoin nearing all-time highs and the resurgence of meme coins, retail interest in altcoins has been subdued. Here’s one analyst navigating the possible loopholes in the current altcoin cycle in 2024. Renowned analyst Miles Deutscher...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners are treading water, but no alarms of a 'total firesale']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612712/Bitcoin-miners-are-treading-water-but-no-alarms-of-a-total-firesale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612712/Bitcoin-miners-are-treading-water-but-no-alarms-of-a-total-firesale"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners are not “full-scale bear market level capitulating,” according to a crypto analyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price prediction – Is $61,000 BTC’s next target on the charts?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612700/Bitcoin-price-prediction-Is-61000-BTCs-next-target-on-the-charts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19612700/Bitcoin-price-prediction-Is-61000-BTCs-next-target-on-the-charts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T05:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the how and why of Bitcoin's short-term future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cantor Fitzgerald CEO Props up Stablecoins in the Fight for US Dollar Hegemony]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7408286908</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cantor-fitzgerald-ceo-props-up-stablecoins-in-the-fight-for-us-dollar-hegemony/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T04:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howard Lutnick, CEO of financial services company Cantor Fitzgerald, highlighted the value of stablecoins in the fight to maintain the hegemony of the U.S. dollar. Lutnick stated that fully redeemable stablecoins allowed citizens in emerging markets to use their digital dollars for commerce, stabilizing the demand and relevance of the currency. Cantor Fitzgerald CEO: The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Will Bitcoin Recover? Top Analyst Says This]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740829ef4a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/when-will-bitcoin-recover-top-analyst-says-this/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T04:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analyst explained that Bitcoin has historically seen recovery from bearish phases like the one the cryptocurrency is going through.
 
Bitcoin Hash Ribbons Show Miner Capitulation Is Ongoing
 
In a new post on X, analyst Willy Woo has discussed the relevance of the Bitcoin hashrate to the asset’s price recovery. The “hashrate” refers to a measure of the total computing power the miners have currently connected to the network.
 
The trend in this metric can be viewed as a representation of the situation among these chain validators. When the indicator rises, it suggests that miners are finding the chain attractive to mine on right now.
 
 
On the other hand, a decline in the metric implies some miners have decided to disconnect from the network, potentially because they are currently find…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US State Regulator Shares Key Crypto Investment Tips for Seniors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74082ade99</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-state-regulator-shares-key-crypto-investment-tips-for-seniors/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T03:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tennessee Department of Commerce & Insurance (TDCI) Division of Securities is raising awareness about the potential risks of investing in unregulated products like cryptocurrency, particularly among seniors. TDCI Commissioner Carter Lawrence emphasized the importance of protecting the financial independence of Tennessee’s elder population and encouraged seniors, their loved ones, or caregivers to contact the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Surges 1,166% In One Day As Activity Spikes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740816c367</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-1166/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T03:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a positive turn of events, the Shiba Inu burn rate has seen another notable spike. This time around, the activity, meaning the number of addresses participating in the burns, has seen a notable increase and the burned tokens have risen by over 1,100% in one day.
 
Shiba Inu 1,166% Spike In Burn Rate
 
According to Shibburn, the official website for tracking the total amount of SHIB tokens burned each day, the Shiba Inu burn rate has seen a 1,166% spike. This spike is significant as it shows an increased willingness among Shiba Inu investors to burn tokens.
 
 
In the 24-hour period, a total of 35.29 million tokens have been burned, which is a marked difference from the previous day’s figures. However, what might be more important is the number of burn transactions that have been recorded in the 24-hour timeframe.
 
Shibburn’s data shows that there has been a total of 12 burn transactions from holders in the last day. This is a welcome change from the average of six burn transactions that have been recorded over this week. Notable burns have also been recorded across a number of transactions instead of concentrated to just one or two transactions only.
 
For example, the highest burn transaction during this time was a wallet which sent a little over 10 million tokens to the burn address. Then there are seven transactions carrying between 2 million and 5.5 million tokens to the address. While the rest of the transactions were carrying much lower volumes.
 
This spike in the burn rate follows a positive trend that began this week. On June 18, Bitcoinist reported that the Shiba Inu burn rate had seen a 5,569% spike. This comes after a notable stretch of time with muted burn performances, making this a positive turn in the tide.
 
 
Elsewhere, more specifically, the daily trading volume, Shiba Inu is performing poorly compared to its burn rate. The daily volume is down 14.22% and sitting at $270 million. In the same vein, the price is seeing daily losses of 0.71% and down 15.17% in the last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise CIO Makes the Case for Adding Ether to Investment Portfolios]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740817af41</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitwise-cio-makes-the-case-for-adding-ether-to-investment-portfolios/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T02:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Hougan, CIO of Bitwise, a crypto-based index fund and ETF provider, has explained why he believes ether might be an interesting asset for an investment portfolio. Hougan states three key reasons for investing in ether: diversification to “own the market,” different use cases than bitcoin, and historical analysis. Bitwise CIO Presents Three Reasons to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese Hackers Indicted in US for $71M Cybercrime Involving Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740811ff88</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/vietnamese-hackers-indicted-in-us-for-71m-cybercrime-involving-cryptocurrency/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T02:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four Vietnamese nationals were charged in a U.S. court for a series of cyber intrusions causing over $71 million in losses. The defendants, part of the cybercrime group “FIN9,” allegedly hacked U.S. companies from May 2018 to October 2021, stealing non-public information, employee benefits, and funds. They used stolen personal and credit card information to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Fraud Alert: Melbourne Man Gets Jail Time for Fake ID Exchange Scam — Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74081db543</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-fraud-alert-melbourne-man-jail-time-fake-id/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T01:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a landmark ruling, an Australian man has received a two-year prison term for committing identity theft and fraudulently setting up cryptocurrency exchange accounts.
 
This case, adjudicated at the Melbourne County Court on June 17, underscores the increasing intersection of cybercrime and cryptocurrency in modern financial systems.
 
 
Cybercrime Meets Severe Penalties
 
The convicted, a 31-year-old from Melbourne, a city in Australia, was involved in using forged documents to create online accounts for trading cryptocurrencies.
 
His apprehension followed a comprehensive probe spearheaded by the Australian Federal Police (AFP), “Operation Stonefish,” which began in August 2022.
 
This operation was initiated in response to UK authorities’ investigation into a website that provided spoo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montenegro Prime Minister Listed Among Top Terraform Labs Investors in SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74081e089b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/montenegro-prime-minister-listed-among-top-terraform-labs-investors-in-sec-filing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T01:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milojko Spajic, Prime Minister of Montenegro, was revealed as an early investor in Terraform Labs, co-founded by Kwon Do-hyung (Do Kwon). A filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) lists Spajic as the 16th investor in Terraform Labs, purchasing 750,000 luna coins at 10 cents each in April 2018. This revelation raises concerns […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Founders Donate $2 Million in Bitcoin to Donald Trump to End Biden’s ‘War on Crypto’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740819cc4c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gemini-founders-donate-2-million-in-bitcoin-to-donald-trump-to-end-bidens-war-on-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T00:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Gemini’s co-founders, Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss, have donated $1 million each in bitcoin to Donald Trump’s presidential campaign. Tyler criticized the Biden administration for allegedly weaponizing government agencies, as well as the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), against the crypto industry. Cameron echoed these sentiments, declaring Trump as the pro-bitcoin, pro-crypto, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Can’t Write a Good Joke, Google Researchers Find]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236599/ai-comedy-humor-study-censorship"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T00:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working comedians used artificial intelligence to develop material, and found it to be “the most bland, boring thing.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin Shoot To $100,000 Amid An Unfolding Banking Crisis In The US?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e740804f36a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-100000-unfolding-banking-crisis-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T00:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin might be weak at spot rates, sliding roughly 13% from $74,800 amid intense liquidation pressure. 
 
Even as prices retract from all-time highs and $66,000 proves to be a mirage, analysts are upbeat about what lies ahead. Most expect the coin to surge towards the all-important psychological line, $100,000, in the coming days or weeks.
 
 
A Banking Crisis In The United States?
 
The spike would be accelerated by Bitcoin riding on the “digital gold” narrative that’s quickly gaining traction amid growing concerns about the financial health of banks in the United States. 
 
 
Taking to X, one observer notes a Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC) report shows that 68 banks in the United States are sitting on over $500 billion in unrealized losses. Most of these losses in their d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Clarifies XRP Is Not a Security After New Court Ruling]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7408008246</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ripple-clarifies-xrp-is-not-a-security-after-new-court-ruling/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T23:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s chief legal officer has clarified that a California district judge has dismissed all allegations that Ripple violated federal securities laws. He stressed that District Judge Analisa Torres’ ruling regarding the non-security status of XRP “stands undisturbed.” New York’s ‘Ruling That XRP Is Not a Security Stands Undisturbed’ Following the ruling by the U.S. District […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Touts Ripple To Be The Next Amazon And Facebook Despite Poor XRP Performance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74080c4057</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-next-amazon-facebook/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T22:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto analyst has predicted that cryptocurrency payments company, Ripple could be the next high-valuation company, similar to Amazon and Facebook. This prediction comes as XRP witnesses poor performance amidst market volatility and Ripple’s ongoing court battle with the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). 
 
Analyst Predicts Ripple Emerging As Billion-Dollar Start-Up
 
The host of the AllinCrypto YouTube channel has released a new video, underscoring Ripple’s future outlook and its ability to become a billion-dollar company. The analyst has expressed confidence that the United States will adopt Ripple as a “unicorn company” just like e-commerce and tech giants like Amazon, Apple, Facebook and Microsoft. 
 
 
The analyst also disclosed that Ripple was on a similar gro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Highlights Risks of ETH Staking Restrictions in Latest SEC Disclosure]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74080c4be7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/grayscale-highlights-risks-of-eth-staking-restrictions-in-latest-sec-disclosure/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T22:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to supplemental disclosures in Grayscale’s Ethereum Trust 8-K report, submitted to the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on June 20, the trust’s inability to utilize its ethereum for staking services places its shares at a “comparative disadvantage.” Grayscale: Ethereum Trust Strategy Could be Impacted by Staking Limitations While multiple exchange-traded fund (ETF) issuers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s Big AI Upgrades Won't Launch in the EU This Year: Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236578</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236578/apple-ai-features-held-back-from-european-union"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T22:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's AI features are not coming to the European Union as the tech giant says it won't “compromise the integrity of our products.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[50 Cent's Twitter Hacked to Promote Solana Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236572/50-cent-twitter-hacked-solana-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T21:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get rich and lie tryin'.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Why Altcoin Investors Struggle Despite Bitcoin, Ether Sitting Near Yearly Highs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74080b49a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/21/this-is-why-altcoin-investors-struggle-despite-bitcoin-ether-sitting-near-yearly-highs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T21:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Constantly diluting supply with token unlocks, selling pressure from venture funds, lack of fresh inflows to crypto and seasonal trends all contributed to the brutal drawdown in altcoin prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foundry Unveils New Hardware Suite Targeting Institutional Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409f4877b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/foundry-unveils-new-hardware-suite-targeting-institutional-bitcoin-mining/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T21:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foundry Digital LLC has launched a new suite of products aimed at enhancing institutional bitcoin mining operations. Dubbed Foundry Hardware, this initiative introduces specialized equipment designed to improve mining system efficiencies and reliability. Foundry’s New Suite Aims to Optimize Institutional Cryptocurrency Mining Foundry Hardware‘s offerings include power supply units, immersion optimization kits, and control boards […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Turnaround: Analyst Predicts Greater Bull Reversal, New ATH Looms?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409f60a94</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/analyst-predicts-greater-bitcoin-bull-reversal/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T21:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues to experience significant gloomy price movement, fueling a broader negative sentiment in the entire cryptocurrency market, which has led to heightened uncertainties among investors and traders. Despite this pessimistic movement in the past few days, popular cryptocurrency analyst and trader Javon Marks investigating Bitcoin’s price action has predicted an impending much greater bull reversal, leading to a new all-time high before 2024 closes.
 
Bitcoin Gearing Up For A Massive Bull Rebound
 
Javon Mark’s prognosis emphasizes the crypto asset’s recent break out from a falling wedge pattern potentially signaling the conclusion of the current bearish phase and paving the way for a substantial upward momentum.
 
 
Market analysts have been keeping a careful eye on the Falling…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can the New Claude AI 3.5 Sonnet Model Beat ChatGPT-4o?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236516/claude-ai-sonnet-comparison-chatgpt-4o-anthropic"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T21:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic says its Claude 3.5 Sonnet release is faster, cheaper, and beats OpenAI's latest model on most benchmarks. We put them to a head-to-head test.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech Giant Flutterwave Partners With Nigerian Anti-Graft Body to Launch Cybercrime Center]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409f27bc2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fintech-giant-flutterwave-partners-with-nigerian-anti-graft-body-to-launch-cybercrime-center/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T20:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutterwave, a Nigerian fintech startup, has partnered with the Economic and Financial Crimes Commission (EFCC) to establish a cybercrime research center. This strategic initiative aims to intensify the fight against internet crime, enhance the security of business transactions, and provide opportunities for Nigerian youth. The partnership was formalized through a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) signed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Campaign Gets A Crypto Kick: $1 Million Bitcoin From Winklevoss Twins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7409fd4c97</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/trump-gets-1m-bitcoin-from-winklevoss-twins/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T20:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a bold political move, the Winklevoss twins, renowned for their early investment in Bitcoin and co-founding the cryptocurrency exchange Gemini, have each contributed $1 million in Bitcoin to the reelection campaign of former President Donald Trump, Reuters reported. This hefty endorsement highlights a significant intersection between the worlds of cryptocurrency and politics, raising eyebrows and stirring debates on both fronts.
 
 
Crypto Kings Endorse Trump
 
Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss are no strangers to making headlines. This time, they’ve done it by diving into the political arena, backing a candidate who once called Bitcoin a scam but has since rebranded himself as the ‘Crypto President.’ Each twin sent 15.47 BTC, translating to about $1 million, to bolster Trump’s campaign effo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Cipher Guide: How to Use Morse Code to Earn a Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hamster-kombat-daily-cipher-guide-morse-codeearn-million-free-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T19:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now there’s another way to rack up free coins ahead of the Hamster Kombat airdrop. Here’s how to do it and where to find the latest code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Soar Thanks to Failing Japanese Banks, Says Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236507/bitcoin-will-soar-thanks-to-failing-japanese-banks-says-arthur-hayes"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T19:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freshly printed U.S. dollars will be needed, so “buy the fucking dip,” he urges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Watches Can Help Detect Parkinson’s Disease Earlier: Study]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236418</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236418/apple-watch-early-detection-parkinsons-disease"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T18:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[”Off-the-shelf” wearables linked to a smartphone app could be useful in measuring disease progression, according to new research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tor Constantino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Fighting Game 'AI Arena' Sets NRN Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236491</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236491/ethereum-fighting-game-ai-arena-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T18:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a play-to-airdrop campaign this spring, Ethereum fighting game AI Arena is nearing its NRN token launch. Here's when it'll happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Slides Amid Options Chaos With Roaring Kitty MIA]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236500</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236500/gamestop-stock-slides-options-chaos-roaring-kitty-mia"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GME shares kept ticking down Friday amid increased volatility around GameStop options and a continued no-show from influencer Roaring Kitty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacmoon Almost Solved Crypto’s SocialFi Problem—Then Elon Musk Crushed It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236455</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236455/pacmoon-blast-crypto-socialfi-problem-elon-musk-crushed"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blast meme coin Pacmoon appeared to solve a key problem that’s vexed crypto for years. The future was limitless—until a Twitter update undid everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 143 - CRYPTO TRENDS LOWER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dvJof6CV/fomo-hour-143-crypto-trends-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dvJof6CV/fomo-hour-143-crypto-trends-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto sinks, ETFs see another $140m outflow. German government likely sells $195m more BTC. 100 day BTC break-out coming: Don Alt. SOL ETF applied for in Canada. Rumours SEC case vs Coinbase also dropped. Standard Chatered setup spot trading desk. ARB has record daily revenue on LayerZero claims. CFTC investigating Jump Crypto. FTM outperforms ahead of Sonic upgrade. Binance integrates USDT on TON. Onchain prediction market TVL continues to soar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Week in Polkadot: $60 Million JAM Prize Fund Open for Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236430</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236430/the-week-in-polkadot-60-million-jam-prize-fund-open-for-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T14:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot developers ready to tackle the JAM implementation challenge will be eligible for up to $60m in prizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team Liquid, Community Gaming Plot Tournaments With USDC Payouts on Base]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236424</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236424/team-liquid-community-gaming-plot-tournaments-usdc-base"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teamfight Tactics and Hearthstone tournaments will pay players a total of $20,000 in prize money during Base’s On-Chain Summer II campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CEO Faces Trial Over Alleged 'Misleading Statements' in 2017 Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236451</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236451/ripple-ceo-faces-trial-over-alleged-misleading-statements-in-2017-interview"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T12:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The charges take issue with the CEO saying he was "very, very long" on XRP. Plaintiffs allege he sold millions worth of XRP the same year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Minsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dips 3.5% as German Government Sells $325 Million BTC Over Two Days]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236448</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236448/bitcoin-dips-german-government-sells-325-million-btc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T11:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin plunged 3.5% on Friday morning, likely still experiencing volatility from the German government selling $195 million the day before.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidirim Ndeche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ethereum Derivatives Traders Are Deploying an Iron Condor Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236438</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236438/ethereum-derivatives-traders-iron-condor-strategy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traders have been using the $3,200 to $3,400 'lines-in-the sand' to define risk, Wintermute told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Is Creating a Bitcoin and Ethereum Trading Desk in London]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236443</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236443/standard-chartered-bitcoin-ethereum-trading-desk"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British bank Standard Chartered is opening a spot Bitcoin and Ethereum trading desk, becoming one of the first in the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Ethereum Trust Faces 'Comparative Disadvantage' Without Staking: SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236435</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236435/lack-of-staking-poses-comparative-disadvantage-for-grayscale-ethereum-trust-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T09:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not being able to stake the Ethereum backing the Grayscale Ethereum Trust will "negatively affect the value of the shares," the firm wrote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Minsberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers Are Using AI Phishing and ‘Juice Jacking’ to Target Travelers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236402</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236402/ai-phishing-smishing-juice-jacking-scamming-travelers"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email attacks are up 4,151%, says security firm SlashNext, as fake USB chargers threaten to steal smartphone data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana ETF Proposal Aims to Be First in North America]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236391</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236391/solana-etf-proposal-3iq-canada"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF approvals in the United States, a firm aims to launch Canada's first Solana ETF. Can the U.S. be far behind?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the AI Wingman That Helps Dudes Get Dates]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236373</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236373/ai-wingman-helps-dudes-get-dates-rizz"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A burgeoning industry teaching men how to talk to women is taking off worldwide. What hath tech wrought?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry Dogecoin Fans: Elon Musk’s Twitter Payments Plan Doesn’t Include Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236396</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236396/sorry-dogecoin-fans-elon-musk-twitter-payments-no-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin supporter Elon Musk is working toward the launch of a Twitter payments service, but it reportedly doesn’t feature crypto for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins Donate $2 Million in Bitcoin to Trump to Fight Biden's 'War on Crypto']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236372</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236372/winklevoss-twins-donate-2-million-bitcoin-trump"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gemini co-founders said they sided with Donald Trump and donated $1 million in Bitcoin apiece to take down President Biden's re-election campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero Airdrop Is Creating Chaos for Polymarket Bettors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236367</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236367/layerzero-zro-airdrop-wager-dispute"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero Labs requiring a donation to receive ZRO tokens left Polymarket with a $680,000 wager disputed by its users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Telegram Game Airdrop: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236360/hamster-kombat-telegram-game-airdrop-everything-need-know"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s hottest game is planning an airdrop via The Open Network (TON)—and Hamster Kombat has teased tips for yielding the best bag.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Preps for Primetime With TV Commercial Ahead of ETF Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236351</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236351/ethereum-tv-ad-etf-launch-bitwise"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T19:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise is again first to release an ETF ad—and they’re minting it as an NFT on Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is 'Yescoin'? The Telegram Tap-to-Earn Game and Airdrop Details]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236328</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-yescoin-telegram-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram-based game Yescoin puts a sspin on the clicker genre, attracting 18 million players as a token airdrop looms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leonardo AI Launches a New Model—Can It Dethrone Ideogram as Best Image Generator?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236173</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236173/leonardo-ideogram-ai-image-generator-comparison"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leonardo AI's latest release, Leonardo Phoenix, brings a host of new features and improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany Begins Selling Its Bitcoin Billions, Triggering Volatility Fears]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236329</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236329/germany-begins-selling-bitcoin-billions-volatility-fears"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German government is starting to sell off its stockpile of over $3 billion in seized Bitcoin, says Arkham. Will it tank the market?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tornado Cash Use Could Complicate CertiK's Defense Against Kraken ‘Extortion’ Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236323/tornado-cash-certik-defense-kraken-extortion-claims"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain sleuths have discovered that CertiK researchers engaged with U.S.-banned crypto mixer Tornado Cash after the "white-hat" Kraken hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin to $1 Million? These Analysts Think It Gets There—Eventually]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236319/bitcoin-1-million-analysts-think-it-gets-there"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bernstein has doubled down on predictions that Bitcoin is about to surge to unprecedented highs—and may hit $200,000 in less than a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 142 - ETH LEADS THE RALLY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/teZMC9Tb/fomo-hour-142-eth-leads-the-rally"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH continues to lead gains, SOL underperforms. BTC may rebound as Fed liquidity rips higher. ETH sees large amount of bullish call activity. LayerZero launches today, 25% unlock. Funding level the lowest in 3 months. German government sends 1000 BTC to exchanges. Stablecoins to become 10% of money: Circle CEO. Stabelcoin transfers up 16x in 4 years. BTC exchanges balances hit 3 year low. SOL again flips ETH for DEX volumes. Kraken reports $3m bug exploit found by CertiK. Debate about whether CertiK were whitehats. Jump Crypto gives $10m to crypto PAC. Binance launches HODLer airdrops. TipLink allows SOL transfers by email. ETHFI proposes 50% revenue for buybacks. JTO teases LSD backed stablecoin. JUP team proposes to reduce 30% of supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Sinks as Meme Stock Trader Roaring Kitty Goes Quiet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236313/gamestop-sinks-roaring-kitty-goes-quiet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is this the end of the latest meme stock revival? GameStop shares keep dipping without Roaring Kitty to pump up traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Not Enough People’: This Robotics Company Is Tackling a Labor Shortage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236160/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of manufacturing jobs are going unfilled, says the CEO of GrayMatter, which today announced raising $45 million to expand its manufacturing efforts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Robotics Company Aims to Solve a Labor Shortage in Manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ub9yvCXi/this-robotics-company-aims-to-solve-a-labor-shortage-in-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GrayMatter Robotics Co-founder and CEO Ariyan Kabir explains the origin of the company, the need for artificial intelligence and robotics to offset a growing labor shortage, and takes Decrypt on a tour of its AI-powered facility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Just Bought Another $786 Million in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236302</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236302/microstrategy-bought-786-million-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor’s software firm has purchased another huge sum of Bitcoin, widening its lead as the top corporate holder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NBCUniversal Will Continue Building on Aptos via Long-Term Agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236289/nbcuniversal-aptos-long-term-agreement"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following “Exorcist” and “Renfield” experiences on Aptos, NBCUniversal will keep collaborating with Aptos Labs for years to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘PixelTap’ Daily Combo Guide: How to Earn Millions of Free Coins in the Pixelverse Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=235998</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/pixeltap-daily-combo-guide-earn-free-coins-pixelverse-telegram-game"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T13:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game PixelTap lets you battle robots to earn coins ahead of a token airdrop—and you can earn way more with this easy bonus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Stays Above $3,500 as Open Interest Drops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=236287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/236287/ethereum-stays-above-3500-as-open-interest-drops"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T12:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum kept its ground above $3,500 as open interest drops—a sign that traders don't expect wild swings in either direction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 141 - SEC DROPS ETH PROBE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zFpVKbtL/fomo-hour-141-sec-drops-eth-probe"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 65.4k (0%), ETH: 3545 (+3%), SOL: 139 (+2%). Top Gainers: LDO, BRETT, PEPE, AR. ETH & beta lead gains after SEC headline. SEC drops probe into ETH as a security. BTC ETFs see another $152m outflow. Pantera show $100m buying interest in ETH ETF. Pantera aims to raise new $1bn fund. Lack of staking won’t harm ETH ETF: 21 Shares. LayerZero airdrop coming June 20th. SEC concerns on USDC may delay Circle IPO. Hayes increasing PENDLE & DOGE positions. Fox News to build L2 with Polygon. EIGEN trades at $10bn pre-market. Drift & Ondo partner on RWAs. Commercial real estate coming on-chain: KPMG.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 140 - MARKETS DOWN BAD]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7BwSoeRf/fomo-hour-140-markets-down-bad"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC touches 1-month lows, dominance hits 56%. $500m of liquidations in fall, $146m ETF outflows. VanEck to launch first ETF in Australia. Coinbase to launch pre-market trading. 56% of Fortune 500 building in web3. Uphold to delist USDT in EU due to MiCA. TON flips DOGE in sell-off. Base DEX users now 2nd place after SOL. Ethena launches staking & restaking with Symbiotic. Lens aiming to raise $50m at $500m valuation. Two ‘crazy’ MATIC announcements coming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 139 - WHATS THE NEXT META?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zEW6uY5Z/fomo-hour-139-whats-the-next-meta"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T17:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC again breaks $66k, dominance rises. Fear & Greed index hits 3 month low. Whales continue to be in accumulation mode. Miners 33 days into capitulation, average 41 days. Financial advisors not buying BTC yet: BlackRock. Crypto funds saw $600m outflows last week. ZKsync airdrop live, prices at $5bn FDV. ZKsync defend sybil measures. Low float, high FDV coins get hammered again. Tether launches product backed by Gold. Korean exchanges reviewing 600 coins for delisting. ETH ETF ‘sell the rumour, buy the news event’. BTC ETF basis buyers roughly 15% of demand. CVX bounces 100% after loan liquidation. TON sees fastest user growth in crypto history. APT may flip SOL in 1-3 years: Hayes. Crypto lifetime funding eclipses $100bn. SEC claims $876m Ripple fine still fair. Gensler could cost Biden election: Cuban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 138 - MORE CELEB COINS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KzCZzgqx/fomo-hour-138-more-celeb-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed out heavy, BTC dominance rises towards 60%. Miners continue to be large BTC sellers, whales accumulate. ETF inflows slow, hedge fund allocations point to basis trades. ETH ETFs approvals see little movement, coming 'in the summer’. Stocks continue to hit ATHs as CPI & PPI both come in soft. TON performs best in L1s, active wallets eclipse ETH. Andrew Tate joins celebrity memecoin meta, DADDY hits $350m. SOL DEX volumes eclipse ETH in memecoin frenzy. Curve founder defaults on CRV debt as DeFi coins tumble. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon to pay $4.5bn fine to SEC. BAMK hits $350m in Runes as it issues BTC stablecoin. Gaming tokens face huge sell-off, PRIME changes tokenomics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 137 - CRYPTO DIPS FURTHER]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mJ28rAx5/fomo-hour-137-crypto-dips-further"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls after slightly hawkish Fed speech. BTC whales buy $1.4bn in 24hrs. Miners continue to be large sellers of BTC. BTC ETFs see $100m inflows. MicroStrategy to raise $500m to buy BTC. Egorov CRV debt positions begin to liquidate  . Circle to support SOL for wallets. 4% of Turkey GDP used to buy stablecoins. QuantMatter say $11m stolen from OKX account. Biden to use Coinbase for crypto donations. Terraform Labs & Do Kwon set to pay $4.5bn fine. Franklin Templeton write report on SOL DePin. TON flips ETH for active addresses. Moonpay & Paypal integration goes live in EU & UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 136 - FIRST MOTHER, NOW DADDY?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LEzSMpGz/fomo-hour-136-first-mother-now-daddy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see another $200m outflows. Another $190m of liquidations in volatility. $1.2bn BTC leaves exchanges in a day. ETF flows largely driven by basis trades: Pal. ‘Perfect setup’ for longs into macro news today. ETH ETF approvals ‘expected this month’. Crypto in best place it has ever been: Circle CEO. China’s ICBC calls ETH ‘digital oil’. Trump wants ‘made in the USA’ BTC. Crypto hacks $19bn since 2011. Symbiotic restaking protocol sees $150m inflows. Polygon launches $720m grants program. ZKsync accused of insider allocations. CRV drop leaves $90m loans at risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>