<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-20T17:12:51.007Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T17:12:51.007Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop worrying about Gensler’s crypto crusade and focus on bitcoin: Novogratz]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786583/Stop-worrying-about-Genslers-crypto-crusade-and-focus-on-bitcoin-Novogratz</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786583/Stop-worrying-about-Genslers-crypto-crusade-and-focus-on-bitcoin-Novogratz"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital’s CEO joined CNBC’s Squawk Box Thursday morning to discuss the artificial intelligence bubble, government spending and the state of crypto regulation in the US]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM) Notches 19% Gains In One Day, Will It Test $0.2?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75614f3d48</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/stellar-xlm-notches-19-gains/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM) has climbed higher as more gains reach the broader crypto market. While XRP’s price action appears to have stalled, XLM’s rally is still ongoing. The payment solution token continued its bullish trend, amassing a 19.66% price increase on the day.
 
Stellar now edges towards the $0.2 target as bulls ramp up action to defend the current support level. 
 
Stellar (XLM) Price Performance In The Past Week
 
Crypto prices continue in a heightened wavy pattern as Bitcoin fights to defend the $30,000 mark and push to $31,000. Amid the heightened volatility and anticipation for the July CPI data as the inflation rate declines, payment facilitators like XLM have been enjoying a bullish ride. 
 
The token saw massive gains in the past weeks, with over 105% monthly price increases. The c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Alameda CEO Caroline Ellison’s Google Docs Diary Exposes Struggles Prior to FTX Collapse]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75614fa6dd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ex-alameda-ceo-caroline-ellisons-google-docs-diary-exposes-struggles-prior-to-ftx-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the New York Times and several sources familiar with the matter, Caroline Ellison, former CEO of Alameda Research, maintained a diary on Google Documents that provides a brief glimpse into the challenges she faced before the collapse of FTX. Excerpts from the diary suggest Ellison lacked confidence in her role. After her breakup with Sam Bankman-Fried, FTX co-founder, her enthusiasm for Alameda “significantly decreased.”
 
Ellison Didn’t Think She Was Well Suited to Lead Alameda Research
 
Caroline Ellison, former CEO of Alameda Research, a quantitative trading firm owned by Sam Bankman-Fried, reportedly maintained a diary on Google Documents. The New York Times, in a report dated July 20, 2023, confirmed with four people familiar with the matter that the publication reviewed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thieves Invade Cryptocurrency Investors' Homes! "Don't Do These"]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786554/Thieves-Invade-Cryptocurrency-Investors-Homes-Dont-Do-These</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786554/Thieves-Invade-Cryptocurrency-Investors-Homes-Dont-Do-These"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thieves' new target is cryptocurrency investors. Police has issued a warning to cryptocurrency investors. Continue Reading: Thieves Invade Cryptocurrency Investors' Homes! "Don't Do These"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP price can fall 40% by September — Fractal analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786523/XRP-price-can-fall-40-by-September-Fractal-analysis</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786523/XRP-price-can-fall-40-by-September-Fractal-analysis"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP is currently mirroring a trend from the April-June 2021 that preceded the price falling by 65% in the following months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto industry is ‘afraid to celebrate’ Ripple’s ‘giant win’ over the SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786521/Crypto-industry-is-afraid-to-celebrate-Ripples-giant-win-over-the-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786521/Crypto-industry-is-afraid-to-celebrate-Ripples-giant-win-over-the-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Right now, what we have is a decision from a federal district court that says the law is what the industry has been saying the law is for years”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance US CEO Brian Brooks Joins Crypto Asset Manager Hashdex]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149368</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149368/former-binance-us-ceo-brian-brooks-joins-crypto-asset-manager-hashdex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His ill-fated stint at Binance US wasn't in a news release, which focused on his time as Coinbase's CLO and acting U.S. Comptroller of the Currency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Binance US CEO Brian Brooks Joins Crypto Asset Manager Hashdex]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786527/Former-Binance-US-CEO-Brian-Brooks-Joins-Crypto-Asset-Manager-Hashdex</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786527/Former-Binance-US-CEO-Brian-Brooks-Joins-Crypto-Asset-Manager-Hashdex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His ill-fated stint at Binance US wasn't in a news release, which focused on his time as Coinbase's CLO and acting U.S. Comptroller of the Currency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Economic Secretary rejects regulating crypto as gambling, advocates for financial services framework]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786498/UK-Economic-Secretary-rejects-regulating-crypto-as-gambling-advocates-for-financial-services-framework</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786498/UK-Economic-Secretary-rejects-regulating-crypto-as-gambling-advocates-for-financial-services-framework"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Griffith, U.K’s Economic Secretary to the Treasury, has rejected the Parliament Treasury Select Committee’s recommendation to regulate cryptocurrency trading as gambling, according to a response published on July 20. In a May report, the U.K’s Treasury Committee acknowledged that...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Reacts to Elon Musk's Unexpected HEX Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786528/Cardano-Founder-Reacts-to-Elon-Musks-Unexpected-HEX-Statement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786528/Cardano-Founder-Reacts-to-Elon-Musks-Unexpected-HEX-Statement"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano founder reacts to Elon Musk's HEX remark]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu ($SHIB) Influencer Explains When Crypto Prices Are Likely To Go ‘Up, Up, Up’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786526/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Influencer-Explains-When-Crypto-Prices-Are-Likely-To-Go-Up-Up-Up</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786526/Shiba-Inu-SHIB-Influencer-Explains-When-Crypto-Prices-Are-Likely-To-Go-Up-Up-Up"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today, “LucieSHIB,” a well-known influencer in the Shiba Inu community and a marketing specialist working for the Shiba Inu (SHIB) team, offered an explanation for the current stagnation in the price of Shiba Inu’s native token, SHIB. Lucie’s comments were in response to growing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison’s diaries reveal Alameda chaos, imposter syndrome, toxic SBF]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786505/Caroline-Ellisons-diaries-reveal-Alameda-chaos-imposter-syndrome-toxic-SBF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786505/Caroline-Ellisons-diaries-reveal-Alameda-chaos-imposter-syndrome-toxic-SBF"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caroline Ellison's personal diaries are expected to play a part in SBF’s upcoming trial, at which she will be called as a ‘star witness.’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upland and FIFA launch Women’s World Cup Australia & New Zealand 2023 metaverse experience]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786504/Upland-and-FIFA-launch-Womens-World-Cup-Australia-New-Zealand-2023-metaverse-experience</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786504/Upland-and-FIFA-launch-Womens-World-Cup-Australia-New-Zealand-2023-metaverse-experience"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upland, the leading Web3 metaverse SuperApp, is extending its partnership with FIFA to provide an immersive Web3 experience to football … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin․me Launches $150,000 in Liquidity Pool Rewards]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75614a4d2e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin%E2%80%A4me-launches-150000-in-liquidity-pool-rewards/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. In its pursuit to revolutionize the cryptocurrency trading landscape, Bitcoin.me is pleased to announce the launch of three remarkable Liquidity Pools: KFI/USDT, KLV/USDT, and the latest addition, KFI/KLV.
 
Cryptocurrencies have reshaped the world of finance, with centralized exchanges like Bitcoin.me playing a crucial role in this paradigm shift. Bitcoin.me provides a secure platform for individuals to buy, sell, and trade cryptocurrencies while employing robust security measures and ensuring regulatory compliance across jurisdictions to legitimize operations and foster trust.
 
Bitcoin.me is proud to spotlight the following Liquidity Pools:
 
1. KFI/USDT Liquidity Pool: Currently active and bustling with activity. The pool will end on October 4, 2023, at 2 PM UTC.
 
2. KL…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler Calls Crypto ‘Wild West’ While Asking for More Money]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786502/SEC-Chair-Gensler-Calls-Crypto-Wild-West-While-Asking-for-More-Money</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786502/SEC-Chair-Gensler-Calls-Crypto-Wild-West-While-Asking-for-More-Money"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an effort to grapple with the new frontier cryptocurrency markets, U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairm Gary Gensler has called for a budgetary increase for the agency. He cited the need for enhanced vigilance against potential non-compliance in this emerging sector in a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK's FCA Is Designing Prudential Requirements for Firms Carrying Out Crypto Activities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75614b1f66</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/20/uks-fca-is-designing-prudential-requirements-for-firms-carrying-out-crypto-activities/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Conduct Authority will consult on rules once the government gives it the necessary powers, the regulator said in its annual report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO Votes to Halt Lending to Tokenized Credit Pool After $2M Loan Default]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786494/MakerDAO-Votes-to-Halt-Lending-to-Tokenized-Credit-Pool-After-2M-Loan-Default</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786494/MakerDAO-Votes-to-Halt-Lending-to-Tokenized-Credit-Pool-After-2M-Loan-Default"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The embattled Harbour Trade credit pool minted $1.5 million of DAI stablecoin secured with loans to a consumer electronics firm, which defaulted on $2.1 million of debt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Rose’s a16z-backed Moonbirds launches 200-day reveal of new collection]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786489/Kevin-Roses-a16z-backed-Moonbirds-launches-200-day-reveal-of-new-collection</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786489/Kevin-Roses-a16z-backed-Moonbirds-launches-200-day-reveal-of-new-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonbirds Mythics NFTs Begin Reveal That Will Last at Least 200 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149362</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149362/moonbirds-mythics-nfts-begin-reveal-last-least-200-days"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 20,000-strong Mythics NFT collection will be revealed gradually over the span of months as Moonbirds and Oddities holders claim them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonbirds Mythics NFTs Begin Reveal That Will Last at Least 200 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786501/Moonbirds-Mythics-NFTs-Begin-Reveal-That-Will-Last-at-Least-200-Days</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786501/Moonbirds-Mythics-NFTs-Begin-Reveal-That-Will-Last-at-Least-200-Days"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tycoon Mike Novogratz Praises Ripple, Slams Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786490/Crypto-Tycoon-Mike-Novogratz-Praises-Ripple-Slams-Gensler</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786490/Crypto-Tycoon-Mike-Novogratz-Praises-Ripple-Slams-Gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto tycoon Mike Novogratz, CEO of Galaxy Digital, praised Ripple and its recent court victory against SEC, calling it 'big win' for wider crypto community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequoia Capital's Turbulent Year: Partners Exit On Heels Of FTX Collapse, $214M Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786495/Sequoia-Capitals-Turbulent-Year-Partners-Exit-On-Heels-Of-FTX-Collapse-214M-Loss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786495/Sequoia-Capitals-Turbulent-Year-Partners-Exit-On-Heels-Of-FTX-Collapse-214M-Loss"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venture firm Sequoia Capital has undergone significant changes over the past year, marked by market volatility, a split, and the departure of at least five investors. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: XLM, LINK 20% Higher on Thursday]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75614bb9f5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-xlm-link-20-higher-on-thursday/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink rose by as much as 20% earlier in today’s session, as markets reacted to the release of its Chainlink Cross-Chain Interoperability Protocol (CCIP). Traders were buoyed by the news, pushing the token to its highest level since April in the process. Stellar rose to a one-week high today.
 
Chainlink (LINK)
 
Chainlink (LINK) was one of Thursday’s most notable gainers, as the token surged nearly 20% higher.
 
After falling to a low of $6.88 on Wednesday, LINK/USD rallied to an intraday peak of $8.32 earlier in the day.
 
The move pushed price to its strongest point since last April, when the token hit a high above $8.60.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the latest rally took place as the relative strength index (RSI) broke out of its ceiling at 72.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is at 73.03, with an upcoming resistance point of 77.00 a possible destination for bulls.
 
In the likely event it reaches this point, LINK could surpass last Thursday’s peak.
 
 
Stellar (XLM)
 
In addition to LINK, stellar (XLM) was another big mover during today’s session, as it also rose by nearly 20%
 
XLM/USD recorded a high of $0.1793 earlier in the day, which comes following yesterday’s low of $0.1414.
 
Similar to chainlink, this peak pushed stellar to its highest point since last Thursday, when the token hit a then 15-month high.
 
 
As a result of this gain, price strength in XLM is now overbought, which could spell a soon end for the current uptrend.
 
The RSI is tracking at a reading of 71.87, but is fast approaching a resistance zone at the 73.00 mark.
 
Traders may already be considering securing profits as price strength heads to this point.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could stellar bulls extend the rally in the coming days? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra And Do Kwon Argue “Torres Doctrine” In Bid To Dismiss SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786464/Terra-And-Do-Kwon-Argue-Torres-Doctrine-In-Bid-To-Dismiss-SEC-Lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786464/Terra-And-Do-Kwon-Argue-Torres-Doctrine-In-Bid-To-Dismiss-SEC-Lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brad Garlinghouse Hails XRP Ruling as Turning Point]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786463/Brad-Garlinghouse-Hails-XRP-Ruling-as-Turning-Point</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786463/Brad-Garlinghouse-Hails-XRP-Ruling-as-Turning-Point"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs wants to subpoena info from FTX to aid its SEC defense]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786471/Terraform-Labs-wants-to-subpoena-info-from-FTX-to-aid-its-SEC-defense</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786471/Terraform-Labs-wants-to-subpoena-info-from-FTX-to-aid-its-SEC-defense"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Country Will Establish Crypto-Based Bank To Resist The Coup, The Bank Will Work On This Altcoin Network!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786473/This-Country-Will-Establish-Crypto-Based-Bank-To-Resist-The-Coup-The-Bank-Will-Work-On-This-Altcoin-Network</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18786473/This-Country-Will-Establish-Crypto-Based-Bank-To-Resist-The-Coup-The-Bank-Will-Work-On-This-Altcoin-Network"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the news of Coindesk, the Government of National Unity of Myanmar (NUG) is preparing to establish the first fully cryptocurrency-based banking institution. Continue Reading: This Country Will Establish Crypto-Based Bank To Resist The Coup, The Bank Will Work On This Altcoin Network!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Users Potentially Targeted in Possible Phishing Attack as Bankruptcy Claims Deadline Nears]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75613577cd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/20/ftx-users-potentially-targeted-in-possible-phishing-attack-as-bankruptcy-claims-deadline-nears/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple FTX users have received a "reset password" request from the defunct exchange's official email address as it appears a hacker is attempting to secure control of user's bankruptcy claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Dramatically Sped Up U.S. Payments, but Has Downplayed Any Tie to CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75613577b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/20/us-federal-reserve-kickstarts-fednow-instant-payments/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some argue it would weaken crypto’s payments use case or form a bridge to a digital dollar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Officially Launches Instant Payments System FedNow]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561358ff5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/federal-reserve-officially-launches-instant-payments-system-fednow"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T16:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an announcement Thursday morning, the Federal Reserve announced that its instant payment system, the FedNow® Service, has officially gone live. This tool aims to empower banks and credit unions of all sizes to facilitate instantaneous money transfers for their customers. The Federal Reserve claims that FedNow transactions can be executed 24/7, 365 days a year.
To start, 35 banks and credit unions, alongside the U.S. Department of the Treasury's Bureau of the Fiscal Service, are among those already equipped to handle payments through the FedNow Service. Furthermore, a lineup of 16 service providers are poised to offer payment processing support for banks and credit unions.
"The Federal Reserve built the FedNow Service to help make everyday payments over the coming years faster and more convenient," said Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell. "Over time, as more banks choose to use this new tool, the benefits to individuals and businesses will include enabling a person to immediately receive a paycheck, or a company to instantly access funds when an invoice is paid."
When asked if the FedNow service is attempting to replace cash, and if it was a central bank digital currency (CBDC) or not, the Federal Reserve stated "No. The FedNow Service is not related to a digital currency. The FedNow Service is a payment service the Federal Reserve is making available for banks and credit unions to transfer funds for their customers. It is like other Federal Reserve payment services, such as Fedwire and FedACH. The FedNow Service is neither a form of currency nor a step toward eliminating any form of payment, including cash."
A comprehensive list of early adopters already equipped with instant payment capabilities can be found in an attached document. Further information can be found on the Federal Reserve Financial Services website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Exchange Whale Ratio Spikes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756137764c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-bearish-signal-exchange-whale-ratio-spikes/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T15:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that the Bitcoin exchange whale ratio has been at very high values during the past few days, a sign that may be bearish for BTC.
 
Bitcoin Exchange Whale Ratio Has Been At Elevated Levels Recently
 
As pointed out by an analyst in a CryptoQuant post, whales have been applying a high amount of selling pressure in recent days. The indicator of relevance here is the “exchange whale ratio,” which measures the ratio between the sum of the top 10 Bitcoin transactions going to exchanges, and the total exchange inflow.
 
The 10 largest transactions going to exchanges are generally coming from the whales, so the exchange whale ratio can tell us about how these transfers currently compare with the deposits being made by the entire market (the total exchange inflow).
 
When the va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Seeks To Recover $71 Million From Philanthropy And Life Science Ventures]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75613f9dcf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ftx-recovery-from-philanthropy-science-ventures/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX, along with its sister firm, Alameda Research, is still maneuvering through its bankruptcy proceedings. And currently, they have their sights set on a substantial sum. Specifically, more than $71 million that they hope to recover from various philanthropic and life science entities.
 
This recovery effort centers on allegations that FTX and Alameda’s corporate funds were channeled to different organizations for the “personal aggrandizement” of their founder, Sam Bankman-Fried, as indicated in recent court documents.
 
Altruism Or Aggrandizement? The Underlying Motives
 
The court filings reveal that the FTX Foundation and Latona were allegedly instrumental in diverting approximately $71.5 million from FTX and Alameda Research. This fund movement was supposedly …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Foundation under Scrutiny as Bankruptcy Team Pursues $71M Recovery]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75613fb728</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftx-foundation-under-scrutiny-as-bankruptcy-team-pursues-71m-recovery/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX and its affiliated hedge fund firm Alameda Research  
are planning to recover USD $71 million spent by the bankrupt cryptocurrency  
exchange on philanthropy. The lawyers representing the companies also plan to  
recover funds from FTX Foundation.
Filed before a US  
bankruptcy court in Delaware, FTX's lawyers have accused several life sciences  
companies, including Lumen Bioscience Inc., Greenlight Biosciences Holdings, and Platform  
Life Sciences Inc., of allegedly receiving funds from the collapsed exchange.
Alleged Misappropriation  
of Funds
The attorneys added that  
although the funds were purported to promote effective altruism, a philosophy  
supporting the transfer of resources from wealthy people to the poor, FTX made  
the donations so that Sam Bankman-Fried, the exchange…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Bitcoin Portfolio Remains Unchanged at $184M for Third Straight Quarter: Q2 2023 Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561381518</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/teslas-bitcoin-portfolio-remains-unchanged-at-184m-for-third-straight-quarter-q2-2023-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Q2 2023 Update reveals that the American electric car and clean energy company refrained from selling any of its bitcoin (BTC) or cryptocurrency holdings in the previous quarter. For the past three quarters, Tesla has maintained a digital asset portfolio worth approximately $184 million.
 
Tesla Holds Steady on Bitcoin in Q2 2023, Maintains $184M in Digital Assets
 
Following the market close on Wednesday, July 19, 2023, electric car manufacturer Tesla reported its financial results for the second quarter. In this quarter, Tesla manufactured 480,000 vehicles and delivered 466,000. “Q2-2023 was a record quarter on many levels with our best-ever production and deliveries and revenue approaching $25B in a single quarter,” detailed Tesla’s Q2 2023 update.
 
Besides a better second quar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Labs Invests $10M in DeFi Lender Radiant, RDNT Jumps 10%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756138b906</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/20/binance-labs-invests-10m-in-defi-lender-radiant/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The protocol was built on the architecture of LayerZero, which raised $120 million at a $3 billion valuation earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenization and Investing: A Look at Tomorrow's Democratized Landscape]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561257731</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/tokenization-and-investing-a-look-at-tomorrows-democratized-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, the financial landscape has witnessed the  
rise of blockchain technology and its potential to revolutionize various  
industries. One of the most promising applications of blockchain is  
tokenization, a process that involves representing real-world assets as digital  
tokens on a blockchain network. This innovation has the power to democratize  
investing, providing new opportunities for a broader range of investors to  
participate in previously exclusive asset classes. In this article, we explore  
how tokenization is transforming the investment landscape, its benefits, and  
the potential challenges that lie ahead.
A Game-Changer for  
Investors: What is Tokenization? 
Tokenization is the process of converting physical or  
financial assets, such as real estate, fine …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FM Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonland Inches Closer to NFT Airdrop Following Early Access Announcement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561271d81</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/moonland-inches-closer-to-nft-airdrop-following-early-access-announcement/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. MoonLand, the groundbreaking social multiplayer metaverse game, is set to redefine the gaming industry with its revolutionary play-to-earn mechanism and immersive gameplay experience. By blending blockchain technology, web 3.0 principles, and the economy model of the metaverse, MoonLand aims to captivate a global audience of gaming enthusiasts.
 
Unlock Early Access with MoonLand’s NFT Airdrop
 
In a significant announcement, MoonLand unveiled its highly anticipated NFT airdrop. Aspiring players have the exclusive opportunity to sign the whitelist and secure their position among the first to receive coveted free NFTs. These unique tokens will not only grant early access to the game but also make participants eligible for a subsequent airdrop of 42 MTK (MoonLand Tokens).
 
MT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Tech Renaissance: AI And Big Data Push 300% Growth In 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756127eaeb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-ai-and-big-data-push-300-growth/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fusion of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and “Big Data” has emerged as a standout phenomenon in the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency. This dynamic sector has earned its place among the top 10 industries experiencing a remarkable market cap growth this year.
 
Revolutionizing the way data is processed and utilized, the AI and Big Data sector uses sophisticated algorithms and machine learning techniques to analyze vast datasets. 
 
By extracting invaluable insights, these domains play a pivotal role in reshaping various industries through data-driven decision-making, predictive analytics, and widespread automation. The result is a substantial boost in efficiency and innovation across sectors.
 
Big data is the term for the enormous, varied sets of information that multiply at an expon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Added Bitcoin Payments Back To Their Website: Rumor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e756127eae6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tesla-added-bitcoin-payments-back-rumor/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the Bitcoin community was set abuzz with a tantalizing rumor suggesting that Tesla might be rekindling its love affair with BTC payments.The spark was ignited by a Twitter user who discovered that BTC can still be found in the source code of Tesla’s official website, alongside Apple Pay, Bancontact and other payment options.
 
 
The discovery that Bitcoin and Dogecoin payment options were still lingering in Tesla’s source code added fuel to the speculation that the electric vehicle giant might soon resume accepting BTC payments. Many enthusiasts were quick to interpret this as a possible signal of a Bitcoin comeback spearheaded by Elon Musk.
 
However, as the excitement escalated, the rumor was promptly debunked. Closer examination revealed that while the source code contained refer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Government Rejects Proposal to Classify Crypto as Gambling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149343/uk-government-rejects-proposal-to-classify-crypto-as-gambling"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government argued that classifying crypto asset trading as gambling would create a misalignment with global standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: ETH Moves Past $1,900 as Traders End Losing Streak]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7561231fc3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-eth-moves-past-1900-as-traders-end-losing-streak/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After six consecutive days trading in the red, ethereum bounced back on Thursday, once again climbing above the $1,900 mark. The move came as bitcoin also edged higher, after falling to a four-week low during Tuesday’s session. 
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) was marginally higher on Thursdays, as the cryptocurrency once again attempted to rebound from recent losses.
 
Following a low of $29,794.27 on Wednesday, BTC/USD rose to an intraday peak of $30,406.45 earlier in the day.
 
The move came as bitcoiners continued to move away from Tuesday’s fall below $30,000, which resulted in BTC hitting a four-week low.
 
 
Price stabilized as the relative strength index (RSI) found a firm floor at the 49.00 mark. It has now surged to a current reading of 53.60.
 
Traders are likely now targeting an upcoming ceiling at $30,800, which has historically been the last line of defense before entering the $31,000 zone.
 
Despite this target, momentum still appears to be bearish, as a result of the recent downwards crossover of the 10-day (red) and 25-day (blue) moving averages.
 
 
Ethereum
 
In addition to bitcoin, ethereum (ETH) rose back above $1,900 in today’s session, ending its own losing streak.
 
ETH/USD hit a high of $1,927.57 earlier in today’s session, which comes a day after edging to a low of $1,883.07.
 
Momentum has been largely bearish in the world’s second largest cryptocurrency in recent days, following last week’s rally.
 
 
Today’s move is the first day since last Thursday that ethereum has traded in the green, with traders still optimistic about future surges above $2,000.
 
A ceiling at $1,960 will likely be the main test for ethereum’s bull strength, and should it pass this level, it is highly likely the price will reach $2,000.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
What fundamentals are behind today’s price rebound? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Ritchie Torres: SEC Chair Gensler 'Intent on Sabotaging' Crypto Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149337</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149337/congressman-ritchie-torres-sec-chair-gensler-intent-on-sabotaging-crypto-industry"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Ritchie Torres doubled down on his recent criticisms of Securities and Exchange Commission chair Gary Gensler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macro State of Crypto – Where It Has Been and What's Next]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75612dd98b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/20/macro-state-of-crypto-where-it-has-been-and-where-is-it-going/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analytics can offer insight into how recent and past crypto and regulatory events have affected prices and movement. Plus: A quick Q&A on retirement funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Morton, Greg Magadini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floor App Reveals Ethereum NFT Art Drops Exclusively on iOS and Android]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149295</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149295/floor-app-reveals-ethereum-nft-art-drops-exclusively-on-ios-and-android"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:01:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artist Vinnie Hager will kickstart the series of drops so Floor can, in the CEO’s words, “meet people where they are—on their phone.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Labs Puts $10 Million Into Radiant Capital to Expand to Other Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149268/binance-radiant-capital-layer-2-cross-chain-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This investment will go toward enabling more Radiant users to move tokens across more chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: XRP Momentum Could Set Precedent for Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75612fe16d</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/20/first-mover-americas-xrp-momentum-could-set-precedent-for-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T12:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for July 20, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's Bonds Have Skyrocketed Alongside Bitcoin in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149335</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149335/el-salvadors-bonds-have-skyrocketed-alongside-bitcoin-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:20:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the start of the year, both Bitcoin and El Salvador's government bonds have soared.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Bot Tokens Surge Toward $100M Market Cap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149313/telegram-bot-tokens-surge-toward-100m-market-cap"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T10:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sector has experienced massive growth in a short period, as projects such as Unibot and Ready Swap flood the markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Museums and Galleries Are Embracing Digital Art, Exploring AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149287/museums-and-galleries-are-embracing-digital-art-exploring-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T01:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of art, its accessibility, and its audience were explored at Christie’s Art+Tech Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT's Performance Is Slipping, New Study Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149272</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149272/chatgpts-performance-is-slipping-new-study-says"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UC Berkeley researchers found that ChatGPT has not improved over time, and in fact, may have gotten worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Billion People Will Go On-Chain Over the Next Decade: Coinbase Protocols Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149270/8-billion-people-onchain-blockchain-crypto-10-years-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Pollak is leading the exchange’s efforts on Base, its Ethereum-focused layer-2 network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orgasm NFTs? NARS Cosmetics Brand Reveals Eyebrow-Raising Art Auctions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149257</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149257/orgasm-nfts-nars-cosmetics-brand-reveals-eyebrow-raising-art-auctions"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NARS has teamed up with SuperRare and digital artists to drop NFTs for National Orgasm Day, continuing a trend for the beauty brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start Playing Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop'—Do You Need an NFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-start-playing-dr-disrespects-deadrop-do-you-need-an-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deadrop is currently in limited early access. Here’s how to unlock the first-person shooter game from Midnight Society.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Is Quietly Creating an AI Chatbot to Compete With ChatGPT: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149251/apple-is-quietly-creating-an-ai-chatbot-to-compete-with-chatgpt-report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike ChatGPT, Apple’s tool isn’t meant for public consumption, and the company has no plans to release it to consumers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia to Start Testing ‘Digital Ruble’ CBDC in August Barring Putin's Veto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149238</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149238/russia-to-start-testing-digital-ruble-cbdc-in-august-barring-putins-veto"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill still requires Vladimir Putin’s signature, but if approved, Russia will become one of the largest adopters of CBDCs to date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian Soccer Club AC Milan Extends Crypto Sponsorship With BitMEX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149241/italian-soccer-club-ac-milan-extends-crypto-sponsorship-bitmex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soccer giant AC Milan is sticking with BitMEX, two years after naming the exchange its official cryptocurrency trading partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Bill Would Give US Treasury Authority Over DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149234/bipartisan-bill-would-give-us-treasury-authority-over-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill’s sponsors highlighted DeFi and crypto ATMs as vectors for financial crime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Jackson Pollock’s Historic Paint-Splattered Floor Is Being Immortalized as NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149229/why-jackson-pollock-historic-paint-splattered-floor-being-immortalized-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An art collection from the Jackson Pollock Studio and Iconic Moments digitally preserves the famed painter's studio floor on Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Wants Bitcoin Backed U.S. Dollars and Tax Breaks for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149222/robert-f-kennedy-jr-wants-bitcoin-backed-u-s-dollars-and-tax-breaks-for-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Bitcoin is among the hardest currencies and the Kennedy administration is going to encourage its proliferation and propagation,” he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Won’t Replace Human Spies, Says Britain’s MI6 Chief]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149220</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149220/ai-wont-replace-human-spies-says-britains-mi6-chief"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of Britain’s SIS says ‘human factors’ important in intelligence gathering can’t yet be replicated by AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Delays Crypto Custody Until Regulatory Concerns Die Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149195/nasdaq-halts-crypto-custody-plans-citing-regulatory-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But Nasdaq CEO Adena Friedman said that the company would “remain committed to supporting the evolution of the digital asset ecosystem.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cymbal Launches 'Human Readable' Ethereum Blockchain Explorer—A Social Etherscan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149202/cymbal-human-readable-ethereum-blockchain-explorer-etherscan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike traditional explorers that can be difficult to understand, Cymbal is both visual and social—and aimed at the masses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is MiCA? What the EU Crypto Governing Framework Means for You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-mica-what-the-eu-crypto-governing-framework-means-for-you"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA does not cover most NFTs (except fractionalized NFTs and NFTs released as collections). Similarly, it does not cover DeFi apps that exist without an intermediary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Wants More Games—This Simple Tool Could Help Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149166/solana-wants-more-games-simple-tool-could-help-developers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameShift from Solana Labs aims to make blockchain game development easier for newcomers and traditional game studios alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ICO Whale Moves $116M in ETH to Kraken]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149142</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149142/ethereum-ico-whale-moves-116m-in-eth-to-kraken"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another dormant Ethereum wallet that participated in the project’s ICO has woken up after years of slumber.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles Launching Real World Play Experience in Chicago With Camp]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149147/doodles-launching-real-world-play-experience-chicago-camp"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pharrell Williams-backed NFT project Doodles is expanding further into the real world in partnership with “shop-and-play” retailer Camp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Société Générale’s Crypto Division Is First To Gain Full License From French Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149144</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149144/societe-generales-crypto-division-is-first-to-gain-full-license-from-french-regulator"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While more than 80 companies are registered with the AMF, SG Forge is the first to be licensed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Police Arrest 21 in $54M USDT Money Laundering Probe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149132/chinese-police-arrest-21-in-54m-usdt-money-laundering-probe"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The suspects allegedly purchased Tether’s stablecoin over-the-counter and sold it at inflated prices over WeChat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK Virtual Machine Developer RISC Zero Raises $40M in Series A]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149121/zk-virtual-machine-developer-risc-zero-raises-40m-in-series-a"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the new funding, the Seattle-based startup is getting closer to the launch of its computing platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev Team p0x Labs Raises $25M for Zero-Knowledge Ecosystem Manta Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149128/zero-knowledge-ecosystem-manta-network-raises-25-million-from-polychain-qiming"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T12:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding round for p0x labs — which has delivered a valuation of $500 million — was led by Polychain Capital and Qiming Venture Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Trading Saw 'Uptick' in Altcoin Activity After Ripple SEC Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149120/genesis-trading-saw-uptick-in-altcoin-activity-after-ripple-sec-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T10:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The institutional trading platform’s head of sales explains that the XRP ruling is the latest in a "series of bullish events" for crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Gains 6% on Possible SEC Settlement Conference, Ripple Metaverse Investment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149118/xrp-gains-6-on-possible-sec-settlement-conference-ripple-metaverse-investment"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T10:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP outperforms the crypto market as hopes of settlement with the SEC and metaverse investment boost buyer sentiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com Adds Reddit’s Moons Token as Kraken Listing Rumor Fades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149113/crypto-com-adds-reddits-moons-token-as-kraken-listing-rumor-fades"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T01:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The listing caused the token's value to double for the second day in a row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Assassin's Creed' Creator Ubisoft Throws Weight Behind Cronos Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149100</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149100/ubisoft-crypto-cronos-blockchain-validator"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T01:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gaming giant continues expanding across the blockchain space, this time as a Cronos blockchain validator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Donates $5 Million to the American Journalism Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149106</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149106/openai-donates-5-million-to-the-american-journalism-project"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T00:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ChatGPT creator previously inked a deal with the Associated Press and Shutterstock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Google Exec Predicts AI Sex Robots Could Replace Human Intimacy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149093</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149093/former-google-exec-predicts-ai-sex-robots-replace-humans"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T00:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could AI be taking over our jobs—and replacing our sex partners?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Neopets' Cancels NFT Game After Raising Money From Polygon, Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149074</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149074/neopets-cancels-nft-game-after-raising-money-from-polygon-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T22:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite $4 million in funding from crypto firms, Neopets is ditching NFTs—and making a game that can "better reflect our values and vision."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinfund Raises $158 Million to Boost Early-Stage Crypto, AI Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149062</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149062/coinfund-152-million-seed-early-stage-crypto-startups"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is launching a new fund after a tumultuous year where many players pulled back from cryptocurrency plays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcadia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcadia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>