<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-07-20T01:18:02.283Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-07-20T01:18:02.283Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: XRP, XLM Climb While Bitcoin Trudges Below $30K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562de43d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/20/first-mover-asia-xrp-xlm-climb-while-bitcoin-trudges-below-30k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T01:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: Ripple's partial victory last week in its ongoing legal feud with the Securities and Exchange Commission left important questions unsettled for token issuers, a crypto lawyer told CoinDesk TV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta and Microsoft Announce Huge AI Collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784856/Meta-and-Microsoft-Announce-Huge-AI-Collaboration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784856/Meta-and-Microsoft-Announce-Huge-AI-Collaboration"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta and Microsoft have joined forces to introduce Llama 2, an open-source large language model...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance Rises in Q2 2023 as Altcoins Suffer Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784853/Bitcoin-Dominance-Rises-in-Q2-2023-as-Altcoins-Suffer-Losses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784853/Bitcoin-Dominance-Rises-in-Q2-2023-as-Altcoins-Suffer-Losses"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s performance in the second quarter of 2023 has been strong, with its market dominance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ICO Participant Reawakens With 619,000% Gains 8-Year Holding Period]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784850/Ethereum-ICO-Participant-Reawakens-With-619000-Gains-8-Year-Holding-Period</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784850/Ethereum-ICO-Participant-Reawakens-With-619000-Gains-8-Year-Holding-Period"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A massive Ethereum ($ETH) initial coin offering (ICO) participant has recently shaken up the cryptosphere after transferring a staggering $116 million in the second-largest cryptocurrency by market capitalization to cryptocurrency Kraken after being dormant for eight years. The dormant...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: XRP, XLM Climb While Bitcoin Trudges Below $30K]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784849/First-Mover-Asia-XRP-XLM-Climb-While-Bitcoin-Trudges-Below-30K</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784849/First-Mover-Asia-XRP-XLM-Climb-While-Bitcoin-Trudges-Below-30K"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:35:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PLUS: Ripple's partial victory last week in its ongoing legal feud with the Securities and Exchange Commission left important questions unsettled for token issuers, a crypto lawyer told CoinDesk TV.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla Didn’t Buy or Sell Any Bitcoin for Fourth Straight Quarter in Q2]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562d86c4e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/19/tesla-didnt-buy-or-sell-any-bitcoin-for-fourth-straight-quarter-in-q2/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The value of its bitcoin holdings remained at $184 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nelson Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation, Polygon Lead $30M Fundraise for Web3 Firm Cosmic Wire]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562d86c4b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/07/19/solana-foundation-polygon-lead-30m-fundraise-for-web3-firm-cosmic-wire/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup offers metaverse-creation tools and a list of general blockchain infrastructure solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche’s Struct Finance TVL Surges 120%, Clinches First Spot.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784843/Avalanches-Struct-Finance-TVL-Surges-120-Clinches-First-Spot</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784843/Avalanches-Struct-Finance-TVL-Surges-120-Clinches-First-Spot"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Struct Finance has recently defied all odds and risen to the top, outshining established platforms in the space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of how the crypto industry fared in Q2 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784840/An-overview-of-how-the-crypto-industry-fared-in-Q2-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784840/An-overview-of-how-the-crypto-industry-fared-in-Q2-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The market was relatively quiet. However, a few developments with Ethereum, and introduction of Bitcoin NFTs lit up the space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT's Performance Is Slipping, New Study Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149272</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149272/chatgpts-performance-is-slipping-new-study-says"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UC Berkeley researchers found that ChatGPT has not improved over time, and in fact, may have gotten worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT's Performance Is Slipping, New Study Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784842/ChatGPTs-Performance-Is-Slipping-New-Study-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784842/ChatGPTs-Performance-Is-Slipping-New-Study-Says"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UC Berkeley researchers found that ChatGPT has not improved over time, and in fact, may have gotten worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Who Caught 2023 Crypto Rally Issues Litecoin Alert, Warns LTC Halving No Longer a Bullish Catalyst]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784806/Trader-Who-Caught-2023-Crypto-Rally-Issues-Litecoin-Alert-Warns-LTC-Halving-No-Longer-a-Bullish-Catalyst</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784806/Trader-Who-Caught-2023-Crypto-Rally-Issues-Litecoin-Alert-Warns-LTC-Halving-No-Longer-a-Bullish-Catalyst"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T00:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trader who rode the crypto surge at the start of the year says that he’s staying away from Litecoin (LTC) even though the peer-to-peer payments network is just a couple of weeks away from its next halving event. Pseudonymous analyst DonAlt tells his 496,000 Twitter followers that based on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Momentum Smashes Above Six Year Long RSI Resistance Line]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562c4d45d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-momentum-smashes-above-six-year-long-rsi/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP rocketed higher by nearly 100% last week, and is up 8% on the day today following last week’s ruling, revealing the asset is not a security.
 
The recent surge to the upside has pushed momentum through a six-year long resistance line, according to the quarterly Relative Strength Index. Will such a high timeframe breakout lead to further upside? Or will this rally fail to produce new highs, much like in 2020?
 
The Cryptocurrency Market Begins To Turn A Corner, Sharply
 
Sentiment across the cryptocurrency market remains bearish overall, but a glimmer of hope arrived last week when a US judge ruled that retail sales of XRP was not the sales of unregistered securities, as the US SEC had claimed.
 
The news immediately dispelled the negativity hanging over XRP and several other coins who …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot;</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Pain As 83% Of SHIB Investors Are Seeing Losses, Is A Change Coming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562c4d454</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/83-of-shib-investors-are-seeing-losses/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu investors are seeing some of the worst losses of the top 20 cryptocurrencies after its price declined by over 90% since its all-time high. Since the cryptocurrency is still relatively new, most of its investors are short-term holders and with the meme coin’s performance over the last year, it is no surprise that the majority of its investors are nursing losses right now.
 
Over 83% Of Shiba Inu Holders Are In Losses
 
Of the over 1.3 million Shiba Inu holders, a total of 83% of them are currently seeing losses. This number is in stark contrast to the likes of Dogecoin (DOGE) and Bitcoin (BTC) which are still seeing around 45-70% of holders in profit despite the persistent bear trend.
 
 
This figure means that only a small percentage of the holders are currently in the green, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former US President Donald Trump Warns of Economic Depression if He’s Not Elected]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562c4fa87</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-us-president-donald-trump-warns-of-economic-depression-if-hes-not-elected/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former U.S. President Donald Trump has warned that the U.S. economy will face “more than a recession” if he is not elected president. Trump also made several other promises, including getting Russia’s President Vladimir Putin to make a deal with Ukraine’s President Volodymyr Zelenskyy “very quickly.”
 
Donald Trump’s Warnings
 
Former U.S. President Donald Trump made several promises and predictions during an interview with Fox News Sunday. He was asked about his plan to get the U.S. economy growing again and whether he thinks the U.S. is going into a recession. “If people think Trump is going to be elected, you’ll never have a recession … because people will start investing,” the former president claimed, adding:
 

If people think I’m not, you’ll have more than a recession. You’re going to have a depression.
 
“But, what I would do is very simple. I’ve got to get interest rates down. We have to get rid of inflation because inflation is a country killer,” he stressed, noting that the Biden administration is “putting the interest rates at a point nobody can borrow.”
 
 
Trump also made a number of other promises. For example, he said: “We’ll close up the border. We’ll become energy independent, then we’re going to be energy dominant. We’ll be taking care of Europe. Energy prices are going to come down. I will get [Russian President] Putin to make a deal with [Ukrainian President] Zelenskyy very quickly. We’re going to have a great world again.” Moreover, Trump opined: “If we don’t win in ’24, this country is finished. I really believe that.”
 
In April, the former president warned that the U.S. dollar is crashing and soon will “no longer be the world standard.” In addition, he cautioned that “we are very close” to a third world war.
 
What do you think about the warnings by former U.S. President Donald Trump regarding the U.S. economy and the dollar? Let us know in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Announces Bold Plan To Back Dollar With Bitcoin, End Bitcoin Taxes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562c5551e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/rfk-jr-plans-to-back-dollar-with-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking at a Heal-the-Divide PAC event, Democratic Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. outlined specific Bitcoin-focused policies that he would enact as president, including gradually backing the U.S. dollar with bitcoin and making bitcoin profits exempt from capital gains taxes.
“My plan would be to start very, very small, perhaps 1% of issued T-bills would be backed by hard currency, by gold, silver platinum or bitcoin,” Kennedy said, describing his vision for returning to a hard currency standard in the U.S. 
He added that, depending on the outcome of that initial step, he would increase that allocation annually.
This potential policy reimagines the financial system, pointing to a future where bitcoin's absolute scarcity and sound monetary principles reinforce the U.S. dollar’…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dylan LeClair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF race gets even more competitive as…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784786/Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-race-gets-even-more-competitive-as</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784786/Bitcoin-Spot-ETF-race-gets-even-more-competitive-as"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valkyrie joins the ETF race and gets approval for a review from the SEC. Short sellers get cautious and begin to hedge their bets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8 Billion People Will Go On-Chain Over the Next Decade: Coinbase Protocols Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149270</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149270/8-billion-people-onchain-blockchain-crypto-10-years-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jesse Pollak is leading the exchange’s efforts on Base, its Ethereum-focused layer-2 network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Momentum Smashes Above Six Year Long RSI Resistance Line]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784763/XRP-Momentum-Smashes-Above-Six-Year-Long-RSI-Resistance-Line</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784763/XRP-Momentum-Smashes-Above-Six-Year-Long-RSI-Resistance-Line"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP rocketed higher by nearly 100% last week, and is up 8% on the day today following last week’s ruling, revealing the asset is not a security. The recent surge to the upside has pushed momentum through a six-year long resistance line, according to the quarterly Relative Strength Index. Will...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, XRP, & Ethereum: Three Top Coins On Brink Of Golden Cross]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784768/Bitcoin-XRP-Ethereum-Three-Top-Coins-On-Brink-Of-Golden-Cross</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784768/Bitcoin-XRP-Ethereum-Three-Top-Coins-On-Brink-Of-Golden-Cross"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Pain As 83% Of SHIB Investors Are Seeing Losses, Is A Change Coming?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784764/Max-Pain-As-83-Of-SHIB-Investors-Are-Seeing-Losses-Is-A-Change-Coming</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784764/Max-Pain-As-83-Of-SHIB-Investors-Are-Seeing-Losses-Is-A-Change-Coming"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Things You Can Buy With The Powerball Jackpot After Taxes: Teslas, Cryptocurrency, Stocks, Gold, Apple Stock And More]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784774/10-Things-You-Can-Buy-With-The-Powerball-Jackpot-After-Taxes-Teslas-Cryptocurrency-Stocks-Gold-Apple-Stock-And-More</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784774/10-Things-You-Can-Buy-With-The-Powerball-Jackpot-After-Taxes-Teslas-Cryptocurrency-Stocks-Gold-Apple-Stock-And-More"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T23:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Powerball jackpot has soared to $1 billion as one of the biggest lottery jackpots of all time. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensler declines to say if, or when, the SEC might appeal Ripple decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784756/Gensler-declines-to-say-if-or-when-the-SEC-might-appeal-Ripple-decision</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784756/Gensler-declines-to-say-if-or-when-the-SEC-might-appeal-Ripple-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Crypto to Buy Now 19 July – FLEX Coin, Stellar, Cardano]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784751/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-19-July-FLEX-Coin-Stellar-Cardano</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784751/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-19-July-FLEX-Coin-Stellar-Cardano"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Predicts $DOGE Could Mimic $XRP’s Massive Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784750/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-DOGE-Could-Mimic-XRPs-Massive-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784750/Crypto-Analyst-Predicts-DOGE-Could-Mimic-XRPs-Massive-Rally"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Bulls Reclaim Crucial Support, Eyeing Retest of $0.38]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784728/Cardano-Bulls-Reclaim-Crucial-Support-Eyeing-Retest-of-038</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784728/Cardano-Bulls-Reclaim-Crucial-Support-Eyeing-Retest-of-038"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New US Senate Bill Tackles Money Laundering via DeFi, Crypto ATMs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562c2ee2e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/new-us-bill-cansee-tackles-money-laundering-via-defi-crypto-atms/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bipartisan group of four senators today (Wednesday) introduced the Crypto-Asset National Security Enhancement and Enforcement (CANSEE) Bill to the United States Senate. In a statement, they explained that the goal of the bill is to  
subject decentralized finance (DeFi) services to the same anti-money laundering (AML)  
and economic sanctions compliance obligations imposed on banks, securities  
brokerages and even centralized crypto exchanges such as  
Binance and Coinbase. 
New Bill Targets DeFi, Crypto ATMs
Specifically, the bill was sponsored by Democratic Senator Jack Reed, with support from fellow Democrat, Mark Warner and Republican lawmakers Mike Rounds  
and Mitt Romney. In addition to DeFi, the new bill is seeking to  
empower public authorities under the US Treasury Department…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Solomon Oladipupo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how Avalanche fared in Q2]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784710/Heres-how-Avalanche-fared-in-Q2</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784710/Heres-how-Avalanche-fared-in-Q2"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Foss & James Lavish | Bitcoin BlackRock ETF | Simply Bitcoin IRL]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784415/Greg-Foss-James-Lavish-Bitcoin-BlackRock-ETF-Simply-Bitcoin-IRL</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784415/Greg-Foss-James-Lavish-Bitcoin-BlackRock-ETF-Simply-Bitcoin-IRL"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nico talks with Greg Foss and James Lavish#bitcoin #jameslavish #gregfossPowered by : Swan Bitcoin► https://www.swan.com/simply► Swan Bitcoin is the best way to build your Bitcoin stack, with automated Bitcoin savings plans and instant purchases. Serving clients of any size, from $10 to $10M+►...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Governance Works on Polygon 2.0 Under New Proposal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784696/How-Governance-Works-on-Polygon-20-Under-New-Proposal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18784696/How-Governance-Works-on-Polygon-20-Under-New-Proposal"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orgasm NFTs? NARS Cosmetics Brand Reveals Eyebrow-Raising Art Auctions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149257</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149257/orgasm-nfts-nars-cosmetics-brand-reveals-eyebrow-raising-art-auctions"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NARS has teamed up with SuperRare and digital artists to drop NFTs for National Orgasm Day, continuing a trend for the beauty brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Platforms And Bitcoin ATMs Face Major KYC Hurdles With New US Bill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562cf8390</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/defi-and-bitcoin-atms-major-hurdles-new-us-bill/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new bill introduced into the US Senate proposes to tighten Know Your Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) regulations for decentralized finance (DeFi) services. 
 
The Crypto-Asset National Security Enhancement and Enforcement (CANSEE) Act aims to prevent money laundering, stop crypto-facilitated crime and sanctions violations, and ensure that DeFi services meet the same AML and economic sanctions compliance as other financial companies, including centralized crypto trading platforms, casinos, and pawn shops.
 
New CANSEE Act Brings DeFi Services Under Same Rules As Banks 
 
According to the press release, DeFi applications are designed to facilitate peer-to-peer financial transactions recorded on blockchains, providing anonymity that enables malicious and criminal actors to ev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Soars 10%, Lifting Altcoins as Bitcoin Dominance Teeters at 1-Month Low]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562c84e9c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/19/xrp-soars-10-lifting-altcoins-as-bitcoin-dominance-teeters-at-1-month-low/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s stall despite the recent wave of positive news is a cause for concern, one observer said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor, James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start Playing Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop'—Do You Need an NFT?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-start-playing-dr-disrespects-deadrop-do-you-need-an-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deadrop is currently in limited early access. Here’s how to unlock the first-person shooter game from Midnight Society.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Securities Regulator Accepts Valkyrie’s Spot Bitcoin ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562c8791f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-securities-regulator-accepts-valkyries-spot-bitcoin-etf-application/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T21:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has formally accepted the spot bitcoin ETF application filed by asset manager Valkyrie. The move, which opens the door to an official review process, follows last week’s acknowledgment of Blackrock’s bitcoin ETF application. 
 
U.S. SEC to Review Valkyrie’s Bitcoin ETF Application, Expects Public Feedback
 
The United States’ securities regulator has given the nod to an official review of the spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) application submitted by financial services company Valkyrie. The application was added to the government agency’s docket on Monday, July 17.
 
The listing on the SEC’s calendar comes after this past Thursday the Commission acknowledged a similar application by Blackrock, the world’s largest asset management firm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Is Quietly Creating an AI Chatbot to Compete With ChatGPT: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149251/apple-is-quietly-creating-an-ai-chatbot-to-compete-with-chatgpt-report"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike ChatGPT, Apple’s tool isn’t meant for public consumption, and the company has no plans to release it to consumers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Blockchain Still Faces Centralization Caveats as Ripple Regulatory Threat Recedes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562b6ceb9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/07/19/xrp-blockchain-still-faces-centralization-caveats-as-ripple-regulatory-threat-recedes/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple scored a partial win against the SEC this week that has been cheered on industry-wide. Why does the project itself remain so controversial?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia to Start Testing ‘Digital Ruble’ CBDC in August Barring Putin's Veto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149238</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149238/russia-to-start-testing-digital-ruble-cbdc-in-august-barring-putins-veto"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill still requires Vladimir Putin’s signature, but if approved, Russia will become one of the largest adopters of CBDCs to date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler Cites 'Wild West' of Crypto in Case to Increase Agency's Budget]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562b036f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/07/19/sec-chair-gensler-cites-wild-west-of-crypto-in-case-to-increase-agencys-budget/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GBTC Discount Is Narrowing; Here's Why It Matters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562b036e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/07/19/the-gbtc-discount-is-narrowing-heres-why-it-matters/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T20:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The possibility the SEC will approve the conversion of GBTC into an ETF is playing a role in the discount narrowing, according to analysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian Soccer Club AC Milan Extends Crypto Sponsorship With BitMEX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149241/italian-soccer-club-ac-milan-extends-crypto-sponsorship-bitmex"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soccer giant AC Milan is sticking with BitMEX, two years after naming the exchange its official cryptocurrency trading partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Hits Pause On Crypto Custody Plans, Citing Regulatory Hurdles]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562b39183</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nasdaq-hits-pause-on-crypto-custody-plans/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a Bloomberg report, Nasdaq, the exchange operator, has announced that it is halting the launch of its crypto custodian business in the United States due to a shifting business and regulatory environment. 
 
Nasdaq’s Crypto Plans On Ice
 
The announcement comes as a surprise as the company previously announced plans to offer custody services for Bitcoin and Ether for institutional investors. The exchange operator had planned to launch the service by the end of the second quarter but now says it will no longer pursue a license related to the business.
 
 
Nasdaq’s decision to halt its digital-asset custodian business is a reflection of the rapidly evolving regulatory environment surrounding crypto. The company cited the changing business and regulatory environment as the reason …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike Father, Spencer Schiff Calls Depression Warning ‘Fearmongering,’ Predicts Hyperdeflationary Boom, Bitcoin Crash; Banks on AI Future]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562b3e292</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/unlike-father-spencer-schiff-calls-depression-warning-fearmongering-predicts-hyperdeflationary-boom-bitcoin-crash-banks-on-ai-future/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to a Zerohedge article titled “The Two Causes of the Coming Great Depression,” Spencer Schiff, son of gold advocate Peter Schiff, labeled the argument “pure fearmongering.” Spencer said he has distanced himself from his dad’s views and now predicts a “hyperdeflationary economic boom.” Notably, the former staunch bitcoin supporter anticipates BTC’s price will “probably fall to near zero over the next few years.”
 
Peter Schiff’s Son, Spencer, Appears to Have Made Complete Turnaround
 
Spencer Schiff, son of renowned economist and gold advocate Peter Schiff, used to engage in debates about bitcoin’s value with his father in 2021. Back then, Spencer was a strong supporter of bitcoin, contradicting his father’s prediction that the cryptocurrency would plummet to zero. In March 2021…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bipartisan Bill Would Give US Treasury Authority Over DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149234</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149234/bipartisan-bill-would-give-us-treasury-authority-over-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill’s sponsors highlighted DeFi and crypto ATMs as vectors for financial crime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Societe Generale’s Crypto Arm Emerges As The First Licensed DASP In France]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562ba3bef</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/societe-generale-is-first-licensed-dasp-in-france/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forge, the crypto subsidiary of European banking giant Societe Generale, has now become the first licensed digital asset service provider (DASP) in France. 
 
According to a report by Bloomberg, France’s stock market regulator, Autorité des Marches Financiers (AMF), approved the first DASP license for SG Forge on Tuesday, July 18, expanding the reach of the Societe Generale Bank in the digital asset space. 
 
Ordinarily, this may sound puzzling as there are a good number of digital assets service providers currently operating in France, such as Binance, Bistamp, Voyager, etc. However, the AMF notes that these businesses are only registered with its agency and do not possess a DASP license. 
 
In France, DASP registration is mandatory for all companies – local or foreign – that intend to pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 80,000 Dormant Ether ICO Tokens Awaken in 2023, Including 61,216 ETH Transfer to Kraken]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562ba7344</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nearly-80000-dormant-ether-ico-tokens-awaken-in-2023-including-61216-eth-transfer-to-kraken/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on onchain metrics, a dormant wallet containing 61,216 ether acquired during the initial coin offering (ICO) has recently transferred the cryptocurrency after lying idle for a span of eight years. The funds have reportedly been sent to the crypto exchange, Kraken. This occurrence marks the fourth instance of activated ETH ICO tokens this year, with a substantial amount of nearly 80,000 dormant ether awakening and becoming active in 2023.
 
Ethereum ICO Whale Moves $116 Million in Ether After 8 Years of Slumber
 
Whale Alert, a blockchain parser, alerted the community on July 18, 2023, about the awakening of 61,216 ether following an eight-year period of inactivity. Lookonchain, onchain market observers, also tweeted regarding the transaction, highlighting that the user paid approxima…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Jackson Pollock’s Historic Paint-Splattered Floor Is Being Immortalized as NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149229</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149229/why-jackson-pollock-historic-paint-splattered-floor-being-immortalized-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T18:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An art collection from the Jackson Pollock Studio and Iconic Moments digitally preserves the famed painter's studio floor on Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EminiFX CEO Bags 9 Years In Prison For $240 Million Crypto And Forex Scam]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562a172ba</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/240-million-crypto-and-forex-scam/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T17:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 18, Eddy Alexandre, the CEO of EminiFX, a cryptocurrency and forex trading platform, was sentenced to nine years in prison by United States District Judge John P. Cronan. 
 
Alexandre was found guilty of defrauding over 25,000 investors of more than $248 million through his fraudulent investment platform.
 
The Deceptive Crypto Scheme Exposed
 
Alexandre’s EminiFX promised investors passive income through automated investments in the digital currency and foreign exchange markets.
 
The “Robo-Advisor Assisted account” offered by EminiFX claimed to double investors’ money within five months, luring thousands to participate in the venture. 
 
 
However, the reality was far from the promised returns as investigations revealed that Alexandre did not invest a substantial portion of the f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Halts Crypto Custody Plans Amid Tough US Regulatory Environment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7562a1eb51</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nasdaq-halts-crypto-custody-plans-amid-tough-us-regulatory-environment/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T17:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adena Friedman, CEO of Nasdaq, the international securities marketplace, announced that the firm is postponing its cryptocurrency custody plans due to the United States’ “regulatory environment.” During a Q2 earnings call, Friedman disclosed that Nasdaq aimed to launch the service last quarter, but it has been put on hold.
 
U.S. ‘Regulatory Environment’ Forces Nasdaq to Postpone Crypto Custody Launch
 
In late March, Nasdaq unveiled its plans to introduce a crypto asset custody service. The company applied for a limited-purpose trust company charter from the New York Department of Financial Services.
 
Initially, it was reported that Nasdaq would provide custody for bitcoin (BTC) and ethereum (ETH), with plans to expand to additional cryptocurrencies. However, during a Q2 earnings call, C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Wants Bitcoin Backed U.S. Dollars and Tax Breaks for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149222</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149222/robert-f-kennedy-jr-wants-bitcoin-backed-u-s-dollars-and-tax-breaks-for-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Bitcoin is among the hardest currencies and the Kennedy administration is going to encourage its proliferation and propagation,” he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Won’t Replace Human Spies, Says Britain’s MI6 Chief]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149220</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149220/ai-wont-replace-human-spies-says-britains-mi6-chief"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of Britain’s SIS says ‘human factors’ important in intelligence gathering can’t yet be replicated by AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nasdaq Delays Crypto Custody Until Regulatory Concerns Die Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149195</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149195/nasdaq-halts-crypto-custody-plans-citing-regulatory-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But Nasdaq CEO Adena Friedman said that the company would “remain committed to supporting the evolution of the digital asset ecosystem.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cymbal Launches 'Human Readable' Ethereum Blockchain Explorer—A Social Etherscan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149202</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149202/cymbal-human-readable-ethereum-blockchain-explorer-etherscan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike traditional explorers that can be difficult to understand, Cymbal is both visual and social—and aimed at the masses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is MiCA? What the EU Crypto Governing Framework Means for You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-mica-what-the-eu-crypto-governing-framework-means-for-you"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA does not cover most NFTs (except fractionalized NFTs and NFTs released as collections). Similarly, it does not cover DeFi apps that exist without an intermediary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Wants More Games—This Simple Tool Could Help Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149166</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149166/solana-wants-more-games-simple-tool-could-help-developers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T15:11:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameShift from Solana Labs aims to make blockchain game development easier for newcomers and traditional game studios alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ICO Whale Moves $116M in ETH to Kraken]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149142</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149142/ethereum-ico-whale-moves-116m-in-eth-to-kraken"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another dormant Ethereum wallet that participated in the project’s ICO has woken up after years of slumber.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles Launching Real World Play Experience in Chicago With Camp]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149147/doodles-launching-real-world-play-experience-chicago-camp"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pharrell Williams-backed NFT project Doodles is expanding further into the real world in partnership with “shop-and-play” retailer Camp.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Société Générale’s Crypto Division Is First To Gain Full License From French Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149144</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149144/societe-generales-crypto-division-is-first-to-gain-full-license-from-french-regulator"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While more than 80 companies are registered with the AMF, SG Forge is the first to be licensed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Police Arrest 21 in $54M USDT Money Laundering Probe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149132/chinese-police-arrest-21-in-54m-usdt-money-laundering-probe"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The suspects allegedly purchased Tether’s stablecoin over-the-counter and sold it at inflated prices over WeChat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZK Virtual Machine Developer RISC Zero Raises $40M in Series A]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149121</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149121/zk-virtual-machine-developer-risc-zero-raises-40m-in-series-a"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the new funding, the Seattle-based startup is getting closer to the launch of its computing platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev Team p0x Labs Raises $25M for Zero-Knowledge Ecosystem Manta Network]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149128</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149128/zero-knowledge-ecosystem-manta-network-raises-25-million-from-polychain-qiming"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T12:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funding round for p0x labs — which has delivered a valuation of $500 million — was led by Polychain Capital and Qiming Venture Partners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis Trading Saw 'Uptick' in Altcoin Activity After Ripple SEC Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149120/genesis-trading-saw-uptick-in-altcoin-activity-after-ripple-sec-decision"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T10:24:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The institutional trading platform’s head of sales explains that the XRP ruling is the latest in a "series of bullish events" for crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Gains 6% on Possible SEC Settlement Conference, Ripple Metaverse Investment]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149118/xrp-gains-6-on-possible-sec-settlement-conference-ripple-metaverse-investment"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T10:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP outperforms the crypto market as hopes of settlement with the SEC and metaverse investment boost buyer sentiments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com Adds Reddit’s Moons Token as Kraken Listing Rumor Fades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149113</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149113/crypto-com-adds-reddits-moons-token-as-kraken-listing-rumor-fades"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T01:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The listing caused the token's value to double for the second day in a row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Assassin's Creed' Creator Ubisoft Throws Weight Behind Cronos Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149100</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149100/ubisoft-crypto-cronos-blockchain-validator"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T01:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gaming giant continues expanding across the blockchain space, this time as a Cronos blockchain validator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Donates $5 Million to the American Journalism Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149106</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149106/openai-donates-5-million-to-the-american-journalism-project"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T00:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ChatGPT creator previously inked a deal with the Associated Press and Shutterstock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Google Exec Predicts AI Sex Robots Could Replace Human Intimacy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149093</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149093/former-google-exec-predicts-ai-sex-robots-replace-humans"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T00:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could AI be taking over our jobs—and replacing our sex partners?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Neopets' Cancels NFT Game After Raising Money From Polygon, Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149074</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149074/neopets-cancels-nft-game-after-raising-money-from-polygon-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T22:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite $4 million in funding from crypto firms, Neopets is ditching NFTs—and making a game that can "better reflect our values and vision."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinfund Raises $158 Million to Boost Early-Stage Crypto, AI Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149062</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149062/coinfund-152-million-seed-early-stage-crypto-startups"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company is launching a new fund after a tumultuous year where many players pulled back from cryptocurrency plays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressman Torres Tells SEC Chairman to End Crypto ‘Crusade’ After Ripple Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149079/end-sec-crusade-rep-ritchie-torres-annalisa-torres-doctrine"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The politician says it's time for the SEC to get comfortable with the “Torres Doctrine.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Decentralized Marketplaces?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=21404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-are-decentralized-marketplaces"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized marketplaces are what blockchains are all about. They allow people to interact and transact on a global, permission-less, and self-executing platform. Houses, hot sauce, and t-shirts can all be bought and sold without needing to trust a middleman.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are cryptocurrency wallets?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/wallets"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wallets are pieces of software that allow a user to hold cryptocurrency. The movement of cryptocurrencies to and from and wallets are controlled by public and private keys. There are several different types of wallets, characterised by their internet connectivity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Broadens AI Bets Beyond OpenAI With Meta Alliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149076</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149076/microsoft-meta-llama-azure-partnership"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T20:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating LLama 2 into the Azure cloud-computing platform brings together two tech titans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Explains How Ethereum Plans to Make Crypto Wallets as Simple as Email]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149063/vitalik-buterin-explains-how-ethereum-plans-to-make-crypto-wallets-as-simple-as-email"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T20:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account abstraction, which would make it possible to store seed phrases in smart contracts, is "a pretty big deal," he said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asset Managers Back Bitcoin But Hold More Ethereum in CoinShares Poll]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149066</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149066/bitcoin-ethereum-asset-manager-poll-coinshares"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T19:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new survey offers a tantalizing insight into sentiment among institutions—and it's clear that BlackRock's filing for a spot Bitcoin ETF has had a huge impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opepen PFPs Are Taking Over NFT Twitter—Here's What's Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149026/opepen-pfps-taking-over-nft-twitter-heres-whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Opepen NFT collection from Jack Butcher became the center of a viral trend on Crypto Twitter, driving up engagement—and prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arkham’s ‘Dox-to-Earn’ Platform Offers Bounty on $415 Million FTX Mystery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149042</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149042/arkhams-dox-to-earn-platform-offers-bounty-on-415-million-ftx-mystery"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company's so-called Intel Exchange went live and Arkham itself has posted its largest bounty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cools and Drops Below $30,000—But XRP, Chainlink Surging]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149014</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149014/bitcoin-cools-and-drops-below-30000-but-altcoins-xrp-link-surge"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has again dropped below $30,000 per coin. But these altcoins are surging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trading Dropped 43% in Q2 Despite Climbing Bitcoin, Ethereum Prices]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149028</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149028/crypto-trading-dropped-43-in-q2-despite-climbing-bitcoin-ethereum-prices"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The contraction in crypto trading volumes comes despite a 7% uptick in Bitcoin's price throughout the quarter, said CoinGecko.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connor Sephton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hold Your Horses: Stability AI Delays Stable Diffusion XL v1.0 Release]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=149016</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/149016/hold-your-horses-stability-ai-delays-stable-diffusion-xl-v1-release"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI pushed the release of the latest version of Stable Diffusion XL "for a week or so" to do some technical tweaking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Disrespect's 'Deadrop': Early Access Gameplay From Snapshot VI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/8l21EHoa/dr-disrespects-deadrop-early-access-gameplay-from-snapshot-vi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin playtests Dr. Disrespect and Midnight Society's first-person shooter Deadrop and shares the latest game updates, as well as her opinions on the game in development. Currently, Deadrop offers Polygon Founders Pass NFTs with no other crypto plans revealed just yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['More and More' Game Publishers Will Embrace NFTs: Mythical Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wBWogSkl/more-and-more-game-publishers-will-embrace-nfts-mythical-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:28:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of EA Sports and Fortnite creator Epic Games embracing Nike's NFT platform, Mythical Games CEO John Linden tells Decrypt's Andrew Hayward how quickly he expects to see more major traditional game publishers enter the blockchain space and how quickly the industry will scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gran Saga Unlimited Early Access: Inside the Anime MMORPG on Aptos]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JeFWMVwo/gran-saga-unlimited-early-access-inside-the-anime-mmorpg-on-aptos"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T21:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin plays Gran Saga: Unlimited's second community playtest, reports her findings, and offers her opinion and insights on the upcoming game, which will offer optional Aptos NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves' Moe Says Blockchain Games Will 'Eventually' Be Accepted by Livestreamers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xHhh62ID/100-thieves-moe-says-blockchain-games-will-eventually-be-accepted-by-livestreamers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[100 Thieves content creator and gamer Moe also goes by "Yassuo" online after his favorite League of Legends character. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks him about 100 Thieves' future crypto plans and whether Moe thinks creators like xQc and Pokimane might ever come around to blockchain games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Games of the Future Are Going to Be Different," Says Splinterlands Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sQv6zcil/games-of-the-future-are-going-to-be-different-says-splinterlands-cofounder"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Splinterlands Cofounder Matt Rosen tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the game has evolved over its five-year history and why he doesn't listen to the FUD around crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Champions Ascension: Like 'For Honor' with NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/gvM9ajww/inside-champions-ascension-like-for-honor-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plai Labs Marketing Director Payton Kaleiwahea tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about player response to the combat game Champions Ascension in development, which offers arena combat, raid bosses, AI landscape features, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Activision VP Michael Lee: Gaming Is Crypto's 'Killer App']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M9ulXrb3/ex-activision-vp-michael-lee-gaming-is-cryptos-killer-app"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Activision Vice President Michael Lee is now the SVP of Growth at Matter Labs. At the 3XP gaming conference, Lee sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss crypto gaming and give his predictions for the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes with AMGI Studios and My Pet Hooligan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/eQ71oapI/behind-the-scenes-with-amgi-studios-and-my-pet-hooligan"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes to Burbank, California for a behind-the-scenes tour of AMGI Studios, the developers of upcoming game My Pet Hooligan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Legend of Arcardia Chose Sui Over EVM Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/H6JSRJIk/why-legend-of-arcardia-chose-sui-over-evm-chains"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legend of Arcadia Executive Producer Andy Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the game and why they switched from EVM to new protocol Sui.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>