<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-10-25T22:13:22.449Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-10-25T22:13:22.449Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Supply On Exchanges Fall To 2015 Levels, 3 Price Targets For Bulls]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994651/Ethereum-Supply-On-Exchanges-Fall-To-2015-Levels-3-Price-Targets-For-Bulls</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994651/Ethereum-Supply-On-Exchanges-Fall-To-2015-Levels-3-Price-Targets-For-Bulls"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T22:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum supply on exchanges has been on a steady decline since the FTX crash happened back in 2022. This was triggered by a growing distrust for centralized exchanges and investors choosing to self-custody their tokens as a result. The constant decline has now seen the Ethereum being held...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Chance At Redemption: Analyst Puts MATIC Price At $1.5]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994642/A-Chance-At-Redemption-Analyst-Puts-MATIC-Price-At-15</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994642/A-Chance-At-Redemption-Analyst-Puts-MATIC-Price-At-15"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T22:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MATIC price has disappointed investors over the course of this year after falling from $1.5 to $0.5. This extended bear trend has significantly impacted investor morale but one analyst sees a redemption in the future of the altcoin, in the form of a 220% surge to $1.5. MATIC Price To Make A...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitmain Unveils New T21 Bitcoin Miner; Offers BTC Fluctuation Protection Plan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8b7c156</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitmain-unveils-new-t21-bitcoin-miner-offers-btc-fluctuation-protection-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, the bitcoin mining rig manufacturer Bitmain announced the introduction of a new air-cooled BTC miner, the T21 Antminer. The new device boasts a production capacity of up to 190 terahash per second (TH/s) and maintains an efficiency ratio of approximately 19 joules per terahash (J/T).
 
Bitmain Debuts T21 Antminer
 
After the recent unveiling of Microbt’s latest mining equipment, Bitmain, a competitor, has added the T21 Antminer to its extensive range of hashing devices. On October 25, Bitmain showcased the T21, capable of delivering 190 TH/s with an efficiency rating of 19 J/T.
 
Additionally, the company introduced an optional bitcoin price fluctuation plan, ensuring customers receive compensation if BTC’s prices fall below the strike on a reference day within a protected period.
 

 
The bitcoin fluctuation protection plan offers various tiers, depending on the duration of the protected period, with Bitmain asserting that “compensation shall be paid immediately upon the triggering event.”
 
The T21 Antminer is the latest in a series of launches by Bitmain, following two new devices from the S21 series introduced last month. The S21 Hyd achieves up to 335 TH/s with an efficiency rating of 16 J/T, while the air-cooled S21 miner provides up to 200 TH/s with an efficiency rating of about 17.5 J/T.
 
 
While the S21 air-cooled machine offers slightly superior ratings compared to the T21, the latter, however, surpasses the S19 Antminers in efficiency ratios. The specifications for the T21 detail a power consumption of 3,610 watts, with expected shipping in the first quarter of 2024.
 
The T21 is also comparable to the S21 air-cooled Antminer in terms of size and weight. This year has seen the release of several new devices by all three major bitcoin mining machine manufacturers: Bitmain with three, Canaan with two, and Microbt with three.
 
What do you think about Bitmain’s new bitcoin miner the T12? Share your thoughts and opinions about this subject in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hashdex sits down with SEC over spot Bitcoin ETF application]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994634/Hashdex-sits-down-with-SEC-over-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-application</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994634/Hashdex-sits-down-with-SEC-over-spot-Bitcoin-ETF-application"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asset manager Hashdex recently met with the U.S. SEC to address the regulator’s concerns over its application for a spot Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘No evidence’ Hamas raised millions in crypto, Elliptic says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994630/No-evidence-Hamas-raised-millions-in-crypto-Elliptic-says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994630/No-evidence-Hamas-raised-millions-in-crypto-Elliptic-says"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:39:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elliptic says that crypto has a “weakness” as a fundraising tool: the public nature of blockchain technology]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovery firm proposes cracking former Ripple CTO's $244M Bitcoin hard drive]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994599/Recovery-firm-proposes-cracking-former-Ripple-CTOs-244M-Bitcoin-hard-drive</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994599/Recovery-firm-proposes-cracking-former-Ripple-CTOs-244M-Bitcoin-hard-drive"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Thomas, the former chief technology officer at Ripple, has an IronKey hard drive containing 7,002 BTC with only two attempts at guessing a password remaining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominance Hits Fresh 30-Month High as Ether, Altcoins Lag in Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994598/Bitcoin-Dominance-Hits-Fresh-30-Month-High-as-Ether-Altcoins-Lag-in-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994598/Bitcoin-Dominance-Hits-Fresh-30-Month-High-as-Ether-Altcoins-Lag-in-Rally"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's [BTC] market share of all cryptocurrencies rose to a fresh 30-month high Wednesday as BTC continues to beat most altcoins or alternative cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S14 E17: Rodolfo Andragnes on Labitconf 2023 & Argentinian Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994582/S14-E17-Rodolfo-Andragnes-on-Labitconf-2023-Argentinian-Elections</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994582/S14-E17-Rodolfo-Andragnes-on-Labitconf-2023-Argentinian-Elections"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Binance About Dominating Hong Kong’s Crypto Scene? The Truth About HKVAEX]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8b307d6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/is-binance-about-dominating-hong-kongs-crypto-scene/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange, has recently been facing some speculation concerning its potential association with a newly unveiled trading platform in Hong Kong.
 
According to local news media South China Morning Post, citing sources familiar with the matter, Binance might be the force behind HKVAEX, a newly minted crypto trading platform in Hong Kong. 
 
 
HKVAEX: A New Contender Or A Strategic Move?
 
Established in December 2022, HKVAEX commenced its trading operations two months later, in February. While the platform presents itself as an independent entity operating under the umbrella of BX Services Limited, the report citing three industry insiders points towards shared resources with Binance. 
 
This speculation is further fueled by the discovery that the ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis moves for early bankruptcy payouts as NYAG suit applies pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994586/Genesis-moves-for-early-bankruptcy-payouts-as-NYAG-suit-applies-pressure</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994586/Genesis-moves-for-early-bankruptcy-payouts-as-NYAG-suit-applies-pressure"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Bitcoin Replace Gold? Bloomberg Analyst Expresses His Views]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994577/Will-Bitcoin-Replace-Gold-Bloomberg-Analyst-Expresses-His-Views</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994577/Will-Bitcoin-Replace-Gold-Bloomberg-Analyst-Expresses-His-Views"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Titans Microsoft and Google Make AI Moves Down Under]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203305/tech-titans-microsoft-and-google-set-their-sights-down-under"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the appeal of a largely untapped market is clear, some say the move could also reflect a regulatory chill in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Titans Microsoft and Google Make AI Moves Down Under]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994572/Tech-Titans-Microsoft-and-Google-Make-AI-Moves-Down-Under</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994572/Tech-Titans-Microsoft-and-Google-Make-AI-Moves-Down-Under"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram's Maestro Bot Hit By $500,000 ETH Heist Due To Contract Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994583/Telegrams-Maestro-Bot-Hit-By-500000-ETH-Heist-Due-To-Contract-Vulnerability</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994583/Telegrams-Maestro-Bot-Hit-By-500000-ETH-Heist-Due-To-Contract-Vulnerability"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preston Pysh: Bitcoin Is Anti-Totalitarianism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8bcf76a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/bitcoin-anti-totalitarianism"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the face of ongoing challenges to our cherished freedoms, it is imperative to critically examine the forces at play that threaten the very fabric of democracy. The ideals of freedom and open markets are at risk of being undermined by influential political forces seeking to impose oppressive order and control in the name of security. This article delves into the pressing need to fix our manipulated markets, protect Bitcoin and its inherent anti-totalitarian qualities, and inform US policymakers that democratic values are what’s at stake. 
The Erosion of Free Markets and Capitalism
People who think we currently have capitalism and free and open markets haven’t been paying attention. The American economic landscape, once a paragon of capitalism, has undergone a seismic shift, particularly …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Pysh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Explains How Investors Can Stay Alert Ahead of Bull Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994580/Crypto-Analyst-Explains-How-Investors-Can-Stay-Alert-Ahead-of-Bull-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994580/Crypto-Analyst-Explains-How-Investors-Can-Stay-Alert-Ahead-of-Bull-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Binance About Dominating Hong Kong’s Crypto Scene? The Truth About HKVAEX]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994556/Is-Binance-About-Dominating-Hong-Kongs-Crypto-Scene-The-Truth-About-HKVAEX</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994556/Is-Binance-About-Dominating-Hong-Kongs-Crypto-Scene-The-Truth-About-HKVAEX"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchange, has recently been facing some speculation concerning its potential association with a newly unveiled trading platform in Hong Kong. According to local news media South China Morning Post, citing sources familiar with the matter, Binance might...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If you bought just $100 of Solana… #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994554/If-you-bought-just-100-of-Solana-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994554/If-you-bought-just-100-of-Solana-shorts"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you bought just $100 of Solana on it's ICO, here's how much you'd have! ●▬▬▬▬▬▬Freebies▬▬▬▬▬▬▬●📖FREE WEEKLY MARKET & NFT UPDATE REPORTS https://t.me/AltcoinBuzzSignals➡️ FREE CRYPTO PROJECT EVALUATION CHECKLISTUse this checklist to help you with the research and due diligence process for any...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Japan Is Leading the Race to Regulate Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8be3d98</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/25/how-japan-is-leading-the-race-to-regulate-stablecoins/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japan’s stablecoin regulations attempt to address some of the biggest fears about major stablecoins: Do issuers really have the assets to back them?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Parker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Altcoins Experience Unusual Volume Spike on South Korean Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994523/5-Altcoins-Experience-Unusual-Volume-Spike-on-South-Korean-Exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994523/5-Altcoins-Experience-Unusual-Volume-Spike-on-South-Korean-Exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the data, there is a South Korea-focused rising wave in the transaction volumes of five altcoins. Here is the list. Continue Reading: 5 Altcoins Experience Unusual Volume Spike on South Korean Exchanges]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-Awaited Development for Polygon (MATIC) Launches Today]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994524/Long-Awaited-Development-for-Polygon-MATIC-Launches-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994524/Long-Awaited-Development-for-Polygon-MATIC-Launches-Today"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developers released a new statement today for the development, which is extremely important for the Polygon (MATIC) ecosystem. Continue Reading: Long-Awaited Development for Polygon (MATIC) Launches Today]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chief Gary Gensler Affirms Crypto As Securities, Cites 'Fraud, Scams, Bankruptcies']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994525/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Affirms-Crypto-As-Securities-Cites-Fraud-Scams-Bankruptcies</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994525/SEC-Chief-Gary-Gensler-Affirms-Crypto-As-Securities-Cites-Fraud-Scams-Bankruptcies"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC chief Gary Gensler remains resolute in his belief that many digital currencies fall under existing securities regulations, despite significant resistance from the crypto community. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elliptic says scale of crypto-based terrorism funding is being misrepresented]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994489/Elliptic-says-scale-of-crypto-based-terrorism-funding-is-being-misrepresented</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994489/Elliptic-says-scale-of-crypto-based-terrorism-funding-is-being-misrepresented"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elliptic said Wednesday that recent figures being used to portray the scale of crypto fundraising by Hamas are being misrepresented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Prediction: Prepare For 5,000% God Candle Above $30]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8ba0a51</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-prediction-5000-30/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the widespread uncertainty in the crypto market following the rally, one crypto analyst has maintained steadfast in their belief in the XRP price. The analyst has come forward with an incredibly bullish analysis and forecast that will see the XRP price rally 5,000%.
 
A God Candle In The Making
 
On Tuesday, crypto analyst Egrag Crypto came forward with their most recent analysis of the XRP price. Egrag’s conclusion on this analysis came with the expectation of what is usually referred to as a ‘God candle’. This simply means a continuously increasing price trend that leaves a straight green line in its wake.
 
 
The post was an update to a previous post where the analyst had first talked about “GODS Candle”. Egrag explains that the XRP price is still trying to scale its personal ‘Berl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trader Who Nailed 2022's Crypto Crash Sends A Warning: Read This Before Going Long]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994498/Trader-Who-Nailed-2022s-Crypto-Crash-Sends-A-Warning-Read-This-Before-Going-Long</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994498/Trader-Who-Nailed-2022s-Crypto-Crash-Sends-A-Warning-Read-This-Before-Going-Long"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) is treading on shaky ground despite its recent remarkable ascent, a widely followed crypto analyst has warned, expressing concerns amid the prevailing read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex Unveils Tether-Denominated Bond Set to Debut in November]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8baadfe</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitfinexs-unveils-tether-denominated-bond-set-to-debut-in-november/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex Securities has announced its first-ever  
tokenized bond set to debut in November. This bond, denominated in  
Tether and offering a coupon rate of 10% over 36 months, aims to enhance the process of raising capital. 
Dubbed ALT2611, the tokenized bond is set to acquire  
risks associated with the debt and equity of microfinance organizations, small  
financial institutions, leasing companies, and banks across Italy, Romania,  
Moldova, and other developing nations along the historic Silk Road, the crypto  
exchange said.  
Bitfinex Lures Investors with Lucrative Returns 
Paolo Ardoino, the Chief Technology Officer at  
Bitfinex and the incoming CEO of Tether praised this initiative, describing it as the dawn  
of a new era in the world of finance. Bitfinex Securities aims to creat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Japan Is Leading the Race to Regulate Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994478/How-Japan-Is-Leading-the-Race-to-Regulate-Stablecoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18994478/How-Japan-Is-Leading-the-Race-to-Regulate-Stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Debtors Evaluate Bids for Dormant Crypto Exchange’s Revival]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8bbfa68</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ftx-debtors-evaluate-bids-for-dormant-crypto-exchanges-revival/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T20:08:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Insiders reveal that FTX creditors are sifting through bids from various entities eager to breathe life into the dormant crypto exchange. The company’s investment banker highlighted that FTX interacts with “multiple parties every day.”
 
FTX Creditors Sift Through Offers for Exchange’s Possible Reawakening
 
Throughout the year, whispers of FTX’s potential revival have surfaced approximately four times. During his first interview post-FTX collapse in January 2023, FTX’s restructuring head, CEO John J. Ray III, hinted at a resurgence. In a subsequent April hearing, the topic resurfaced. By mid-June, murmurs of “FTX 2.0” were in the air, and with each whisper, the value of FTX’s native crypto asset FTT spikes.
 
On October 24, Kevin M. Cofsky, the financial strategist from Perella Weinberg P…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Now Up Over 110% This Year In Anticipation of Spot ETF Approval And Halving]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8a7da53</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/bitcoin-now-up-over-110-this-year-in-anticipation-of-spot-etf-approval-and-halving"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T19:36:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has risen over 110% in 2023 at the time of writing, where the price of the asset started the year off at $16,677 on January 1, has now pumped to above $35,000 only 10 months later. With more room to run this year as hype builds in the market around the potential approval of a spot Bitcoin ETF by the SEC and the upcoming halving event, many are now questioning if this is the end of this cycle's eventful bear market.
Since the few disastrous incidents that happened in the bear market causing the price drop, things are now looking more optimistic. As some of the worlds largest asset managers, including Fidelity, VanEck and WisdomTree, have filed in hopes to be the first in the United States to get approval for a spot Bitcoin ETF. One name in particular though is making more headlines than the rest, and that is the worlds largest asset manger BlackRock, who manages about $10 trillion.
BlackRock CEO Larry Fink recently made an appearance on Fox Business stating that their clients around the world are interested in getting exposure to Bitcoin, saying the recent price rally has been a "flight to quality." Earlier this month, Bloomberg ETF analysts Eric Balchunas and James Seyffart raised their approval odds for a spot Bitcoin ETF by the SEC to 90% by January 10, 2024.



The next Bitcoin having is expected to take place in roughly 180 days in late April, 2024. The event will see the Bitcoin block reward drop from 6.25 BTC per block to only 3.125 BTC. This will be the fourth halving in Bitcoin's history, with the first happening in November 2012, the second happened in July 2016, and the third happened in May 2020. Historically, a year leading up to and after the halving, the price of BTC goes up substantially.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You Playing Starfield? Over 11 Million Gamers Are, Says Microsoft CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203299</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203299/starfield-11-million-players-best-selling-game-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T19:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first new universe for Bethesda in 25 years was the top-selling video game last month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Show Signs Of Euphoria, Will This End The Rally?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8a1591a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-investors-signs-of-euphoria-will-end-rally/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T19:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows that traders on social media are showing signs of euphoria right now, something that could lead to a setback for the Bitcoin rally.
 
Bitcoin Social Volume Suggests Rise Of Bullish Bias Among Investors
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Santiment, BTC traders have turned optimistic on social media after the latest price surge. The relevant indicator here is the “social volume,” which tells us about the amount of discussion that social media users are taking part in related to a given topic.
 
The metric calculates this in terms of the unique number of posts/threads/messages that are making mentions of the term in question. By “unique,” what’s meant here is that every post is counted only once, regardless of how many mentions it contains of the topic (as long as…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Teams Up With MoonPay for Web3 Push]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8a37408</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/10/25/mastercard-teams-up-with-moonpay-for-web3-push/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T19:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MoonPay will incorporate compliance-friendly Mastercard's Crypto Credential system and integrate payments tech like Mastercard Send and Click to Pay, according to a blog post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Allison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stocks Are Down, Bitcoin Is Way Up—Will This Time Be Different?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203287</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203287/stocks-are-down-bitcoin-is-way-up-will-this-time-be-different"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF hype can explain a lot about why BTC appears to have decoupled from stocks. But analysts say that's not the only reason.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried’s Desperate Last Stand]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8ae25ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/10/25/sam-bankman-frieds-desperate-last-stand/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If his trial were going better, the fallen crypto king wouldn’t be testifying in his own defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Gensler Won’t Say What’s Next With Bitcoin ETFs After Grayscale Loss]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8af406e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/10/25/secs-gensler-wont-say-whats-next-with-bitcoin-etfs-after-grayscale-loss/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The agency chairman also declined to give any indications on timing or the order applications might be considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bulls Rejoice: Blockstream CEO Sees Price Over $100,000 – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8a8e684</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-ceo-sees-price-over-100000/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) enthusiasts have been eagerly anticipating a monumental surge past the $100,000 mark, spurred by the cryptocurrency’s robust fundamentals. However, amidst the recent upheaval in the market, optimism has been met with volatility. 
 
Adam Back, the CEO of Blockstream, expressed his belief in Bitcoin’s potential, underlining that its current valuation should have ideally surpassed the coveted six-figure milestone. 
 
Back’s comment arrives during a period of significant market turbulence triggered by the abrupt removal of BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust from the listing of the Depository Trust & Clearing Corporation, sending ripples through the crypto community.
 
 
Stahp reloading, you guys crashed dtcc website  it doesn’t mean anything anyway. Yes ETF coming in a while, but …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nansen: FTX and Alameda Research Wallets Shift $8.6M in Crypto Assets to Binance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8abcfd5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nansen-ftx-and-alameda-research-wallets-shift-8-6m-in-crypto-assets-to-binance/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T18:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday, Nansen, an onchain analytics provider, illuminated a series of intriguing transactions originating from FTX and Alameda Research addresses, now under the stewardship of the FTX creditors. A substantial sum of $8.6 million in cryptocurrency assets found its way to an address associated with Binance, the largest exchange in the world by trade volume.
 
$8.6M in Crypto Assets Transferred From FTX and Alameda to Binance
 
In a breakdown of onchain data, it was revealed that crypto addresses linked to FTX and Alameda, laden with assets such as LINK, AAVE, MKR, and ETH, orchestrated a movement of $8.6 million. This onchain move did not escape the watchful eyes of Nansen, a firm dedicated to blockchain intelligence and analytics. Nansen detailed the transaction, disclosing the movem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Retreats From $35K; Miner Selling Pressure May Cap Prices, Crypto Hedge Fund Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8948c56</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/10/25/bitcoin-retreats-from-35k-miner-selling-pressure-may-cap-prices-crypto-hedge-fund-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC could run towards $40,000-$45,000 after consolidating around current prices, Capriole Investments said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All of a Sudden, It’s All About Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a896c482</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/10/25/all-of-a-sudden-its-all-about-bitcoin/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a lot of activity happening in Bitcoin tech development – with innovations that might help the original and oldest blockchain to catch up with the boom of projects building in the Ethereum ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Poised To Explode As Grayscale Makes A Major Play]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8913719</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-explode-grayscale-play/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) has been slowly creeping into the mainstream and onto the radar of major players. This rising popularity of the cryptocurrency has led it to Grayscale, as the asset manager unveils a new way for institutional investors to gain exposure to Cardano.
 
Grayscale Announces Cardano Indices
 
On Tuesday, October 24, Grayscale Investments announced that it is bringing five new crypto indices to the crypto market. These five indices would allow institutional investors to gain some level of exposure to a number of assets in the industry without having to go through the hassle of actually buying the coins.
 
 
Of the five indices that were announced, Cardano made the cut as one of the smart contract platforms that were being explored. This adds to the existing exposure already availabl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried's Trial Gamble: To Testify in His Defense]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a891678f</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sam-bankman-frieds-trial-gamble-to-testify-in-his-defense/"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried (SBF), the indicted founder of the  
cryptocurrency exchange FTX, will testify in his defense. This move,  
announced by his attorney during a recent conference call, paves the way for a  
potentially intense cross-examination by federal prosecutors who aim to  
scrutinize his role in the collapse of the crypto exchange.
According to a report by CNBC, SBF's decision to  
take the stand followed a resolution  
of a dispute regarding his access to attention-deficit/hyperactivity  
disorder (ADHD) medication. This issue had previously  
raised concern about his ability to actively participate in the ongoing trial.
A Risky Legal Strategy?
SBF’s decision to testify was made after  
his legal team, in collaboration with the prosecution, ensured that he had an  
adequate supply …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Payment Splitting And Switching: Improving Privacy And Payment Success Simultaneously]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a893c982</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/payment-splitting-and-switching-improving-privacy-and-payment-success-simultaneously"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T17:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the fundamental limitations of the Lightning protocol is how payment routing is handled and accomplished. It is entirely source routed, meaning that the sender of a payment is the one who constructs the entire route from themselves to the receiver in order to facilitate the payment. This presents an issue when it comes to the changing balances of channels over time as they are routing payments between numerous different users across the network, once a sender "locks in" and decides on a specific route, that route cannot be changed until a failure message makes it way back to the sender, allowing them to construct an entirely new route going around the point where the initial attempt failed. 
This necessitates either dealing with a cumbersome and annoying UX, or the use of payment pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Selling the Pump? Estate Moves $8.6M Ethereum, Chainlink, Aave and Maker to Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203262</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203262/ftx-moves-8-6-million-ethereum-chainlink-aave-maker-to-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The funds are on the move again—this time to the collapsed exchange’s rival]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amanda Cassatt on Web3 Marketing and the early days of Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5Cm0ENyc/amanda-cassatt-on-web3-marketing-and-the-early-days-of-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week's episode, our host is joined by Amanda Cassatt! 

Amanda is the founder of Serotonin, a web3 marketing agency, the author of the first book ever published on web3 marketing, and led the marketing team that helped bring Ethereum to market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hits $35,000, Reaching 16-Month High Amid ETF Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203274</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203274/bitcoin-hits-35000-reaching-16-month-high-amid-spot-etf-hype"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin continues its climb amid speculation of an imminent ETF approval, this time breaching a key milestone not seen since May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin = Anti-Totalitarianism]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74a8993861</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/legal/bitcoin-anti-totalitarianism"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T16:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the face of ongoing challenges to our cherished freedoms, it is imperative to critically examine the forces at play that threaten the very fabric of democracy. The ideals of freedom and open markets are at risk of being undermined by influential political forces seeking to impose oppressive order and control in the name of security. This article delves into the pressing need to fix our manipulated markets, protect Bitcoin and its inherent anti-totalitarian qualities, and inform US policymakers that democratic values are what’s at stake. 
The Erosion of Free Markets and Capitalism
People who think we currently have capitalism and free and open markets haven’t been paying attention. The American economic landscape, once a paragon of capitalism, has undergone a seismic shift, particularly …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Pysh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Parallel' Game Adds Over 120 New NFT Cards in Planetfall Expansion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203199</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203199/parallel-game-adds-over-120-new-nft-cards-planetfall-expansion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel is releasing new cards for its game via blind bundles. While little is known about the cards so far, some new art has been revealed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried Will Testify at His Criminal Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203261</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203261/sam-bankman-fried-will-testify"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T15:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX founder will testify after the defense presents three witnesses, his lead attorney, Mark Cohen of Cohen & Gresser, told the court.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Stablecoins and How Do You Use Them?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins are cryptocurrencies that claim to be backed by fiat currencies. Unlike cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin, their prices remain steady.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Scott Chipolina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Shrapnel' Game Studio Neon Machine Raises $20 Million Led by Polychain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203208</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203208/shrapnel-game-studio-neon-machine-raises-20-million-led-polychain"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neon Machine has completed its Series A funding round to polish the upcoming shooter Shrapnel, which is built around NFTs on Avalanche.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Deploys New POL Token Contracts on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203226/polygon-launches-new-pol-token-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of Polygon's updated roadmap, the new POL token will replace the MATIC token as the ecosystem's primary coordination tool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Winners of This Week's Crypto Rally? MINA, Chainlink, and PEPE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203218/biggest-winners-week-crypto-rally-mina-chainlink-pepe"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T09:43:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Besides heavyweights in Bitcoin and Ethereum, several notable altcoins also enjoyed serious rallies amid the spot ETF craze.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Tech 'Stuck in the Eighties': Fantom's Andre Cronje]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203217</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203217/blockchain-tech-is-stuck-eighties-says-fantoms-andre-cronje"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T09:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of Sonic's testnet yesterday, Andre Cronje is hoping to bring Fantom and blockchain technology back to the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Could Use a Poison Pill to Combat AI Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203153</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203153/ai-prompt-data-poisoning-nightshared"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T02:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers hope Nightshade will serve as an example of "data poisoning" that can prevent unauthorized ingestion of artists' works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[While Meta Pushes Into AI, 34 States File Suit Over Child Manipulation Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203194</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203194/while-meta-pushes-into-ai-34-states-file-suit-for-child-manipulation-claims"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T01:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Meta’s claims of a safe environment, states argue that Facebook and Instagram pose risks to the mental health of kids.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Habitat is Meta's Vision for the Future of Human-Robot Cohabitation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203160</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203160/meta-human-robot-habitat-embodied-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From following you around to helping you tidy up your room, Meta's latest AI advancements promise a future where robots are more than just tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adult Entertainment Actors Say Their Defenses Against AI Are More Elusive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203159</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203159/porn-stars-fight-ai-deepfakes-with-less-support"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like SAG-AFTRA, Adult film performers seek protection from unauthorized AI deepfake porn and compensation for their work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Execs Are Deserting The Company–Here’s Who They Are]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203181/who-are-the-executives-leaving-binance"/>
        <updated>2023-10-25T00:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the reasons varied, sixteen executives have left the company over the past few years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Senators Set in Motion Bipartisan Proof-of-Reserves Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203131/u-s-senators-set-in-motion-bipartisan-proof-of-reserves-bill"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T22:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto advocates across the spectrum applaud the legislative action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Submits Final Argument to Dismiss SEC Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203106</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203106/coinbase-submits-final-argument-to-dismiss-sec-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T22:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal loggerheads have persisted between the SEC and Coinbase since June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Fines BlackRock $2.5 Million as Bitcoin ETF Review Awaits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203120/sec-fines-blackrock-bitcoin-etf-review"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T21:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not the first time the Wall Street giant has been fined by the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Funds Gain $57 Million in Fresh Cash Amid ETF Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203101/bitcoin-funds-gain-57-million-amid-etf-mania"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most deposits went to spot Bitcoin ETFs in Canada and Germany, showing that investors want physical Bitcoin over anything else, said Coinshares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ally Tom Emmer Drops Out of Race for House Speaker After Trump Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203109</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203109/tom-emmer-nominated-as-house-speaker-to-crypto-cheers-trump-jeers"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T20:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ardently pro-crypto congressman was one vote away from the gavel, but the former president torpedoed his chances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Lender BlockFi Ends Bankruptcy With a Plan to Repay Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203099/blockfi-ends-bankruptcy-prepares-to-return-customer-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T19:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlockFi custodial wallet customers can submit withdrawal requests today, but interest bearing account customers will have to wait until 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maison Margiela Invites Its Fans To Play Blockchain Bingo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203053/maison-margiela-numbers-mint-blockchin-bingo"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To advance in the numerological project, minters have got to collect them all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wobbles as BlackRock ETF Removed From DTCC List]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=203012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/203012/bitcoin-wobbles-as-blockrock-etf-removed-from-dtcc-list"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T17:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The removal puts a damper on suspicions that a spot Bitcoin ETF was only days away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can a FanDuel Co-Founder's 'Fantasy Music' Game Help Discover the Next Taylor Swift?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202927/fanduel-cofounder-fantasy-music-game-help-discover-next-taylor-swift"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vault’s Solana NFT music platform is spinning up a fantasy sports-like experience around emerging artists. Can it push them to prominence?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Denis Katana Helped Russian Crime Boss Launder Money With Bitcoin, Says Spanish Judge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202807/hacker-denis-katana-bitcoin-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T15:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Bitcoin czar' is accused of advising a crime ring to launder their money with Bitcoin because of its “lack of state control.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dYdX Releases Cosmos-Based Chain Source Code Ahead of Mainnet Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202941/dydx-releases-cosmos-based-chain-source-code-ahead-mainnet-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:07:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of the open source code marks the initial phase of dYdX Chain’s mainnet launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Soar Double Digits as Crypto Markets Add $100 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202944/bitcoin-ethereum-soar-crypto-markets-add-100-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T12:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and Ethereum soared nearly double digits early on Tuesday, as the wider crypto market added nearly 10% to its market cap overnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz-Backed Nym Launches $300M Privacy-Centric 'Innovation Fund']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202861/andreessen-horowitz-backs-nym-300m-privacy-centric-innovation-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applications for the innovation fund, which is not strictly limited to Nym’s privacy-preserving tech, will be accepted starting in November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest Sells $5.8M in Coinbase, Grayscale Bitcoin Trust Shares as Crypto Market Surges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202938/cathie-woods-ark-invest-sells-5-8m-in-coinbase-grayscale-bitcoin-trust-shares-as-crypto-market-surges"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T09:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Bitcoin jumped over 10% amid renewed hopes of a spot ETF approval, Ark Invest opted to sell some of its Bitcoin-related assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deepfakes Made Simple With AI: An In-Depth Look at FaceFusion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=201688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/201688/how-to-ai-deepfake-video-facefusion-face-swap-ai-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T08:07:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open-source FaceFusion tool is described as a next-generation face swapper and enhancer, and an accessible entry into the world of deepfake creation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Snapdragon Chip Leaks: The Upcoming Mobile CPU Is Packed with AI Power]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202905</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202905/snapdragon-8-generation-3-artificial-intelligence-smartphone-chip"/>
        <updated>2023-10-24T01:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From enhanced performance to groundbreaking AI capabilities, the Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 is set to redefine what you can do with your smartphone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Touches $34K as $114 Million in Shorts Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202894</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202894/bitcoin-price-34000-35000-liquidiations-2023-record"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T23:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A second rally for the day triggered $145 million in overall crypto market liquidations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Film3 Summit Returns to L.A. Alongside Streaming Festival With Theta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202668/film3-summit-returns-la-alongside-streaming-festival-theta"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T23:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The live Film3 Summit will run alongside MetaFilm3 Fest, an on-chain festival powered by Theta that includes multiple film premieres.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghost in the Machine: OpenAI CEO Sees ChatGPT on Track From AI to AGI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202877</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202877/openai-ai-agi-sam-altman-wall-street-journal"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T22:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI CEO Sam Altman delved into the transformative potential of AI, hinting at a future where data takes a backseat to reasoning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Odds Sam Bankman-Fried Testifies in His Trial?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202863</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202863/what-are-the-odds-sam-bankman-fried-testifies-in-his-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T21:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The formal crypto mogul has remained silent in court so far. But that could change as his trial progresses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Ordered to Review Grayscale’s Bitcoin ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=202874</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/202874/sec-must-again-review-grayscale-bitcoin-etf-application"/>
        <updated>2023-10-23T20:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will the SEC find another reason to reject Grayscale, or will it finally approve a spot Bitcoin ETF?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society's Rob Bowling on Deadrop's New Cars and User-Generated Modes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/A0auyZzn/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-on-deadrops-new-cars-and-user-generated-modes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-22T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin interviews Midnight Society Studio Head Rob Bowling about Deadrop's development and Snapshot VII.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Review: 'Raini: The Lords of Light' Brands Itself With Memes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/32YyJHCJ/game-review-raini-the-lords-of-light-brands-itself-with-memes"/>
        <updated>2023-10-20T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raini: Lords of Light is an NFT-optional card game bursting with crypto memes. From SBF to CZ and Elon, this free-to-play game has some truly wild animations. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares his honest thoughts on the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks Marfa Weekend Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QaTBP6eO/art-blocks-marfa-weekend-recap"/>
        <updated>2023-10-19T19:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relive the Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023 event with this highlights video, produced by Vincent Roazzi Jr. for Decrypt Studios in partnership with Art Blocks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phantom Galaxies: A Look Inside the Mech Shooter NFT Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QI1uDwQv/phantom-galaxies-a-look-inside-the-mech-shooter-nft-game"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands and game studio Blowfish are developing Phantom Galaxies, an upcoming sci-fi mech shooter game inspired by mech battlers like Transformers. Decrypt's Kate Irwin asks Blowfish Studios Cofounder and Managing Director Ben Lee about what it's like to play the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clip: DeepMedia's DeepID Deepfake Detection Tool at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/m4Vy4vhC/clip-deepmedias-deepid-deepfake-detection-tool-at-work"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T16:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clip showcasing how DeepMedia's DeepID deepfake detection tool works. Courtesy: DeepMedia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland AI World Fair Trailer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/3tUb56Fv/decentraland-ai-world-fair-trailer"/>
        <updated>2023-10-18T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trailer for the AI World Fair event in metaverse game Decentraland, taking place from October 25-27. Courtesy: Decentraland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BackTheBunny - Money, Conspiracy, Milady]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BRoKZzer/backthebunny-money-conspiracy-milady"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T19:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our host Reza Jafery sits down with BackTheBunny to dive deep into money, the fight against crypto that we're witnessing in real-time, and milady culture. 

Our Host: https://twitter.com/rezajafery
Our Guest: https://twitter.com/BackTheBunny

Our Sponsors
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['A Grand Experiment': Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury Talks Game Economics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Z2OMMsC5/a-grand-experiment-shrapnel-studio-head-don-norbury-talks-game-economics"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much of Shrapnel's in-game items are tradeable NFTs? Don Norbury, Studio Head at Shrapnel and CTO at game studio NEON, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Shrapnel's approach to game economics, including different game pricing models and how NFT game economies create different challenges for developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor Safe 3 and Trezor Keep Metal Unboxing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/IjqnO9pR/trezor-safe-3-and-trezor-keep-metal-unboxing"/>
        <updated>2023-10-17T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trezor has launched the Safe 3, a hardware wallet aimed at "new entrants to crypto," alongside the new Keep Metal recovery seed storage device. We take a first look at what comes in the box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI Arena is Building on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gl80TQOm/why-ai-arena-is-building-on-arbitrum"/>
        <updated>2023-10-12T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss the challenges that come with building on Ethereum, ETH sidechains, and layer-two blockchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pet3rPan_ on venture DAOs and blockchain games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DawNLI3O/pet3rpan-on-venture-daos-and-blockchain-games"/>
        <updated>2023-10-11T18:24:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 4th episode of this time will be different.

Our guest for today's episode is Pet3rpan_ from Metacartel, 1kx, HydraVentures, and more!

https://twitter.com/pet3rpan_

This Time Will Be Different is sponsored by 1000x
https://decrypt.co/1000x]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Shrapnel's Marketplace, New Map, and 'AI Director' Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F5RQCmvH/inside-shrapnels-marketplace-new-map-and-ai-director-feature"/>
        <updated>2023-10-06T16:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Shrapnel's Head of Studio Don Norbury to get the latest updates on how the NFT-powered first-person sci-fi extraction shooter's development is progressing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Art of the Times': Art Blocks Founder Erick Calderon on the State of Generative Art]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zSjfRrl5/art-of-the-times-art-blocks-founder-erick-calderon-on-the-state-of-generative-art"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T18:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO Erick Calderon sat down with Sander Lutz, lead culture reporter at Decrypt's SCENE, at Art Blocks Marfa Weekend 2023. They discuss the evolution of the company and the generative art world, along with what draws art enthusiasts to be an active part of the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: Digital Ownership Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6udZCotB/decrypt-learn-digital-ownership-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-10-05T10:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful aspects of blockchain technology is its ability to provide us genuine ownership of our digital assets. This is called digital ownership. In this video, we’ll deep dive into digital ownership, why it matters, and how web3 makes owning digital assets like our social networks, music libraries, personal data, and beyond possible. Author: Clarissa Watson, Senior Writer at Consensys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli on E/ACC and SBF in Prison]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QONaWXKZ/martin-shkreli-on-e-acc-and-sbf-in-prison"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T22:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza Jafery and Martin Shkreli sit down for a casual conversation about the growing movement that is E/ACC, what songs they could recite at gunpoint, and whether or not SBF will thrive or just survive during his time in prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can AI Do in Gaming?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JKuqCMao/what-can-ai-do-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-10-03T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Arena CEO Brandon Da Silva and COO Wei Xie discuss how artificial intelligence can shape the video game experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['There Are No Real Standards': Ready Player Me CEO Timmu Tõke on Building for an Open Gaming Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/TH3KEAI0/there-are-no-real-standards-ready-player-me-ceo-timmu-tke-on-building-for-an-open-gaming-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-09-29T17:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timmu Tõke, co-founder and CEO of Ready Player Me, joins Decrypt contributor Ryan Gladwin to discuss the startup's approach to powering avatars that are interoperable across games and metaverse platforms—and what's needed to convince the industry to adopt standards and open up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Is 'Only Way' Forward for Gaming, Says Shrapnel Studio Head]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/fhoy7Z8f/blockchain-is-only-way-forward-for-gaming-says-shrapnel-studio-head"/>
        <updated>2023-09-28T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shrapnel Studio Head Don Norbury tells Kate Irwin the reasons why the upcoming first-person shooter game will offer a wide range of NFTs. He also reveals team-based gameplay plans and shares how game maps have already changed this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Sentiment Is Key to Crypto Price Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/981TBppa/social-media-sentiment-is-key-to-crypto-price-discovery"/>
        <updated>2023-09-27T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sacha Ghebali, Director of Strategy and Business Development at The TIE, says social media sentiment remains a key factor in price movements for major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum. However, he notes that sentiment has turned more negative lately amid regulatory uncertainty. Ghebali believes events like the Ripple lawsuit ruling significantly impacted sentiment and prices. André Beganski interviewed him at Messari Mainnet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>