<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-08T03:18:06.144Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-08T03:18:06.144Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi tokens UNI, MKR lose lucky break: What’s going on?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468878/DeFi-tokens-UNI-MKR-lose-lucky-break-Whats-going-on</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468878/DeFi-tokens-UNI-MKR-lose-lucky-break-Whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T03:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Declining volumes affect UNI and MKR's prices. Will the tokens recover anytime soon?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean OTC Crypto ‘Thieves’ Admit Guilt in USDT Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468883/South-Korean-OTC-Crypto-Thieves-Admit-Guilt-in-USDT-Trial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468883/South-Korean-OTC-Crypto-Thieves-Admit-Guilt-in-USDT-Trial"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T03:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four suspected South Korean OTC crypto “thieves” have pleaded guilty to stealing around $735,000 from a crypto buyer in a “bogus” USDT deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Slerf (SOLSLERF) Will Explode 11,000%, as it Looks to Challenge Shiba Inu and Dogecoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468861/Solana-Slerf-SOLSLERF-Will-Explode-11000-as-it-Looks-to-Challenge-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468861/Solana-Slerf-SOLSLERF-Will-Explode-11000-as-it-Looks-to-Challenge-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T02:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Slerf (SOLSLERF) could become a viral memecoin, like Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE)....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly All FTX Creditors Will Get 118% of Their Funds Back in Cash, Estate Says in New Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468864/Nearly-All-FTX-Creditors-Will-Get-118-of-Their-Funds-Back-in-Cash-Estate-Says-in-New-Plan</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468864/Nearly-All-FTX-Creditors-Will-Get-118-of-Their-Funds-Back-in-Cash-Estate-Says-in-New-Plan"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T02:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange FTX has proposed a new reorganization plan that would see a whopping 98% of its creditors get back 118% of their claims – in cash – within 60 days of court approval, according to new documents filed Tuesday evening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Go 74,000% Wild: Investors Bet on Country Coins Ahead of Olympics]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468863/Meme-Coins-Go-74000-Wild-Investors-Bet-on-Country-Coins-Ahead-of-Olympics</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468863/Meme-Coins-Go-74000-Wild-Investors-Bet-on-Country-Coins-Ahead-of-Olympics"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T02:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A curious trend has emerged in memecoin world: national pride is going digital as, with the Paris Olympics on the horizon, investors are flocking to a new niche country-themed meme coins, betting that the global sporting event will inflate their value. An online tracking platform, as first...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ethereum, Dogecoin Sink Further As Regulatory Woes Weigh Down Investors: Analyst Says Majority Top Market Cap Cryptos In 'Slight Buy Zones']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468845/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Sink-Further-As-Regulatory-Woes-Weigh-Down-Investors-Analyst-Says-Majority-Top-Market-Cap-Cryptos-In-Slight-Buy-Zones</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468845/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Sink-Further-As-Regulatory-Woes-Weigh-Down-Investors-Analyst-Says-Majority-Top-Market-Cap-Cryptos-In-Slight-Buy-Zones"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T02:27:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market slid further Tuesday as market sentiment remained weak amid regulatory potshots taken at cryptocurrency entities. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Heist Funds On The Move: Poloniex Hacker Transfers $3.4 Million To Tornado Cash]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f75f584</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-heist-funds-on-the-move-poloniex-hacker-transfers-3-4-million-to-tornado-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T02:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports unveiled that part of the stolen funds from crypto exchange Poloniex have been moved for the first time. After six months, one of the identified accounts where the exploit proceedings were sent in November 2023 transferred $3.5 million to a crypto mixer.
 
 
Stolen Funds Transferred For The First Time
 
On Monday night, one of the labeled addresses holding the stolen assets moved the funds to a US-banned Tornado Cash. The transfers are the first time since the crypto heist that the hacker has moved part of the money to launder it.
 
Per Wu Blockchain’s report, the Poloniex hacker transferred 100 ETH, worth around $308,000, from address 0x3E…fDFd to the mixer. Later, PeckShieldAlert informed that the address had sent 1,100 ETH, worth nearly $3.5 million, to Tornado Cash.
 
 
#PeckSh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Gary Gensler is getting irked being asked about crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468817/SECs-Gary-Gensler-is-getting-irked-being-asked-about-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468817/SECs-Gary-Gensler-is-getting-irked-being-asked-about-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T02:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler says he gets an “outsized ratio” of questions about crypto despite its relatively small size compared to the overall financial market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India Working on Offline Transferability of Digital Rupee, Says Central Bank Governor]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f779dd4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/india-working-on-offline-transferability-of-digital-rupee-says-central-bank-governor/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T01:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s central bank, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI), is in the process of making its central bank digital currency (CBDC) available without relying on internet access. RBI Governor Shaktikanta Das has emphasized the importance of ensuring the digital rupee’s ease of use. RBI Governor Updates Digital Rupee Progress During an event hosted by the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Robinhood Wells Notice Hits Harder]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468797/Why-the-Robinhood-Wells-Notice-Hits-Harder</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468797/Why-the-Robinhood-Wells-Notice-Hits-Harder"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T01:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood is the latest crypto-aligned company to be targeted by the SEC. In today's episode NLW explores why the crypto community is more surprised by this one than even recent actions against Consensys and the Ethereum Foundation. ﻿Today's Show Brought To You ByLedger - 5% to Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX commits to 100% creditor payback and substantial bonuses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468782/FTX-commits-to-100-creditor-payback-and-substantial-bonuses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468782/FTX-commits-to-100-creditor-payback-and-substantial-bonuses"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T01:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX cryptocurrency exchange, which went bankrupt in November 2022, has revealed that a new debt settlement plan will be proposed that would let almost all the creditors of the exchange be paid off in full. On May 7, the company announced that it will try to pay 100% of the allowable bankruptcy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azuro –  Infrastructure and Liquidity for On-chain Predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468813/Azuro-Infrastructure-and-Liquidity-for-On-chain-Predictions</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468813/Azuro-Infrastructure-and-Liquidity-for-On-chain-Predictions"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T01:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rossen is a core contributor at Azuro, an infrastructure/liquidity layer for on-chain predictions. It utilizes a new Liquidity Pool design, the Liquidity Tree, which creates and maintains market liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler: Crypto Represents ‘Outsized’ Share Of Scams And Fraud In Overall Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f73dc12</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-chair-crypto-represents-outsized-share-of-scams/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T01:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with CNBC, Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chair Gary Gensler reiterated his concerns regarding the crypto industry, emphasizing its alleged association with scams, fraud, and compliance issues within the broader market. 
 
Compliance With Securities Laws In Crypto
 
Gensler began by acknowledging that while cryptocurrencies constitute a relatively small segment of the overall financial markets, they allegedly exert an “outsized” influence regarding scams, fraud, and problems due to non-compliance with existing securities laws. 
 
The SEC Chair stressed that many digital assets fall under the classification of securities according to interpretations by the US Supreme Court, making compliance with securities regulations a crucial aspect of the industry.
 
 
Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trading Firm Wintermute to Provide Liquidity for Hong Kong Bitcoin and Ether ETFs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f7c88d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/08/crypto-trading-firm-wintermute-to-provide-liquidity-for-hong-kong-bitcoin-ether-etfs/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T01:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to strengthen its market share in the Asia region, Wintermute will become a liquidity provider to the recently launched Hong Kong-listed spot bitcoin and ether exchange-traded funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helene Braun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON and DOGE See Surge in Non-Empty Wallets as They Outperform Rivals XRP, ADA, and Others]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468728/TON-and-DOGE-See-Surge-in-Non-Empty-Wallets-as-They-Outperform-Rivals-XRP-ADA-and-Others</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468728/TON-and-DOGE-See-Surge-in-Non-Empty-Wallets-as-They-Outperform-Rivals-XRP-ADA-and-Others"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New data suggests a surge in cryptocurrency market activity, with Toncoin ($TON) and the meme-inspired cryptocurrency Dogecoin ($DOGE) showing surprising strength compared to established players including leading stablecoins and other altcoins such as XRP, LINK, and ADA. According to data shared...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just In: Grayscale Withdraws Ethereum ETF Application Amid SEC Delays]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468721/Just-In-Grayscale-Withdraws-Ethereum-ETF-Application-Amid-SEC-Delays</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468721/Just-In-Grayscale-Withdraws-Ethereum-ETF-Application-Amid-SEC-Delays"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leader in the cryptocurrency asset management field, Grayscale, has unambiguously shelved his application for a futures Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF). The 23rd of September 2023 is when Grayscale registered with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), the company has withdrawn...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Are We Back?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468732/Bitcoin-Are-We-Back</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468732/Bitcoin-Are-We-Back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin news, crypto market and altcoin updates! 🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTH_MASTERY💎 BITGET 👉 $30,000 IN BONUSES ►► https://cryptolark.co/BITGET30K 💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Crypto Gainers Today on DEXScreener – WALLETAI, BOBO, MEW]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468729/Top-Crypto-Gainers-Today-on-DEXScreener-WALLETAI-BOBO-MEW</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468729/Top-Crypto-Gainers-Today-on-DEXScreener-WALLETAI-BOBO-MEW"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a mostly bearish day in the cryptocurrency market on Tuesday, Render (RNDR), Kaspa (KAS) and Tron (TRX) are top crypto gainers today and some of the only coins trading in the green over the past 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero excludes staff from airdrop, collaborates with Nansen, Chaos Labs to enhance Sybil detection]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468708/LayerZero-excludes-staff-from-airdrop-collaborates-with-Nansen-Chaos-Labs-to-enhance-Sybil-detection</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468708/LayerZero-excludes-staff-from-airdrop-collaborates-with-Nansen-Chaos-Labs-to-enhance-Sybil-detection"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LayerZero has partnered with analytics firm Nansen and security company Chaos Labs to enhance Sybil detection mechanisms ahead of its token generation event (TGE). Bryan Pellegrino, co-founder and CEO of LayerZero, also claims that the project's staff are excluded from the upcoming...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Digitex CEO Admits to AML Violations in Federal Court]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468720/Former-Digitex-CEO-Admits-to-AML-Violations-in-Federal-Court</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468720/Former-Digitex-CEO-Admits-to-AML-Violations-in-Federal-Court"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adam Todd has pleaded guilty to failing to establish an Anti-Money Laundering (AML) program, a requirement under the Bank Secrecy Act. This plea was made in the federal court of the Southern District of Florida, as communicated by the U.S. Attorney’s Office on May 7. Todd is charged with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Whale Moves 1.7 Trillion SHIB As Price Struggles, Where Are They Headed?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f796471</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-whale-1-7-trillion/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community’s attention has been drawn to a Shiba Inu whale that recently moved trillions of the meme coin. Given the magnitude of these transactions, community members have sought to discover where these tokens were transferred and the motive behind them.
 
Shiba Inu Whale Moves 1.7 Trillion SHIB
 
On-chain data shows that the whale (crypto trading platform Robinhood) moved 1.7 trillion SHIB tokens from one of its wallets to another in two separate transactions, with 875 billion SHIB tokens moved in the first transaction and the same amount transferred in the second. 
 
 
The crypto platform has become known for moving enormous amounts of SHIB tokens between their wallets, possibly to meet demand from customers. Bitcoinist recently reported how the trading platform moved 3 trilli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Has Billions More Than Needed to Pay Bankruptcy Victims]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468812/FTX-Has-Billions-More-Than-Needed-to-Pay-Bankruptcy-Victims</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468812/FTX-Has-Billions-More-Than-Needed-to-Pay-Bankruptcy-Victims"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by   /u/TakingChances01 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Last Dip Ever’ – Analyst Predicts Solana Rally, Says Three Memecoins Will Surge Alongside SOL]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468650/Last-Dip-Ever-Analyst-Predicts-Solana-Rally-Says-Three-Memecoins-Will-Surge-Alongside-SOL</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468650/Last-Dip-Ever-Analyst-Predicts-Solana-Rally-Says-Three-Memecoins-Will-Surge-Alongside-SOL"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closely followed crypto trader believes that Solana (SOL) just witnessed its last major correction for this market cycle. Pseudonymous analyst Inmortal tells his 213,300 followers on the social media platform X that SOL bulls successfully defended support at around $120. The trader shares a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Whale Moves 1.7 Trillion SHIB As Price Struggles, Where Are They Headed?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468665/Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-17-Trillion-SHIB-As-Price-Struggles-Where-Are-They-Headed</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468665/Shiba-Inu-Whale-Moves-17-Trillion-SHIB-As-Price-Struggles-Where-Are-They-Headed"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto community’s attention has been drawn to a Shiba Inu whale that recently moved trillions of the meme coin. Given the magnitude of these transactions, community members have sought to discover where these tokens were transferred and the motive behind them. Shiba Inu Whale Moves 1.7...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM) Bull Run: 8% Price Surge And Robust Double-Digit Growth In Key Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468648/Fantom-FTM-Bull-Run-8-Price-Surge-And-Robust-Double-Digit-Growth-In-Key-Metrics</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19468648/Fantom-FTM-Bull-Run-8-Price-Surge-And-Robust-Double-Digit-Growth-In-Key-Metrics"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantom (FTM), a Layer-1 (L1) protocol, and its native token, FTM, have experienced significant gains and notable achievements in the first quarter (Q1) of 2024.  According to a comprehensive performance analysis conducted by Messari, amid the emerging crypto bull market, Fantom has emerged as...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler Calls Crypto ‘Outsized Piece of Scams, Frauds, and Problems in Our Markets’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f668421</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-chair-gary-gensler-calls-crypto-outsized-piece-of-scams-frauds-and-problems-in-our-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T23:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chairman of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Gary Gensler, has reiterated his view that crypto is a field full of noncompliance. While noting that crypto is a small piece of the overall U.S. financial market that his agency oversees, the SEC chair emphasized that it is “an outsized piece of the scams […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Withdraws Ethereum Futures ETF Application to SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229830</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229830/ethereum-futures-etf-grayscale-etf-withdrawal"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T23:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm appears to sidestep an “approve futures, deny spot” ETF strategy that could have landed in the courts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Industry Flexes Financial Muscle With $100M Super PAC War Chest For 2024 US Elections]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f67cd31</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-industry-100m-super-pac-war-chest/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T23:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent report by OpenSecrets.org revealed that cryptocurrency industry Super Political Action Committees (PACs) have accumulated a staggering $102 million war chest to exert their influence on the upcoming 2024 US congressional elections. 
 
The data, compiled by Public Citizen, highlights the sector’s concerted efforts to sway elections in favor of pro-crypto candidates and impede regulatory measures to ensure compliance within the industry.
 
Crypto Billionaires Lead Funding Surge
 
Rick Claypool, a research director for Public Citizen and author of the report, emphasized that a fresh wave of crypto corporations, executives, and their allies have returned to the political landscape, pouring millions of dollars into campaigns. 
 
Their objectives reportedly include influencing elections…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Epic Sat' That Sold for $2 Million Used to Inscribe Ordinals Art—With Grimes' AI Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229804</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229804/bitcoin-epic-sat-sold-2-million-inscribed-ordinals-grimes-ai-voice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T23:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Ordinals inscription featuring Grimes' AI-generated voice has been created as part of a Bitcoin art project—on an "epic" satoshi that cost over $2 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Haven't Lived Up to the Hype? It's Still Too Early to Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229809</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229809/bitcoin-runes-havent-lived-up-hype-still-early"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T22:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The immediate hype around Bitcoin Runes tokens has cooled off, but proponents believe this is a natural and expected lull.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Prepares to Fight SEC in Court Over Crypto, CEO Reveals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f6d306b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robinhood-prepares-to-fight-sec-in-court-over-crypto-ceo-reveals/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T22:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Markets is preparing to fight the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) in court to defend its crypto business and establish “regulatory clarity in the United States for the benefit of our customers,” CEO Vlad Tenev said after his company received a Wells notice from the securities regulator. “The SEC’s continued attack on crypto, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Networth Bitcoin Whales Accumulating: Will This Buying Spree Push BTC Above $74,000?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f6ef5f2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-whales-buying-spree-btc-above-74000/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T22:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bitcoin continues to trade within the $60,000 to $70,000 range, a new wave of optimism is emerging from on-chain analysis. Willy Woo, an on-chain analyst, took to X on May 7 to point out an exciting development: high-net-worth BTC holders have been rapidly accumulating the coin. 
 
High Net-worth Whales Accumulating
 
In a chart, the analyst noted that whales, entities holding between 100 and 1,000 BTC, have been gobbling up BTC over the past two months. Their involvement, Woo says, has been the “strongest buying spree” by such whales in recent history. 
 
 
However, while there is excitement, some argue that this cohort’s sharp spike in BTC accrual could be due to spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) issuers. Since the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 Bitcoin L2 Projects Secure Investments to Enhance Bitcoin’s Defi Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f6a32e8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/2-bitcoin-l2-projects-secure-investments-to-enhance-bitcoins-defi-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, two Bitcoin-centric layer two (L2) initiatives successfully secured funding from strategic investors. Botanix Labs, a startup focused on developing a decentralized Turing-complete L2 EVM (Ethereum Virtual Machine), garnered $11.5 million. Meanwhile, the Bitcoin L2 ZKM attracted $5 million during a pre-seed investment phase. Bitcoin L2 Projects Gain Momentum With New Financing Rounds Throughout […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neuralink Safety Concerns Drove Co-Founder to Break Up With Elon Musk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229816/neuralink-safety-concerns-drove-co-founder-to-break-up-with-elon-musk"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Neuralink is already testing its brain implants in humans, a scientist who helped start the company says he left to develop a less intrusive technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock, Ondo, Superstate: The Biggest Movers in the RWA Sector in Q1]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f550202</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/07/blackrock-ondo-superstate-the-biggest-movers-in-the-rwa-sector-in-q1/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catching up on the biggest news from the real-world asset space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Rodenbaugh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Chair Predicts Tsunami Of Crypto Enforcement Actions In Next 2 Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f565898</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cftc-predicts-tsunami-of-crypto-enforcement-actions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) continues to scrutinize crypto industry players, including Robinhood, Binance, Coinbase, and Ripple, the Chair of the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), Rostin Behnam, warns of an impending surge in enforcement actions. 
 
Crypto Faces Inevitable Wave Of Enforcement Actions
 
At the Milken Institute’s 27th annual Global Conference, Behnam emphasized the lack of regulatory framework and transparency within the growing crypto industry, which he believes will inevitably lead to more fraud and manipulation cases.
 
Behnam anticipates a “cycle of enforcement actions” within the next six months to two years, driven by the rapid appreciation of digital assets and heightened interest from retail investors. 
 
 
As a regulator, Behnam exp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Big Short’ Investor Calls Crypto One of the ‘Great Themes of Our Time,’ But He’s Not a Believer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f50967d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/big-short-investor-calls-crypto-one-of-the-great-themes-of-our-time-but-hes-not-a-believer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview on Bloomberg Television, Steve Eisman of Neuberger Berman, who gained prominence from “The Big Short,” shared insights on the impending U.S. election and his investment strategies. Eisman identified three significant current themes, including cryptocurrency, about which he expressed skepticism. Steve Eisman’s Take: Trump’s Re-Election and the So-Called Crypto Conundrum Steve Eisman, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Obama and RFK Jr. Have Equal Odds of Becoming Next President on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229803</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229803/michelle-obama-rfk-jr-presidential-win-odds-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former first lady has no plans to run for U.S. President, but oddsmakers are backing her as enthusiastically as the actual, crypto-friendly candidate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investment Firm Discloses Over $1.8 Billion in Bitcoin ETF Holdings in SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f525163</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/investment-firm-discloses-over-1-8-billion-in-bitcoin-etf-holdings-in-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Susquehanna International Group, LLP (SIG), a global trading, technology, and investment firm, disclosed that it holds over $1.8 billion in Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) through a 13F-HR filing submitted to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), providing a detailed breakdown of SIG's investment portfolio.
The filing reveals the investment firms biggest positions were in Grayscales Bitcoin ETF GBTC, totaling $1,091,029,663.
 
                         
                         
                         
                     
                    
The documents also revealed that SIG holds positions in ARK 21SHARES BITCOIN ETF, BITWISE BITCOIN ETF TR, BITWISE FUNDS TRUST (BITCOIN AND ETHER), FIDELITY WISE ORIGIN BITCOIN, FRANKLIN TEMPLETON DIGITAL BITCOIN ETF, GLOBAL X BITCOIN T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independent Presidential Candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Joins Consensus as a Headline Speaker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f5dd7b6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/independent-presidential-candidate-robert-f-kennedy-jr-joins-consensus-as-a-headline-speaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. May 7, 2024, Austin, TX – In less than four weeks, independent presidential candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. will take the stage in Austin, TX, at Consensus 2024, the world’s largest, longest-running, and most influential gathering that brings together all sides of the crypto and Web3 community. As an environmental lawyer, scion of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Holders In Profit across 82%, What About Shiba Inu?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f5e5a45</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-holders-profit-shiba-inu/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies have exhibited an interesting price dynamic in the past few days. According to data from Coinmarketcap, the majority of cryptocurrencies, including Dogecoin, have posted losses in the past 24 hours. On the other hand, some of these cryptocurrencies are still on a price increase when looking at a larger timeframe and many more addresses have crossed into the profitability zone in the past seven days. 
 
Dogecoin, for instance, is still up by 9% in a 7-day timeframe. As a result, the number of DOGE addresses in profitability has now been pushed to 83%, with 163,000 more addresses waiting to be pushed into profit if DOGE crosses over $0.1657.
 
Holders of Shiba Inu, Dogecoin’s meme counterpart, haven’t been treated to the same effect. At the time of writing, the number …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coincheck’s Nasdaq Listing Gains Traction, Proposal Submitted to SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f5fb08d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/coinchecks-nasdaq-listing-gains-traction-as-spac-submits-proposal-to-sec/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coincheck and Spacial Purpose Acquisition Company Thunder Bridge Capital Partners IV are progressing with their merger deal, that will enable the Japanese cryptocurrency exchange to list on Nasdaq. Coincheck has reportedly submitted a proposal regarding the agreement,  signifying a significant step for both companies and implications for investors seeking exposure to the growing crypto industry.
Gateway to Nasdaq
Coincheck is a renowned digital asset exchange with a market share of over 1.98 million accounts, while Thunder Bridge Capital Partners IV is an SPAC that facilitates mergers and acquisitions within the financial sector. The proposed merger signifies Coincheck's ambition to expand its global footprint and  
gain access to the Nasdaq market. According to the press release, the comb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitpay Partners With Moonpay to Enhance Crypto Selling Experience on App]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f59c44f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitpay-partners-with-moonpay-to-enhance-crypto-selling-experience-on-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, the crypto payments processor based in Atlanta, Bitpay, revealed its collaboration with Moonpay. The partnership, Bitpay emphasized, enables users to sell bitcoin and other crypto assets directly through the Bitpay app. Bitpay Now Allows Direct Sales via Moonpay Partnership Users of the Bitpay app can now sell their crypto assets through Bitpay’s integration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Republicans Move To Crush SEC's Anti-Crypto Banking Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229786/us-house-resolution-sec-bank-bulletin-crypto-custodians"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress is mulling a resolution aimed at rescinding guidance that proponents say drives U.S. banks away from holding digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s Electoral Impact: Over 20% Of Swing State Voters Weigh Digital Currency Policies Heavily]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f466119</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cryptos-electoral-impact-over-swing-state-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the political temperature in the United States heats up ahead of upcoming elections, cryptocurrency is emerging as a significant topic among voters in key battleground states.
 
An extensive online survey spearheaded by the Digital Currency Group (DCG) has highlighted the growing importance of digital currency policies in the electoral dialogue, particularly in states known for their pivotal role in election outcomes.
 
 
Voter Sentiment On Crypto: A New Electoral Battleground
 
The influence of digital currency in shaping political landscapes is increasingly apparent, as evidenced by the recent survey conducted by The Harris Poll for DCG. From April 4-16, this poll involved 1,201 registered voters across Michigan, Ohio, Montana, Pennsylvania, Nevada, and Arizona.
 
Results indicate tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Game 'Fantasy Top' Pays $1.25M to Twitter Influencers It Turned Into NFT Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229775/ethereum-game-fantasy-top-pays-1-25m-twitter-influencers-turned-nft-cards"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto influencers got a share of $1.25 million in ETH and potentially millions in Blast Gold for being tradable "heroes" in Fantasy Top.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoMA’s Madeleine Pierpont: NFTs Are Already a Part of Art History]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742f420a01</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/05/07/momas-madeleine-pierpont-nfts-are-already-a-part-of-art-history/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Yes, there has been a hyper-financialization in the NFT space, but money is not a dirty word in art,” says the Consensus 2024 speaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Defeating Biden Would Be Good for Bitcoin: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229761/trump-defeating-biden-good-bitcoin-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts at British bank Standard Chartered today said that a second Donald Trump presidency could do Bitcoin good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fan Jack Dorsey Takes Kendrick Lamar’s Side in Drake Beef]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229729/bitcoin-fan-jack-dorsey-kendrick-lamar-drake"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s winning the Kendrick and Drake lyrical war? Dorsey says it’s no contest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Says It’s Our Fault the SEC Appears So Focused on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229736/gary-gensler-our-fault-sec-focused-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s an “outsized ratio of journalist questions and crypto journalists to market cap,” SEC Chair Gary Gensler claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood CEO Decries 'Regulatory Onslaught' on Crypto, Vows to Fight SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229728/robinhood-ceo-decries-regulatory-onslaught-crypto-fight-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though Robinhood Crypto thought its "safety-first" approach was distinct, the SEC said that enforcement action is on its way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Take In $217 Million for Second Consecutive Day of Net Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229727/bitcoin-etfs-take-in-217-million-for-second-consecutive-day-of-net-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every single fund saw another day in the green with net inflows yesterday—including Grayscale Bitcoin Trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Crypto Crackdown: Every Company That Is Being Investigated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229723/sec-crypto-crackdown-every-company-wells-notice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T15:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is taking aim at crypto companies in the United States. Here's who has disclosed a Wells Notice or is reportedly under investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[University Speaker Takes Ayahuasca, Shills Bitcoin, Gets Booed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229687/osu-commencement-speaker-bitcoin-ayahuasca"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ohio State University commencement speech included Bitcoin shilling and some cringe-worthy karaoke—all fueled by psychedelics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: It's official: Nintendo has announced a Switch "successor." Here's everything we've heard so far about the Switch 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play Social Games, Earn Crypto Rewards: Solana Gaming App 'Cupcake' Launches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229618</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229618/play-social-games-earn-crypto-rewards-solana-cupcake"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cupcake uses a TikTok-like feed of social games to help bring players deeper into the crypto world—and serves up Solana-based rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Demands Release of Employee Detained in Nigeria]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229630/binance-ceo-demands-release-of-employee-detained-in-nigeria"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T11:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng alleged that Tigran Gambaryan is being held in "a dangerous prison in order to control Binance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady Ridiculed for FTX and Crypto Investments in Netflix Roast]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229627/tom-brady-ridiculed-for-ftx-and-crypto-investments-in-netflix-roast"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Star NFL quarterback Tom Brady was ridiculed for his Bitcoin affinity and ties to bankrupt crypto exchange FTX during a live roast on Netflix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's AI Ambitions Emerge Ahead of iPad Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229615/apple-ai-strategy-siri-xcode-music"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T00:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between Tuesday's iPad event and WWDC, AI is expected to play a part in nearly every corner of the Apple ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ethereum Game ‘Fantasy Top’ Is Taking Over Crypto Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229595/why-ethereum-game-fantasy-top-taking-over-crypto-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantasy Top is like fantasy football, but with crypto influencers. The Blast game is the hot new thing amid a cooling crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallet Maker Exodus Jumping Up to New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229589/bitcoin-wallet-exodus-nyse-exod-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exodus says it is the only U.S. company that will have its EXOD common stock tokenized on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's Ethereum Fund Discount Steadies as ETF Deadline Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229584/grayscale-ethereum-ethe-fund-discount"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale hopes to convert its Ethereum Trust to a spot ETH ETF, and current investors see opportunity in the uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Down, But These Analysts Still Think BTC Hits $150K This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229582</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229582/bitcoin-150000-price-doubling-18-months-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AllianceBernstein join Standard Chartered analysts in seeing the price of BTC more than doubling in the next 18 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-Term Bitcoin Investors Have Returned To HODLing: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229577/bitcoin-long-term-btc-holders-grow"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales eagerly bought the latest dip, and long-term investors are now patiently awaiting the next leg up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Back? $378 Million In Gains Marks Best Day In Over a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229553</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229553/bitcoin-spot-etf-inflows-across-the-board-gbtc-turns-green"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every fund flipped green on Friday, as more traditional investors hold on to their BTC-based shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Dogwifhat Pumps as Bonk, Dogecoin and Other Meme Coins Lose Ground]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229555/meme-coin-wif-bonk-doge-pepe"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIF is the only meme coin in the top 100 posting gains amid a broader crypto dip. Other popular meme coins are struggling to maintain momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mixers Pull Out of the US Amid Regulatory Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229543/bitcoin-coin-mixers-shut-americans-out"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy preserving crypto services are shutting down or shutting out American users as U.S. agencies turn up the pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $44 Million After a Decade—Here's How Much It Gained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229534</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229534/bitcoin-whale-moves-44-million-after-decade-how-much-gained"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unidentified Bitcoin whale just moved 687 BTC after it sat for more than a decade. Here's how much the value increased during that span.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Jumps Nearly 5% as Bitcoin, Ethereum Lag Behind]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229533/solana-price-jumps-bitcoin-ethereum-lag-behind"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is the biggest gainer in the top 10 cryptocurrencies on an otherwise quiet Monday morning, as Bitcoin and Ethereum tick down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[90% of Ethereum, Tron, Solana Stablecoin Transactions Are ‘Inorgranic Activity’, Visa Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229515/stablecoin-transactions-inorganic-bots-ethereum-tron-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart contracts, not humans, are driving nearly all stablecoin arbitrage, liquidity provision, and market making.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Crypto Says SEC Has 'Weak' Case in Response to Wells Notice]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229516</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229516/robinhood-crypto-sec-wells-notice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T13:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company said it's looking forward to showing "just how weak any case against Robinhood Crypto would be on both the facts and the law."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Sees Modest Gains as Network Processes Its 1 Billionth Transaction]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229504</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229504/bitcoin-sees-modest-gains-as-network-processes-its-1-billionth-transaction"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T12:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world's oldest and largest cryptocurrency just celebrated a birthday of sorts: Its network has processed more than 1 billion transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>