<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-01-05T04:18:38.046Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-01-05T04:18:38.046Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logan Paul to ‘personally commit’ $2.3 million to buy back CryptoZoo NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151949/Logan-Paul-to-personally-commit-23-million-to-buy-back-CryptoZoo-NFTs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151949/Logan-Paul-to-personally-commit-23-million-to-buy-back-CryptoZoo-NFTs"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T04:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet personality announced the refund program on X, adding he also filed a crossclaim against the co-creators of the NFT project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF vs. Trust: Which suits traditional investors more?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151948/Bitcoin-ETF-vs-Trust-Which-suits-traditional-investors-more</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151948/Bitcoin-ETF-vs-Trust-Which-suits-traditional-investors-more"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T04:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency world has been abuzz with the potential approval of a Bitcoin spot exchange-traded fund (ETF) in the United States, a development eagerly anticipated by both crypto enthusiasts and traditional investors. With a long list of prominent applicants like BlackRock, Fidelity, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto lender Celsius to unstake $470M in Ethereum ahead of repayments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151947/Crypto-lender-Celsius-to-unstake-470M-in-Ethereum-ahead-of-repayments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151947/Crypto-lender-Celsius-to-unstake-470M-in-Ethereum-ahead-of-repayments"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T04:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto lender has 206,300 Ether (ETH) currently in the staking withdrawal queue, according to Nansen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Founded By Ex-Citigroup Execs To Launch Bitcoin-Backed Securities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484d6d939</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ex-citigroup-execs-launch-bitcoin-backed-securities/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T04:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Bloomberg report revealed that a group of former Citigroup executives had introduced an investment offering called Bitcoin (BTC) depositary receipts (BTC DRs). 
 
These securities, backed by the largest cryptocurrency in the market, are being positioned as an alternative to spot-Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) that require approval from US regulators. 
 
The startup behind this initiative, Receipts Depositary Corporation (RDC), plans to issue the first Bitcoin depositary receipts to qualified global institutional investors, providing them a convenient and regulated way to gain exposure to BTC.
 
Bitcoin Depositary Receipts Vs Bitcoin ETFs
 
Bitcoin depositary receipts, introduced by Receipts Depositary Corporation, offer distinct differences compared to spot Bitcoin ETFs. 
 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup Founded By Ex-Citigroup Execs To Launch Bitcoin-Backed Securities]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151945/Startup-Founded-By-Ex-Citigroup-Execs-To-Launch-Bitcoin-Backed-Securities</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151945/Startup-Founded-By-Ex-Citigroup-Execs-To-Launch-Bitcoin-Backed-Securities"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T04:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Bloomberg report revealed that a group of former Citigroup executives had introduced an investment offering called Bitcoin (BTC) depositary receipts (BTC DRs).  These securities, backed by the largest cryptocurrency in the market, are being positioned as an alternative to spot-Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A close look at the crypto explosion of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151930/A-close-look-at-the-crypto-explosion-of-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151930/A-close-look-at-the-crypto-explosion-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T04:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2023 witnessed a remarkable surge in the cryptocurrency domain, marking a significant era in the digital finance world. This period was characterized by substantial advancements, widespread adoption, and a plethora of intriguing developments that captivated both seasoned investors and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan crypto exchange ACE faces criminal probe over shitcoins]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151931/Taiwan-crypto-exchange-ACE-faces-criminal-probe-over-shitcoins</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151931/Taiwan-crypto-exchange-ACE-faces-criminal-probe-over-shitcoins"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a striking turn of events, ACE, Taiwan’s largest cryptocurrency exchange, has found itself in the throes of a criminal investigation. This probe, led by Taiwan’s criminal police, centers around allegations of fraud exceeding NT$1 billion. The spotlight of this investigation falls on the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s reality check: The failed forecasts of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151932/Cryptos-reality-check-The-failed-forecasts-of-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151932/Cryptos-reality-check-The-failed-forecasts-of-2023"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:48:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the Fed being so mysterious about rate cuts?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151933/Why-is-the-Fed-being-so-mysterious-about-rate-cuts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151933/Why-is-the-Fed-being-so-mysterious-about-rate-cuts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve’s recent stance on interest rate adjustments has left market analysts and investors scratching their heads. Despite indications that rate hikes might be pausing, the Fed’s discussions have shrouded the possibility of rate cuts in mystery. At their December 12-13 meeting,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seattle Takes the Lead in AI Tech for Traffic Optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151918/Seattle-Takes-the-Lead-in-AI-Tech-for-Traffic-Optimization</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151918/Seattle-Takes-the-Lead-in-AI-Tech-for-Traffic-Optimization"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seattle has emerged as the inaugural city to test Google’s innovative Project Green Light, a pioneering application of artificial intelligence (AI) aimed at alleviating traffic congestion. Leveraging Google’s vast Maps database, this AI-driven system analyzes data to optimize traffic lights,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Government Trials AI-Powered Virtual Assistants for Efficient Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151905/Government-Trials-AI-Powered-Virtual-Assistants-for-Efficient-Communication</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151905/Government-Trials-AI-Powered-Virtual-Assistants-for-Efficient-Communication"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces Back — Dogecoin, Ethereum Rise As Spot ETF Hopes Get Revived: Analyst  Predicts Eventual Rebound To $57K For King Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151910/Bitcoin-Bounces-Back-Dogecoin-Ethereum-Rise-As-Spot-ETF-Hopes-Get-Revived-Analyst-Predicts-Eventual-Rebound-To-57K-For-King-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151910/Bitcoin-Bounces-Back-Dogecoin-Ethereum-Rise-As-Spot-ETF-Hopes-Get-Revived-Analyst-Predicts-Eventual-Rebound-To-57K-For-King-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rebounded over the $44,000 level on Thursday after the cryptocurrency valuations plummeted a day earlier. The global cryptocurrency market cap rose nearly 1% to $1.66 trillion at the time of publishing. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin O’Leary Anticipates Strong Institutional Interest in Crypto Regardless of Spot Bitcoin ETF Outcome]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484d3b93f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/kevin-oleary-anticipates-strong-institutional-interest-in-crypto-regardless-of-spot-bitcoin-etf-outcome/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:09:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shark Tank investor Kevin O’Leary, also known as Mr. Wonderful, has emphasized that institutional interest in crypto and bitcoin will remain high regardless of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s decision on spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). “Even a no decision will not change the long-term potential,” he stressed.
 
Kevin O’Leary Discusses Impact of Spot Bitcoin ETFs on Institutional Demand for Crypto
 
Kevin O’Leary, the chairman of O’Leary Ventures, has weighed in on the potential impact of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approving spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) on institutional interest in crypto.
 
He shared on social media platform X Wednesday: “Bitcoin has a spectacular appreciation. Why? The anticipation of the SEC approving the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Mexico and Canada’s bid to ditch the US dollar]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151898/Inside-Mexico-and-Canadas-bid-to-ditch-the-US-dollar</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151898/Inside-Mexico-and-Canadas-bid-to-ditch-the-US-dollar"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Price Sell-Off Sparks ‘Buy the Dip’ Frenzy on Social Media Amid ETF Hopes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151904/Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Sell-Off-Sparks-Buy-the-Dip-Frenzy-on-Social-Media-Amid-ETF-Hopes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151904/Bitcoin-BTC-Price-Sell-Off-Sparks-Buy-the-Dip-Frenzy-on-Social-Media-Amid-ETF-Hopes"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency world has been abuzz after the price of the flagship cryptocurrency Bitcoin surpassed the $40,000 mark late last year and topped $445,000 earlier this year before enduring a slight correction. Bitcoin’s price has been rising on expectations a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Haggle-Bots Empower Shoppers to Command Better Bargains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151899/AI-Haggle-Bots-Empower-Shoppers-to-Command-Better-Bargains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151899/AI-Haggle-Bots-Empower-Shoppers-to-Command-Better-Bargains"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is ushering in a new era for consumers, challenging the profit-maximizing tactics employed by major corporations. The rise of AI haggle-bots is revolutionizing the way individuals secure deals, turning the tables on businesses that have long exploited customer data....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Fraud Unveiled: $1.3B Loss As Chuck Norris-Endorsed CEO Turns Out To Be Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151886/Crypto-Fraud-Unveiled-13B-Loss-As-Chuck-Norris-Endorsed-CEO-Turns-Out-To-Be-Illusion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151886/Crypto-Fraud-Unveiled-13B-Loss-As-Chuck-Norris-Endorsed-CEO-Turns-Out-To-Be-Illusion"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T03:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto industry saw over $2b in investments last year]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151878/Crypto-industry-saw-over-2b-in-investments-last-year</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151878/Crypto-industry-saw-over-2b-in-investments-last-year"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T02:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Invest continues to offload its Coinbase stocks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151879/ARK-Invest-continues-to-offload-its-Coinbase-stocks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151879/ARK-Invest-continues-to-offload-its-Coinbase-stocks"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T02:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Elephant in Bitcoin ETF Room, Role in Proposed Products Questioned]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151893/Coinbase-Elephant-in-Bitcoin-ETF-Room-Role-in-Proposed-Products-Questioned</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151893/Coinbase-Elephant-in-Bitcoin-ETF-Room-Role-in-Proposed-Products-Questioned"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T02:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) fever heats up, eyes are turning to the major players and they’re not all big asset managers such as BlackRock and Fidelity.  Coinbase is positioned to play a major role as a middleman between the crypto market and traditional stock exchanges if the SEC...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Just F*cking Do It Already!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151775/Bitcoin-ETF-Just-Fcking-Do-It-Already</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151775/Bitcoin-ETF-Just-Fcking-Do-It-Already"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T02:43:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana ($SOL) Price could Soon See a ‘Mind-Blowing’ Parabolic Move Upward, Analyst Suggests]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151859/Solana-SOL-Price-could-Soon-See-a-Mind-Blowing-Parabolic-Move-Upward-Analyst-Suggests</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19151859/Solana-SOL-Price-could-Soon-See-a-Mind-Blowing-Parabolic-Move-Upward-Analyst-Suggests"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T02:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A popular cryptocurrency strategist who has gained a large following on social media after accurately calling Bitcoin’s 2018 bear market bottom above $3,000 has recently revealed he believes that Solana (SOL) could soon see a “mind-blowing” parabolic move upward. In a post shared with their over...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is This Bitcoin Rally Already Over? HODLers Don’t Think So]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484d941dc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-rally-already-over-hodlers-dont-think-so/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T02:07:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin long-term holders haven’t reacted much to the crash as their supply has stayed near all-time highs.
 
Bitcoin Long-Term Holder Supply Has Continued To Rise Recently
 
According to data from the market intelligence platform IntoTheBlock, the Bitcoin long-term holders (LTHs) have recently been in a phase of accumulation.
 
The LTHs refer to those investors who have been holding onto their coins since at least one year ago (as defined by IntoTheBlock; other analytics firms usually go with a period of around 155 days) without having sold or transferred them on the blockchain.
 
 
A statistical fact is that the longer holders keep their coins still on the network, the less likely they become to move them at any point. As such, the LTHs, who remain dormant for con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Verma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Sees Surge in Spot Bitcoin ETF Securities Registrations as Approval Deadline Approaches]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484c684c4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-sees-surge-in-spot-bitcoin-etf-securities-registrations-as-approval-deadline-approaches/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T01:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five spot bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) applicants have filed to register their funds as securities with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) as the approval deadline draws near. While some interpret this development as approval confirmation of spot bitcoin ETFs by the SEC, experts clarify that several steps remain before these ETFs are greenlighted to launch.
 
Vaneck, Valkyrie, Fidelity, Bitwise, and Grayscale File to Register Spot Bitcoin ETFs as Securities With SEC
 
Several asset managers have filed to register their spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) as securities with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The first deadline for a spot bitcoin ETF decision is Jan. 10. However, many expect the SEC to make a decision before that date.
 
Vaneck, Val…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Regulators Zoom In On Banks’ Crypto Involvement: A New Era Of Oversight?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484c686c2</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/eu-regulators-zoom-in-on-banks-crypto-involvement/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T01:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move concerning crypto, the European Banking Authority (EBA), in collaboration with the European Systemic Risk Board (ESRB) and the Financial Stability Board (FSB), has announced a joint initiative to investigate the interconnectedness of legacy banks with non-bank financial institutions (NBFIs).
 
Shining A Light On Shadow Banking
 
As disclosed by EBA chair José Manuel Campa in an interview with the Financial Times, this move aims to shed light on the potential risks and contagion effects that could arise between banking and non-banking financial sectors in “stress scenarios.”
 
 
The EBA’s approach marks a significant step in understanding the extent of banks’ exposure to the crypto sector, including hedge funds, crypto platforms, and private equity.
 
The EBA’s investigation will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saga Airdrop Coming Ahead of Blockchain Launch—Here’s Who Is Eligible]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211794</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211794/who-is-eligible-for-the-saga-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Polygon, Avalanche, Cosmos, and Celestia users will be included in Saga’s community token airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’re Not Here to Sell You Another ChatGPT’: Perplexity AI CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211784</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211784/perplexity-ai-answer-engine-not-another-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder Aravind Srinivas wants to change the perception of generative AI through a trustworthy "answer engine."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Draws Closer: Grayscale Files 8-A Form, Here’s What It Means]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484cc1a34</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-etf-grayscales-8-a-filing-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Investments has filed its Form 8-A with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), signaling substantial progress in their pursuit of launching a spot Bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF). This step, taken on January 4, follows closely on the heels of similar actions by Fidelity and Bitwise, highlighting a growing trend among financial firms aiming to offer spot ETFs.
 
The filing of an 8-A form is a pivotal regulatory requirement for companies aiming to list securities on an exchange. In the context of ETFs, it indicates a readiness to trade on an exchange pending product approval. This move is a crucial part of the approval process for Bitcoin ETFs, as evidenced by Valkyrie’s filing for a Bitcoin Strategy ETF (BITO) in October 2021.
 
 
JUST IN: Grayscale also filed Form 8-A (…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Calls Dogecoin Chart ‘Beautiful’, Here’s why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484c9ce0c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/analyst-dogecoin-chart-beautiful/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T23:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite a hard week of muted performance and an eventual crash, the bullishness around Dogecoin has not waned, especially among crypto analysts. Expectations for the crypto’s price are still high with crypto analyst JD referring to the Dogecoin price chart as beautiful.
 
Dogecoin Getting Ready To Breakout
 
In a recent analysis that was posted on X (formerly Twitter), crypto analyst JD has revealed why he finds the Dogecoin chart to be beautiful. The chart that was shared showed JD’s analysis and the expected price movement of DOGE over the year 2024.
 
 
The chart shows that the DOGE price has seen a bullish cross on the Moving Average Convergence Divergence (MACD). This development, the analyst shows, is bullish because of the coin’s historical performance after the MACD bullish cross w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Meets With Major Exchanges to Discuss Spot Bitcoin ETFs — Analysts Expect Imminent Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484ca0386</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-meets-with-major-exchanges-to-discuss-spot-bitcoin-etfs-analysts-expect-imminent-approval/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T23:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has met with officials from major exchanges to discuss spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs). Sources close to the proceedings say the securities regulator could begin notifying issuers of spot bitcoin ETF approval on Friday and trading could begin as early as next week. “SEC is giving final comments as we speak,” a Bloomberg analyst described, adding that this is “as close to ‘done’ as we’ve been.”
 
SEC Meeting With Exchanges to Discuss Spot Bitcoin ETFs
 
The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)’s staff attorneys from the Division of Trading and Markets reportedly held meetings with officials from major exchanges, including the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), Nasdaq, and Chicago Board Options Exchange (CBOE), on Wednesday. F…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s LFG Token Lures Ethereum Users, Plans Second Airdrop and Grants Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211778</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211778/solana-lfg-ethereum-users-second-airdrop-grants-program"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's “Less Fn Gas” airdropped LFG tokens to Ethereum users who spent over $4,269 in gas over the last year. It doesn't want to stop there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rebounds Above $44K as Spot BTC ETF Approval Looks Increasingly Likely]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484b42538</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/04/bitcoin-rebounds-above-44k-as-spot-btc-etf-approval-looks-increasingly-likely/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reports swirled that the SEC was giving final comments to issuers and may approve multiple spot-based bitcoin ETF applications very soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Taiwanese Crypto Exchange Under Investigation For Alleged NT$1 Billion Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484b7ff45</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/major-taiwanese-crypto-exchange-under-investigation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ACE, one of Taiwan’s leading crypto exchanges, founded by David Pan and Lian Nan in 2018, is under investigation for a major fraud case exceeding NT$1 billion ($32M). 
 
Recent reports reveal that the exchange, known as “ACE Exchange,” allegedly engaged in fraudulent activities and was subjected to a thorough investigation by the New Taipei City Criminal Police Brigade. 
 
The investigation found that Lin Nan and Pan collaborated in deceiving over 100 investors through fake advertisements, resulting in substantial financial losses. The suspects used social media platforms, such as Instagram and Facebook, to promote shitcoins, allegedly taking advantage of information gaps and promising quick wealth.
 
Massive Raid On ACE Crypto Exchange
 
According to authorities, Lin Nan allegedly exploit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logan Paul Launches CryptoZoo NFT ‘Buyback,’ Files Countersuit As Legal Battles Rage On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211776</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211776/logan-paul-launches-cryptozoo-nft-buyback-files-countersuit-as-legal-battles-rage-on"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The famous YouTuber and influencer alleges two of his CryptoZoo co-creators engaged in “nefarious trading activity.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blame Human Lawyers, Not Tech, for Courtroom Blunders: Robin AI Cofounder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211764</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211764/uk-startup-raises-26-million-to-build-law-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:42:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robin AI is taking on hallucinations and other thorny issues to ensure tech is an effective courtroom partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchanges Witness Bitcoin Deposit Boom Amidst Ethereum Retreat]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484befa6b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-exchanges-witness-bitcoin-deposit-boom-amidst-ethereum-retreat/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to recent data, in the past month, the quantity of bitcoin residing in centralized cryptocurrency exchanges surged by 32,058 bitcoin. Concurrently, the ethereum reserves on these exchanges have diminished, with 262,904 ether, valued at $597.42 million, being withdrawn from trading platforms since Dec. 4, 2023.
 
Bitcoin Bulks Up as Ethereum Eases Off in Latest Crypto Exchange Reserve Trends
 
An upsurge in bitcoin deposits and a decline in ether holdings have been observed at the world’s leading crypto exchanges, as per cryptoquant.com. The data indicates that on Dec. 4, 2023, exchanges housed 2,058,106 BTC, which has since risen by 1.55% to a current tally of 2,090,164 BTC. This surge reflects an accumulation of 32,058 BTC, valued at $1.4 billion, within the last month.
 
Data r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Rivals Shiba Inu And FLOKI Record Massive Surges In Burn Rate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484bef981</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-shiba-inu-and-floki/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The burn rates of Dogecoin rivals Shiba Inu and FLOKI have seen a significant spike over the last few days. Interestingly, the spikes in the burn rates of both of these meme coins are almost identical, raising questions of whether there is a coordinated effort going on to drastically reduce the available supply of both of these cryptocurrencies.
 
Shiba Inu Burn Rate Sees 3,963% Rise
 
The Shiba Inu burn rate which had seen a drawdown over the holidays had begun to pick up once more as soon as the market was back in full swing. It started out the week on a low note. But by Wednesday, the burn rate had begun to spike, starting with a 300% increase in a 24-hour timeframe.
 
 
This accelerated burn rate has carried on into Thursday where there has been a more than 10x increase in the spike re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Advisors Are Still Skeptical SEC Approves Bitcoin ETF, Bitwise Says]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211770/financial-advisors-are-still-skeptical-sec-approves-bitcoin-etf-bitwise-says"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T21:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only 39% of 437 financial advisors polled said they think we'll see a Bitcoin ETF available to U.S. investors in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto’s Predictable Unpredictability: Investor Decodes The Rhythms Of Digital Asset Cycles]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484a68d3f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-investor-decode-rhythms-digital-asset-cycles/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T20:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raoul Paul, a seasoned crypto investor, has recently shed light on the cyclical nature of the crypto markets. In a recent interview with Scott Melker, another notable investor, Paul painted a vivid picture of these cycles, likening them to the changing seasons.
 
Crypto Cycles Decoded
 
Paul’s metaphorical ‘crypto spring’ marks the beginning, leading into various phases such as altcoin season, decentralized finance (DeFi) season, explosive growth, and a harsh crypto winter, according to Paul.
 
 
Paul elaborates on the intricacies of these cycles, noting the recurring patterns that seem to define the crypto landscape. “It seems to be always DeFi season.,” he observes, highlighting Ethereum’s (ETH) pivotal role as it begins outperforming Bitcoin during periods of heightened global liquidity…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beam Token Up 36% as Merit Circle Network Transactions Hit All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211737/beam-token-up-merit-circle-transactions-hit-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T20:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Avalanche subnet token is climbing back toward its highest price ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Implications Of Cash Creation Instead of In Kind]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484a2ac60</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/the-real-implications-of-cash-creation-instead-of-in-kind"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has been busy, meeting with all of the potential issuers of spot Bitcoin ETFs with active applications in December. These meetings have resulted in the universal adoption of a cash creation methodology by those issuers instead of “in kind” transfers, as is typical for other ETFs. Much has been said about this change, ranging from the absurd to the serious. The TLDR, however, is the overall impact will be minimal to investors, relatively meaningful to the issuers and it reflects poorly on the SEC overall.
In order to provide context, it is important to describe the basic structure of Exchange Traded Funds. ETF issuers all engage with a group of Authorized Participants (APs) that have the ability to exchange either a predefined amount of the funds assets (stocks, bonds, commodities, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Weisberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Dominates as Crypto Investments Hit $2.2B on ETF Speculations: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484a2e38c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitcoin-dominates-as-crypto-investments-hit-22b-on-etf-speculations-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2023 marked a significant surge in the  
crypto investment landscape, witnessing a staggering $2.2 billion inflow into  
digital asset investment exchange-traded products (ETPs). 
This surge, unveiled by CoinShares' data cited by  
Coindesk, showcased a significant shift, notably driven by the escalating  
anticipation surrounding spot Bitcoin ETFs.
According to James Butterfill from CoinShares, the  
surge in the final quarter was propelled by mounting enthusiasm as the SEC  
hinted at potential approvals for Bitcoin spot-based ETFs in the United States.  

Bitcoin Records Soaring Inflows
The momentum of this surge in investment was  
observed in the final week of 2023. During this period, there was an influx of  
$243 million into digital asset ETPs, underlining the heightened investor  
interest in cryptocurrencies.
Bitcoin emerged as the frontrunner in these  
investments, capturing the largest share of $1.9 billion in inflows,  
representing a remarkable 87% of the total $2.2 billion. This dominance,  
unprecedented in the crypto investment landscape, marked a significant shift,  
surpassing the previous high of 80% in 2020.

The final week of 2023 saw US$243m of inflows into digital asset ETPs, bringing 2023 total flows to US$2.2bn. pic.twitter.com/EtdHQWlu2K
— James Butterfill (@jbutterfill) January 3, 2024
The price rally of Bitcoin through the year  
contributed substantially to this surge, witnessing a notable 155% climb and  
concluding 2023 at an impressive $42,000.
While Bitcoin led the charge, Solana (SOL) also  
showcased a robust performance in 2023, garnering $167 million in net inflows.  
Ethereum (ETH), however, lagged with a comparatively modest $78 million  
in the same period.
 
  
 
  
This article was written by Jared Kirui at www.financemagnates.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Adds Dedicated AI Key to Windows 11 Keyboard]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211739/microsoft-copilot-keyboard-dedicated-key"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cortana didn’t fare much better than Clippy, but the Redmond-based tech giant is betting that Copilot will finally earn its spot at our fingertips.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nikon, Sony, and Canon Pitch a New Way to Fight Deepfakes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211744</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211744/nikon-sony-and-canon-pitch-a-new-way-to-fight-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of watermarking AI images, top cameramakers propose encoding signatures into real photos instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Acquisition Scandal Rocks GOP: Lawmaker Accused Of Unlawfully Obtaining Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484ae4e86</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/republican-lawmaker-accused-acquiring-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:04:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent report by Raw Story sheds light on a Republican congressman who allegedly violated a federal financial disclosure law by failing to report two crypto purchases within the required timeframe. 
 
The congressman in question, Rep. Mike Collins (R-GA), reportedly purchased Ethereum (ETH) on October 9 and November 5. However, Collins did not publicly disclose them until December 22, well past the deadline mandated by the Stop Trading on Congressional Knowledge (STOCK) Act.
 
Crypto Investments And Congressional Ethics
 
Enacted in 2012, the STOCK Act was designed to combat insider trading, address conflicts of interest, and enhance transparency in Congress. 
 
It requires members of Congress to publicly report most purchases, sales, and exchanges of stocks, bonds, commodity futures, se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Obituary Bounce — Decline in ‘Death Calls’ Signals Resilient 2023]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484ae8017</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoins-obituary-bounce-decline-in-death-calls-signals-resilient-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T19:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following numerous proclamations of bitcoin’s demise in 2021 and 2022, totaling 47 and 27 on the Bitcoin Obituaries list respectively, a mere eight declarations were noted in 2023. The final one emerged at the year’s end, attributed to crypto advocate Arthur Hayes, who warned that if exchange-traded funds (ETFs) achieve excessive success, “they will completely destroy bitcoin.”
 
Bitcoin Obituaries Dwindle in 2023
 
2023 has passed, and as recorded by the Bitcoin Obituaries list on 99bitcoins.com, a total of eight proclamations of bitcoin’s end were noted. Apart from 2010, 2011, and 2012, the year recorded one of the lowest counts for bitcoin eulogies. There was one in 2010, six in 2011, and another single obituary in 2012. Notably, the initial declaration of bitcoin’s demise in the year c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale, VanEck and ARK Bitcoin ETFs Register to Trade on Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211735</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211735/grayscale-and-vaneck-bitcoin-etfs-register-to-trade-on-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T18:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two more Bitcoin ETF applicants have gotten the green light to have their funds listed on exchanges—but it's all pending SEC approval.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Spot ETF: Legal Expert Reveals What Would Happen If The SEC Denies Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484952e86</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-spot-etf-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T18:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent development has cast a shadow of doubt over the imminent approval of the pending Spot Bitcoin ETF applications by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). In line with this, a legal expert has hinted at what could happen next if the SEC were to reject these applications. 
 
Applicants To Sue SEC If Bitcoin ETF Gets Rejected
 
Lawyer and Web3 enthusiast James “MetaLawMan” Murphy mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that the Spot Bitcoin ETF applicants would immediately sue the SEC if all applications were denied. He further suggested that the Commission would likely lose as the Court of Appeals would once again rule that the decision was “arbitrary and capricious.”
 
 
In Murphy’s opinion, the Commission has no justifiable reason to deny these applications. Alluding to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoinMarketCap Announces Gaimin’s GMRX Token to Be Incubated by CMC Labs in a Historic First]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748495a0e2</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinmarketcap-announces-gaimins-gmrx-token-to-be-incubated-by-cmc-labs-in-a-historic-first/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T18:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. GAIMIN (www.gaimin.io), the world’s leader in delivering decentralised data processing power through gaimin.cloud (www.gaimin.cloud), has been selected by CoinMarketCap as an inaugural incubatee of the new CMC Labs accelerator program. 
 
CoinMarketCap (CMC) is the most valued source of news, data and community engagement for the crypto market and crypto stakeholders. With over 64 million daily active users, CMC only links their name to trusted and proven organisations. The newly launched CMC Labs incubator program is designed to leverage the expertise and brand of CMC with only those organisations who demonstrate proven strategic ability to deliver innovative products and services within the crypto industry.
 
GAIMIN has been handpicked by CMC for the incubation of GMRX, GA…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Investment Products Saw $2.2B of Inflows in 2023: CoinShares]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7484965472</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/01/04/crypto-investment-products-saw-22b-of-inflows-in-2023-coinshares/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mundane year of flows turned nicely higher in the final quarter of last year as excitement rose surrounding spot bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rebounds From Flash Crash as Market Fixates on ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211732</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211732/bitcoin-rebounds-flash-crash-btc-etf-price"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T17:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC has recovered losses after slipping briefly yesterday on fears that Bitcoin ETFs might again be denied or delayed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Coins Monero, Zcash, Horizen 'At Risk' of Delisting by Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211717/privacy-coins-monero-zcash-horizen-at-risk-of-delisting-by-binance"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T11:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has flagged several privacy coins with a "monitoring tag" indicating that they are at risk of being delisted from its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's What's Coming to Xbox Game Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=208162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/208162/heres-whats-coming-xbox-game-pass"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Xbox Game Pass is adding more indie games to its subscription service, as well as a few big names. Here's a look at the lineup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF: Is It Priced In?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211708</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211708/bitcoin-etf-priced-in"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T22:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts are split on whether the long-awaited approval of a Bitcoin ETF will halt BTC’s momentum, or pump the cryptocurrency even higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Bitcoin ETF Set to Trade on CBOE—But No Word From SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211702</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211702/fidelity-bitcoin-etf-set-to-trade-on-cboe-but-no-word-from-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T20:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fidelity Wise Origin Bitcoin Trust got the ok to trade on the CBOE under the FBTC ticker, but there's still no word from the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Justice Ponders Impact of AI on Law]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211696</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211696/supreme-court-justice-warns-of-ais-impact-on-legal-system"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T20:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justice Roberts emphasized AI's ability to aid people, but also 'dehumanize' the legal processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Before AI Puts Us Out of Work, AI Jobs Could Pay Well]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211675/before-ai-puts-us-out-of-work-ai-jobs-could-pay-well"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI jobs are paying on average 77% more than other jobs, with entry-level positions paying more than twice the average salary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Possible Scenarios for Bitcoin ETFs in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211560</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211560/three-possible-scenarios-bitcoin-etf-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will they or won’t they? The SEC is on the clock and crypto markets eagerly await its decision on a Bitcoin ETF. Here’s what could happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing 1500 BTC on Mt Gox and the Problem with Women in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EfNuNu8a/losing-1500-btc-on-mt-gox-and-the-problem-with-women-in-web3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T19:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host is joined by Brooke Lacey! 

They discuss:  
- Making and losing generational wealth
- Trauma Bond
- Women in Web3
- The Problem with WAGMI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming Tokens IMX, SAND and AXS Plunge Following Bitcoin Flash Crash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211671</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211671/gaming-tokens-imx-sand-and-axs-plunge-following-bitcoin-flash-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T18:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immutable, The Sandbox, Axie Infinity, and Gala tokens dropped 8-15%, facing deeper losses after Bitcoin’s dip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Upgrade Could Create a Centralized Fork, Says BRC-20 Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211665/bitcoin-ordinals-upgrade-could-be-unsafe-create-centralized-fork"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T18:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest drama in Bitcoin inscriptions swirls around the BRC-20 protocol, which allows the creation of meme coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearish Bitcoin ETF Report Spooks Market—But Analysts Say Denial Is Unlikely]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211658/bearish-bitcoin-etf-report-spooks-market-analysts-say-denial-unlikely"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T17:09:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A line about approval by Q2 2024 didn’t calm fears. The suggestion that none of the ETF applications will be approved in January panicked the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's MixMob Launches 'Race-to-Earn' Game Ahead of Airdrop, Saga Phone Perks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211637</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211637/solanas-mixmob-launches-race-earn-game-ahead-airdrop-saga-phone-perks"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MixMob's Racer 1 lets players gamble on races or earn crypto for wins. An airdrop is coming, along with benefits for Solana Saga owners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Plunges 7% to $42,000 in Flash Crash as Bull Run Falters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211634/bitcoin-plunges-7-to-42000-in-flash-crash-as-bull-run-falters"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin plunged by over 7% in the past 24 hours, erasing the past week's gains in a matter of minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor to Sell $216 Million in MicroStrategy Stock Options, Buy More Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211626</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211626/michael-saylor-to-sell-216-million-in-microstrategy-stock-options-buy-more-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T11:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy co-founder Michael Saylor plans to "acquire additional Bitcoin" for his personal holdings with some of the proceeds of the sale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Powered Cybercrime Will Explode in 2024: CrowdStrike Executive]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211596</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211596/ai-powered-cybercrime-will-explode-in-2024-crowdstrike-executive"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T02:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security exec Shawn Henry says the capability of AI to deceive and misinform is coming of age just in time for the 2024 elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midjourney Leaps into AI Video Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211583</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211583/midjourney-leaps-into-ai-video-creation"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T01:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI image generator MidJourney will begin training its video model in the upcoming days and they expect to release a final product "in a few months"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s When to Expect the Jupiter JUP Airdrop for Solana DeFi Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211576/heres-when-expect-jupiter-jup-airdrop-solana-defi-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T00:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter’s airdrop draws nearer and nearer. Here’s when the Solana DEX aggregator plans to launch JUP to the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source or OpenAI: What's the Best Path to Advanced AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211563/open-source-or-openai-whats-the-best-path-to-advanced-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T23:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long tweet went viral among AI enthusiasts, revisiting a decades-long debate over how AI will best evolve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Traders Flock to Sei and Its Dragon Ball-Inspired Meme Coin—Will It Last?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211551</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211551/crypto-traders-flock-to-sei-and-its-dragon-ball-inspired-meme-coin-will-it-last"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dragon Ball-themed SEIYAN meme coin has been gathering energy—and gains—on the Sei Network's Layer 1 blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFT Sales Skyrocket, Topping Ethereum in Monthly Volume for First Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211547</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211547/solana-nft-sales-skyrocket-ethereum-monthly-volume"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T21:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rising momentum around Solana catapulted NFT sales above Ethereum in December, according to data from CryptoSlam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sell Signal? Jim Cramer Pulls U-Turn on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211530/sell-signal-jim-cramer-pulls-u-turn-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infamous crypto skeptic admits Bitcoin's resilience in the face of government pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake Reveals Crypto Casino Stake's Rebranded F1 Racing Team]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211523</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211523/drake-reveals-crypto-casino-stakes-rebranded-f1-racing-team"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T20:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sauber's F1 team is now officially the Stake team. Rapper, spokesperson, and frequent bettor Drake took to social media to share the news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dymension Is the Latest Airdrop for Solana, Ethereum, and Cosmos Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211515</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211515/dymension-latest-airdrop-solana-ethereum-cosmos-users"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than a million crypto users and NFT owners across chains can now claim DYM tokens in Dymension’s airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Bitcoin ETF: Here’s What’s in the Latest SEC Filing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211514</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211514/grayscale-bitcoin-etf-latest-sec-filing"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T19:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale is one of many high-profile firms vying to launch a spot Bitcoin ETF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Are the High-Profile Spot Bitcoin ETF Applications Currently in Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=62912</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/62912/high-profile-bitcoin-etf-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T18:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has dragged its heels on approval of a Bitcoin spot ETF—but analysts are optimistic that there's light at the end of the tunnel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear and Loathing in Miami: Inside Art Basel and the Rug Radio Merger]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=210169</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/210169/fear-and-loathing-miami-inside-art-basel-rug-radio-merger"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T18:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writer’s note: Every time I mention something illegal in this story, it's intended as satire or for educational purposes only.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Fantasy Maker Square Enix Plans 'Aggressive' AI Moves in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211477</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211477/final-fantasy-maker-square-enix-plans-aggressive-ai-moves-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T17:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Square Enix wants to use AI to increase productivity and create content—despite broader industry backlash against the use of generative AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crystal Ball 2024: Are NFTs Dead—Or Reborn?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211258</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211258/crypto-crystal-ball-2024-are-nfts-dead-reborn"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T16:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts predict that NFTs will make a major rebound in 2024. But that doesn't mean old projects are going to surge again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Still Soaring on ETF Hype as $133 Million in Shorts Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211442/bitcoin-soaring-etf-hype-133-million-shorts-liquidated"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T15:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has gained 7% in the past day and ORDI, the biggest token built on the BRC-20 standard, is still rising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESL Faceit Group Exploring Blockchain 'Opportunistically,' Says Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yvrs4lBx/esl-faceit-group-exploring-blockchain-opportunistically-says-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T02:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Braithwaite—ESL Faceit Group's VP of Game Ecosystems, Mobile, and Snapdragon Pro Series—shares the esports firm's approach to blockchain technology with GG's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard's Plans for 2024 with Founders Paul and Katy Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/TI3aFBhO/wildcards-plans-for-2024-with-founders-paul-and-katy-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T21:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wildcard developers Paul and Katy Bettner tell Decrypt's Kate Irwin about why they see their game as a "Web3 game," not a crypto game, and share why they've stuck with their initial vision despite the challenging broader market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio Merge to Create Global Web3 Publishing Company]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VTEBYFD8/decrypt-and-rug-radio-merge-to-create-global-web3-publishing-company"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T17:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt and Rug Radio have announced their intent to merge, creating the world’s biggest decentralized publishing company. Codenamed [REDACTED], the alliance is aimed at revolutionizing tech-media, bringing together the forces of content creation and consumption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['If You Play Well, You're Gonna be Rewarded': How FPS Web3War is Bringing 'Skill-to-Earn' to Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Jl5AEFuD/if-you-play-well-youre-gonna-be-rewarded-how-fps-web3war-is-bringing-skill-to-earn-to-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roll1ng Thund3rz co-founder Valentin Cobelea and Zilliqa CEO Matt Dyer joined Decrypt to discuss how the new FPS game Web3War is shaking up the crypto gaming space with a novel "skill to earn" mechanic that rewards players for high-quality gameplay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating peaceful money & taking over your local government w/ Joseph Schiarizzi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zb0VG27G/creating-peaceful-money-taking-over-your-local-government-w-joseph-schiarizzi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:23:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week our host Reza Jafery is joined by Joseph Schiarizzi, founder of OpenDollar and prolific solidity developer. 


We discuss: 
- Onchain beer
- Taking over your local government
- His Emmy and 3 patents?!?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: Ember Sword CEO Says NFT Games Are More 'Transparent']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M9OHCVpA/interview-ember-sword-ceo-says-nft-games-are-more-transparent"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ember Sword CEO Mark Laursen shares why some big game studios "irk" him—and why he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>