<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-19T07:18:01.867Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-10-19T07:18:01.867Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Close to Rallying to New All-Time High, According to Analyst Michaël van de Poppe – But There’s a Catch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048555/Bitcoin-Close-to-Rallying-to-New-All-Time-High-According-to-Analyst-Michael-van-de-Poppe-But-Theres-a-Catch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048555/Bitcoin-Close-to-Rallying-to-New-All-Time-High-According-to-Analyst-Michael-van-de-Poppe-But-Theres-a-Catch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:04:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A widely followed crypto analyst believes that Bitcoin (BTC) is on the verge of printing new all-time highs (ATHs) as it reclaimed the $68,000 level Friday. Crypto trader Michaël van de Poppe tells his 730,800 followers on the social media platform X that Bitcoin’s surge past the current ATH of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Set To File Form C Next Week; What’s Next For SEC?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048557/Ripple-Set-To-File-Form-C-Next-Week-Whats-Next-For-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048557/Ripple-Set-To-File-Form-C-Next-Week-Whats-Next-For-SEC"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC recently filed its Form C, appealing a court ruling regarding Ripple’s XRP sales. The appeal focuses on three key points: the sale of XRP through exchanges, Ripple’s distribution of XRP to employees, and the sales made by executives Brad Garlinghouse and Chris Larsen. Ripple’s Chief...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s promised upgrades could aid price recovery, but until then…]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048552/Ethereums-promised-upgrades-could-aid-price-recovery-but-until-then</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048552/Ethereums-promised-upgrades-could-aid-price-recovery-but-until-then"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A rising leverage ratio can be seen as a sign of a heated up derivatives market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Poised to Surpass $70,000 Amid Political Changes, Says Matrixport]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048558/Bitcoin-Poised-to-Surpass-70000-Amid-Political-Changes-Says-Matrixport</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048558/Bitcoin-Poised-to-Surpass-70000-Amid-Political-Changes-Says-Matrixport"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's recent stability above $65,000 has fueled optimism for further market gains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[POPCAT Nears Breakout Towards New ATH, But Analysts Warn Of Possible Correction]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048554/POPCAT-Nears-Breakout-Towards-New-ATH-But-Analysts-Warn-Of-Possible-Correction</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048554/POPCAT-Nears-Breakout-Towards-New-ATH-But-Analysts-Warn-Of-Possible-Correction"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple market watchers suggest that memecoin sensation Popcat (POPCAT) is about to rally towards a new all-time high (ATH). As the token attempts to reclaim key resistance levels, some analysts warn the cat-themed memecoin could see a correction soon toward its monthly opening. Related...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Olympian’s drug empire busted, over $3M in crypto seized]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048518/Ex-Olympians-drug-empire-busted-over-3M-in-crypto-seized</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048518/Ex-Olympians-drug-empire-busted-over-3M-in-crypto-seized"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Olympian snowboarder Ryan James Wedding has been charged in a cocaine trafficking ring that allegedly used stablecoin Tether (USDT) to run billion-dollar deals. The US Attorney’s Office, Central District of California has charged Wedding and 15 other defendants for shipping kilograms of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Predicted To Hit 6-Figure Price In 2025, Bitwise CEO Says Next Year Will Be 'Exceptional' For King Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048521/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Hit-6-Figure-Price-In-2025-Bitwise-CEO-Says-Next-Year-Will-Be-Exceptional-For-King-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048521/Bitcoin-Predicted-To-Hit-6-Figure-Price-In-2025-Bitwise-CEO-Says-Next-Year-Will-Be-Exceptional-For-King-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (CRYPTO: BTC) enthusiasts have reason to be optimistic as the Chief Investment Officer of Bitwise, Matt Hougan, has projected that the apex crypto could hit a six-figure price by 2025. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is the Crypto Market Up Today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048513/Why-Is-the-Crypto-Market-Up-Today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048513/Why-Is-the-Crypto-Market-Up-Today"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency Market Today: The global cryptocurrency market is experiencing a boost today, with a 1.31% rise in market cap, bringing the total to $2.33 trillion. Market sentiment remains neutral, as indicated by the Fear & Greed Index sitting at 58. Bitcoin dominance has climbed to 57.7%,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple News: Court Set to Accept SEC’s Form C Filing; Spokesperson Denies Backdating Allegations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048511/Ripple-News-Court-Set-to-Accept-SECs-Form-C-Filing-Spokesperson-Denies-Backdating-Allegations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048511/Ripple-News-Court-Set-to-Accept-SECs-Form-C-Filing-Spokesperson-Denies-Backdating-Allegations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has shared details about its appeal in the Ripple XRP lawsuit, confirming its intention to challenge a recent court decision. They filed a Form C on October 16, but there’s some confusion because the court’s stamp on the document shows it was filed on October 17. This discrepancy has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI Is Driving the Next Stock Market Rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048508/How-AI-Is-Driving-the-Next-Stock-Market-Rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048508/How-AI-Is-Driving-the-Next-Stock-Market-Rally"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is transforming investment strategies, driving significant changes in stock market performance and investor behavior Artificial intelligence (AI) is a powerful tool that reshapes investment strategies in the financial landscape. Investors now use AI to analyze data and make decisions. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TAP Price Falls by 96% as Tapioca DAO Suffers $4.5 Million in Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048506/TAP-Price-Falls-by-96-as-Tapioca-DAO-Suffers-45-Million-in-Hack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048506/TAP-Price-Falls-by-96-as-Tapioca-DAO-Suffers-45-Million-in-Hack"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tapioca DAO has recently lost $4.5 million to a crypto hack; the consequence of which has been a 96.9% drop in the value of the TAP token. The hacker took advantage of the five vesting and stablecoin smart contracts in the DAO to siphoned 30 million TAP tokens. TAP for instance reduced its price …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Dominates Crypto Market with $100 Trillion Trading Milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048505/Binance-Dominates-Crypto-Market-with-100-Trillion-Trading-Milestone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048505/Binance-Dominates-Crypto-Market-with-100-Trillion-Trading-Milestone"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance under immense regulatory pressure has managed to reach a significant milestone, surpassing a staggering $100 trillion in cumulative spot and derivatives trading volume, according to CCData. Following Binance, OKX holds the second position with $24.9 trillion, while Bybit and Bitget rank...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWE Legends Kane and The Undertaker Endorse Donald Trump for President]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048500/WWE-Legends-Kane-and-The-Undertaker-Endorse-Donald-Trump-for-President</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048500/WWE-Legends-Kane-and-The-Undertaker-Endorse-Donald-Trump-for-President"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the U.S. presidential election nears, WWE Hall of Famers Kane and The Undertaker have publicly endorsed Donald Trump. In a recent social media video, they slammed actor Batista, who has criticized Trump’s character. The Undertaker, in a wrestling promo style, stated, “You can go with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, XRP, Litecoin Crypto ETFs Await SEC Decision—Will They Be Approved?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048498/Solana-XRP-Litecoin-Crypto-ETFs-Await-SEC-DecisionWill-They-Be-Approved</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048498/Solana-XRP-Litecoin-Crypto-ETFs-Await-SEC-DecisionWill-They-Be-Approved"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2024 will go down in history as the moment when Bitcoin and Ethereum exchange-traded funds (ETFs) finally launched, transforming the crypto landscape. Eleven Bitcoin spot ETFs were approved in January, a huge leap after years of futures-based products that started trading in 2021. Soon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seized Bitcoin Worth $378M Locked: Ireland’s Crime Bureau Missing Private Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048497/Seized-Bitcoin-Worth-378M-Locked-Irelands-Crime-Bureau-Missing-Private-Keys</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048497/Seized-Bitcoin-Worth-378M-Locked-Irelands-Crime-Bureau-Missing-Private-Keys"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland’s Criminal Assets Bureau (CAB) is facing a major roadblock. Back in 2019, they seized $378 million worth of Bitcoin from Clifton Collins, a convicted drug dealer. However, despite holding such a valuable amount of cryptocurrency, they can’t access it because the keys to the wallets are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Discussion, October 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048482/Daily-Discussion-October-19-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048482/Daily-Discussion-October-19-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please utilize this sticky thread for all general Bitcoin discussions! If you see posts on the front page or /r/Bitcoin/new which are better suited for this daily discussion thread, please help out by directing the OP to this thread instead. Thank you! If you don't get an answer to your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UAE Plans New Rules to Regulate Decentralized Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048352/UAE-Plans-New-Rules-to-Regulate-Decentralized-Organizations</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048352/UAE-Plans-New-Rules-to-Regulate-Decentralized-Organizations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A free zone in the UAE specializing in digital assets, is set to roll out a new legal framework aimed at decentralized autonomous organizations (DAOs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aptos Tech: how does the super scalable blockchain of the future work?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048493/Aptos-Tech-how-does-the-super-scalable-blockchain-of-the-future-work</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048493/Aptos-Tech-how-does-the-super-scalable-blockchain-of-the-future-work"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we delve into Aptos, one of the most scalable blockchain techs in the crypto landscape that competes as an alternative to Ethereum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF surges as investors flock to spot products]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048345/BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-surges-as-investors-flock-to-spot-products</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048345/BlackRocks-Bitcoin-ETF-surges-as-investors-flock-to-spot-products"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T05:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Bitcoin ETF received more than $1.05 b in the past five trading days as investors continue to show more interest in the spot products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market sentiment not as bullish as 'echo chamber' suggests, trader says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048341/Crypto-market-sentiment-not-as-bullish-as-echo-chamber-suggests-trader-says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/20048341/Crypto-market-sentiment-not-as-bullish-as-echo-chamber-suggests-trader-says"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T05:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A crypto trader argued that it is easy for crypto market participants to be "convinced sentiment is one way or the other," while claiming that the sentiment is not "that bullish currently."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Coinbase Sites Steal $20M — How Indian Man Led the Massive Crypto Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450661fc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fake-coinbase-sites-steal-20m-how-indian-man-led-the-massive-crypto-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T05:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cryptocurrency scam targeting Coinbase users has resulted in a significant theft of over $20 million. An Indian national, Chirag Tomar, was sentenced for orchestrating this scheme, where fake websites mimicking Coinbase led to victims surrendering credentials. U.S. authorities revealed how fraudsters used advanced tactics, including remote desktop access and posing as support agents, to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Tops Safe Haven Assets, According To Bank Of America—Can Bitcoin Compete?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450c8f6f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/gold-tops-safe-haven-assets-according-to-bank-of-america-can-bitcoin-compete/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T04:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, the financial community has debated on the best and safest investment during uncertain times. For most conservative traders and investors, bonds are an obvious choice. But for the younger set and tech-savvy individuals, Bitcoin is a better option. Despite fiscal challenges and current global economic trends, gold remains the best bet for analysts at Bank of America.
 
 
According to Bank of America, gold remains solid, regardless of falling or even higher interest rates. Interestingly, the bank is silent on Bitcoin’s role in the financial markets. However, many leading American banks are starting to get friendly, with Bank of America’s Merrill Lynch and Wells Fargo offering Bitcoin ETFs to their eligible clients.
 
 
 WOW: Bank of America today: Gold is the ‘last safe haven’ as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Expands Mobile Money Across Africa — 6 More Countries Gain Access]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450f137f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-expands-mobile-money-across-africa-6-more-countries-gain-access/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T03:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Binance has expanded its reach in West and Central Africa, integrating mobile money payments for cryptocurrency purchases in six countries. This move supports Binance’s goal to boost financial inclusion and make digital assets more accessible. By offering a secure, user-friendly entry into crypto, Binance aims to empower millions across Africa with greater access […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Bettor ‘Fredi’ Distorts Trump Odds On Polymarket, Researcher Claims]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450aeb51</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-bettor-distorts-trump-odds-polymarket/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T02:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a story within the decentralized prediction market sphere, a researcher has accused a crypto bettor, operating under the pseudonym ‘Fredi9999’ or simply ‘Fredi,’ of significantly manipulating the odds for former President Donald Trump on the crypto platform Polymarket. Over the past fortnight, Trump’s probability of winning has surged from near parity with Vice President Kamala Harris to a substantial 60.7%, while Harris’s odds have dwindled to 39.3%.
 
The allegations were brought to light by Domer (@Domahhhh), a pseudonymous political crypto bettor, who detailed his findings in an extensive thread on X. Domer stated: “A long-winded and winding update on Fredi9999 — the person or entity — who is singlehandedly rocketing up the price of Trump on prediction markets around the world. Spoi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Ruble and Sanctions: Expert Analyzes Russia’s Digital Currency Plan to Evade Western Control]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74450bb138</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/digital-ruble-and-sanctions-expert-analyzes-russias-digital-currency-plan-to-evade-western-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T02:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Fellow at the Carnegie Russia Eurasia Center and former adviser at the Central Bank of Russia has weighed in on the digital ruble, Russia’s central bank digital currency (CBDC), highlighting its potential role in reshaping Russia’s financial landscape amid sanctions. While the digital currency could offer new avenues for trade and reduce reliance on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Predicts Massive Upshoot For XRP Price To $5, Shiba Inu Price To $0.0008, ETFSwap Price From $0.03846 To $8]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446f4f805</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/expert-predicts-massive-upshoot-for-xrp-price-to-5-shiba-inu-price-to-0-0008-etfswap-price-from-0-03846-to-8/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T02:14:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi ecosystem expert has given an eye-opening investment alert that could help you make millions of dollars if you take early action. This expert has predicted the ETFSwap (ETFS) price to make a meteoric 20,700% rally from its current presale price of $0.03846 to $8 in the coming crypto market cycles. Alongside the ETFSwap price, this reliable DeFi expert has also predicted the XRP price to experience a massive upshoot to $5 and the Shiba Inu price to hit $0.0008 in millionaire-making rallies. Consequently, investment experts have nudged whale and retail investors alike to take advantage of the floor levels of the ETFSwap price, the Shiba Inu price, and the XRP price to make maximum gains. 
 
ETFSwap (ETFS) To Rally 20,700% To $8 — Set To Make Crypto Millionaires 
A leading DeFi ecosystem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$230M Bitcoin Heist Takes Dark Turn — $100M Still Missing, FBI Probes Kidnapping Link]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446f7c295</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/230m-bitcoin-heist-takes-dark-turn-100m-still-missing-fbi-probes-kidnapping-link/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T01:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two young men pulled off a $230 million bitcoin heist in one of the largest crypto thefts from a private individual in U.S. history. But after indulging in luxury cars and a $2 million watch, the story took a sinister twist. Now, prosecutors say the crime may be tied to a shocking kidnapping — and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Major' Telegram Game Puzzle Durov Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-major-telegram-puzzle-durov-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T01:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to complete Major’s daily Pavel Durov puzzle on Telegram? Here’s the solution for Friday, October 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analyst Says Dogecoin Price Could Pull An XRP This Cycle, What This Means]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446f13387</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-price-pull-an-xrp/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T01:12:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A prominent crypto analyst has sparked a thought-provoking debate on social media platform X, suggesting that the Dogecoin price may mirror XRP’s performance during the previous bull market. 
 
While most major cryptocurrencies surged to new all-time highs in the 2021 bull run, XRP struggled to break past its previous peak. Now, crypto analyst Tony “The Bull” Severino has drawn a comparison to Dogecoin displaying similar price action, noting the question of what if Dogecoin “pulls an XRP this cycle?”
 
Drawing Parallels Between XRP And Dogecoin Price
 
According to a technical analysis of the XRP and Dogecoin price charts Tony shared on social media platform X, Dogecoin’s price action in the past few years closely mirrors that of XRP’s price years back. Despite being one of the top cryptoc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock Targets $3 Trillion Crypto Derivatives Market, Quietly Pushing Game-Changing Token]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446f3e6f1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/blackrock-targets-3-trillion-crypto-derivatives-market-quietly-pushing-game-changing-token/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T00:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blackrock, the world’s largest asset manager, is reportedly seeking to disrupt the $3 trillion crypto derivatives market by pushing to have its BUIDL token accepted as collateral. Discussions are ongoing with major exchanges like Binance and Deribit. The token’s interest-paying structure could appeal to institutional investors seeking alternative collateral options in the growing derivatives sector. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside GOAT’s Wild Market Ride: What’s Driving This AI-Meme Coin Craze?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446fe2283</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/inside-goats-wild-market-ride-whats-driving-this-ai-meme-coin-craze/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T00:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The artificial intelligence (AI)-driven meme coin goatseus maximus (GOAT), launched on pump.fun, has reached a market valuation of $418 million after gaining more than 36% against the U.S. dollar by 7 p.m. Eastern Time on Friday. Earlier in the day, the meme coin hit an all-time high (ATH) of $0.461 per coin, although it has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Short-Term Holders Back In Action As Demand Resumes, Price Spike Looming?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446ff8fb3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-short-term-holders-back-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid the recent renewed upward price movement in Bitcoin, the demand for the largest cryptocurrency asset among short-term holders has witnessed a notable rise, suggesting strong optimism about BTC’s potential for growth in the near term.
 
Short-Term Holders Demand For Bitcoin Rebounds
 
Axel Adler Jr., a macro researcher and author at leading on-chain firm CryptoQuant, recently reported that the average demand for Bitcoin from short-term holders has resumed after spotting positive advancements in the BTC’s Short-Term Holders Supply 30D Change metric following a period of decline.
 
 
According to market data, these investors, who are usually identified by their ownership of BTC for fewer than 155 days, are actively buying the cryptocurrency once more. This rebound reflects renewed intere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Possible You Shouldn't Tell Journalists About Your Wash Trading Biz]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446f81812</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/18/its-possible-you-shouldnt-tell-journalists-about-your-wash-trading-biz/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, the Department of Justice announced charges against over a dozen individuals and entities, arguing these market makers were actually wash trading funds and defrauding people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Complete Decentralization of Finance Realistic? Fed Governor Waller Says No]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446f8770e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/is-complete-decentralization-of-finance-realistic-fed-governor-waller-says-no/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:32:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Federal Reserve governor questioned whether decentralized finance (defi) can truly eliminate the need for intermediaries, despite bitcoin’s revolutionary promise. While decentralized systems aim to bypass traditional structures, he argues that trust in intermediaries still resurfaces. Could crypto ever be fully decentralized, or will it mirror traditional finance? The potential regulatory challenges and the role […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining vs. AI Hosting: The Unexpected Parallels Unveiled]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446e5cc52</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-mining-vs-ai-hosting-the-unexpected-parallels-unveiled/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T22:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners and artificial intelligence (AI) cloud providers, along with high-performance computing (HPC) operators, share an unexpected bond in their quest for computing muscle. As the cryptocurrency scene shifts, some bitcoin mining setups are finding fresh purpose in the fast-growing fields of generative AI and large language models (LLMs). A Closer Look at the Unseen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polymarket Is “Good” But Critic Picks Out This One Big “Ethical” Problem]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446e7b3df</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/polymarket-good-critic-picks-out-ethical-problem/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T22:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polymarket, the predictions market on Polygon, is drawing global attention. Not only is it among the most active dapps without their token, but it is also closely being monitored by pollsters tracking the ongoing presidential campaign in the United States.
 
In the hotly contested campaign, the current vice president, Kamala Harris, is battling with Donald Trump. The former president lost to Joe Biden in 2020 but now wants to take over. 
 
Is Polymarket Misleading Punters?
 
Looking at Polymarket, Trump has extended his lead over the past few days. Punters place the probability of Donald Trump winning at 61% versus 39% for Harris. 
 
 
Interestingly, the Presidential Election Winner 2024 market has an overall volume of over $2 billion. As big as this may appear, one analyst thinks Polymark…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE, Cboe Win SEC Approval for Bitcoin ETF Options]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446e28717</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/10/18/nyse-cboe-win-sec-approval-for-bitcoin-etf-options/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T21:41:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decision follows Nasdaq recently also getting permission for options on spot bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Closes in on Price Peak – $69K Resistance in Sight]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446ec74e3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-closes-in-on-price-peak-69k-resistance-in-sight/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T21:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, bitcoin reached its highest price since late July, coming within just $2 of breaking through the $69,000 mark. Recent data shows the cryptocurrency market has been on a consistent upward trend, with the entire digital asset economy now valued at $2.35 trillion, reflecting a 2.63% rise over the last day. Crypto Market Rallies, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed’s Rate Cut Trajectory Remains Intact, Boosting the Crypto Outlook]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446ec911a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/10/18/the-feds-rate-cut-trajectory-remains-intact-boosting-the-crypto-outlook/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T21:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trend for inflation is returning back toward pre-pandemic levels of normal, giving policymakers more latitude on interest rates, says Scott Garliss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Garliss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Reasons Why Buying Shiba Inu Could Be Your Best Bet This Cycle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446e884cf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-best-bet-this-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are still reasons to believe that Shiba Inu (SHIB) could be one of the major gainers in this market cycle despite its underperformance compared to other meme coins. These reasons relate to the meme coin’s fundamentals, which paint a bullish outlook for it. 
 
Why Shiba Inu Could Be The Best Bet This Cycle
 
Shiba Inu could be the best bet in this cycle because of its burn rate. The number of tokens burned continues to spike, which opens up the possibility of the meme coin becoming more valuable and enjoying significant price rallies. Recently, the burn rate spiked by over 7,900%, a development that could catalyze the price surge to $0.00008. 
 
 
Shiba Inu’s burn rate will only keep rising, considering the team’s deliberate effort to implement deflationary mechanisms to help remove a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Shorts Surge On Binance – Bear Trap Or Downside Risk?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7446e884cd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-shorts-surge-on-binance-bear-trap-or-downside-risk/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After reaching new local highs recently, Bitcoin is at a turning point, pushing the market into a cautious yet optimistic mood. Despite the surge, analysts and investors remain wary, as BTC has repeatedly dropped from these levels since March, leading to concerns about another potential decline. 
 
The question on everyone’s mind is whether Bitcoin can break through this resistance or if history will repeat itself.
 
 
Key data shared by a top analyst reveals that many open positions on Binance are shorts, signaling bearish sentiment among traders. This has led to predictions of an impending drop for Bitcoin, further fueling caution in the market. 
 
However, some analysts argue this could be a trap for bearish investors, as the overwhelming number of short positions might trigger a short …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Villafuerte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluesky Signups Surge After Elon Musk's Twitter Says AI Can Be Trained on Tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287241/bluesky-signups-surge-elon-musk-twitter-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:31:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk's controversial moves at Twitter have sparked another user exodus, fueling explosive growth for decentralized rival Bluesky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, the SEC Isn't Backing Off Solana—Here's the Latest]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287253</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287253/sec-isnt-backing-off-solana-binance-latest"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New developments in the SEC’s lawsuit against Binance indicate the regulator is ratcheting up its case against SOL and other crypto tokens—not backing down, as some had hoped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge week for BTC ETFs, Crypto now through Venmo, Memes Dominate Gainers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rLpBnnaQ/huge-week-for-btc-etfs-crypto-now-through-venmo-memes-dominate-gainers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see biggest inflow week since July. BlackRock ETF sees $1bn inflows in a week. Venmo can now be used to buy crypto on Moonpay. SEC’s XRP appeal doesn’t challenge security status. Worldcoin rebrands to World with new orb. EigenLayer X account compromised. FBI arrests hacker of SEC X account. SCB in Thailand adopts stablecoins for transfers. DBS in Singapore adopts ‘token services’. Trump family to get 75% of WLFL revenue. Scroll team accused of owning sybil addresses. STX Nakamoto upgrade to happen next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Olympic Snowboarder Used Tether in Cocaine-Smuggling Murder Scheme, Feds Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287204/olympic-snowboarder-tether-cocaine-murders"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Canadian Olympic snowboarder and his gang used Tether (USDT) as part of its cocaine trafficking operation, U.S. authorities allege.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Trump Trade' Returns as BlackRock's ETF Brings in Another $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287209</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287209/bitcoin-trump-trade-blackrock-etf-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF inflows have accelerated this week as the 2024 presidential election tightens in its final weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will 'Off the Grid' Take Crypto Games Mainstream?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287211</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287211/will-off-the-grid-take-crypto-games-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche shooter Off the Grid has already made a huge splash in early access. We discuss the launch and potential impact on gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Let Him Come Home': Jailed Binance Exec’s Trial Postponed Due to Illness]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287207</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287207/jailed-binance-exec-trial-postponed-illness"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imprisoned Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan failed to attend a Nigerian court hearing due to his poor health, forcing a delay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scammer Gets 5 Years in Prison After Swiping $20 Million via Fake Coinbase Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287203/scammer-prison-fake-coinbase-websites"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T17:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chirag Tomar, an Indian national, drained the accounts of unsuspecting Coinbase customers in a scam built around impostor websites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Booming—You Can Earn More by Playing These Free Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205392</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205392/bitcoin-booming-you-earn-more-playing-free-games"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: Bitcoin is making a move for $69,000 as "Uptober" takes root, and you can earn more BTC by playing these games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radiant Capital’s $50M Breach Among ‘Most Sophisticated Hacks’ in DeFi History]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287162</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287162/radiant-capitals-50m-breach-among-most-sophisticated-hacks-in-defi-history"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi project claimed that hackers compromised the hardware wallets of its long-term developers and injected malware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dGEN1 Mobile Device Launches for ‘Seamless’ Onchain Ethereum Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287120</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287120/dgen1-mobile-device-launches-for-seamless-onchain-ethereum-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Created by Freedom Factory, dGEN1 integrates Ethereum at the operating system level to streamline dapp interactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy's Bitcoin Scheme Isn't an 'Infinite Money Glitch', Says Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287163/microstrategy-bitcoin-scheme-isnt-infinite-money-glitch"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy founder Michael Saylor dismissed criticism over the firm's $16 billion Bitcoin haul, saying it's driving BTC scarcity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EigenLayer Twitter Account Hacked to Share Ethereum Airdrop Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287159</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287159/eigenlayer-twitter-hack-airdrop-scam"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacker published a series of posts Friday from EigenLayer's Twitter account, urging users to click on an apparent phishing link.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning AI Helped Detect $4 Billion Worth of Fraud in 2024, Says US Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287141</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287141/machine-learning-ai-us-treasury"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI models helped the department prevent $2.5 billion in fraud, while its check fraud detection systems facilitated the recovery of $1 billion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Captain Tsubasa: Rivals' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=250928</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/captain-tsubasa-rivals-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anime soccer game Captain Tsubasa: Rivals gives out 5 million free daily balls ahead of the TON token airdrop. Here’s the combo for Friday, October 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Wright Says Bitcoin Devs 'Misled the Public' in New $1 Billion Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287138</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287138/craig-wright-bitcoin-new-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the SegWit and Taproot upgrades, Craig Wright claims Bitcoin “fundamentally deviated” from Satoshi Nakamoto’s vision and misled investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Hit Turbulence From US Bond Yields, Fed Policy: Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287119</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287119/bitcoin-could-hit-turbulence-from-us-bond-yields-fed-policy-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has climbed 11% in the past week, but there could be some macroeconomic headwinds on the horizon, say analysts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Is Today’s 'Tomarket' Telegram Game Daily Combo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-is-todays-tomarket-telegram-game-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Tomarket is handing out free tomatoes and bonus items ahead of the airdrop. Here’s the combo for Friday, October 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Moons Again After Musk Drops Token Mention During Pennsylvania Town Hall]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287079/dogecoin-moons-again-musk-drops-token-mention-during-pennsylvania-town-hall"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone asked Musk if he would head up a new “Department of Government Efficiency.” Musk responded with a lighthearted grin, “Yeah, Doge.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Files Last-Minute Appeal in Ripple Case—Why the XRP Army is Outraged]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287069</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287069/sec-files-last-minute-appeal-in-ripple-case-why-xrp-army-outraged"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T02:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the SEC isn't contesting the ruling that XRP sales to retail investors aren't securities, it is instead focusing on other key aspects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Rebrands as World, Launches New Eyeball Scanning Orb]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=287051</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/287051/worldcoin-rebrands-as-world-launches-new-retina-scanning-orb"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World's redesigned Orb has 30% fewer parts and triple the production capacity of its predecessor, powered by NVIDIA’s Jetson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Researchers Hacked AI Robots Into Breaking Traffic Laws—And Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286994</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286994/how-researchers-hacked-ai-robots-into-breaking-traffic-laws-and-worse"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T23:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers showed vulnerabilities in AI-powered robots being exploited to perform dangerous tasks, including detonating bombs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Worldcoin Built an Ethereum Network Specifically for Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286983</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286983/world-chain-launches-mainnet-world-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World, previously called Worldcoin, has debuted an Ethereum layer-2 chain with an aim to onboard real humans—not bots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Bulls Have Reason to Worry If L2s Remain Dominant, Says VanEck Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286970/ethereum-price-target-plunge-vaneck-analyst"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T22:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's "changing fundamentals" and growing embrace of layer-2 networks could massively impact ETH's future price, a VanEck analyst said Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk-Themed ‘X Empire’ Ends Telegram Gameplay Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286977</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286977/x-empire-ends-telegram-gameplay-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tap-to-earn game X Empire is gearing up for next week’s X token launch and airdrop on The Open Network (TON).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo Can Now Be Used to Buy Bitcoin and Ethereum via MoonPay]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286969</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286969/paypal-venmo-buy-crypto-moonpay"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T20:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal's Venmo can now be used by U.S. customers to top up and make crypto purchases on MoonPay, according to a Thursday announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Race Past $20 Billion Milestone in Just 10 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286948/bitcoin-etf-20-billion-milestone-inflows-blackrock"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approved in January, Bitcoin exchange-traded funds have experienced trading activity like no other ETF product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxis Teams Up With TV Show ‘Killer Whales’ to ‘Empower Creators’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=285090</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/285090/galaxis-teams-up-with-tv-show-killer-whales-to-empower-creators"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T19:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will see Galaxis showcased throughout the reality show, as well as “actively supporting” the Web3 projects featured.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrapped Bitcoin Wars Ramp Up as Kraken Reveals kBTC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286934/wrapped-bitcoin-wars-kraken-kbtc"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Kraken has unveiled a new wrapped Bitcoin product dubbed kBTC, joining a growing battle with Coinbase, 21.co, and BitGo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Presidential Election Tops $2 Billion in Betting Volume on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286923</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286923/us-presidential-election-2-billion-volume-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump is currently leading the Polymarket betting pool on the winner of the U.S. election, which has topped $2 billion in total volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Majors Fall 1 to 2%, A New Tiger takes to the Charts, Van Eck teases Big Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a6Tm7OGW/majors-fall-1-to-2-a-new-tiger-takes-to-the-charts-van-eck-teases-big-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lucky GOAT memecoin trader turned $5,000 into $1.5M during GOAT's run to $300M. A new memecoin based on Disney Park's new baby tiger "Bakso" was a top mover on Wednesday, running to $10M (now $6M). Crypto majors fall 1-2%, memes red across board. a16z calls 2024 crypto's biggest year yet in "State of Crypto" report. Vitalik publishes part 2 of blog outlining ETH's future. Van Eck teases big bet on Parallel and web3 gaming. Huge day for digital art with 4 marquee mints seeing success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gnosis Pay Isn’t Just Another Crypto Card]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=283801</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/283801/why-gnosis-pay-isnt-just-another-crypto-card"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The self-custodial crypto debit card is a step towards ‘banking 3.0,’ combining legacy payments infrastructure with Web3 innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins Blast Past Bitcoin Gains as Crypto Market Gets Frothy Again]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286859</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286859/meme-coins-blast-past-bitcoin-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T16:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's been a good week for Bitcoin—but meme coins like TURBO and BRETT are really riding the "Uptober" rocket ship to the moon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Arrests Suspect in SEC Twitter Hack That Pumped Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=286910</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/286910/fbi-arrest-sec-twitter-hack-bitcoin-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T15:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when the SEC's Twitter account was hacked to prematurely share that Bitcoin ETFs were approved? The FBI has arrested a suspect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Season 2 Teaser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/qcvjjJxN/hamster-kombat-season-2-teaser"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T12:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a first look at Season 2 of Telegram tap-to-earn game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68K, Trump odds Continue to Rise, GOAT nears $300M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/c88qN8eB/btc-hits-68k-trump-odds-continue-to-rise-goat-nears-300m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $68k as ETF inflows continue to soar. Open Interest at CME hits ATH, funding still low. Tesla moves $750m BTC to new wallet. Canary applies for Litcoin ETF, LTC up 8%. Grayscale asks SEC to convert altcoin fund to ETF. Kraken integrates with EigenLayer for restaking. ‘Network state’ Praxis raises $525m for new city. Trump project raises only $11m so far. a16z founders donate $2.5m to Trump PAC. TikTok accused of being crypto exchange in UK. Gotbit CEO arrested in Portugal. Perplexity AI launches finance platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETF Inflows Soar, Kamala Courts Crypto, TURBO Nears $1BN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zn2lboMV/etf-inflows-soar-kamala-courts-crypto-turbo-nears-1bn"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T18:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETFs see $800m inflows in 2-days, huge volume. ETF inflows may be linked to Trump odds: CoinShares. Bitcoin will rival housing market as asset class: Fink. Vitalik proposes drop to 1ETH to become validator. Kamala reveals pro-crypto policies. Kamala mocked for linking crypto to race. Hyperliquid announces HYPE token coming. PUFFER airdrop claim goes live. Tether considering lending to commodities trader. Man takes $500m lost Bitcoin case to court. Google removes crypto prices from search. SUI Foundation denies $400m insider selling. UAE approves $AED stablecoin. Bitget wallet now only behind Binance for downloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week High, China Stocks Rally again, GOAT hits $120M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0V0rYhMX/btc-hits-2-week-high-china-stocks-rally-again-goat-hits-120m"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits 2-week high as China stocks rise. SUI breaks into the top 15 coins. $1.3bn ETH might be sold from PlusToken scam. S. Korea may approve BTC & ETH ETFs this month. Australia launches first ETH ETF. Samara to buy BTC with $33m bond. Altcoins to see $500m unlocks this week. Vitalik writes blog on the future of ETH. Grayscale reveals 35 altcoins considered for funds. Ethena proposes SOL for USDe collateral. Only one Binance launchpad coin up this year. AVAX summit begins this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi, Google may be Broken-up, Murad’s Wallets Doxxed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pLw8b2d2/todd-revealed-as-satoshi-google-may-be-broken-up-murads-wallets-doxxed"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC will be range bound until election: Bernstein. TAO & memecoins dominate mindshare. Peter Todd ‘revealed’ as Satoshi by HBO. US government able to sell $4.4bn Silk Road BTC. Ireland unable to access $378m seized BTC. SOL could do 5x if Trump wins: StanChart. Coinbase integrates Taproot addresses for BTC. Canary Capital applies for XRP ETF. S. Korea to regulate stablecoin transfers. CryptoCom files countersuit against SEC. Babylon fills cap with 22k BTC. Scroll airdrop coming Oct 22nd. USDC goes live on SUI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Falls Ahead of CPI, Stripe Reinstates Crypto, Fed Charges Market-makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/aYgFvZqj/crypto-falls-ahead-of-cpi-stripe-reinstates-crypto-fed-charges-market-makers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors drop despite stocks hitting ATHs. Stripe reinstates crypto payments. Crypto settlements near $20bn in 2024. S. Korea to review ban on BTC ETFs. US charges market makers for market manipulation. FBI created their own coin to ensnare targets. Vitalik ‘outside pick’ for Nobel Prize. Trump family token to built on Aave stack. $16m OP tokens allocated to superchain users. Wisdomtree debuts debit card for on-chain fund. 47% of hedge funds have crypto exposure. Argentina overtakes Brazil for crypto inflows. Tucker interviews Ryan Salame over FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bounces from $59K, Tesla unveils Robotaxis, Memecoins Outperform]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cyJj6tWj/bitcoin-bounces-from-59k-tesla-unveils-robotaxis-memecoins-outperform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T07:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC briefly dips under $59k, $160m liquidations. Mt Gox extends repayment plan by 1 year. Uniswap plans L2 for DeFi. SEC sues crypto trading firm Cumberland. Binomial sues SEC over futures trading. SEC’s Uyeda criticises agency’s policy. Justin Sun named prime minister of Liberland. MicroStrategy wants to become BTC bank. Binance pre-market trading goes live. Nearly 50% of US investors want crypto ETFs. Whale phished for $35m crypto. Ethena invests $46m in RWA funds. Trump’s crypto project aims to raise $300m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentraland Desktop Client Preview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qqzvDcTC/decentraland-desktop-client-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum metaverse game Decentraland has shared an exclusive look at the visual and performance upgrades coming via its new desktop client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins.]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Hj3nDp7G/crypto-trader-murad-mahmudov-talks-about-the-supercycle-and-how-he-chooses-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Trader Murad Mahmudov talks about the Supercycle and how he chooses Meme Coins. Crypto stable, had sold off after China stocks fall. Crypto adopted faster than other tech: BlackRock. Crypto adoption to hit 8% of world population. CryptoCom recieves Wells notice from SEC. HBO documentary on Satoshi airs tonight. FTX bankruptcy plan approved by judge. Scroll airdrop may be imminent. Jupiter goes live on mobile iOS. Phantom rolls out support for Base. AAVE launches GHO on Base. Gensler may be replaced by Robinhood CLO. 87% of new token launches on SOL. National Bank of Bahrain creates BTC fund. BedRock DeFi allows BTC staking on ARB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/703mAYhV/memecoins-take-off-funding-stays-low-china-stocks-keep-on-rising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR EP213. Memecoins take off, funding stays low, China stocks keep on rising!
Many altcoins & memecoins soar despite stable BTC. Funding rates continue to be low or negative. Crypto funds saw $147m of outflows last week. BTC remains best performing major assets this year. SUI breaks into the top 20 coins again. TAO leads top 100 away from memes, sifu shorts. $100m bridge to SOL over the last 7 days. Metaplanet buys $6.7m more BTC. ETH proposal aims to improve throughput 50%. EIGEN, OP, APT lead token unlocks this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Walrus Protocol Unlocks New Applications for Decentralized Data Storage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kwEYLYWj/how-walrus-protocol-unlocks-new-applications-for-decentralized-data-storage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mysten Labs Chief Scientist George Danezis joined Decrypt to talk about its new decentralized storage protocol Walrus, which promises to unlock new applications such as AI and social media, thanks to its novel Red Stuff data encoding algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Sees Crypto as a Bipartisan, 'Purple' Political Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YR2YmmwR/why-coinbase-sees-crypto-as-a-bipartisan-purple-political-issue"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase VP of Corporate and Business Development, Shan Aggarwal, joined Decrypt's Sander Lutz and Liz Napolitano at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss the exchange's efforts to grow mainstream crypto adoption—and how the changing political conversation around digital assets is rapidly playing a major role in that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Playing Offense—Not Just Defense—Against Crypto Crime, Says Head of Financial Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DiJ8D2Qc/binance-is-playing-offensenot-just-defenseagainst-crypto-crime-says-head-of-financial-investigations"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T01:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nils Anderson Röed, the exchange’s global head of financial investigations, sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at Messari Mainnet 2024 to discuss how Binance is proactively dismantling criminal networks around the world, the strategy with which the crypto exchange is approaching sensitive conflicts in the Middle East, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 212 - SEEDPHRASE TALKS ART!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PJfaJNkZ/fomo-hour-212-seedphrase-talks-art"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T19:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Payrolls Higher than expected, Bitcoin reacts hard. Crypto sank early in the week as Middle East tensions spooked markets. Powell signals two more rate cuts this year. SUI leads L1s again, nears YTD high despite large unlock. Majority of FTX repayments still months away. EIGEN becomes non-transferable, hits $6bn FDV. SEC to appeal Ripple securities law ruling. Visa launches tokenization platform for banks. SWIFT plans digital asset trial in 2025. ByBit launched trading of global stock indices. SPX, GIGA & FWOG hit ATHs, most memes fall. XCOPY to release 250 piece collection on Shape. HBO documentary claims to have identified Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins bleed, ByBit launches stock index trading, POCHITA soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/kYjAt3nt/altcoins-bleed-bybit-launches-stock-index-trading-pochita-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins sink, BTC dominance nears cycle high. BTC in ‘three blind mice’ downtrend. Tron revenue hits record $577m in Q3. ByBit to launch trading of major stock indices. Franklin Templeton launch fund on APT. SWIFT banks to trial digital assets in 2025. Aerodrome hits $1bn TVL on Base. Cronje calls out Aerodrome for copyright. ETH ICO wallet sells $47m. SEC files appeal against Ripple ruling. EIGEN falls 20% on staking rewards FUD. FTX to auction off WLD position. Half of US voters think crypto ‘important’. North Korea ‘infiltrating’ crypto industry. Snowden challenged over SOL centralisation view. Top SEC official on crypto set to depart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DACOM Summit: Fastex CLO Vardan Khachatryan on Crypto Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LGGnxkb6/dacom-summit-fastex-clo-vardan-khachatryan-on-crypto-compliance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fastex Chief Legal Officer Vardan Khachatryan joined Rug Radio creator Mlow at DACOM Summit to discuss how the crypto exchange is advancing compliance, and the regulatory challenges that lie ahead for the sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 210 - MIDDLE EAST TENSIONS RISE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Bcj37IF2/fomo-hour-210-middle-east-tensions-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T17:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto drops as Middle East tensions flare. $500m liquidations in drop. BTC ETFs see largest outflows in a month. Fidelity ETH ETF sees 2nd highest outflow ever. SUI hits 6-month highs, bridge goes live on mainnet. Hashdex set to launch XRP ETF. Wormhole leads altcoin gains after Upbit lists. BTC miners hit record low profits in September Crypto hackers stole $750m in Q3. Telegram has been disclosing IPs since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Arbitrum is Simplifying Web3 for Web2 Adopters]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Mm9OGAoG/how-arbitrum-is-simplifying-web3-for-web2-adopters"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T14:19:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbitrum's Head of Korea, John Park, joined Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow at ArbiVerse to talk about the Ethereum layer-2's strategy in Asia, hackathons, and bringing enterprise clients to its ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>