<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-07T08:20:27.876Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-07T08:20:27.876Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Attract $488M as BTC Price Nears Record High]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564928/Bitcoin-ETFs-Attract-488M-as-BTC-Price-Nears-Record-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564928/Bitcoin-ETFs-Attract-488M-as-BTC-Price-Nears-Record-High"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T08:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs attract $488M in net inflows, propelling BTC price to $71,767 and nearing its all-time high, reflecting renewed investor confidence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Atty. General Goes After Crypto Crooks In $1 Billion Scam Bust]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7412235dc1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-crooks-busted-in-1-billion-scam/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T08:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James has filed a lawsuit against two crypto companies, NovaTech Ltd and AWS Mining Pty Ltd, alleging a staggering $1 billion scam. The lawsuit, targeting not just the companies but also their associates, paints a disturbing picture of religious manipulation and exploited trust within immigrant communities.
 
 
Targeting The Flock: Social Media Sermons And WhatsApp Whispers
 
NovaTech Ltd, led by the charismatic Cynthia Petion who styled herself as the “Reverend CEO,” allegedly preyed on Haitian and other immigrant communities. Leveraging social media platforms, prayer groups, and communication channels like WhatsApp, they conducted their operations primarily in Creole. The lawsuit details a calculated strategy. Trust in religious figures and the allure of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buy Now, Crypto Bull Market Returns, Says Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564880/Buy-Now-Crypto-Bull-Market-Returns-Says-Arthur-Hayes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564880/Buy-Now-Crypto-Bull-Market-Returns-Says-Arthur-Hayes"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T08:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new essay titled “Group of Fools,” Arthur Hayes, the outspoken co-founder of crypto exchange BitMEX, casts a critical eye over recent macroeconomic developments and their implications for the crypto market. Hayes, known for his direct and often provocative commentary, employs a blend of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Taps Kaiko for Enhanced Cryptocurrency Derivatives Trading]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74122c7b11</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gemini-taps-kaiko-for-enhanced-cryptocurrency-derivatives-trading/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaiko, a prominent player in the crypto data sector, has announced a strategic partnership with Gemini Foundation, the derivatives trading platform of the cryptocurrency exchange, Gemini. This collaboration will see Gemini Foundation utilizing Kaiko’s Benchmark Reference Rates to power its derivatives platform. The partnership aims to enhance the stability and security of Gemini’s platform by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Debuts TON-Linked In-App Digital Payment Token ‘Stars’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564861/Telegram-Debuts-TON-Linked-In-App-Digital-Payment-Token-Stars</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564861/Telegram-Debuts-TON-Linked-In-App-Digital-Payment-Token-Stars"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Telegram’s CEO Pavel Durov, with the Telegram Stars, mini apps will be able to accept payments for digital services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop rally sends Roaring Kitty’s shares to $1B]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564856/GameStop-rally-sends-Roaring-Kittys-shares-to-1B</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564856/GameStop-rally-sends-Roaring-Kittys-shares-to-1B"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If GameStop opens at its current after-hours price, Roaring Kitty’s holdings would be worth around $1 billion combined.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Whales Are Buying Up Bitcoin Like It’s 2020 Again]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564910/Crypto-Whales-Are-Buying-Up-Bitcoin-Like-Its-2020-Again</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564910/Crypto-Whales-Are-Buying-Up-Bitcoin-Like-Its-2020-Again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a CryptoQuant weekly report, large investors, known as “whales,” are accumulating Bitcoin at a pace similar to that seen before the 2020 bull run. The firm’s data reveals daily injections of $1 billion into Bitcoin and a significant increase in holdings by these whales. This mirrors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin may retest $69K next as shorts keep BTC price below all-time high]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564794/Bitcoin-may-retest-69K-next-as-shorts-keep-BTC-price-below-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564794/Bitcoin-may-retest-69K-next-as-shorts-keep-BTC-price-below-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin sees surprise selling into the latest daily close, giving rise to predictions of a support retest before new BTC price all-time highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges Past $71,000 as Institutions and Economic Data Boost Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564906/Bitcoin-Surges-Past-71000-as-Institutions-and-Economic-Data-Boost-Confidence</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564906/Bitcoin-Surges-Past-71000-as-Institutions-and-Economic-Data-Boost-Confidence"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has recently experienced a significant boom, reaching over $71,000 due to positive macroeconomic indicators and rising interest from institutional investors. This surge, the longest in three months for the cryptocurrency, stems from anticipation of potential rate cuts by the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-driven crypto crime is only just beginning — Elliptic report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564768/AI-driven-crypto-crime-is-only-just-beginning-Elliptic-report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564768/AI-driven-crypto-crime-is-only-just-beginning-Elliptic-report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elliptic’s 2024 report exposes how AI is increasingly used for sophisticated crypto crimes, from deepfake scams to state-sponsored cyberattacks, signaling that these threats are just beginning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Dive: Why Almost Every Bitcoin Holder is Winning Right Now]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564800/Data-Dive-Why-Almost-Every-Bitcoin-Holder-is-Winning-Right-Now</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564800/Data-Dive-Why-Almost-Every-Bitcoin-Holder-is-Winning-Right-Now"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain analytics firm Santiment reported on X that nearly 98% of Bitcoin’s (BTC) total supply is currently profitable, marking substantial gains for investors since the cryptocurrency’s inception. To clarify its methodology for readers unfamiliar with blockchain data analysis, Santiment...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum to Introduce Extensive Pectra Upgrade in Q1 2025]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74122a9535</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ethereum-to-introduce-extensive-pectra-upgrade-in-q1-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum network is set to undergo one of its most extensive upgrades named Pectra, which will integrate the EVM Object Format (EOF) and introduce Vitalik Buterin’s proposed EIP-7702, allowing Ethereum account addresses to act as smart contract wallets temporarily during transactions. The Pectra upgrade, expected to be rolled out in the first quarter of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Never Banned Bitcoin Mining, Researcher Reveals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74122ab664</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/china-never-banned-bitcoin-mining/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a striking revelation that challenges widely-held perceptions, Daniel Batten, a Bitcoin environmental impact analyst, disclosed that BTC mining was never officially banned in China. According to Batten’s research, despite widespread reports to the contrary, the so-called “ban” was actually a temporary suspension, and mining activities have largely resumed across the country.
 
Bitcoin Mining Was Never Banned In China
 
Batten’s report highlights that the hashrate within China, which is a measure of the computational power used in mining and processing Bitcoin, currently accounts for approximately 15% of the global total. This information stands in stark contrast to the dominant narrative that emerged in May 2021, when numerous major news outlets reported a comprehensive crackdown on cry…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin on Cusp of Major ‘Blue Sky Breakout’, Says Crypto Analyst Kevin Svenson – Here Are His Targets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564726/Bitcoin-on-Cusp-of-Major-Blue-Sky-Breakout-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Kevin-Svenson-Here-Are-His-Targets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564726/Bitcoin-on-Cusp-of-Major-Blue-Sky-Breakout-Says-Crypto-Analyst-Kevin-Svenson-Here-Are-His-Targets"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:04:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst and trader Kevin Svenson is saying that Bitcoin (BTC) is flashing a bullish signal amid the flagship crypto asset’s double-digit bump over the past month. In a new video, Svenson tells his 78,400 YouTube subscribers that Bitcoin is on a parabolic trend and is close to a “point of going...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Partners With Swiss Crypto Valley]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74122b5f47</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hong-kong-partners-with-swiss-crypto-valley/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Invest Hong Kong, the government department responsible for attracting foreign direct investment and the Crypto Valley Association (CVA) of Zug, Switzerland, have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to bolster the fintech ecosystems of both regions. The agreement, signed on June 6, 2024, aims to enhance collaboration, particularly in blockchain and cryptographic technologies. It also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Important Polkadot (DOT) Price Predictions to Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564712/Three-Important-Polkadot-DOT-Price-Predictions-to-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564712/Three-Important-Polkadot-DOT-Price-Predictions-to-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out which resistance zones appear to be crucial for a potential DOT bull run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Never Banned Bitcoin Mining, Researcher Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564707/China-Never-Banned-Bitcoin-Mining-Researcher-Reveals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564707/China-Never-Banned-Bitcoin-Mining-Researcher-Reveals"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a striking revelation that challenges widely-held perceptions, Daniel Batten, a Bitcoin environmental impact analyst, disclosed that BTC mining was never officially banned in China. According to Batten’s research, despite widespread reports to the contrary, the so-called “ban” was actually a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jasmycoin set for another rally? Potential 60% gains ahead!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564704/Jasmycoin-set-for-another-rally-Potential-60-gains-ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564704/Jasmycoin-set-for-another-rally-Potential-60-gains-ahead"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RSI on the 3-day chart showed intense bullish momentum and the CMF's reading of +0.12 supported the idea of firm capital inflow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard and Visa Payments Return After a Hiatus on Binance]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564727/Mastercard-and-Visa-Payments-Return-After-a-Hiatus-on-Binance</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564727/Mastercard-and-Visa-Payments-Return-After-a-Hiatus-on-Binance"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T06:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has announced the reinstatement of crypto payment services through Mastercard and Visa. Binance revealed this decision via a recent X post, stating, “Use Mastercard, Visa, or SEPA for bank transfers and experience seamless transactions!” A Binance spokesperson shared insights into the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Illuvium is launching on 25th of July with new features]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564611/Illuvium-is-launching-on-25th-of-July-with-new-features</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564611/Illuvium-is-launching-on-25th-of-July-with-new-features"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T06:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illuvium recently announced the official launch of its Web3 game with several new features and rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bets Hit Peak of $37B as ETF Inflows Set New Record]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564620/Bitcoin-Bets-Hit-Peak-of-37B-as-ETF-Inflows-Set-New-Record</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564620/Bitcoin-Bets-Hit-Peak-of-37B-as-ETF-Inflows-Set-New-Record"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T06:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The long-short ratio is starting to tilt in favor of bulls since Wednesday, data indicates, as some traders expect bitcoin to set fresh all-time highs in the coming weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s (WLD) Price Has a Shot at Recovery Thanks to Whales]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564709/Worldcoins-WLD-Price-Has-a-Shot-at-Recovery-Thanks-to-Whales</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564709/Worldcoins-WLD-Price-Has-a-Shot-at-Recovery-Thanks-to-Whales"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T06:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s (WLD) price is on a bullish path propelled by one of the most influential cohorts, the whale addresses. This investors’ accumulation has enabled WLD to recover recent losses with the help of investors potentially. Worldcoin Investors Accumulate Worldcoin’s price is above the $5 mark...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia bull superano Apple nella corsa per il titolo più prezioso al mondo]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564678/Nvidia-bull-superano-Apple-nella-corsa-per-il-titolo-piu-prezioso-al-mondo</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564678/Nvidia-bull-superano-Apple-nella-corsa-per-il-titolo-piu-prezioso-al-mondo"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T06:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft maintains a slight advantage in the competition among the major tech companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea's Popular Cryptocurrency Exchange Announces the Listing of a New Memecoin!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564572/South-Koreas-Popular-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Announces-the-Listing-of-a-New-Memecoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564572/South-Koreas-Popular-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Announces-the-Listing-of-a-New-Memecoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T06:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bithumb, South Korea's leading cryptocurrency platform, announced that it has added a new meme token to the KRW market. Continue Reading: South Korea's Popular Cryptocurrency Exchange Announces the Listing of a New Memecoin!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain.com: the crypto company launches its Web3 domain with Unstoppable Domains]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564677/Blockchaincom-the-crypto-company-launches-its-Web3-domain-with-Unstoppable-Domains</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19564677/Blockchaincom-the-crypto-company-launches-its-Web3-domain-with-Unstoppable-Domains"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T06:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.blockchain will be enabled for DNS through the request to ICANN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, Nodo Partner to Drive Stablecoin and Bitcoin Education in Africa]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74121cf97d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tether-nodo-partner-to-drive-stablecoin-and-bitcoin-education-in-africa/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Tether has partnered with Nodo to educate prospective African users about the use cases of stablecoins and facilitate transactions with the former’s digital asset. The six-month campaign will include Ask Me Anything (AMA) sessions, workshops, and question-and-answer sessions with crypto experts on social media. African Users to Learn of Stablecoin Use Cases The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Creditors Filed an Objection against Bankruptcy Reorganization Plan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74121da062</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftx-creditors-filed-an-objection-against-bankruptcy-reorganization-plan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of creditors of the now-collapsed FTX has moved to court, objecting to the crypto exchange’s bankruptcy reorganization plan, which would pay the unsecured creditors the entirety of their claims, if not more.
The Formal Objection of FTX Creditors
A group led by Sunil Kavuri, one of FTX's vocal creditors, filed the objection yesterday (Thursday) in the US bankruptcy court. They reject the reorganization plan on several grounds, including the assertion that it does not serve the best interests of the creditors.
The objection further highlighted that the plan ignores property rights issues. Furthermore, it pointed out that, as the settlement with the creditors would be done in cash, it would trigger a taxable event.
Creditors additionally objected to the release of the funds to the cre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Survey Reveals Nearly 90% Of Spanish Users Support Its Return]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741219c68c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/worldcoin-survey-reveals-nearly-90-of-spanish-users-support-its-return/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin (WLD) recently faced more regulatory scrutiny after halting its operations in Spain. Its developer, Tools For Humanity (TFH), has agreed to extend the operational pause in the country as part of the ongoing investigation regarding the company’s data collection and processing.
 
 
On Thursday, the project revealed that a recent survey showed nearly 90% of its users in Spain support Worldcoin’s return to the country.
 
87% Of Spanish Users Support Worldcoin’s Return
 
This week, Tools For Humanity announced it would voluntarily halt its operations in Spain for the rest of the year. This move would allow the Bayerische Landesamt für Datenschutzaufsicht (BayLDA) to complete its audit regarding the company’s compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
 
TFH committe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uzbekistan’s Islamic Authority Retracts Fatwa Against Cryptocurrency, Issues Apology]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7412055d5b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/uzbekistans-islamic-authority-retracts-fatwa-against-cryptocurrency-issues-apology/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T04:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uzbekistan’s highest Islamic authority has retracted a fatwa it issued on June 3 that deemed trading with cryptocurrencies impermissible. This declaration, which stated that cryptocurrency trading violated Sharia law, was mistakenly released on social media due to an oversight. In response, the Fatwa Center issued a statement titled “Correction and Apologies.” The statement disclosed that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETFs Brace For Sluggish Reception, JPMorgan Expects Modest $1-$3 Billion Inflows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741207bb5d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/jpmorgan-predicts-sluggish-interest-ethereum-etfs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T04:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a Bloomberg report, analysts suggest that the debut of the recently approved Ethereum ETFs in the US may generate significantly less demand than spot-Bitcoin products. Major financial institutions, including BlackRock and Fidelity, await final approvals from the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to list the long-awaited Ethereum funds. 
 
However, JPMorgan strategists anticipate much smaller net inflows into Ethereum ETFs than the $15.3 billion flowing into Bitcoin vehicles this year.
 
Analysts Divided On Ethereum ETFs’ Potential
 
Per the report, the success of the five-month-old Bitcoin ETFs can be attributed to a controversial narrative that presents Bitcoin as digital gold, a concept that Ether lacks. Additionally, the Ether funds will not offer staking rewards for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross Border CBDC Project Mbridge Enters MVP Stage]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741202b7be</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cross-border-cbdc-project-mbridge-enters-mvp-stage/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T03:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Project Mbridge, the cross-border central bank digital currency (CBDC) project that seeks to integrate several currencies into a global network, has reached its minimum viable product stage. This means that each one of the participant central banks has deployed a validating node in the network, that is ready to perform real-value transactions CBDC Project Mbridge […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO Sends Crucial Warning To Community – Here’s What It Is]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74120dea57</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-cto-warning-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T03:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple CTO David Schwartz has sent a crucial warning to the community members in regards to a number of scams that have been proliferating. With the crypto market prices recovering once more, scammers are back in full force and they tend to hone in on a community as their target victims, warranting warnings such as this.
 
Ripple CTO Warns Community Of Scams
 
A new type of scam targeting X (formerly Twitter) has made the rounds, seemingly harnessing the fear of accounts getting banned as a way to hack user accounts. The DM, which was posted by another X user who goes by @3YearLetterman, reveals a threatening message from someone pretending to be from the X team.
 
 
The contents of the DM show an initial accusation that the X user’s account was being investigated for copyright violations.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Federal Prosecutors, Agents Ask U.S. Sec. Blinken to ‘Step Up’ Efforts to Secure Detained Binance Exec’s Release]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74120ff8f7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/07/former-federal-prosecutors-agents-ask-us-sec-blinken-to-step-up-efforts-to-secure-detained-binance-execs-release/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T02:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of 108 former federal prosecutors and agents have signed a public letter to U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken urging the State Department to “step up” its efforts to secure Binance compliance head Tigran Gambaryan’s release from a Nigerian prison, Axios reported Thursday evening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheyenne Ligon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Stand With Crypto’ Advocacy Alliance Surpasses 1 Million Supporters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74120a4d0a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/stand-with-crypto-advocacy-alliance-surpasses-1-million-supporters/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T02:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Stand with Crypto” alliance has achieved a notable milestone, surpassing one million supporters as reported on its official website. This non-profit organization is committed to mobilizing global crypto advocates. Initiated by crypto exchange Coinbase, which promotes clearer and more effective regulations for the cryptocurrency industry in the U.S., the alliance has gained substantial momentum. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin vs Ethereum: Expert Predicts Doom For ETH’s Price – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74120beea8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-vs-ethereum-expert-predicts-doom-for-eth/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T02:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin maximalist Max Keiser has recently reiterated his stance on Ethereum, predicting a dire future for the cryptocurrency against Bitcoin. Keiser’s latest critique, shared on social media platform X, revives his longstanding view that Bitcoin outshines Ethereum and other altcoins on fundamental levels.
 
According to Keiser, Ethereum is “heading to zero against BTC,” citing fundamental differences in their underlying technologies and legal classifications.
 
 
Commodity Status And Decentralization Concerns
 
Keiser’s argument hinges on the idea that Ethereum is not centralized and lacks the commodity status and a decentralized proof-of-work algorithm that “bolsters” Bitcoin’s appeal.
 
He points out that in countries like El Salvador, where he advises President Nayib Bukele on Bitcoin …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin Agrees to Temporarily Stop Operations in Spain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7413f62faa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/worldcoin-agrees-to-temporarily-stop-operations-in-spain/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T01:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the biometric proof-of-personhood identification protocol, has agreed to temporarily stop its operations in Spain. According to statements from the Spanish privacy watchdog AEPD, the company committed to stop its data collection practices for a year or until Baviera’s privacy regulator finishes its investigation into Worldcoin’s inner workings. Worldcoin to Pause Biometric Data Collection Activities […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s First Crypto Fraud Trial Ends With Student’s 4-Year Prison Sentence]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7413f15a91</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chinese-student-4-year-prison-for-crypto-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T01:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a groundbreaking case that has drawn significant attention in China, a college student named Yang Qichao has been sentenced to 4 years and 6 months in prison and fined 30,000 yuan ($41,000) for “fraudulently” issuing a cryptocurrency called BFF on the Binance’s BNB Chain. 
 
The case, which took place at the People’s Court of Nanyang High-tech Industrial Development Zone in Henan Province, marks the first criminal trial in China involving the issuance of a virtual currency. The Asian country has strict regulations that prohibit people from participating in the issuance, trading, or investing in these assets.
 
Criminal Trial On Crypto Fraud
 
According to local media reports, the incident began in May 2022 when Yang Qichao, a senior student at a university in Zhejiang, created a digital…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Charge UK Nationals With $3 Million ‘Evolved Apes’ Ethereum NFT Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234302</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234302/evolved-apes-nft-game-ethereum-crypto-rug-pull"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T00:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The trio said they would release a battle royale game, but instead pocketed the crypto and ran.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Confirms Mastercard and Visa Support for Crypto Purchases but No Binance Credit Card Issued]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7413fda64d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/binance-confirms-mastercard-and-visa-support-for-crypto-purchases-but-no-binance-credit-card-issued/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T00:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Binance posted on social media platform X Thursday that users can purchase cryptocurrency using Mastercard, Visa, or SEPA for bank transfers. The announcement led to confusion among some users regarding the reintroduction of Binance-branded credit cards. Binance Customer Support clarified that the current facilities allow the use of existing payment methods to buy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Says Dogecoin Ready To See A Breakout Massive Whale Accumulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7413ff1083</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/dogecoin-ready-breakout-massive/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T00:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto analyst Kevin (Formerly OG Yomi) has highlighted a bullish pattern on the Dogecoin (DOGE) chart, which shows that a breakout is imminent. His prediction follows the recent wave of accumulation by DOGE whales, with these buys likely contributing to the potential breakout. 
 
Dogecoin Indicator Flashing Breakout Signal
 
Kevin mentioned in an X (formerly Twitter) post that the two-month Bollinger Bands breakout indicator on Dogecoin is flashing an imminent breakout, which is set to occur for the foremost meme coin for the first time since November 2020.
 
 
He added that DOGE was also about to see the first two-month Moving Average Convergence/Divergence (MACD) bullish cross since November 2020. 
 
 
The analyst sounded confident about this imminent breakout, suggesting it was inevita…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DuckDuckGo Launches a Private Portal to Top AI Chatbots]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234252</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234252/duckduckgo-ai-chatbot-anonymous-privacy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T23:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world's best-known private browser launches a privacy-first gateway to popular AI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Kiyosaki Says His Prediction of Bitcoin Hitting $350K in August ‘Is Not a Lie’ — Also Bullish on Ethereum and Solana]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7413fb5cb5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/robert-kiyosaki-says-his-prediction-of-bitcoin-hitting-350k-in-august-is-not-a-lie-also-bullish-on-ethereum-and-solana/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T23:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki has emphasized that his prediction of bitcoin hitting $350K on Aug. 25 “is not a lie.” He also expressed his bullish outlook for ethereum and solana, noting that he will keep buying the three cryptocurrencies because he is “quite certain their prices will continue to rise.” Robert Kiyosaki […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ashton Kutcher Says AI Will Make Movies Better—Hollywood Disagrees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234277</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234277/ashton-kutcher-ai-movie-filmmaking-sora-slammed"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T23:18:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The star of “Dude, Where’s My Car?” responded to the backlash, saying that AI won't replace the arts, but “acting like it doesn't exist will be catastrophic.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Hulk Hogan Really Pump and Dump a Solana Meme Coin?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234285</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234285/hulk-hogan-pump-dump-solana-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T22:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro wrestler Hulk Hogan was accused of a celebrity meme coin scam on Thursday, but says the tweets were “not from me.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Sues Crypto Miner and Exchange for $1 Billion In Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234261</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234261/new-york-1-billion-fraud-crypto-exchange-miner"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T22:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little-known crypto exchange drew $1 billion from investors by generating fake returns using old investor money, the state attorney general alleges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Reveals Livestream Return as GameStop Stock Blasts Off]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234259</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234259/roaring-kitty-reveals-livestream-gamestop-stock-blasts-off"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T21:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares of GameStop (GME) soared to the end of the trading day up nearly 50% as trader Roaring Kitty schedules a YouTube livestream for Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Telegram Game Hits 100 Million Players—Here's When the Token Is Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234260</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234260/hamster-kombat-telegram-game-100-million-when-token"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T21:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s fast-rising crypto game Hamster Kombat is gearing up to launch a token on The Open Network in the near future. Here's when.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Launches TON-Linked 'Stars' Currency After Toncoin Hits All-Time High Price]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234246</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234246/telegram-ton-linked-stars-currency-toncoin-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T20:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers of mini apps on Telegram will now be able to sell digital goods and services for Stars, which can be converted into Toncoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McDonald's Just Launched Its Own Metaverse—And Grimace NFT Owners Are VIPs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234239</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234239/mcdonalds-metaverse-grimace-nft-owners-vips"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T20:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fast food chain McDonald’s just rolled out a metaverse world to Singapore customers, with special perks for Grimace NFT holders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humane AI Pin Implosion? Poor Sales, Fire Risk, and Potential Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234228</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234228/humane-ai-pin-implosion-poor-sales-fire-risk-potential-acquisition"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sleek and expensive device was pitched as the future of AI hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xai Reveals Vanguard: Genesis Campaign With New Ethereum Games and Rewards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234231</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234231/xai-vanguard-genesis-campaign-ethereum-games-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xai, the layer-3 Ethereum gaming network built on Arbitrum, plans to roll out several games in the coming months along with rewards for players and builders alike.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['The Sandbox' Ethereum Game Valued at $1 Billion With New Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234224</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234224/sandbox-ethereum-game-valued-1-billion-funding"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T18:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Metaverse game The Sandbox is the latest crypto unicorn following a $20 million raise led by parent Animoca Brands alongside Kingsway Capital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Central Bank Cuts Rates—What It Means for the Fed and Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234218</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234218/european-central-bank-cuts-rates-what-means-fed-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T17:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts believe the Fed won’t lower interest rates until later this year, with inflation proving more stubborn in the United States than in Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin Giant Tether Now Owns 25% of Bitcoin Miner Bitdeer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234183</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234183/stablecoin-giant-tether-bitcoin-miner-bitdeer"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T16:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether, the firm behind USDT, now owns 25% of Bitcoin miner Bitdeer's shares according to a new SEC filing on Thursday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Rising as Roaring Kitty YouTube Channel Mysteriously Updated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234210</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234210/gamestop-stock-rising-roaring-kitty-youtube"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T16:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares in GameStop (GME) are climbing again Thursday amid speculation that influencer Roaring Kitty is returning to livestreams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Templeton Eyeing New Crypto Fund After Ethereum ETF Approval: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234197</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234197/franklin-templeton-crypto-fund-ethereum-etf-approval"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T15:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fund would cater to institutional investors and focus on altcoins, according to a report—and could offer staking rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F1 Team McLaren Reveals Free Ethereum NFTs With OKX]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234186</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234186/f1-team-mclaren-reveals-free-ethereum-nfts-with-okx"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T15:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[McLaren and F1 team sponsor OKX are launching free NFTs on the Ethereum network X Layer with potential VIP prizes up for grabs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Let’s Push Boundaries’: NFC Summit Takes in Awards, AI and ‘Post-Human Modernism’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233949</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233949/nfc-summit-takes-in-awards-ai-and-post-human-modernism"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T13:12:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third edition of the Non-Fungible Conference in Lisbon celebrated NFTs, Bitcoin Ordinals, AI filmmaking and meme coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Network Ronin Launches ‘Forge’ Program to Onboard More Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234104</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234104/ethereum-network-ronin-forge-onboard-games"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The network behind Pixels and Axie Infinity is starting to open up to more studios and games. Here’s what Ronin Forge has in store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Xociety’ Developer Raises $7.5 Million to Launch Sui Shooter Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234095</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234095/xociety-developer-raises-7-5-million-sui-shooter-game"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T12:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vibrant third-person shooter game Xociety is gearing up to launch on Sui later this year after raising some fresh funding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Coin BNB Sets All-Time High as Chain Volume Soars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234164</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234164/binance-coin-bnb-sets-all-time-high-as-chain-volume-soars"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T12:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB Chain’s total value locked has increased by $460 million in the past 30 days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Acquires Crypto Exchange Bitstamp in $200 Million Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234163</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234163/robinhood-acquires-crypto-exchange-bitstamp-in-200-million-deal"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T11:32:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The $200 million cash deal is expected to close in the first half of 2025, subject to regulatory approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Bitcoin Jesus' Roger Ver Released on Bail in Spain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234135</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234135/bitcoin-jesus-roger-ver-released-on-bail-in-spain"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T10:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin early adopter and Bitcoin Cash evangelist faces extradition to the U.S. on charges of evading taxes to the tune of $48 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riot Stock Shrugs Off Short Seller's 'War Against Bitcoin Miners']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234132</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234132/riot-stock-shrugs-off-short-sellers-war-against-bitcoin-miners"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T10:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Bitcoin mining is one of the stupidest business models we've come across in our time short selling," the Kerrisdale CIO said yesterday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warped Games Embraces Premature Teaser Release to Highlight "Warped Universe"]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234148</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234148/warped-games-embraces-premature-teaser-release-to-highlight-warped-universe"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T09:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delaware, United States, 6th June 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenAI Safety Researcher Says ‘Security Was Not Prioritized’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234079/openai-safety-security-china-leopold-aschenbrenner"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T01:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leopold Aschenbrenner joins a growing chorus of former and current OpenAI employees that say CEO Sam Altman is leaving responsible AI development behind in his pursuit of profit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This iPhone Challenger Could Transform Smartphones by Trading Apps for AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234063/nothing-phone-3-ai-companion"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T00:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next high-end smartphone from British electronics maker Nothing will make AI everything, including a personalized AI companion that feels “almost like a best friend.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia Flips Apple As Stock Hits $3 Trillion Market Cap Amid AI Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234061</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234061/nvidia-stock-3-trillion-market-cap"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T00:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With NVDA stock flying high, investors have good reason to cheer—including Nancy Pelosi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Users Just Wasted $100K on Invalid Rune Mints]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234046</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234046/bitcoin-runes-mint-invalid-leeroy-jenkins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$97,662 in BTC evaporated as late transactions killed attempts at minting on the Rune Protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Price to Hit $22,000 by 2030, Predicts VanEck]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234047</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234047/ethereum-price-to-hit-22000-by-2030-predicts-vaneck"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm’s spot Bitcoin ETF has pulled in $513 million so far, and it foresees a bright future for Ethereum, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Devs Shut Down Linea—Can Layer-2 Networks Be Trusted?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234040</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234040/ethereum-devs-shut-down-linea-layer-2-networks-trusted"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Layer-2s have been sold as Ethereum’s future—but are they actually decentralized? Linea's weekend crisis raises tough questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Cipher Guide: How to Use Morse Code to Earn a Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hamster-kombat-daily-cipher-guide-morse-codeearn-million-free-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T20:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now there’s another way to rack up free coins ahead of the Hamster Kombat airdrop. Here’s how to do it and where to find the latest code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Pumps 16% as SEC Chair Gensler Sidesteps Roaring Kitty Question]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234020</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234020/gamestop-gme-stock-price-roaring-kitty"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T19:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Gill’s trading activity and social media posts are reportedly being scrutinized by federal and state regulators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Rises After Bank of Canada Cuts Interest Rate Below 5%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234022</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234022/bitcoin-price-71600-after-canada-cut-interest-rate-below-5-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T19:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada is the first G7 nation to pull back on inflation controls, with the European Union likely next in line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Is Now Being Asked About Bonk ETFs Following Ethereum Approvals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234012</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234012/gary-gensler-asked-about-bonk-etfs-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T19:14:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gary Gensler took a less hostile approach to crypto in a new interview following Ethereum ETF approvals—and was asked what's next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Creator Vitalik Buterin Explains What Celebrity Tokens Get Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234014</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234014/vitalik-buterin-celebrity-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto veteran railed against star-studded token cash grabs, saying the hype can be harnessed for good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jil Sander, Maison Margiela, and Marni Fashion Brands Adopt On-Chain Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233986</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/233986/jil-sander-maison-margiela-marni-fashion-on-chain-authentication"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parent company OTB has announced plans to use Aura’s NFC chip-based blockchain model for digital certificates of authenticity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 122 - ETH ETF MOVES CLOSER!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs move closer to approval, drop staking. Blackrock ETF see biggest inflow in 6 weeks. Grayscale ETH discount narrows under 10%. BTC & ETH heading for ATH: StanChart. Banana zone squared coming for ETH: Raoul Pal. Trump accepts crypto donations including DOGE. Pelosi mulls support of crypto bill. Farcaster raises $150M, DEGEN up 20%. Coinbase to launch gold & oil futures trading. Uniswap ‘ready to fight’ against SEC. Vitalik proposes solutions to MEV problems. Phantom may soon support email sign-up. Jupiter announces initiative to tokenise RWAs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 120 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL again leads majors, DEX volume dwarfs others. BTC whales buys $106M in 24hrs. ETH ETF decision on Thursday or Friday. 5 of 7 onchain indicators ‘point to bull-run’. ETH ETF may be rejected due to weak link to futures. AI coins in focus ahead of Nvidia earnings. Cobie inks new article on low float, high FDV coins. ETH foundation staff reveal links to EigenLayer. 12 L2 & L3s controlled by single multisig. Layer Zero pauses sybil rewards. Aevo to airdrop pre-launch tokens on platform. FTM to migrate one-to-one to Sonic S coin. UK judge rules Craig Wright is not Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 119 - GOOD MORNING BULLS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher again, BTC stable. ETFs see $257M inflow, volumes hit 2 month high. 414 holders of BlackRock ETF ‘blows away record’. SOL continues to be fastest blockage despite usage. Pump. fun exploited for $1.9M by ex-employee. LINK up 20% after partnership with top banks. Senate also repeals SEC crypto rule. US Senator uses laser eyes PFP. Tether mints another $1B USDT. Bitcoin production costs now $45K: JP Morgan. Pink Drainer retires after stealing $85m assets. PancakeSwap to reimburse fees on Uniswap. TON & Tether partnership on payment solution. Trabucco writes character defence of Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 118 - ARE THE ETFS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has best day in 2 months after dovish CPI. ETFs see $300M inflow, highest in weeks. ETH continues to underperform ahead of ETF ruling. Millennium buys $2B of BTC ETF. CME group to launch BTC spot trading. Fed’s Kashkari compares BTC to beanie babies. Tate says he will buy $100M BTC. El Salvador now owns 5750 BTC. Binance creates ‘antidote’ to address poisoning. Tornado Cash developer appeals conviction. China busts $1.9B USDT banking racket. MEV bot operators charged with fraud by DoJ. Swiss to adopt global crypto tax rules. FTX repayments create ‘bullish overhang’ for crypto. SEI up 30% after proposing v2 upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 117 - BITCOIN GAINS ON CPI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces driven by spot buying. US ETF sees $100M+ inflow for first time in weeks. State of Wisconsin buys $170M of BTC ETF. Vanguard appoints Bitcoin friendly CEO. Coinbase sees billions of BTC leave exchange. BTC to consolidate between $55-75K: Novogratz. SOL beats ETH TEV for first time ever. ETH may be labelled a security by SEC next week. AI & memes the only two positive sectors this week. Crypto hostility led by TradFi: Lubin. Tornado Cash developer guilty of money laundering. Circle shifts legal hope to US ahead of IPO. Cypher developer gambled $300K of customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>