<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-21T10:16:44.282Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-21T10:16:44.282Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inflows into Bitcoin ETFs Continue as the Likelihood of Approval of Ethereum ETFs Increases! Here are the Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507710/Inflows-into-Bitcoin-ETFs-Continue-as-the-Likelihood-of-Approval-of-Ethereum-ETFs-Increases-Here-are-the-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507710/Inflows-into-Bitcoin-ETFs-Continue-as-the-Likelihood-of-Approval-of-Ethereum-ETFs-Increases-Here-are-the-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) rose on Monday with net inflows of $241.12 million. Continue Reading: Inflows into Bitcoin ETFs Continue as the Likelihood of Approval of Ethereum ETFs Increases! Here are the Details]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's Dankrad Feist joins EigenLayer, faces community backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507701/Ethereums-Dankrad-Feist-joins-EigenLayer-faces-community-backlash</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507701/Ethereums-Dankrad-Feist-joins-EigenLayer-faces-community-backlash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feist's decision to join Eigenlayer as an Advisor follows in the recent controversial footsteps of Ethereum researcher Justin Drake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drop Hunting on CryptoRank: The Best Airdrop Guides at One Place]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507690/Drop-Hunting-on-CryptoRank-The-Best-Airdrop-Guides-at-One-Place</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507690/Drop-Hunting-on-CryptoRank-The-Best-Airdrop-Guides-at-One-Place"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently we released a new product dedicated to airdrops, Drop Hunting, and in this article we want to familiarize you with its functionality. This tool is now available to every CryptoRank user. With it, airdrop hunting will become more advanced, efficient and simple. Airdrop mania has taken...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Bybit Reaches 30 Million Registered Users Around the Globe]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742686b112</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-exchange-bybit-reaches-30-million-registered-users-around-the-globe/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Bybit has announced that it has surpassed 30 million registered users globally, marking a significant milestone in its growth. The company’s market share in spot trading has increased from 2% in 2023 to 9.3% in 2024, according to the latest Kaiko Research quarterly report. This growth is attributed to Bybit’s commitment to user […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit celebrates 30 million users milestone amid unprecedented Web3 growth]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507668/Bybit-celebrates-30-million-users-milestone-amid-unprecedented-Web3-growth</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507668/Bybit-celebrates-30-million-users-milestone-amid-unprecedented-Web3-growth"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit, one of the world’s top three crypto exchanges by trading volume, has reached a monumental milestone, surpassing 30 million … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC takes surprising step towards approving spot Ether ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507616/SEC-takes-surprising-step-towards-approving-spot-Ether-ETFs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507616/SEC-takes-surprising-step-towards-approving-spot-Ether-ETFs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC has taken the first step towards approving spot-based Ether (ETH) ETFs in collaboration with partner exchanges.The article SEC takes surprising step towards approving spot Ether ETFs was first published on Crypto Valley Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin’s explosive growth drives crypto adoption on Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507614/Notcoins-explosive-growth-drives-crypto-adoption-on-Telegram</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507614/Notcoins-explosive-growth-drives-crypto-adoption-on-Telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain games built on TON are onboarding millions to Web3 on Telegram, with idle games like Notcoin leading the charge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is NFT Crypto: The Complete 2024 Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507598/What-is-NFT-Crypto-The-Complete-2024-Guide</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507598/What-is-NFT-Crypto-The-Complete-2024-Guide"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to NFTs NFTs, or Non-Fungible Tokens, represent a groundbreaking evolution in how we think about digital ownership. Unlike traditional cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin or Ethereum, which are fungible, meaning each unit is the same as every other unit, NFTs are unique. Each token is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu, Dogecoin Volumes Fail to Catch Up with PEPE’s Popularity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507709/Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-Volumes-Fail-to-Catch-Up-with-PEPEs-Popularity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507709/Shiba-Inu-Dogecoin-Volumes-Fail-to-Catch-Up-with-PEPEs-Popularity"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme token PEPE has experienced a remarkable surge in trading volume, surpassing both Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE) in recent activity. According to CoinMarketCap data, PEPE currently ranks as the eighth-highest digital asset by trading volume. PEPE’s current trading volume sits at...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Redefines Token Listings: Aims to Favor Serious Projects Amid Market Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507646/Binance-Redefines-Token-Listings-Aims-to-Favor-Serious-Projects-Amid-Market-Concerns</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507646/Binance-Redefines-Token-Listings-Aims-to-Favor-Serious-Projects-Amid-Market-Concerns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, announced a project applicant plan for the crypto listing, where it will give preference to “high-quality” projects. It admitted that there is a pattern of tokens being issued with high valuations and low initial floats. Binance noted that there is concern in the community, as there are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Issues Important “Black Mirror” Statement to Warn Community]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507570/Elon-Musk-Issues-Important-Black-Mirror-Statement-to-Warn-Community</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507570/Elon-Musk-Issues-Important-Black-Mirror-Statement-to-Warn-Community"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Influential tech entrepreneur Musk has published a crucial dystopian warning about a new AI product by Microsoft]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games $200M Exploit Was An ‘Isolated Event,’ Team Working Closely With Law Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507566/Gala-Games-200M-Exploit-Was-An-Isolated-Event-Team-Working-Closely-With-Law-Enforcement</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507566/Gala-Games-200M-Exploit-Was-An-Isolated-Event-Team-Working-Closely-With-Law-Enforcement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gala Games CEO owned up to the lapse in internal controls that resulted in the theft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Holds Discounted ETH Tokens: Will the Portfolio Survive the Denial of an Ethereum ETF?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507552/Grayscale-Holds-Discounted-ETH-Tokens-Will-the-Portfolio-Survive-the-Denial-of-an-Ethereum-ETF</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507552/Grayscale-Holds-Discounted-ETH-Tokens-Will-the-Portfolio-Survive-the-Denial-of-an-Ethereum-ETF"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale is sitting on a large wallet of Ethereum (ETH) acquired at discounted prices during previous market downturns. The Grayscale Ethereum Trust is now awaiting a verdict on whether it could transform into an ETF. In case the ETF proposal is declined by the US Securities and Exchange...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hex Trust Issues First Native Stablecoin on Layer-1 Blockchain Flare]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742682f305</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/21/hex-trust-issues-first-native-stablecoin-on-layer-1-blockchain-flare/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hex Trust Group has issued USDX, the first native stablecoin on layer-1 blockchain  Flare, according to a press release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrease of Bitcoin ATMs in the USA]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507705/Decrease-of-Bitcoin-ATMs-in-the-USA</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507705/Decrease-of-Bitcoin-ATMs-in-the-USA"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time in the last nine months, a few hundred crypto ATMs disappear in the United States and Canada.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Wind in Ethereum ETFs! Did President Joe Biden Change His Mind?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507547/Biden-Wind-in-Ethereum-ETFs-Did-President-Joe-Biden-Change-His-Mind</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507547/Biden-Wind-in-Ethereum-ETFs-Did-President-Joe-Biden-Change-His-Mind"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts consider that this sudden change in the Ethereum ETF situation may be a reflection of the Biden government's policy change. Continue Reading: Biden Wind in Ethereum ETFs! Did President Joe Biden Change His Mind?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI suspends ChatGPT voice accused of mimicking Scarlett Johansson]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507539/OpenAI-suspends-ChatGPT-voice-accused-of-mimicking-Scarlett-Johansson</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507539/OpenAI-suspends-ChatGPT-voice-accused-of-mimicking-Scarlett-Johansson"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI halts use of a new ChatGPT voice amid controversy involving Scarlett Johansson, who claims the AI voice closely mimics her own.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple v. SEC case update as of May 21, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507544/Ripple-v-SEC-case-update-as-of-May-21-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507544/Ripple-v-SEC-case-update-as-of-May-21-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the wait for the final resolution to the long-running courtroom standoff between Ripple and the United States Securities and … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INCREDIBLY POPULAR BITCOIN NEWS, Something MAJOR Is Happening, Down 94% IN 2 MONTHS]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507568/INCREDIBLY-POPULAR-BITCOIN-NEWS-Something-MAJOR-Is-Happening-Down-94-IN-2-MONTHS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507568/INCREDIBLY-POPULAR-BITCOIN-NEWS-Something-MAJOR-Is-Happening-Down-94-IN-2-MONTHS"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had NO IDEA that news like this could be so popular about Bitcoin, and yet, here we are. It looks like a lot of movement is starting to pick back up within the cryptocurrency space as all eyes are on the summer bull run. Countries with terrible economies are starting to understand what Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Prediction as BTC Blasts Toward All-Time High – Are Whales Buying Again?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507508/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-as-BTC-Blasts-Toward-All-Time-High-Are-Whales-Buying-Again</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507508/Bitcoin-Price-Prediction-as-BTC-Blasts-Toward-All-Time-High-Are-Whales-Buying-Again"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Bitcoin approaching $71,000, speculation rises about whether whales are buying again, driven by significant ETF inflows and market optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Ethereum Dev Joins Staking Startup: Can He Prevent a Dystopian Future?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507572/Ex-Ethereum-Dev-Joins-Staking-Startup-Can-He-Prevent-a-Dystopian-Future</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507572/Ex-Ethereum-Dev-Joins-Staking-Startup-Can-He-Prevent-a-Dystopian-Future"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Foundation researcher Dankrad Feist has been appointed as an advisor to EigenLayer, a restaking protocol for the Ethereum blockchain. Feist’s decision, announced in a recent online post, follows a similar move by fellow Ethereum researcher Justin Drake, who joined EigenLayer earlier....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspa (KAS) Price Breaks Free from Death Cross: 12% Rally Possible]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507643/Kaspa-KAS-Price-Breaks-Free-from-Death-Cross-12-Rally-Possible</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19507643/Kaspa-KAS-Price-Breaks-Free-from-Death-Cross-12-Rally-Possible"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:20:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspa’s (KAS) price is observing positive signals from its investors, and the broader market is also supporting a rally. The chances of the altcoin marking a monthly high in May are solid, which could propel KAS to a key price point. Kaspa Holders Pour in Money Kaspa’s price is increasing, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Forecast Sudden Crypto Regulation Pivot By US President Biden]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74268fb0da</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/experts-crypto-regulation-pivot-us-president-biden/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden administration may be preparing for a strategic pivot on crypto regulations, potentially aligning closer with the digital asset community ahead of the upcoming November election. This speculation follows recent developments indicating a possible approval of a spot Ether ETF, a significant change in stance by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).
 
On Thursday, Bloomberg ETF analysts James Seyffart and Eric Balchunas dramatically increased their forecast for the approval of a spot Ether ETF from 25% to 75%, citing sources close to the SEC. The analysts reported a sudden change in sentiment within the SEC, possibly reflecting a broader political recalibration by the Biden administration in response to former President Donald Trump’s endorsement of Bitcoin and cryptocurrenci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MOG, PEPE Rocket as Traders Search for Ether Beta Bets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426891319</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/21/mog-pepe-rocket-as-traders-search-for-ether-beta-bets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins have been increasingly seen as a way to bet on the growth of the underlying network they are issued on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pompliano Foresees Historic Milestone for Crypto Industry With Potential Ethereum ETF Approval]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426897b5d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/pompliano-foresees-historic-milestone-for-crypto-industry-with-potential-ethereum-etf-approval/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a series of recent social media posts, renowned crypto investor and influencer Anthony “Pomp” Pompliano has shared his optimistic outlook on the future of the cryptocurrency industry. Highlighting the potential approval of an Ethereum exchange-traded fund (ETF) by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, Pomp stated, “If they approve the Ethereum ETF, they are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Still Above $3,600 as ETF Approval Hopes Swell]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231587</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231587/ethereum-above-3600-etf-approval-hopes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The late rumor yesterday caused Ethereum trading volume to spike by 219% in the past day, according to Coinglass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether ETF Hopes Drive Futures Open Interest to Record $14B]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74267540f1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/21/ether-etf-hopes-drive-futures-open-interest-to-record-14b/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The notional open interest, or the dollar value locked in the number of active ether futures contracts, surged by 25% in a single day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SDX Breaks through 1 Billion CHF in Digital Asset Transactions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426705092</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/sdx-breaks-through-1-billion-chf-in-digital-asset-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SIX Digital Exchange (SDX) has announced transactions  
exceeding 1 billion Swiss Francs (CHF) in digital asset issuance. This was  
marked by the settlement of a CHF 200 million bond by the World Bank, which was  
priced on May 15. 
The collaboration between the World Bank, Swiss National  
Bank, and SIX Digital Exchange highlights a collective effort to advance  
digitalization within capital markets.
Leading in wCBDC Settlements
The participation of key issuers, such as The World Bank,  
UBS AG, various Swiss municipalities, and SIX Group AG, has played a pivotal  
role in propelling the Swiss Financial Centre's journey toward digital  
transformation. 
Notably, several issuances have been part of the Swiss  
National Bank's Project Helvetia Phase III, enabling settlements in Swiss Fran…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Surges Over $71K as Ether ETF Hopes Lead to $260M in Short Liquidations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742673af24</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/21/bitcoin-surges-over-71k-as-ether-etf-hopes-lead-to-260m-in-short-liquidations/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T07:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some traders expect ether prices to reach as high as $4,000 in the coming days, with odds of an ether ETF approval raised to 75%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out! Dogecoin Creator Warns Of Exploding Social Media Ad Scams]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74267e0037</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/watch-out-dogecoin-creator-warns-of-exploding-social-media-ad-scams/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T07:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin creator Billy Markus, the internet personality also known as “Shibetoshi Nakamoto,” fired a shot across the bow of social media advertising with a recent critique.
 
Markus, a major figure in the cryptocurrency world, took to his favorite platform, X, to express his frustration with the prevalence of scam ads. This issue has long been a thorn in the side of crypto users, who have repeatedly been targeted by fraudulent schemes on social media platforms.
 
 
Markus’s message struck a chord with the crypto community, long plagued by fraudulent activities on social media platforms. Projects like Shiba Inu and Ripple have consistently warned their communities about these dangers, highlighting the pervasiveness of the problem.
 
Click Here, Steal Your Crypto: The Malware Menace
 
The Do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Vs. SEC Reaches Climax With Final Filing: Details]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7426658ddd</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-sec-climax-final-filing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal battle between Ripple Labs and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has intensified with the SEC’s latest court filing, marking the final submission before Judge Analisa Torres of the Southern District of New York deliberates on the remedies phase of this landmark case.
 
Ripple Vs. SEC: The Final Move
 
In its filing dated May 20, 2024, the SEC provided a comprehensive rebuttal to Ripple’s request to seal certain financial documents and other evidence crucial to the case. The SEC’s letter to Judge Torres articulates a staunch opposition to Ripple’s motion, particularly concerning the concealment of financial data and contractual terms integral to the Court’s evaluation of appropriate remedies.
 
 
The SEC’s opposition hinges on the principle of public access to judici…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ether (ETH) Surges 17%, Polymarket Approval Chances Rocket, as ETF Makes Regulatory Progress]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742666b189</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/21/ether-eth-surges-17-polymarket-approval-chances-rocket-as-etf-makes-regulatory-progress/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:14:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. SEC has asked exchanges to update 19b-4 filings for ether ETFs ahead of a key deadline, suggesting potential approval progress, though approval is not guaranteed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investors Pile Into Bitcoin: Over $1 Billion Inflows Fuel ETF Rally, Price Tops $71,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74266388b8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-over-1b-inflows-fuel-etf-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lower-than-expected inflation data and a dominant Bitcoin have sparked a cautious return to crypto investment, with the US leading the charge. However, whispers of regulatory scrutiny cast a shadow over Ethereum, leading to outflows for the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency.
 
 
CoinShares, a leading digital asset manager, reports a second consecutive week of positive inflows for crypto investment products, totaling $932 million. Bitcoin, the ever-controversial “digital gold” that just breached the $71,000 level in as many weeks, is the clear frontrunner, attracting a whopping $942 million.
 
This bullish sentiment appears linked to the recent US Consumer Price Index (CPI) report, which fueled hopes of a less aggressive interest rate hike by the Federal Reserve. Historically, lower int…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYAG Takes Victory Lap as Court Approves Genesis Settlement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742663ad31</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/21/nyag-takes-victory-lap-as-court-approves-genesis-settlement/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYAG says the settlement will establish a fund for New Yorkers who invested more than $1.1 billion in Genesis through the Gemini Earn program and blocks Genesis from operating in the state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria’s SEC-Crypto License]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74266cfa67</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nigerias-sec-crypto-license/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In May 2022, Nigeria’s Securities and Exchange Commission introduced a robust regulatory framework for virtual asset service providers, including digital asset exchanges. The framework required compliance with various laws and regulations to foster market integrity, safeguard investors, and deter financial crimes. The rules mandated digital asset exchanges to register, adhere to anti-money laundering (AML) practices, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Author</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrat House Leadership Says Crypto Bill Vote Won't Be Whipped]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74266d4c9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/21/democrat-house-leadership-says-crypto-bill-vote-wont-be-whipped/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ranking members strongly oppose this bill as written, an email obtained by Politico reads, but will stop short of putting it to a whipped vote]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds, Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Notcoin: The Token Behind the Click-to-Mine Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742650b221</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/understanding-notcoin-the-token-behind-the-click-to-mine-telegram-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T03:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, the crypto community has been buzzing about a new token called notcoin (NOT), recently launched on The Open Network (TON). This token is tied to a game on Telegram where users earn NOT by completing tasks and clicking a button, featuring a distinctive click-to-mine system. The following is a comprehensive overview of what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CryptoPunks NFT Collection Unravels After Backlash to 'Woke' Artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231563</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231563/new-cryptopunks-nft-project-unravels-backlash-woke-artwork"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T03:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs revealed Nina Chanel Abney's Super Punks World NFT collection Monday, but will "no longer touch" CryptoPunks following backlash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Inc., Reflects on His Company’s Transformational Pivot to Bitcoin and More]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74265ce935</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/david-bailey-ceo-of-bitcoin-inc-reflects-on-his-companys-transformational-pivot-to-bitcoin-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T02:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Bailey, CEO of Bitcoin Inc., took time out of running the Bitcoin Asia Conference in Hong Kong to sit down with Bitcoin.com’s COO, Jason Sheman. The conversation delved into the lessons learned from past mistakes, the strategic pivot to Bitcoin, the Bitcoin Conference, Bitcoin Layer twos, and stablecoins on Bitcoin. Bitcoin Asia Conference Highlights: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NY Attorney General Secures $2 Billion Settlement With Bankrupt Crypto Lender Genesis]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742658cefa</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ny-attorney-general-secures-2-billion-settlement-with-bankrupt-crypto-lender-genesis/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T02:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Letitia James has secured a $2 billion settlement with bankrupt cryptocurrency firms Genesis Global Capital, Genesis Asia Pacific, and Genesis Global Holdco. The settlement, which requires bankruptcy court approval, will establish a victims’ fund to compensate over 29,000 New Yorkers who invested more than $1.1 billion through the Gemini Earn program. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Investment Fund Exec Sentenced To 3 Years For $55 Million Scheme]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742659c439</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-investment-fund-exec-sentenced-to-3-years-for-55-million-scheme/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T02:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lilian Nurieva, former Head of Networks at Russian crypto Investment fund Finiko, has been sentenced to three years for defrauding private investors and participating in an organized criminal group.
 
The $55 million pyramidal scheme is considered the second-largest financial scam in Russia’s post-Soviet history by the Federal Foundation for the Protection of Investors and Shareholders Rights.
 
 
Crypto Investment Fund Turns Ponzi Scheme
 
In 2021, Russian authorities began investigating the ‘crypto investment fund’ Finiko for fraud and organized crime. According to the investigation, the fund was a Ponzi scheme that took millions in investors’ money.
 
From 2018 to 2021, Finiko served as a pyramidal scheme presented as a crypto fund to investors. The scam’s main organizer and beneficiary…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Messed Up': Gala Games Confirms $240 Million Worth of Tokens Swiped via Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231528</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231528/gala-games-240-million-worth-tokens-swiped-exploit"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T02:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attacker used an exploit to mint and swipe 5 billion Gala Games (GALA) tokens Monday, with the firm calling it an "isolated incident."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Insists It Will Keep USDT Listed in European Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74265bd2b1</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/kraken-insists-it-will-keep-usdt-listed-in-european-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T01:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken, a U.S.-based cryptocurrency exchange, insists it will keep USDT listed in European markets as long as regulations regarding stablecoins are not finalized. Mark Greenberg, Global Head of Kraken’s Asset Growth and Management Business, clarified they will “continue to look at all options to offer USDT under the upcoming regime.” Kraken Will Keep Tether’s USDT […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Soars 20%, Lifting Arbitrum and Optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231530/ethereum-arbitrum-optimism-soar-20-percent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T00:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ETH ecosystem is mooning on the renewed belief that an ETF approval is near, and most cryptocurrencies are rising with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Booming—You Can Earn More by Playing These Free Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=205392</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/205392/bitcoin-booming-you-earn-more-playing-free-games"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: With Bitcoin rising again after its recent all-time high surge, here's an expanded list of games that pay out BTC rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum's Ethereum Custody Controversy Reignites SEC Security Label Fears]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231468</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231468/prometheums-ethereum-custody-controversy-sec-security-fears"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:41:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prometheum's move to offer Ethereum custody services sparked backlash from a crypto advocacy group that claims it's in cahoots with the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Debuts AI PCs That Will ‘Recall‘ Everything You Do]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231509/microsoft-ai-pc-recall-everything-laptops-tablets"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redmond tech giant unveiled the “designed for AI” Copilot+ PC that indexes everything displayed on screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Avalanche Soar as Ethereum Price Tops $3,500]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231498/solana-avalanche-up-bitcoin-over-70k-ethereum-over-3500"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two top cryptocurrencies are leading a parade of rising coins today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Nab Incognito Market Owner Accused of Running World's Biggest Narcotics Shop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231483</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231483/incognito-market-darkweb-owner-indicted-nyc-arrest"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T20:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Taiwanese national was arrested in New York over the weekend, indicted for facilitating $100 million in illicit drug sales on the dark web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Hits $70,000 as Crypto Liquidations Top $235 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231480/bitcoin-price-hits-70000-liquidations-top-235-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T20:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is back above $70,000 for the first time in over a month as investors throw money at ETFs again—and hype over Ethereum ETFs grows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Spikes 9% Within Minutes on ETF Approval Rumors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231481</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231481/ethereum-spikes-etf-approval-rumors"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Ethereum jumped by 9% in about 20 minutes on Monday amid fresh speculation that spot ETFs will indeed be approved this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Trader Who Bought 1% of the Supply in January Is Down Nearly $2 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231467</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231467/bored-ape-trader-bought-1-percent-supply-down-2-million"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The once-dominant Ethereum NFT collection continues to shed value. How low can the Bored Ape Yacht Club go?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Back With Nearly $1 Billion In Fresh Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231473</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231473/bitcoin-etf-surge-1-billion-btc-above-68000"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of BTC has risen above $68K and ETF flows last week reflect the rebound, both surging thanks to promising inflation data, one analyst says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trading Memes: Dogecoin Still Outperformed GameStop Over the Last Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231453</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231453/trading-memes-dogecoin-outperformed-gamestop-gme"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GameStop stock trading frenzy has faded, but leading meme coin Dogecoin is still in the green over the last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 120 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/7jrsiszc/fomo-hour-120-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL again leads majors, DEX volume dwarfs others. BTC whales buys $106M in 24hrs. ETH ETF decision on Thursday or Friday. 5 of 7 onchain indicators ‘point to bull-run’. ETH ETF may be rejected due to weak link to futures. AI coins in focus ahead of Nvidia earnings. Cobie inks new article on low float, high FDV coins. ETH foundation staff reveal links to EigenLayer. 12 L2 & L3s controlled by single multisig. Layer Zero pauses sybil rewards. Aevo to airdrop pre-launch tokens on platform. FTM to migrate one-to-one to Sonic S coin. UK judge rules Craig Wright is not Satoshi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker Who Exploited Solana Meme Coin Factory Pump.fun Says He Faces Theft, Conspiracy Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231428/hacker-who-exploited-solana-meme-coin-factory-pump-fun-says-he-faces-theft-conspiracy-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T16:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After admitting to being responsible for an exploit which drained $2 million from Pump.fun, the attacker claims to have been arrested.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miners Targeted by Venezuela in Latest Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231450</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231450/bitcoin-miners-targets-venezuela-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T16:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelan authorities have launched a crackdown on Bitcoin miners, and don't want any crypto mining operations to use the energy grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Pulls ‘Horny’ ChatGPT Voice, Denies It's a Scarlett Johansson Knockoff]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231436/openai-pulls-horny-chatgpt-voice-denies-scarlett-johansson"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T16:20:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATE: The Hollywood actress says OpenAI CEO Sam Altman had tried to get her permission—twice—and that she is “shocked, angered, and in disbelief.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Crypto Lender Genesis Agrees to $2 Billion Settlement to Repay Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231431</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231431/bankrupt-crypto-lender-genesis-2-billion-settlement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genesis will pay a $2 billion settlement to partially repay customers of the firm's bankrupt crypto lending division.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Notcoin? The Telegram-Based Game, NOT Token, and Future Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=223640</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-notcoin-telegram-based-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: NOT is live and it's 2024's biggest gaming token launch so far. But Notcoin isn't over: Here's what to expect in the game's future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale CEO Michael Sonnenshein Steps Down]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231425/grayscale-ceo-michael-sonnenshein-steps-down"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading crypto asset manager, Grayscale, has announced its CEO, Michael Sonnenshein, is stepping down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Has Stopped Posting. Is This the End of GameStop Mania?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231421/roaring-kitty-has-stopped-posting-is-this-the-end-of-gamestop-mania"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears the GameStop bull has stopped tweeting after the company filed to increase its total number of shares by 15%. Is this the end?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chain of Alliance Game Guide: Getting Started With the Turn-Based RPG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230997</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230997/chain-of-alliance-game-guide-getting-started-with-the-turn-based-rpg"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain RPG Chain of Alliance sees you assemble a party of Heroes to take on all comers in turn-based battles. Here’s how to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 119 - GOOD MORNING BULLS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ikMRioZH/fomo-hour-119-good-morning-bulls"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher again, BTC stable. ETFs see $257M inflow, volumes hit 2 month high. 414 holders of BlackRock ETF ‘blows away record’. SOL continues to be fastest blockage despite usage. Pump. fun exploited for $1.9M by ex-employee. LINK up 20% after partnership with top banks. Senate also repeals SEC crypto rule. US Senator uses laser eyes PFP. Tether mints another $1B USDT. Bitcoin production costs now $45K: JP Morgan. Pink Drainer retires after stealing $85m assets. PancakeSwap to reimburse fees on Uniswap. TON & Tether partnership on payment solution. Trabucco writes character defence of Ryan Salame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 118 - ARE THE ETFS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/KJXI4MVU/fomo-hour-118-are-the-etfs-back"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has best day in 2 months after dovish CPI. ETFs see $300M inflow, highest in weeks. ETH continues to underperform ahead of ETF ruling. Millennium buys $2B of BTC ETF. CME group to launch BTC spot trading. Fed’s Kashkari compares BTC to beanie babies. Tate says he will buy $100M BTC. El Salvador now owns 5750 BTC. Binance creates ‘antidote’ to address poisoning. Tornado Cash developer appeals conviction. China busts $1.9B USDT banking racket. MEV bot operators charged with fraud by DoJ. Swiss to adopt global crypto tax rules. FTX repayments create ‘bullish overhang’ for crypto. SEI up 30% after proposing v2 upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 117 - BITCOIN GAINS ON CPI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JMdi3Lp7/fomo-hour-117-bitcoin-gains-on-cpi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC bounces driven by spot buying. US ETF sees $100M+ inflow for first time in weeks. State of Wisconsin buys $170M of BTC ETF. Vanguard appoints Bitcoin friendly CEO. Coinbase sees billions of BTC leave exchange. BTC to consolidate between $55-75K: Novogratz. SOL beats ETH TEV for first time ever. ETH may be labelled a security by SEC next week. AI & memes the only two positive sectors this week. Crypto hostility led by TradFi: Lubin. Tornado Cash developer guilty of money laundering. Circle shifts legal hope to US ahead of IPO. Cypher developer gambled $300K of customer funds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 116 - ROARING KITTY RETURNS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cXfQ3AJh/fomo-hour-116-roaring-kitty-returns"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, stays in range ahead of CPI tomorrow. US ETFs see small net inflow led by Fidelity HK ETFs wipe 2 weeks of inflows in a single day. Bracebridge bought $363m of BTC ETFs. Coinbase has system wide outage. Poloniex hacker sends funds to Tornado Cash. Brazil biggest in LATAM for crypto trading. Biden removes China BTC miner near military base. CertiK patches $5m flaw in Aptos bridge. LayerZero sees 100k bot accounts self-report. DYDX CEO set to leave. Tate sells $500k BTC to buy GME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Edges Past $67K as Analysts Predict It'll Keep Climbing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231418</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231418/bitcoin-edges-past-67k-as-analysts-predict-itll-keep-climbing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's growing accumulation of Bitcoin call options for the December 2024 expiry on Deribit, indicating traders' optimism for the year end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iconic Japanese Soccer Game Captain Tsubasa Launches on Oasys Blockchain]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231410</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231410/iconic-japanese-soccer-game-captain-tsubasa-launches-on-oasys-blockchain"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T01:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a significant development for gaming and soccer fans, the blockchain version of beloved Japanese soccer manga series Captain Tsubasa has officially launched on the gaming-centric blockchain Oasys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epik Duck: From Joke to $25 Million Solana Meme Coin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231317</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231317/epik-duck-from-joke-25-million-solana-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T20:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins like EPIK are looking more and more like crypto’s future. Is that good or bad?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Roaring Kitty Returns, Pump.fun Attacker Bares All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231347</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231347/this-week-crypto-twitter-roaring-kitty-gamestop-pump-fun-attacker"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dominant personalities stole the narrative this week. Industry leaders also decried the conviction and sentencing of a Tornado Cash developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Crypto Games: Notcoin Token Launches, GameStop Mania, and NYAN Incoming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231333</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231333/this-week-crypto-games-notcoin-gamestop-nyan"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Catch up on this week’s biggest crypto and NFT gaming news and find some weekend reads in our latest roundup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: GameStop Surge Spurs Meme Coin Mania, and Bitcoin Ends on a High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231321</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231321/this-week-coins-gamestop-surge-meme-coins-bitcoin-price"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T15:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop bull Roaring Kitty returned to the internet, prompting a huge meme stock and coin surge. And Bitcoin hit its highest price since the halving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feds Charge Chinese Nationals in $73 Million 'Pig Butchering' Crypto Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231343</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231343/feds-charge-chinese-nationals-73-million-crypto-scam"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T22:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Justice charged Daren Li and Yicheng Zhang with orchestrating a “pig butchering” cryptocurrency scam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Crypto Trader Made Over $100K With Two Tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231324</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231324/how-crypto-trader-made-over-100k-two-tweets"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T21:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Only in crypto." Meme coin Pacmoon rewarded one user with a hefty airdrop—which was bigger than expected thanks to a pal’s costly mistake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Founder Pavel Durov Says He’ll Hold $7 Million Notcoin Gift Until 100x]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231320/telegram-pavel-durov-hold-7-million-notcoin-gift-until-100x"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T20:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pavel Durov holds 1% of this year’s biggest gaming token, donated by players. And he’s not selling his Notcoin—not now, at least.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Is Getting Political—Ethereum Giant Consensys Wants to Stay Out of It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231241</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231241/crypto-getting-political-ethereum-giant-consensys-stay-out"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T19:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As other firms spend millions on pro-crypto candidates, Joe Lubin tells Decrypt that Consensys has resisted the impulse. Here's why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Exec Who Quit Says Safety 'Took a Backseat to Shiny Products']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231294</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231294/openai-exec-quit-safety-took-backseat-shiny-products"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T18:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jan Leike explains his resignation from OpenAI, citing a lack of support and concerns over the company's focus on AGI over safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Booming, Hits Highest Price Since the Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231289</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231289/bitcoin-booming-highest-price-since-halving"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T18:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Bitcoin just touched its highest point since last month's halving, hitting a level not seen in more than a month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Lorenzo Protocol is Supercharging Bitcoin DeFi With Liquid Restaking]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=230634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/230634/how-lorenzo-protocol-is-supercharging-bitcoin-defi-with-liquid-restaking"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T17:16:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin liquid restaking protocol is opening the door for Asian BTC capital to meet western projects, said founder Matt Ye.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Roaring Kitty Is the Villain': GameStop Trader's Tweets Are Getting Sad]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231251</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231251/roaring-kitty-villain-gamestop-trader-tweets-sad"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T17:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop filed to increase its total shares by 15% and the market hated it, tanking the price even further. The GME bull isn't happy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ETF Approval Coming Sooner Rather Than Later, Says Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231264</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231264/ethereum-etf-approval-sooner-rather-than-later-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T16:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America's biggest crypto exchange Coinbase is confident that the SEC will approve spot Ethereum ETFs very soon, despite broader pessimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says Neuralink Needs a Volunteer for 'Telepathy' Brain Implant]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=231258</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/231258/elon-musk-neuralink-needs-volunteer-telepathy-brain-implant"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T16:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who's next? Elon Musk announced that Neuralink is accepting applications for the second test subject for its brain chip trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With  Roger Dickerman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/F6mt1fXu/we-do-a-little-with-roger-dickerman"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T14:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and founder of the 24 Hours of Art, Roger Dickerman. We dive into Roger’s background in trading and fitness, his love of art, founding Artifex and 24 Hours of Art, the power of routines, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Funghi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9USXAFZb/we-do-a-little-with-funghi"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and co-founder of Shillr, Funghibull. Funghi is one of our favorite collectors, builders and overall people in the space. 

We dive into Funghi’s background playing rugby, going to medical school in Scotland, 10 gram mushroom trips, finding punks, forming Shillr, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Breaks Down Solana Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/5lkvPCM1/mika-breaks-down-solana-congestion"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:12:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains what happened during Solana's Q1 2024 network congestion through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Explains the Bitcoin Halving]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/f9rUBkUS/mika-explains-the-bitcoin-halving"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer Mika explains the recent Bitcoin halving and how you can build your understanding through Kraken's Learn Center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Neighbor Alice Season 1 Beta Goes Live]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/sGfYcHuB/my-neighbor-alice-season-1-beta-goes-live"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator Orangie plays the new season of multiplayer builder-game My Neighbor Alice and tries out all its features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Leads The Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QoXLhFzb/solana-leads-the-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto up despite ETF outflow, SOL outperforms. HK ETFs also see another net daily outflow. SOL flips ETH again in 24hr DEX volume. SOL revenue now 50% of ETH. Bitcoin above $1m by 2030: Dorsey. Bitcoin & Kucoin get license in India. Kraken tries to get SEC case dismissed. Stand with Crypto sets up election war chest. VIP customers make up two thirds of Binance volume. NOT to launch on Binance & OKX. TON up 20%, speculation it will be listed after NOT. Securitize & BlackRock look to launch on ARB. Franklin Templeton calls for ‘Base season’. EIGEN claims go live today, will be un-transferable. Eclipse founder leaves after harassment claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Manhattan’s Newest On-Chain Fashion Store: 9dcc]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Oyjyb2JX/inside-manhattans-newest-on-chain-fashion-store-9dcc"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT NYC, Decrypt’s Sander Lutz explored the on-chain fashion brand’s latest pop-up, and spoke to its founder Gmoney about 9dcc’s future expansion plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Sinks Lower]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HK ETF volumes disappoint at $11M, crypto sinks. US ETFs see another $52M outflow, 4th straight day. EigenLayer FUD after 5% non-transferable airdrop. EigenLayer also geoblocks USA for claims. 5K+ withdrawals after EigenLayer announcement. Microstrategy bought another $8M BTC in April. Miner revenue drops to 2023 lows. Consensys vs SEC litigation will take years: Cowen. SEC had been investigating ETH for a year. Gensler may have misled Congress with ETH stance.KMNO hits $363M on launch. Decentralised Rune airdrop opens at $102M. Friend Tech airdrop delayed until Thursday. NFTfi airdrop claim today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Red Week For Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors hit locals lows, break key support levels. Liquidations hit $420M, funding remains neutral. ETFs saw $344M withdrawals in April. CZ gets 4-month jail sentence. FTX sells $232M locked SOL at ‘around $100’. Final integration of SOL Firedancer ‘well underway’. SOL, DOGE, XRP open interest down 51% in a month. BlackRock BUIDL largest tokenised treasury fund. Uniswap integrates with Robinhood connect. Stablecoin bill may be coming very soon. Gensler lied to Congress: McHenry. KSI steps back from crypto trading. Coinbase supports Lightning network. BCH creator arrested in Spain. EigenLayer sees 12K queued withdrawals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Full Send]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher, DEX volume flips ETH. ETH burn rate hits yearly low. BTC needs to reach $67k for a ‘higher high’. Robinhood receives Wells Notice from SEC. Only 10% of stablecoin transactions are real: Visa. May 15th will see corporate filings of BTC purchases. Hayes continues to OTC buy PENDLE. Cartier arrested for USDT money laundering. ENA up 20% on rumours of integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto volatile but bounces after dovish Fed speech. ETFs see record $563m outflow. BlackRock ETF sees first outflow in 77 days. BlackRock expects more institutions to buy BTC. BNP bank buys BlackRock ETF. BTC continues to sit below STH average cost. Coinbase earnings today. Tether made $4.5bn profit in Q1. MicroStrategy building identity protocol on Ordinals. Dorsey’s Block Inc investigated in US. BlackRock leads investment in RWA firm. STX Nakamoto upgrade delayed by 8 weeks. LayerZero 1st snapshot taken ahead of airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our friend and co-founder of Rainbow Wallet, Mike Demarais. We dive into Mike’s background as a software engineer, how he fell into the crypto rabbithole, co-founding Rainbow, important lessons learned from raising capital, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>