<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-05-08T14:14:03.559Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-05-08T14:14:03.559Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRC-20 Meme Coins Frenzy Spikes Bitcoin Network Fees]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516b74742</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/brc-20-meme-coins-frenzy-spikes-bitcoin-fees/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent shift of meme coins to the BRC-20 standard has changed Bitcoin’s network fees. More emerging meme coins flock to BTC’s BRC-20 standard as more coins emerge. 
 
Notably, the hype and frenzy about meme coins spiked due to the impressive performance of Pepe Coin (PEPE) and Wojak (WOJAK). The influx of these projects has congested the BTC network. As a result, BTC’s transaction fees surged to a multi-year peak.  
 
BRC-20 Tokens Fees Hit Multi-Year High
 
With the growing hype around meme coins, the activities surrounding the tokens within the Bitcoin network keep rising. According to the crypto data analytics platform Dune Analytics, the daily minting fees on BRC-20 hit a record high of 247 BTC on May 7. The value shows that the fees reached their highest level in two years.
 
Rela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto community with 89% historical accuracy sets XRP price for May 31, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290918/Crypto-community-with-89-historical-accuracy-sets-XRP-price-for-May-31-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290918/Crypto-community-with-89-historical-accuracy-sets-XRP-price-for-May-31-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although the price of XRP has been dropping in the past few weeks, the community’s optimism remains, particularly against the … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRC-20 Meme Coins Frenzy Spikes Bitcoin Network Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290908/BRC-20-Meme-Coins-Frenzy-Spikes-Bitcoin-Network-Fees</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290908/BRC-20-Meme-Coins-Frenzy-Spikes-Bitcoin-Network-Fees"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent shift of meme coins to the BRC-20 standard has changed Bitcoin’s network fees. More emerging meme coins flock to BTC’s BRC-20 standard as more coins emerge. Notably, the hype and frenzy about meme coins spiked due to the impressive performance of Pepe Coin (PEPE) and Wojak (WOJAK)....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maker To Spark ‘New Explosion of DAI’ with Custom Lending Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290885/Maker-To-Spark-New-Explosion-of-DAI-with-Custom-Lending-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290885/Maker-To-Spark-New-Explosion-of-DAI-with-Custom-Lending-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adapted from Aave, Spark Lend will directly connect end users to the Maker stablecoin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy Project Railgun DAO Adopts Chainway’s ‘Proof of Innocence’ Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290910/Privacy-Project-Railgun-DAO-Adopts-Chainways-Proof-of-Innocence-Tool</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290910/Privacy-Project-Railgun-DAO-Adopts-Chainways-Proof-of-Innocence-Tool"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Railgun DAO’s new functionality – initially developed by the developer Chainway for use on Tornado Cash – could allow users to mathematically demonstrate that coins involved in transactions did not come from blacklisted addresses. Digital Currency Group, owner of CoinDesk, is an investor in Railgun DAO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium 'Good News' Coming 'Very Soon,' Shibarium Channel Admin States, Here's What It May Be]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290896/Shibarium-Good-News-Coming-Very-Soon-Shibarium-Channel-Admin-States-Heres-What-It-May-Be</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290896/Shibarium-Good-News-Coming-Very-Soon-Shibarium-Channel-Admin-States-Heres-What-It-May-Be"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRC-20 tokens have major flaws and issues, Mintlayer CEO says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290884/BRC-20-tokens-have-major-flaws-and-issues-Mintlayer-CEO-says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290884/BRC-20-tokens-have-major-flaws-and-issues-Mintlayer-CEO-says"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Someone Just Lost $120K in a Costly Mistake With ETH Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290890/Someone-Just-Lost-120K-in-a-Costly-Mistake-With-ETH-Fees</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290890/Someone-Just-Lost-120K-in-a-Costly-Mistake-With-ETH-Fees"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals break bitcoin: Transaction fees exceed rewards as congestion rises]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290894/Ordinals-break-bitcoin-Transaction-fees-exceed-rewards-as-congestion-rises</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290894/Ordinals-break-bitcoin-Transaction-fees-exceed-rewards-as-congestion-rises"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin block 788695 registered higher transaction fees than miner's rewards, triggering criticism that ordinals are breaking bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Estonia’s Registered Crypto Firms Drop 80% as Tough New Checks Reveal 'Suspicious' Behavior]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516b229b9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/08/estonias-registered-crypto-firms-drop-80-as-tough-new-checks-reveal-suspicious-behavior/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators in the tech-friendly nation say they’ll return to business-as-usual monitoring after money laundering fears led it to take a tough line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike McGlone Shares Insight into Next Direction for Bitcoin Price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290854/Mike-McGlone-Shares-Insight-into-Next-Direction-for-Bitcoin-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290854/Mike-McGlone-Shares-Insight-into-Next-Direction-for-Bitcoin-Price"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Walbroehl (Halborn) on Blockchain Cybersecurity (EP.423)]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290852/Steven-Walbroehl-Halborn-on-Blockchain-Cybersecurity-EP423</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290852/Steven-Walbroehl-Halborn-on-Blockchain-Cybersecurity-EP423"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Walbroehl, the co-founder and CTO of Halborn joins the show. In this episode we discuss: Steven’s crypto origin story and how he began tinkering with public blockchains. How Halborn’s work differs across traditional financial services customers versus decentralized organization customers....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Payment Option 'Is Coming', Says Liechtenstein's Prime Minister]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139303</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139303/bitcoin-payment-option-is-coming-says-liechtenstein-finance-minister"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Principality of Liechtenstein may follow suit of several cantons in the neighboring Switzerland by accepting Bitcoin for state services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Estonia’s Registered Crypto Firms Drop 80% as Tough New Checks Reveal 'Suspicious' Behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290840/Estonias-Registered-Crypto-Firms-Drop-80-as-Tough-New-Checks-Reveal-Suspicious-Behavior</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290840/Estonias-Registered-Crypto-Firms-Drop-80-as-Tough-New-Checks-Reveal-Suspicious-Behavior"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Ethical’ SBF game axed, Web3 games sign-up process sucks, Tomb Chaser: Web3 Gamer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290841/Ethical-SBF-game-axed-Web3-games-sign-up-process-sucks-Tomb-Chaser-Web3-Gamer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290841/Ethical-SBF-game-axed-Web3-games-sign-up-process-sucks-Tomb-Chaser-Web3-Gamer"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Supreme Court Clarifies Framework for Crypto Disputes]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290824/Chinese-Supreme-Court-Clarifies-Framework-for-Crypto-Disputes</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290824/Chinese-Supreme-Court-Clarifies-Framework-for-Crypto-Disputes"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although cryptocurrencies are now technically banned in China, the local system still provides a framework for legal disputes arising from their use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is The Lifeline Argentina Desperately Needs]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516bd8d37</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/as-peso-inflates-argentina-needs-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Jonathan Buck, founder of JB & GS Mining GmbH, a German bitcoin mining hosting company.
Argentina is currently in the midst of a crippling inflation crisis, with the national currency, the Argentine peso (ARS), losing value at an alarming rate. Just one year ago, the exchange rate from the U.S. dollar to the ARS was 115.75, and at the time of this writing, it stands at 224.52. Reports indicate that on the black market, people are paying more than double this rate. The country's annual inflation rate has skyrocketed to a staggering 104%, presenting significant challenges to both its economy and citizens. In response, the country’s central bank has raised interest rates to an astounding 81%.
As the peso's value continues to nosedive, Argentinians urgently need…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Buck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Extends Declines, as Markets Continue to React to Nonfarm Payrolls]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516befb64</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-extends-declines-as-markets-continue-to-react-to-nonfarm-payrolls/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin fell below $28,000 to start the week, as markets continued to react to last Friday’s United States nonfarm payrolls (NFP) report. The payrolls report came in at 250,000 versus expectations of 180,000 jobs. Ethereum was also lower, as prices fell back below $1,900.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) moved lower to start the week, as cryptocurrency markets continued to react to the latest nonfarm payrolls report.
 
The number of jobs added to the U.S. economy came in higher than expected, in many’s eyes justifying the Federal Reserve’s decision to hike interest rates by 0.25%.
 
As a result, BTC/USD fell to an intraday low of $27,691.26 earlier in today’s session, following a peak of $29,119.38 the day prior.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Overall, BTC has now fallen for a third straight session, with this latest drop sending prices to a one-week low.
 
One of the catalysts for the decline was a breakout which took place on the relative strength index (RSI), which fell below a floor at 47.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 44.32, with a floor of 42.00 a potential target for bears.
 
 
Ethereum
 
In addition to BTC, ethereum (ETH) was also in the red on Monday, with prices plunging below $1,900.
 
Following a high of $1,934.00 on Sunday, ETH/USD dropped by almost $100, hitting a low of $1,839.89 earlier in the day.
 
Similar to bitcoin, today’s decline saw the world’s second largest cryptocurrency fall for its third consecutive day.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
From the chart, it appears that ethereum bears are now attempting to take the RSI to its own point of support at 45.00.
 
Currently, the index is at the 47.02 level, having recently moved below a higher support point at 49.00.
 
Should price strength hit the target of 45.00, there is a possibility that ETH will be trading under $1,800.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect further drops in ethereum this week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Remain Greedy, But Why Are Prices Falling?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516bff453</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-investors-remain-greedy/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies in the market are being abysmal price action lately. This comes despite the fact that the Fear & Greed Index shows that investors are still very greedy when it comes to digital assets. So why are prices still falling?
 
Investors Await CPI Data Release
 
The latest iteration of the United States Consumer Price Index (CPI) is scheduled to be released later this week and crypto investors seem to be waiting for this before taking any action. The release will happen on May 10, 2023, and will show if inflation in the country increased, decreased, or stayed the same, which can have a great impact on financial markets.
 
 
If inflation were to come in higher, the Fed could retake a hawkish stance which would be brutal for risk assets such as Bitcoin. However, if…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first-ever Reddit thread on Bitcoin 14 years ago; Here’s what it said]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290786/The-first-ever-Reddit-thread-on-Bitcoin-14-years-ago-Heres-what-it-said</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290786/The-first-ever-Reddit-thread-on-Bitcoin-14-years-ago-Heres-what-it-said"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this day in 2009, a Reddit user posted the first-ever thread on Bitcoin (BTC), titled “Bitcoin: A peer-to-peer network … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin takes flight in Liechtenstein: Minister proposes government services paid in crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290778/Bitcoin-takes-flight-in-Liechtenstein-Minister-proposes-government-services-paid-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290778/Bitcoin-takes-flight-in-Liechtenstein-Minister-proposes-government-services-paid-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Knowledge Privacy Startup Webb Protocol Raises $7M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516b90158</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/es/business/2023/05/08/zero-knowledge-privacy-startup-webb-protocol-raises-7m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polychain Capital and Lemniscap co-led the seed round for the bridge protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman’s Crypto Project, Worldcoin, Releases First Major Consumer Product]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516b9013e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/08/sam-altmans-crypto-project-worldcoin-releases-first-major-consumer-product/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin’s “minimalist” wallet, World App, wants to help you prove you’re human in the age of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: PEPE Peaks After Binance Listing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516b90132</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/08/first-mover-americas-memecoin-pepe-hits-1b-market-cap/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for May 4, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 Firm Artifact Labs Raises $3.25M From Blue Pool Capital, Animoca, Others]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516b90235</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/05/08/web3-firm-artifact-labs-raises-325m-from-blue-pool-capital-animoca-others/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s South China Morning Post spun off its NFT business into a new firm called Artifact Labs in March 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple's Tussle With SEC to Cost the Firm $200M, CEO Garlinghouse Says: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516b90226</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/08/ripples-tussle-against-sec-to-cost-the-firm-200m-ceo-garlinghouse-says-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. puts politics ahead of policy, Brad Garlinghouse has said at the 2023 Dubai Fintech Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI is coming for your job: What industries will be affected?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290779/AI-is-coming-for-your-job-What-industries-will-be-affected</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290779/AI-is-coming-for-your-job-What-industries-will-be-affected"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Accenture, 40% of working hours across different industries could be lost to AI as tools like ChatGPT continue to improve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These HUGE Media Companies are BEGGING to Compromise Millions of Crypto Users]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290807/These-HUGE-Media-Companies-are-BEGGING-to-Compromise-Millions-of-Crypto-Users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290807/These-HUGE-Media-Companies-are-BEGGING-to-Compromise-Millions-of-Crypto-Users"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[✴︎Sign Up Here for the CT Club! https://patreon.com/cryptotips✴︎Ledger hardware wallets 👉 https://shop.ledger.com/?r=67ef✴︎Trezor hardware wallet 👉 https://shop.trezor.io/?offer_id=10&aff_id=10937✴︎Buy Gift Cards with Your Crypto! 👉 https://www.bitrefill.com/signup?code=47y2uwl4✴︎Begin Trading...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman’s Worldcoin rolls out app as token launch looms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290759/Sam-Altmans-Worldcoin-rolls-out-app-as-token-launch-looms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290759/Sam-Altmans-Worldcoin-rolls-out-app-as-token-launch-looms"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin, the eyeball-scanning crypto project co-created by OpenAI’s Sam Altman, today announced the launch of a self-custodial mobile app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Remain Greedy, But Why Are Prices Falling?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290732/Bitcoin-Investors-Remain-Greedy-But-Why-Are-Prices-Falling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290732/Bitcoin-Investors-Remain-Greedy-But-Why-Are-Prices-Falling"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies in the market are being abysmal price action lately. This comes despite the fact that the Fear & Greed Index shows that investors are still very greedy when it comes to digital assets. So why are prices still falling? Investors Await CPI Data Release The latest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human ID project ‘Worldcoin’ launches gas-free wallet only for humans]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290780/Human-ID-project-Worldcoin-launches-gas-free-wallet-only-for-humans</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18290780/Human-ID-project-Worldcoin-launches-gas-free-wallet-only-for-humans"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wallet relies on “World ID,” a protocol that verifies humanness through zero-knowledge proofs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Quarter NFT Volumes Outpace Q4 Thanks to Blur Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139296</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139296/first-quarter-nft-volumes-outpace-q4-thanks-blur-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T12:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the NFT space reported impressive numbers at the start of 2023 thanks in part to Blur's token launch, Q2 progress has been much slower.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Creator’s Latest Project: World Coin Launches Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516a0a081</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/chatgpt-latest-project-world-coin-launches-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T12:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Altman, the creator of ChatGPT, attracted attention from the crypto industry in 2021 by reviving a token founded in 2013, World Coin. The project has been progressing slowly, but today will launch a new tool designed for the “AI Age.”
 
 
Per a press release shared with Bitcoinist, the team behind World Coin launched a new crypto wallet called World App, a financial and identity manager. Previously in a testing phase running on Polygon, the crypto wallet is now open to the public and free to download.
 
ChatGPT, Not The Only Tool That Will Change The World?
 
With a simplified interface, the wallet will natively support the World Coin and Ethereum ecosystems. The app has been designed to remove the friction from onboarding new users to crypto.
 
In that sense, the app was created to fu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do You Stake Cryptocurrencies? Earning Passive Income With Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=77177</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-do-you-stake-cryptocurrencies-earning-passive-income-with-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T12:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof-of-stake networks like Ethereum will reward you with crypto for staking your coins. Here’s how that works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekin Genç</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syrian Crypto Dealer Freed From Kidnappers Who Demanded Ransom of Over $1.1 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516a3a08a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/syrian-crypto-dealer-freed-from-kidnappers-who-demanded-ransom-of-over-1-1-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T11:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish law enforcement recently nabbed three individuals who befriended and eventually kidnapped a Syrian cryptocurrency dealer. Following their arrest, the kidnappers, who were demanding a ransom of over $1.1 million, were found in possession of weapons and fake identity documents. 
 
Syrian Crypto Dealer’s Captors Were His Party Friends
 
Spanish law enforcement recently freed a Syrian cryptocurrency dealer from three kidnappers that were demanding a ransom of $1.12 million (or €1 million). According to a report by a Spanish-language publication, the captured trio was set to appear in court on May 6 where they were expected to face kidnapping as well as illegal possession of weapons charges.
 
As revealed in the report, the unnamed Syrian crypto dealer had partied with the trio before the kidnapping. However, when they four met on May 3, the Hungary-based crypto dealer’s party friends pounced and started demanding the ransom money. According to the report, the crypto dealer whose company is based in Dubai, was told to access applications that he uses to manage his crypto business and to contact the intended recipient of the ransom money.
 
 
However, whilst in captivity, the Syrian crypto dealer is said to have taken a picture through the window and sent this over to a colleague who was negotiating his release. The colleague, in turn, then sent this to the victim’s other acquaintance who then forwarded this to law enforcement.
 
Upon receiving the information, Spanish law enforcement launched an investigation which eventually led to the raid on a luxury villa located in Benalmádena. In addition to finding weapons and gardening tools, law enforcement agents also found one of the kidnappers in possession of several fake identity documents. In addition, two of the Syrian crypto dealer’s captors had fake Greek Passports.
 
What are your thoughts on this story? Let us know what you think in the comments section below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block Demand Leads to Fee Spike as Bitcoin-Based Memecoins Flourish]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516ad19d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/08/block-demand-leads-to-fee-spike-as-bitcoin-based-memecoins-flourish/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T11:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 11,000 tokens have been issued and traded on the Bitcoin network, data shows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liechtenstein Plans to Accept Bitcoin for Payments to State, Prime Minister Says: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516ad19c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/08/liechtenstein-plans-to-accept-bitcoin-for-payments-to-state-prime-minister-says-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T11:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the plans, any crypto received will immediately be exchanged for Swiss francs, Prime Minister Daniel Risch told German news publication Handelsblatt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandali Handagama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Trading Volume Surges to Two-Year High, Signals Caution for Bitcoin Bulls]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516941e93</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/08/meme-coin-trading-volume-surges-to-two-year-highs-signals-caution-for-bitcoin-bulls/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T10:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speculative mania in meme coins has historically presaged bearish reversals in bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Authorities Investigate Lawmaker Over Suspicious Crypto Transfers: Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516941e7e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/05/08/south-korea-authorities-investigate-lawmaker-over-suspicious-crypto-transfers-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T10:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic Party lawmaker Kim Nam-kuk had reportedly co-sponsored a bill seeking to defer taxation on crypto profits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lavender Au</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Options Exchange Deribit's Ether Volatility Index Hits Record Low]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516941e71</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/05/08/ether-volatility-measure-hits-record-low/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T10:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deribit's forward-looking ether volatility index (ETH DVOL) hit lifetime lows over the weekend. Expectations for price turbulence appear underpriced considering the lingering macroeconomic uncertainties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aave DAO Passes Proposal to Deploy on Ethereum Layer 2 Metis Network]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516941e6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/05/08/aave-dao-passes-proposal-to-deploy-on-ethereum-layer-2-metis-network/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T10:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The move could bolster market liquidity for the burgeoning Metis ecosystem, community members say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Calls Bitcoin Withdrawal Pause 'a Learning Opportunity']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139276</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139276/binance-calls-bitcoin-withdrawal-pause-learning-opportunity"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T10:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance has since resumed Bitcoin withdrawals on the platform after reports of "congestion" issues on the network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI, PEPE Lead Market Losses, Down Double Digits Overnight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139277</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139277/sui-pepe-lead-market-losses-down-double-digits-overnight"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T10:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning’s biggest losers include the newly-launched SUI token as well as the popular PEPE coin, which has finally tapered some.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Vs. SEC: Will The Ruling Come By This Unexpected Day?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7516971929</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-vs-sec-will-the-ruling-come-by-this-day/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T10:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speculation and rumors about when a ruling will come in the legal battle between Ripple Labs and the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) are currently picking up steam again. For a long time, the end of April was considered the most likely date when the judge of the US District Court of the Southern District of New York, Analisa Torres, will issue a ruling.
 
Several lawyers from the XRP community favored that date because it would have fit Torres’ previous rulings in other cases. In addition, the judge needed 52 days to rule on the Daubert motions. If she had again taken 52 days to issue the summary judgment, she would have had to publish the ruling on April 27.
 
No Ruling For Ripple Until Summer 2024?
 
However, all rumors and speculations have so far proven to be false. A new r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Insights: Bolivia Sells Gold for Dollars, Argentina Bans Fintech Crypto, Fitch Upgrades El Salvador’s Credit Rating]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75169d75f8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-bolivia-sells-gold-for-dollars-argentina-bans-fintech-crypto-fitch-upgrades-el-salvadors-credit-rating/"/>
        <updated>2023-05-08T09:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of the most relevant crypto and economic development news from Latin America during the last week. In this issue, Bolivia passes a law to sell gold for dollars, the Central Bank of Argentina bans fintech companies from using crypto, and Fitch improves El Salvador’s credit rating.
Bolivia Passes Law to Sell Gold for Dollars
Bolivia recently passed a law that will allow the government to sell up to 50% of its gold reserves in dollars, easing the internal scarcity of dollars. The law gives faculties to the government to negotiate the sale of 22 tons of gold out of the almost 44 available in the local reserves.
The initiative had been presented back in 2021, but it was only recently rescued and passed by the Congress, which is dominated by the party of B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Attack on Bitcoin’ Claims Circulate as Transaction Fees Climb Higher]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139259</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139259/bitcoin-ddos-ordinals-inscriptions-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-05-07T22:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some point the finger at Ordinals, and a few see nefarious intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: CZ Calls Out Justin Sun, Sun Apologizes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139242</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139242/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-cz-calls-out-justin-sun-apologizes"/>
        <updated>2023-05-07T20:21:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Web3 enthusiast started a viral rumor that Amazon will launch its own NFT marketplace on May 15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin ‘Speedrun’ Goes Viral, Sparks Scam Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139220</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139220/meme-coin-speedrun-goes-viral-sparks-scam-concerns"/>
        <updated>2023-05-07T19:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin season may be primed for a new twist, initiated by a competition on Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Pauses Bitcoin Withdrawals, Blames Network Congestion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139228</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139228/binance-pauses-bitcoin-withdrawals-blames-network-congestion"/>
        <updated>2023-05-07T19:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The average Bitcoin transaction fee was near its highest point in almost two years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget FOMO—JOMO Effect NFT Project Aims to Boost Mental Health in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139147</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139147/joy-of-missing-out-nfts-to-launch-on-magic-eden-supporting-mental-health-through-digital-art"/>
        <updated>2023-05-07T17:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The JOMO Effect collection emphasizes the "joy of missing out" and features NFTs from 40 artists to support mental health charities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Bitcoin and Ethereum Stand Still After Fed Rate Hike]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139187</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139187/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-and-ethereum-stand-still-after-fed-rate-hike"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T18:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto is fast becoming a hot topic among expected 2024 U.S. Presidential candidates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sui Is Built for Games—Here's Why Developers Are Bullish]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139169</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139169/sui-built-games-heres-why-developers-bullish"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T18:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newly launched blockchain Sui already has over 40 games building on its network, from shooters to MMORPGs. What’s the hook for creators?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than 'Frens': How Two Family-Run NFT Projects Found Success in a Volatile Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139017</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139017/how-family-run-nft-projects-handle-ups-downs-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creators of Women and Weapons and Chimpers share their respective journeys from family to prominent NFT founders in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Farren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Deepfakes Just Got Better With This Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139118</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139118/ai-deepfakes-just-got-better-midjourney-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MidJourney 5.1 is here. Deepfakes have never looked better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Your NFTs Safe? How to Protect Digital Assets From Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138676</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138676/are-your-nfts-safe-how-to-protect-digital-assets-from-disaster"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As FTX NFTs and other closed platforms showed, an on-chain token doesn't always mean the art is secure. But there are ways to protect NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mason Marcobello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​AI Invasion: Hollywood Writers Strike to Save Your Netflix From Robot Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139156</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139156/ai-invasion-hollywood-writers-strike-save-netflix-robot-takeover"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T10:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the ongoing writers strike, streaming services and studios are being asked to address the elephant in the room: artificial intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabe Nikias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Staking Deposits Outpace Withdrawals by $189M in ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139152</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139152/ethereum-staking-deposits-outpace-withdrawals-eth"/>
        <updated>2023-05-06T09:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Shanghai was executed last month, the network has shown that most Ethereum enthusiasts are still very eager to start staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sui NFT Scene Already Has Early Buzz—Will It Last?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139103</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139103/sui-nft-scene-already-early-buzz-will-last"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T23:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early Sui NFT projects are minting out and yielding near-seven-figure trading sums, albeit not without some technical hitches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voyager Gives Up Finding Buyer, Plans to Liquidate After Binance Deal Goes Bust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139079</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139079/crypto-broker-voyager-will-liquidate-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T19:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers should receive their funds in a matter of weeks, the collapsed crypto broker said, barring any objections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Won't Support Gala Games V2 Token Airdrop—Why Not?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139053</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139053/coinbase-wont-support-gala-games-v2-token-airdrop-why-not"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T19:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games is rolling out an upgraded token this month, but Coinbase refuses to support the transition—and won't give clear answers as to why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terra’s Do Kwon Caught in Jurisdictional Battle Between US and South Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139063</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139063/terras-do-kwon-caught-in-jurisdictional-battle-between-us-and-south-korea"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T18:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean prosecutors are pushing for him to face criminal charges in his home country, claiming it would be best for victims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina Bans Payment Apps From Offering Bitcoin to Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139068/argentinas-central-bank-clamps-down-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T18:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The central bank said Thursday that payment platforms cannot offer crypto trading services to their customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games GM: Play-to-Earn Games Are DeFi Products, Not Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yp7btQtl/solana-games-gm-play-to-earn-games-are-defi-products-not-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Games' General Manager Johnny Lee offers a hot take on the first generation of Web3 gaming with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Inserts 'Bug' in Bitcoin Ordinals—How Bad Is It?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139036</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139036/developer-inserts-bug-bitcoin-ordinals-how-bad-is"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T15:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something really weird has just happened on the Ordinals protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COIN Pumps 14% After Coinbase Posts Bullish Q1 Earnings Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139030</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139030/coin-pumps-14-after-coinbase-posts-bullish-q1-earnings-report"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T14:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite regulatory headwinds stateside, Coinbase stock has soared this morning following a rather bullish Q1 earnings report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Role Is Mostly Symbolic’, Says ENS Director Candidate Ahead of Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139026</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139026/role-is-mostly-symbolic-says-ens-director-candidate-ahead-elections"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T13:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone could nominate themselves to be an ENS Foundation director but only two stepped forward. Why is that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Lists PEPE as Meme Coin Market Cap Hits $1 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=139010</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/139010/liam-binance-lists-pepe-meme-coin-market-cap-hits-1-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T12:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly-launched meme coin PEPE has been given another boost after the market's largest exchange, Binance, listed the token this afternoon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coin Mania: What's Going On and What Are the Risks?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138915</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138915/meme-coin-mania-what-are-the-risks"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T12:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The roller coaster ride is a compelling draw, but it's rife with risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Mint a Free Ethereum NFT for King Charles’ Coronation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138961</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138961/you-can-mint-a-free-ethereum-nft-for-king-charles-coronation"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T12:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[London's Evening Standard newspaper has teamed up with artist Trevor Jones to issue a commemorative NFT for the coronation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bright Moments Transports Live NFT Art Minting Experience to Tokyo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138965</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138965/bright-moments-transports-live-nft-art-minting-experience-tokyo"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Venice Beach to the heart of Shibuya in two years—Bright Moments founder Seth Goldstein walks Decrypt through its biggest event yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s Cash App Posts $2.16B in Bitcoin Revenue for Q1 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138999</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138999/jack-dorseys-cash-app-posts-2-16b-in-bitcoin-revenue-for-q1-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T10:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech company Block reported over $2 billion in Bitcoin revenue through its Cash App unit for the first quarter of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE Meme Coin Hysteria Pushes Ethereum Gas Fees to 1-Year High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138989</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138989/pepe-meme-coin-hysteria-pushes-ethereum-gas-fees-1-year-high"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T09:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The massive rise in the latest wave of popular meme coins has put Ethereum under pressure, driving gas fees even higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White House Meets With AI Leaders in Attempt to 'Protect Our Society']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138925</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138925/white-house-meets-ai-leaders-attempt-protect-our-society"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T01:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris met with several AI and tech company CEOs today to emphasize the need for ethical AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gambling Games for 'OG and Crypto Degens' Coming to Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138931</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138931/gambling-games-og-crypto-degens-coming-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T01:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi platform Hxro sees gambling and crypto as a match made in degen heaven, but gambling is controversial in the video game industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedi Raises $17M in a Bid to 'Accelerate the Adoption of Bitcoin and Lightning']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138948</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138948/fedi-raises-17m-to-accelerate-bitcoin-lightning-adoption"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T01:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedimint federations allow users to set up communities to custody Bitcoin and Lightning together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Wars Limited Edition 'Digital Toy' NFTs Land on Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138944</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138944/cryptoys-launches-star-wars-digital-toys-nft-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-05-05T00:51:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time for "Star Wars Day," Cryptoys reveals plans for NFTs featuring 15 cartoonish recreations of franchise icons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Gets Court Approval for LedgerX Sale at Massive Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138901</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138901/ftx-approval-ledgerx-sale"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T22:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American affiliate of FTX bought the derivatives exchange for nearly six times as much just two years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LACMA Ventures Deeper Into NFT Art With Experimental Deafbeef Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138903</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138903/lacma-deafbeef-nft-art"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T21:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famed art museum LACMA continues its NFT exploration with a project from Deafbeef that interprets the 19th-century work of Eadweard Muybridge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Reports Q1 Revenue of $736M, Up 22% From Q4]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138929</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138929/coinbase-reports-736-q1-revenue"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T20:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The San Francisco-based exchange beat analysts' profit and revenue expectations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCG’s Barry Silbert Sells $755K Worth of Grayscale Ethereum Classic Trust Shares]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138916</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/138916/dcg-barry-silbert-sells-grayscale-ethereum-classic-trust-shares"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T20:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears to be the first time Silbert has sold any of his ETCG shares, according to SEC filings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent's Advice For Gaming Content Creators]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/o19nZCeN/brycents-advice-for-gaming-content-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-05-04T20:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET's Brycent shares his advice for Web3 content creators with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, including which social media platform is best for posting content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes of Jeremy Cowart's 'Auras' NFT Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/C0ZeidQg/behind-the-scenes-of-jeremy-cowarts-auras-nft-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T22:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the preparation behind "Auras," an event in which photographer Jeremy Cowart produced and starred in 10,000 photo-based NFTs, captured in less than 30 minutes before a live audience. Credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart Discusses 'Auras' Event, Live-Shooting 10,000 Photo NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/E3ViHsPd/jeremy-cowart-discusses-auras-event-live-shooting-10-000-photo-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T18:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy Cowart speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz in Nashville ahead of the "Auras" event, in which the noted photographer live-shot 10,000 unique photo-based NFTs in less than 30 minutes. The NFTs will be released through OpenSea on May 9. Video credit: Brett Carlsen for Decrypt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO on Putting Fun Before Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/03W3KZjM/azra-games-ceo-on-putting-fun-before-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-05-03T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The Web3 interfaces cannot be on the foreground of the player's initial experience," says Azra Games CEO Mark Otero.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Meet Immunefi's White Hat Whisperer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/2vTAgpTC/gm-meet-immunefis-white-hat-whisperer"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Web3 bug bounty platform Immunefi launched two years ago, CEO and founder Mitchell Amador says the bug bounties weren't great and adoption was slow. But the tides started to turn because even if exploiting a smart contract nets a bigger payday than a bounty, it comes with a huge drawback. "There's a ton of risk when you engage in this, you know, wantonly criminal behavior and steal $200 million from someone else," he said. "There's no way someone's not going to come looking."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Co-Founder on Why Mirandus Will Not Have NPCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5pey6epR/gala-games-co-founder-on-why-mirandus-will-not-have-npcs"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lead Mirandus Developer and Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the Web3 MMORPG Mirandus and what its world will be like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFC Lisbon Founder John Karp Heralds 'Level 2' Content for 2023 Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cYaJ25qv/nfc-lisbon-founder-john-karp-heralds-level-2-content-for-2023-event"/>
        <updated>2023-05-02T09:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No panels, no problem. This year's NFC Lisbon from June 7 to June 9 boasts a variety of alternative formats, catering to a decentralized (and sometimes pseudonymous) NFT community. The event also plans to take a closer look into one of the faster-growing niches in NFTs: Photography and what founder John Karp calls "level 2" content. Not to be missed, as NFC Lisbon's media partner, Decrypt will be on-site for all three days. Come say hi!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Magic Eden Vet Web3 Games?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ogci0VQ6/how-does-magic-eden-vet-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-01T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer Chris Akhavan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the NFT marketplace vets potential Web3 games for its platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Kevin Rose on the 'Weird Dynamic' of Building an NFT Project]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rb2MhkWH/interview-kevin-rose-on-the-weird-dynamic-of-building-an-nft-project"/>
        <updated>2023-04-30T18:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Proof co-founder and CEO Kevin Rose chats with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward during NFT NYC 2023 to discuss his startup's reaffirmed focus on digital art and collectors, the challenges of building in the NFT market, and what he's learned in the last year since the buzzy Moonbirds drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How MMORPG Mirandus is Managing its Web3 Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XETXOt0k/how-mmorpg-mirandus-is-managing-its-web3-elements"/>
        <updated>2023-04-29T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Cofounder Michael McCarthy says an "unbelievable" amount of Mirandus conversations are about its approach to Web3 and crypto transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Azra Games's Creative Process?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zyYFJkg0/what-is-azra-gamess-creative-process"/>
        <updated>2023-04-28T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO Mark Otero tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Azra's creative process to game development and storytelling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory Is 'Pokemon Meets The Matrix,' Says Executive Producer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/AotiTeMz/aurory-is-pokemon-meets-the-matrix-says-executive-producer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T20:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Aurory Web3 game's Executive Producer Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 2023 Game Developer's Conference about the game and what it's like to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Marco Santori]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JDZuMy3q/gm-marco-santori</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JDZuMy3q/gm-marco-santori"/>
        <updated>2023-04-27T18:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no doubt that the SEC dealt Kraken—and the outlook for crypto staking products in the U.S.—a big blow when it announced a $30 million settlement and ordered the company to stop offering the service to its customers in the states in February. Now Marco Santori, the company's chief legal officer, says the exchange is eager to move on from it. That means reckoning with a really challenging regulatory environment and growing its customer base overseas. And as Santori quips: "Kraken's master account application has not yet been rejected."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent on Web3 Games and the Problem with 'NFT Value']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET gamer and content creator Brycent tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the problem with gaming NFTs—and what needs to happen instead in the next generation of Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Yogurt Shop Started Mark Otero's Video Game Career]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nZzUeNAR/how-a-yogurt-shop-started-mark-oteros-video-game-career</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nZzUeNAR/how-a-yogurt-shop-started-mark-oteros-video-game-career"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Azra Games CEO Mark Otero tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his career developing eight RPG games and being acquired by Electronic Arts before getting into Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Games Will Shed Their 'Well-Deserved' Bad Reputation In 2023, Says Solana Games Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HrFRBQIL/blockchain-games-will-shed-their-well-deserved-bad-reputation-in-2023-says-solana-games-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HrFRBQIL/blockchain-games-will-shed-their-well-deserved-bad-reputation-in-2023-says-solana-games-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-04-26T13:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Foundation's General Manager of Games Johnny Lee tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his predictions for Web3 gaming in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We're Going to Stop Calling it Web3 Gaming, Says Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VMeXv9Mb/were-going-to-stop-calling-it-web3-gaming-says-magic-eden-chief-gaming-officer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VMeXv9Mb/were-going-to-stop-calling-it-web3-gaming-says-magic-eden-chief-gaming-officer"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T23:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden Chief Gaming Officer Chris Akhavan talks Web3 adoption and Web3's reputation problem with Decrypt's Kate Irwin. Also, he shares his stance on the word "NFT."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs' Ed Chang on the Future of Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Wdrl0iqp/ava-labs-ed-chang-on-the-future-of-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Wdrl0iqp/ava-labs-ed-chang-on-the-future-of-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-04-25T20:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Game Developer's Conference in San Francisco, Ava Labs' Head of Gaming Ed Chang spoke with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Ava Labs' approach to Web3 gaming, building games on Avalanche, and gave his thoughts on what the coming months and years will look like for the ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Dying in this game is different than other games,' Says Lead Mirandus Dev]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GbkRmy1x/dying-in-this-game-is-different-than-other-games-says-lead-mirandus-dev</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/GbkRmy1x/dying-in-this-game-is-different-than-other-games-says-lead-mirandus-dev"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games Cofounder and Mirandus Developer Michael McCarthy tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about Mirandus' hardcore fantasy world and its high stakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>