<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-12T12:28:30.265Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-12T12:28:30.265Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shibarium Hits Massive New Record, Here's What Happened]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558818/Shibarium-Hits-Massive-New-Record-Heres-What-Happened</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558818/Shibarium-Hits-Massive-New-Record-Heres-What-Happened"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu's Layer 2 protocol beta test version has passed new utility milestone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US sees 78% decline in market depth following SEC lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558795/BinanceUS-sees-78-decline-in-market-depth-following-SEC-lawsuit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558795/BinanceUS-sees-78-decline-in-market-depth-following-SEC-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US market depth plunged by 78% in the aftermath of the SEC lawsuit as market makers seemingly exit the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘Antifragile’ to Regulatory Pressures: Blockstream CEO Adam Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144193</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144193/bitcoin-antifragile-to-regulatory-pressures-blockstream-ceo-adam-back"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Blockstream co-founder told Decrypt that the U.S. crypto crackdown won’t have far-reaching consequences for Bitcoin traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Diamond Hands Unfazed By Recent FUD As Exchange Inflows Remain Very Low]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75787742c8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-diamond-hands-fud-exchange-inflows-low/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin long-term holders don’t care too much about the ongoing market FUD as their exchange inflows remain very low.
 
Bitcoin Long-Term Holder Inflows Have Remained Muted Recently
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the long-term holders have only been depositing around 0.004% of their supply to exchanges recently. The “long-term holders” (LTHs) here refer to investors who have been holding onto their coins since at least 155 days ago.
 
The LTHs make up for one of the two main segments the Bitcoin market is generally divided in, with the other cohort being the “short-term holders” (STHs). Naturally, the STHs are holders who acquired their BTC less than 155 days ago.
 
Statistically, the longer an investor holds onto their coins, the l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Receives Hong Kong Legislator’s Support Amid Regulatory Storm]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75787742be</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-gets-hong-kongs-support/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, one of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, is being beckoned toward the shores of Hong Kong as the region’s progressive stance on cryptocurrencies continues to gain traction. 
 
Johnny Ng, a prominent Legislative Council member, recently took to Twitter to extend an inviting hand to Coinbase and other global virtual asset trading operators, offering support and assistance in establishing operations in the bustling financial hub. 
 
Ng’s gesture not only underscores Hong Kong’s commitment to embracing the crypto industry but also hints at potential stock listing opportunities, promising an enticing prospect for Coinbase and its peers. 
 
This invitation comes hot on the heels of the US Securities and Exchange Commission’s recent lawsuits against major industry players li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Diamond Hands Unfazed By Recent FUD As Exchange Inflows Remain Very Low]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558786/Bitcoin-Diamond-Hands-Unfazed-By-Recent-FUD-As-Exchange-Inflows-Remain-Very-Low</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558786/Bitcoin-Diamond-Hands-Unfazed-By-Recent-FUD-As-Exchange-Inflows-Remain-Very-Low"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin long-term holders don’t care too much about the ongoing market FUD as their exchange inflows remain very low. Bitcoin Long-Term Holder Inflows Have Remained Muted Recently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the long-term holders have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Storage Firm Censo Offers Institutions Mobile Phone-Enabled Self Custody]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558787/Crypto-Storage-Firm-Censo-Offers-Institutions-Mobile-Phone-Enabled-Self-Custody</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558787/Crypto-Storage-Firm-Censo-Offers-Institutions-Mobile-Phone-Enabled-Self-Custody"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Censo is the latest in a crop of cheap, open-source options for organizations looking to store digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Chamath Palihapitiya Says SEC Covering Its Faults in Regulator’s Current Assault on Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558766/Billionaire-Chamath-Palihapitiya-Says-SEC-Covering-Its-Faults-in-Regulators-Current-Assault-on-Crypto-Firms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558766/Billionaire-Chamath-Palihapitiya-Says-SEC-Covering-Its-Faults-in-Regulators-Current-Assault-on-Crypto-Firms"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Chamath Palihapitiya says that the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) recent enforcement actions against the crypto industry are an attempt to cover its previous mistakes. In a new episode of the All-In Podcast, the business magnate says that the SEC’s latest assault on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bearish Signal: Miners Sell At 3rd Largest Scale Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558764/Bitcoin-Bearish-Signal-Miners-Sell-At-3rd-Largest-Scale-Ever</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558764/Bitcoin-Bearish-Signal-Miners-Sell-At-3rd-Largest-Scale-Ever"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows that Bitcoin miners may have been selling at a historical rate recently, something that could be bearish for the asset’s price. Bitcoin Miner Inflow To Exchanges Has Registered A Spike Recently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, miner exchange...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latam Insights — Volcano Energy Bitcoin Mining Project Rises in El Salvador, Venezuelan Miners Leaving Amidst Crypto Corruption Probe]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757871fd3a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/latam-insights-volcano-energy-bitcoin-mining-project-rises-in-el-salvador-venezuelan-miners-leaving-amidst-crypto-corruption-probe/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Latam Insights, a compendium of Latin America’s most relevant crypto and economic news during the last week. In this issue, Volcano Energy rises in El Salvador, Venezuelan bitcoin miners flee amidst nationwide mining ban, and Argentina deepens usage of the Chinese yuan to pay imports.
Volcano Energy Green Mining Project Rises out of Stealth in El Salvador
Volcano Energy, a bitcoin mining project, announced the construction of a 241MW renewable power generation facility in El Salvador. The operation, which will get most of its energy using photovoltaic (solar) cells, will power what it calls “one of the world’s largest bitcoin mining farms,” with a mining processing capacity of 1.3 EH/s in its first stage.
The cost of the whole development is estimated to reach $1 billion, with t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin to fight against European challenges — Northern Lightning founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558758/Bitcoin-to-fight-against-European-challenges-Northern-Lightning-founder</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558758/Bitcoin-to-fight-against-European-challenges-Northern-Lightning-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin community continues to develop tools and services that could be helpful as Europe grapples with conflict, migration and government overreach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Cuban slams SEC’s crypto guidelines as ‘near impossible’ to navigate]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558740/Mark-Cuban-slams-SECs-crypto-guidelines-as-near-impossible-to-navigate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558740/Mark-Cuban-slams-SECs-crypto-guidelines-as-near-impossible-to-navigate"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American businessman Mark Cuban said it is almost impossible to know what qualifies as a security under the current regulatory regime of the U.S. Security and Exchange Commission (SEC), citing documents from the financial regulator’s website. In a June 11 tweet, Cuban pointed to an SEC document...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu: Shibarium Token BONE Secures New Exchange Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558746/Shiba-Inu-Shibarium-Token-BONE-Secures-New-Exchange-Listing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558746/Shiba-Inu-Shibarium-Token-BONE-Secures-New-Exchange-Listing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BONE continues to gain further exposure with new exchange listings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newton's Third Law Will Turn UFOs into UTXOs, ep 288 The Breakup]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558736/Newtons-Third-Law-Will-Turn-UFOs-into-UTXOs-ep-288-The-Breakup</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558736/Newtons-Third-Law-Will-Turn-UFOs-into-UTXOs-ep-288-The-Breakup"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:31:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[- @joerogan on @realDonaldTrump- @realDailyWire, @GovRonDeSantis and Newton's 3rd law- @RobertKennedyJr on China-USA- @balajis on Taiwan-USA- @EricRWeinstein on UFOs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insights from Dubai’s cryptocurrency scene as city looks to be global digital assets hub]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558716/Insights-from-Dubais-cryptocurrency-scene-as-city-looks-to-be-global-digital-assets-hub</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558716/Insights-from-Dubais-cryptocurrency-scene-as-city-looks-to-be-global-digital-assets-hub"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghassan Jumblat, fintech director at financial services company Integrated Communications Channel discusses the evolution of the cryptocurrency and blockchain industry in Dubai in the United Arab Emirates, as the city positions itself as a future hub for digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto market cap on the brink of catastrophic crash below $1 trillion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558713/Crypto-market-cap-on-the-brink-of-catastrophic-crash-below-1-trillion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558713/Crypto-market-cap-on-the-brink-of-catastrophic-crash-below-1-trillion"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The total market capitalization of cryptocurrencies has experienced a notable decline in recent days as investors jumped ship amid the … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mark Cuban: ‘Near Impossible To Know’ What Is or Is Not ‘A Security in the Crypto Universe’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558711/Billionaire-Mark-Cuban-Near-Impossible-To-Know-What-Is-or-Is-Not-A-Security-in-the-Crypto-Universe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558711/Billionaire-Mark-Cuban-Near-Impossible-To-Know-What-Is-or-Is-Not-A-Security-in-the-Crypto-Universe"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:18:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Receives Hong Kong Legislator’s Support Amid Regulatory Storm]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558678/Coinbase-Receives-Hong-Kong-Legislators-Support-Amid-Regulatory-Storm</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558678/Coinbase-Receives-Hong-Kong-Legislators-Support-Amid-Regulatory-Storm"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase, one of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, is being beckoned toward the shores of Hong Kong as the region’s progressive stance on cryptocurrencies continues to gain traction. Johnny Ng, a prominent Legislative Council member, recently took to Twitter to extend an inviting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Lending Protocol Sturdy Finance Hit By Exploit, Over $750K Drained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144188</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144188/defi-lending-protocol-sturdy-finance-hit-by-exploit-over-750k-drained"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi platform’s team is trying to communicate with the attackers as its stolen ETH is moved through Tornado Cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Lending Protocol Sturdy Finance Hit By Exploit, Over $750K Drained]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558705/DeFi-Lending-Protocol-Sturdy-Finance-Hit-By-Exploit-Over-750K-Drained</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558705/DeFi-Lending-Protocol-Sturdy-Finance-Hit-By-Exploit-Over-750K-Drained"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoSlots Celebrates Fifth Birthday with New Bonuses, a Revamped Cashback System, and World-Class VIP Treatment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75787f0f4e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cryptoslots-celebrates-fifth-birthday-with-new-bonuses-a-revamped-cashback-system-and-world-class-vip-treatment/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. June 12, 2023 — It’s time to pop the champagne and raise a toast, because CryptoSlots, one of the premier online casinos for crypto enthusiasts, has just turned 5 years old. Ever since its launch in 2018, CryptoSlots has been a mainstay for iGaming enthusiasts who prioritize the safety and anonymity of cryptocurrencies while spinning unique Provably Fair slots for excellent payouts.
 

 
To celebrate the occasion, CryptoSlots has been pulling out all the stops to make sure this year is one to remember by offering all players special tokens for its signature Jackpot Trigger slot. These tokens are normally only acquired by playing slots on the site, but everyone could receive this premium currency by making deposits in May while using the birthday bonus codes.
 

 
Even in the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Inscriptions Get Revolutionary Upgrade, Enabling Video Games On-Chain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757878390f</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-inscriptions-get-revolutionary-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Inscriptions have created a huge hype in recent months and divided the BTC community into two parts. And the newest upgrade “Recursive Inscriptions” is likely to be no less controversial. The upgrade will allow Inscriptions to “indirectly” break the 4 MB block space limit.
 
Via Twitter, Luxor’s Charlie Spears wrote that the mastermind behind Ordinal’s Casey Rodarmor “just merged Recursion. Now the real fun begins.” The idea is similar to BRC721. Although the size of each individual inscriptions does not exceed 4 MB, the combined inscription can break that limit now.
 
 
Casey just merged Recursion. Now the real fun begins.
 
Inscriptions 2.0https://t.co/uRsEQo7bHc
 
— cbspears ◉ (@cbspears) June 12, 2023
 

 
What Do Recursive Inscriptions Bring To Bitcoin?
 
Earlier this year, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Prague 2023: ‘Anyone can produce value in the Bitcoin ecosystem’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558680/BTC-Prague-2023-Anyone-can-produce-value-in-the-Bitcoin-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558680/BTC-Prague-2023-Anyone-can-produce-value-in-the-Bitcoin-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T11:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordinals recursive inscriptions could unlock 3D video games on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558673/Ordinals-recursive-inscriptions-could-unlock-3D-video-games-on-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558673/Ordinals-recursive-inscriptions-could-unlock-3D-video-games-on-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Global bid and ask Metric Plunged 20% Over Weekend, Points to Paper Thin Liquidity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578793f3a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/12/crypto-global-bid-and-ask-metric-points-to-paper-thin-order-books/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyblock Capital's global bid and ask indicator plunged 20% during Saturday's altcoin crash, indicating a sharp deterioration in the crypto market liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Global Bid and Ask Metric Plunged 20% Over Weekend, Points to Paper Thin Liquidity]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558667/Crypto-Global-Bid-and-Ask-Metric-Plunged-20-Over-Weekend-Points-to-Paper-Thin-Liquidity</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558667/Crypto-Global-Bid-and-Ask-Metric-Plunged-20-Over-Weekend-Points-to-Paper-Thin-Liquidity"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyblock Capital's global bid and ask indicator plunged 20% during Saturday's altcoin crash, indicating a sharp deterioration in the crypto market liquidity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Crypto Crackdown Adds Urgency for U.S. Lawmakers to Produce Regulatory Framework This Year: JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75787a68e6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/12/sec-crypto-crackdown-adds-urgency-for-us-lawmakers-to-produce-regulatory-framework-this-year-jpmorgan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without a more solid legal framework, cryptocurrency activity will probably continue moving outside the U.S. and into decentralized entities, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Finance Founder Deposits $24M CRV into Aave to Safeguard $65M Stablecoin Loan]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75787a68d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/12/curve-finance-founder-deposits-24m-crv-into-aave-to-safeguard-65m-stablecoin-loan/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curve Finance founder Michael Egorov has deposited $24 million worth of Curve DAO (CRV) tokens to decentralized lending platform Aave to mitigate against liquidation risk on a $65 million stablecoin loan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No prediction about Bitcoin is reliable]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558661/No-prediction-about-Bitcoin-is-reliable</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558661/No-prediction-about-Bitcoin-is-reliable"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Removes 10 BNB Trading Pairs]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558640/Binance-Removes-10-BNB-Trading-Pairs</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18558640/Binance-Removes-10-BNB-Trading-Pairs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's move could be result of ongoing legal battle with SEC]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lummis Renews Commitment to US Crypto Regulation: ‘The Fight is Far From Over’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144182</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144182/lummis-renews-commitment-to-us-crypto-regulation-the-fight-is-far-from-over"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T10:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Senator said to ‘stay tuned’ for more on her efforts to establish a regulatory framework for the crypto sector in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria Orders Binance to Halt Operations while Hong Kong Welcomes Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578636c47</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/nigeria-orders-binance-to-halt-operations-while-hong-kong-welcomes-coinbase/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T09:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria's financial regulator has ordered Binance to halt  
its services in the country saying the exchange was neither registered nor  
regulated. In a circular issued on June 9, the Securities and Exchange  
Commission (SEC), Nigeria, termed the exchange's operations in the West  
African country as illegal.
"Binance Nigeria  
Limited is hereby directed to immediately stop soliciting Nigerian investors in  
any form whatsoever," SEC, Nigeria directed. "Any member of the  
investing public dealing with the entity is doing so at his or her own risk."  

Binance’s Regulatory  
Challenges Escalate
Nigeria SEC's circular came barely a week after Binance  
was charged by the US  
SEC alongside its CEO and Co-founder, Changpeng Zhao, for operating an illegal  
trading platform, offering unregis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A16z Chooses London as Destination for First Office Outside U.S.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75786eabd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/12/a16z-chooses-london-as-destination-for-first-office-outside-us/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T09:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The venture capital firm plans to use the office, which will open later this year, to fund growth in the crypto and startup ecosystems in the U.K. and Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX Customers' Names Can Permanently Remain Undisclosed: US Court]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757869135e</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/ftx-customers-names-can-permanently-remain-undisclosed-us-court/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T09:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A US court permitted now-bankrupt crypto exchange FTX to permanently remove individual customer names from all bankruptcy filings to avoid scams and identity theft risks.  

Protecting FTX Customers from Scams  

"It is the customers who are the most important issue in this case," US Bankruptcy Judge John Dorsey in Wilmington, Delaware, stated. "We want to make sure that they are protected and they don't fall victim to any types of scams."  

Though the judge permitted the permanent removal of individual customer names from FTX, the permission to remove the names of companies and institutional investors from its customer lists was provided on a temporary basis. FTX needs to make a new request in 90 days to keep those customer names a secret.  

According to Judge Dorsey, institutional cust…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and Russia Talk Crypto Cooperation, Unveil Tool Streamlining Trade in National Currencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757854dd5a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/iran-and-russia-talk-crypto-cooperation-unveil-tool-streamlining-trade-in-national-currencies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T08:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts and business representatives from Iran and Russia have discussed the potential uses of cryptocurrencies and blockchain. The two countries are also collaborating on implementing new financial instruments facilitating bilateral trade in their national fiats.
 
Financial Expo Brings Together Crypto Experts From Russia and Iran
 
Business leaders and industry professionals from Iran and Russia have discussed the potential applications as well as the pitfalls of employing crypto assets and blockchain technologies. They met during the 15th International Financial Industry Exhibition (Finex) in Tehran, local media reported.
 
The discussion brought together speakers from the crypto and fintech sectors of both countries and government officials, including Mustafa Amiri, secretary of the Ir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Explosive Week For Bitcoin And Crypto In 2023 Ahead: Key Events]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578593cd3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/most-explosive-week-for-bitcoin-and-crypto-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T07:03:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the massive sell-off of altcoins and the resulting (moderate) Bitcoin price drop on Friday, the market for digital assets may be facing the most explosive week of the year. Traders should prepare for a sharp increase in volatility.
 
There are extremely important events coming up in the trading week starting today: the release of the U.S. Consumer Price Index (CPI) and Producer Price Index (PPI), the U.S. Federal Reserve Bank (Fed) interest rate decision, a long-awaited release in the Ripple v. SEC case, a SEC response to Coinbase`s rulemaking request and a U.S. District Court hearing on the SEC`s request for a preliminary restraining order against Binance US, and much more.
 
Tuesday Turns Into Blockbuster Day
 
Tuesday is packed with important events. At 8:30 a.m. EST, the U.S. Bur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Interest in Binance's BNB Token Futures Jumps to 5-Month High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75785b5bab</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/12/open-interest-in-binances-bnb-token-futures-jumps-to-5-month-high/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T06:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surge in open interest comes alongside a decline in price and signals an influx of bearish short positions in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL, ADA, MATIC Prices Stabilize as Foundations Hit Back on SEC Lawsuit Allegations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757846ceed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/12/sol-ada-matic-prices-stabilize-as-foundations-hit-back-on-sec-lawsuit-allegations/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T06:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokens were up as much as 5% in the past 24 hours even as the broader market remained nominally changed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potential of NFTs and the Metaverse ‘Remain Vast and Largely Untapped’ Says Peer Inc CEO]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757842fc06</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/the-potential-of-nfts-and-the-metaverse-remain-vast-and-largely-untapped-says-peer-inc-ceo/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T05:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Tony Tran, the chairman and CEO of Peer Inc, the cooling interest in non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and the metaverse particularly by corporations and tech giants like Meta does not signal their end but instead “it reflects the natural cycle of innovation.” In written answers to questions from Bitcoin.com News, Tran, whose firm is behind the 3D social networking app Peer, insisted that such a downward trend is commonly experienced by early adopters of new technologies.
 
Ignorance a Key Barrier to Mass Adoption
 
Tran also attributed the public’s seemingly limited interest in NFTs to ignorance and their lack of “tangible utility.” However, Tran also argued that these barriers can be overcome by doing a “better job educating the public on the value of digital ownership and the broa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirdweb Plots Web3 Gaming Push With Ex-Facebook Exec Hire]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144131</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144131/thirdweb-plots-web3-gaming-tools-push-ex-facebook-exec-hire"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T04:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infrastructure firm has added Atif Khan to lead its gaming charge, and recently created the game Web3 Warriors on Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Farren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former SEC Official Predicts Impending DOJ Indictment Against Binance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757836fd8c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/former-sec-official-predicts-impending-doj-indictment-against-binance/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T03:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) official John Reed Stark said on Sunday via Twitter that he believes the U.S. Department of Justice (DOJ) has filed or will file a criminal indictment related to Binance. Stark, who draws from his experience in the SEC Enforcement Division, pointed to various indicators suggesting potential criminal charges in his recent statement.
 
DOJ Likely to Charge Binance Following SEC and CFTC Actions, Says Former SEC Official
 
According to John Reed Stark, the former head of internet enforcement at the SEC, the DOJ has either already filed or will file a criminal indictment against Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange. Stark’s opinion comes after the SEC sued Binance on June 5, 2023, for violating securities laws. The former SEC official emp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Asia: Here's Why Bitcoin's Support is Holding at $25K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75783d8398</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/12/first-mover-asia-heres-why-bitcoins-support-is-holding-at-25k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T02:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These are challenging times for the crypto market, but bitcoin is holding firm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turks Turn to Tether Amid Record Inflation, Limited Access to Dollar, Report Reveals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7578391806</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/turks-turn-to-tether-amid-record-inflation-limited-access-to-dollar-report-reveals/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T01:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People in Turkey have been seeking refuge in stablecoins as their national fiat continues to depreciate against the greenback. The Turkish lira saw a record drop in its exchange rate with the U.S. dollar when the country’s central bank halted intervention after the recent presidential vote. 
 
Turkish Investors Seek Safe Haven in Stablecoin Tether Despite Global Crackdown on Crypto
 

 
Demand for tether (USDT) in Turkey has been high since early May despite an ongoing crackdown on crypto assets around the world, Bloomberg noted. While the prices of major cryptocurrencies are falling, the Turkish lira has fared even worse, the report points out.
 

 
The national fiat dropped 11% against the dollar during the past week after the central bank pulled back from intervention following the reel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain-Based, AI Compute Protocol Gensyn Closes $43M Series A Funding Round Led by a16z]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75783bbe44</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/11/blockchain-based-ai-compute-protocol-gensyn-closes-43m-series-a-funding-round-led-by-a16z/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T00:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The capital infusion comes as interest in AI surges. Gensyn said it would use the money to accelerate the launch of the protocol and expand its workforce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins Say 'War On Crypto' Will Hurt Democrats]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144172</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144172/winklevoss-twins-say-war-on-crypto-will-hurt-democrats"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T00:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The billionaire co-founders of Gemini say that “crypto has already won the hearts and minds of Millennials and GenZ."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andreessen Horowitz Opening Crypto Office in London]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144159</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144159/andreessen-horowitz-a16z-crypto-expanding-london-uk"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T23:43:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citing "a clear regulatory regime" in the UK, a16z crypto sets up shop outside the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gensyn AI Secures $43M for Decentralized Machine Learning Led by a16z]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144068</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144068/gensyn-ai-secures-43m-for-decentralized-machine-learning-led-by-a16z"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T23:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK-based startup aims to democratize machine learning and AI development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, Cardano, Polygon Push Back Against SEC 'Security' Label]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144124/solana-cardano-polygon-push-back-against-sec-security-label"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T22:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although all disagreed, each organization tied to the trio of tokens show varying levels of conviction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorand and Flow Crash to All-Time Lows Following SEC Lawsuits]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144119</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144119/algorand-flow-all-time-lows-sec-lawsuits"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T19:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prices for a number of altcoins fell after they were namechecked by the Securities and Exchange Commission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Outrage Over the SEC Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144099</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144099/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-outrage-over-sec-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-06-11T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between bombshell lawsuits against two crypto titans and talk of a weekend Bitcoin dump, it's been a wild ride.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Court Finds a 'DAO Is a Person,' Owes $643,542 in Shutdown Order]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144075</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144075/court-finds-a-dao-is-a-person-owes-643542-in-shutdown-order"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T23:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CFTC touts the "wake-up call to anyone who believes they can circumvent the law by adopting a DAO structure."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picking and Choosing Tokens to Prosecute Is 'Pretty Unfair,' Says Former SEC Cyber Chief]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144085</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144085/picking-and-choosing-tokens-to-prosecute-is-pretty-unfair-says-former-sec-cyber-chief"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T21:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Cohen says the SEC's selective enforcement is having a "real impact on real people and real businesses.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foodmasku Dishes Out Edible Masks on Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144033</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144033/foodmasku-food-mask-proof-of-eat-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T20:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The multimedia artist has embraced the blockchain as a means to safeguard his work and explore the intersection of technology and humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Market Crashes as SEC Slams Binance and Coinbase]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144061</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144061/this-week-in-coins-market-crashes-as-sec-slams-binance-and-coinbase"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T17:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a relentless week of enforcement actions by the SEC against crypto’s major players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Worldwide Tax Standard Includes Cryptocurrencies and CBDCs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144050</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144050/new-worldwide-tax-standard-includes-cryptocurrencies-and-cbdcs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-10T09:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new set of rules from the OECD also takes aim at reducing tax evasion executed using cryptocurrencies and blockchain technologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Toxic Cocktail': EU Watchdog Calls Out Instagram, TikTok for Enabling Crypto Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144028</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144028/toxic-cocktail-eu-watchdog-calls-out-instagram-tiktok-enabling-crypto-scams"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T21:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading social media networks have been targeted by the BEUC for allegedly allowing misleading cryptocurrency ads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Will Have 'Enormous Impact' on Business, Execs Admit—But Not Right Away]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144011</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144011/generative-ai-enormous-impact-business-execs-admit-not-right-away"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T21:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate executives are optimistic about the benefits of generative AI, according to a KPMG study, but it'll take time to implement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Bankrupt FTX Wants to Keep its List of Customers Private]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144001</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144001/why-bankrupt-ftx-wants-keep-list-customers-private"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T20:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A partner at investment bank Perella Weinberg said that revealing customer names would hurt FTX's ongoing sales process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet PassGPT, the AI Trained on Millions of Leaked Passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144004</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144004/meet-passgpt-ai-trained-millions-leaked-passwords"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T20:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It shares a name with a past April Fool's gag, but this PassGPT is no joke—and the AI model could help develop more secure passwords.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft Still Hasn't Officially Banned NFTs—But It's Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143996</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143996/minecraft-still-hasnt-officially-banned-nfts-but-coming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T19:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a year after making the announcement, Microsoft shares an update about Minecraft’s intended NFT ban.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Launches Avalanche Arcad3 to Help Game Studios Enter Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143978/ava-labs-launches-avalanche-arcad3-help-game-studios-enter-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T18:46:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche Arcad3 is connecting traditional game publishers with crypto firms to help bring legacy IP into the fledgling Web3 gaming space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto.com to Close US Institutional Service Amid SEC's Crypto Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143988</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143988/crypto-com-close-us-institutional-service-amid-sec-crypto-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T18:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore-based cryptocurrency exchange Crypto.com said Friday that it will wind down its institutional service in the States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Ethereum Fails' Without These 3 Changes, Says Vitalik Buterin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143991</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143991/ethereum-fails-without-these-3-changes-says-vitalik-buterin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T17:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without scaling solutions, secure wallets, and better privacy measures, the future of Ethereum may be under threat, said its co-founder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Metaverse? No Problem, Says the Sandbox COO on Apple's VR Headset Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143980</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143980/no-metaverse-no-problem-says-sandbox-coo-apple-vr-headset-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though Apple didn’t mention metaverse in their launch, The Sandbox’s Sebastien Borget said it will still onboard more users to digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Hits Two Russians With Criminal Charges Over Mt. Gox Bitcoin Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143970</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143970/us-hits-two-russians-criminal-charges-over-mt-gox-bitcoin-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T16:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Department of Justice charged the men over the Mt. Gox attack, with one also charged over the shuttered BTC-e exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lone Star State ‘Will Be Silicon Valley’ of Crypto: Texas Blockchain Council President]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143962</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143962/texas-will-be-silicon-valley-crypto-thanks-key-legislative-wins-texas-blockchain-council-president"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the latest legislative session in Texas done and dusted, Bitcoin miners in the Lone Star state have struck digital gold.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Krantz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Moves to Cut Support for Cardano, Polygon and Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143946/robinhood-moves-cut-support-cardano-polygon-solana"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T14:24:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood opted to axe three tokens after the SEC listed them as unregistered securities in their lawsuits against Coinbase and Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custodia Lands Court Win After Judge Denies Fed Request to Dismiss ‘Master Account’ Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143942</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143942/custodia-lands-court-win-judge-denies-fed-request-dismiss-master-account-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We look forward to the court’s review of this power grab by the Fed,” said Custodia after a judge denied the Fed’s motion to dismiss the lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moody’s Drops Coinbase Outlook From Stable to Negative Over Medium Term]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143941</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143941/moodys-drops-coinbase-outlook-from-stable-to-negative-over-medium-term"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T12:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moody’s affirmed its previous Coinbase credit rating but changed its price outlook to negative for the next 12 to 18 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Chair Gensler Says Crypto Is Rife With ‘Hucksters, Fraudsters, Scam Artists’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143940</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143940/sec-chair-gensler-says-crypto-is-rife-hucksters-fraudsters-scam-artists"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T12:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler is stepping up his language amid a wider crackdown on the crypto industry which intensified last week with a pair of fresh lawsuits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance US Shifts to ‘Crypto-Only’ Operations Amid Intensified SEC Scrutiny]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143938</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143938/binance-us-shifts-crypto-only-operations-amid-intensified-sec-scrutiny"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T10:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US is transitioning to a "crypto-only" platform, suspending USD operations, including deposits and withdrawals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Andreessen Warns Against 'Government-Protected Cartel' of Major AI Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143934</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143934/marc-andreessen-warns-again-government-protected-cartel-major-ai-firms"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T02:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noted venture capitalist Marc Andreessen says the market should decide which AI companies succeed or fail—not government restrictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HyperPlay Raises $12 Million to Accelerate Web3 Game Launcher]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143913</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143913/hyperplay-raises-12-million-accelerate-web3-game-launcher"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T21:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The round was co-led by Griffin Gaming Partners and Bitkraft Ventures, and will fuel HyperPlay’s growth and expansion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If You Don’t Like It, Leave: CZ's Message to Employees After SEC Leaks Chat Logs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143907</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143907/cz-messages-employees-after-sec-leaks-binance-chat-logs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T21:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to a translated copy of an internal memo, Binance's CEO said the leaked chat logs "did a lot of damage."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Wants Another DOJ Investigation Into Binance, Binance US]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143896</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143896/elizabeth-warren-wants-another-doj-investigation-into-binance-binance-us"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T20:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Her letter makes no mention of the DOJ investigation that's reportedly been ongoing since 2018.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Myst Creator’s New Game Was Built With AI—Now Gamers Are Mad]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143901</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143901/myst-creators-new-game-built-with-ai-now-gamers-mad"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T20:20:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyan Worlds is seeing pushback from players after its new adventure game Firmament was developed using AI assistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Circle CEO Says 'Regulate Us' as Company Hires an Ex-Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143886</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143886/circle-ceo-says-regulate-us-as-company-hires-an-ex-regulator"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T20:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meanwhile: On-chain data shows that 15,000 wallets completely sold their USDC within a five-hour window on Thursday, according to Glassnode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Can Identify AI-Generated Academic Writing with '99% Accuracy']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143856/researchers-identify-ai-generated-academic-writing-with-99-accuracy"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T18:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT’s penchant for using the words "others" and "researchers" over words like "however," "but," and "although" proved to be a dead giveaway]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cathie Wood Slams the SEC, Claims Coinbase Will Come Out a Winner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143863</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143863/cathie-wood-slams-the-sec-claims-coinbase-will-come-out-a-winner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T18:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Invest’s CEO said that the SEC’s prompt action against Coinbase following the Binance lawsuit was “unfortunate.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Type of 'Social Token': PairedWorld Aims to Incentivize Real-World Connection]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=143872</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/143872/new-type-social-token-pairedworld-incentivize-real-world-connection"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developed with health experts, PairedWorld is designed to add value to existing NFT communities and encourage physical world interactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Superfan Base’: SuperDuper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-superfan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-superfan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand SuperDuper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cyber Cafe to Web3: How Everquest Dev Jeffrey Butler Got Into Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everquest developer turned Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Machines Arena Game Preview: Is This the Next Overwatch?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares an inside look at The Machines Arena, an upcoming top-down 4v4 shooter from Directive Games that will offer NFTs minted on Ethereum sidechain network Ronin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You 'Have' to Be on Mobile: InfiniGods Cofounders on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue share their stance on why mobile gaming is essential to Web3 adoption and general success in the video games industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Chaos of 2022 'Didn't Damage Technology Underlying the Industry': X Ventures Co-Founder Matthias Reiser]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PDArXOkZ/crypto-chaos-of-2022-didnt-damage-technology-underlying-the-industry-x-ventures-co-founder-matthias-reiser</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PDArXOkZ/crypto-chaos-of-2022-didnt-damage-technology-underlying-the-industry-x-ventures-co-founder-matthias-reiser"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T13:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of this month's Proof of Talk event in Paris on June 14 and June 15, X Ventures co-founder and the event's co-organizer Dr. Matthias Reiser said nothing's changed for those with a "long-term view" of the industry. Still, events like the collapse of Terra and FTX in 20222 have certainly damaged investors' trust in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tron's Justin Sun Thinks Hong Kong Will Be a Big Fiat Onramp for Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/agBnfg7Z/trons-justin-sun-thinks-hong-kong-will-be-a-big-fiat-onramp-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/agBnfg7Z/trons-justin-sun-thinks-hong-kong-will-be-a-big-fiat-onramp-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T12:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Sun, Tron founder and advisor to crypto exchange Huobi, talks to Decrypt's Liam Kelly and Stacy Elliott about the impact of Hong Kong allowing residents to trade crypto, complications of restricting access based on location, and how AI will change the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA's AI Push Could Change Gaming Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/79ArMuzj/nvidias-ai-push-could-change-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/79ArMuzj/nvidias-ai-push-could-change-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2023-05-31T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer tech firm NVIDIA profited off the crypto mining industry. Now, it's looking to artificial intelligence—and its stock price is soaring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why InfiniGods Laughs at 'AAA' Web3 Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WzdrzXOY/why-infinigods-laughs-at-aaa-web3-games"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The InfiniGods founders share their approach to game development and offer a critique of games that call themselves "AAA."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make it Fast, Make it Friendly: Jerome de Tychey Unpacks Key Themes at This Year's EthCC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yNyunUz4/make-it-fast-make-it-friendly-jerome-de-tychey-unpacks-key-themes-at-this-years-ethcc"/>
        <updated>2023-05-30T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After six years running, EthCC is back, this time in Paris from July 17 to July 20. Decrypt sat down with the brains behind one of Ethereum’s longest-running events Jerome de Tychey to get an inside look into what’s on the agenda this year, several unannounced guests, and the rollout of at least one “secret” DeFi project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unioverse Game Preview: Hands-on With the Cinematic Proving Grounds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/t68sovuN/unioverse-game-preview-hands-on-with-the-cinematic-proving-grounds"/>
        <updated>2023-05-29T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unioverse is a multimedia sci-fi franchise with plans to facilitate user-generated content. Decrypt reporter and GG producer Kate Irwin checked out the Unioverse as Reyu, an alien character, and navigated the Proving Grounds with him. In the Proving Grounds, you'll fight an array of different drone-like flying robots (some have tentacles!!) as you navigate the puzzle-like dystopian environment. Alien meets Portal, anyone?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>