<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-24T17:13:38.362Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-04-24T17:13:38.362Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETH Boston Conference and Hackathon Returns April 28-30 at Boston University]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e43b2d3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/eth-boston-conference-and-hackathon-returns-april-28-30-at-boston-university/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. ETH Boston and The Boston DAO are thrilled to announce the return of ETH Boston, a conference and hackathon event taking place at Boston University on April 28-30, 2023.
 
The conference will feature three stages of 50+ industry experts, founders, and builders, technology-specific workshops, networking events, and a hackathon. We are excited to bring to you high quality discussions with tracks covering DeFi, Infrastructure, Data, Identity, Zero-Knowledge, DAOs, DeSci, Institutional Adoption, Regulation, and more!
 
ETH Boston aims to build awareness and directly impact developers, investors, students, and companies who are creating the next generation of infrastructure and applications that will power the decentralized web.
 
The ETH Boston Hackathon provides an opportunity for builders to display their technical abilities and creativity across a 3-day competition where hackers will work to create innovative ideas and products to be judged for cash prizes and funding.
 
We are excited to invite you to participate in this upcoming event and contribute to the growing ecosystem of the decentralized web. Please join us in Boston for ETHBoston 2023, and be a part of the future of web3.
 
Register for ETH Boston and buy your tickets at https://www.ethboston.xyz/. Use code NEWS10 for a discount.
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
This is a press release. Readers should do their own due diligence before taking any actions related to the promoted company or any of its affiliates or services. Bitcoin.com is not responsible, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any content, goods or services mentioned in the press release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Money?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e4c2fd9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/what-is-money"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Money is crucial to regulating our lives and economies. Here’s an essential guide to understanding money and its role in today’s economic system.
Introduction
Money is something that most of us take for granted, as we use it daily to buy goods and services. We constantly transact in money, think in money and strive to earn more of it. However, few genuinely understand what money is, and even those who do often perceive it in very different ways. 
Some say that money is a form of energy that can be transformed and exchanged. Others see it as a technological tool that facilitates trade and commerce. Still others argue that money is a social construct shaped and governed by cultural norms and values. All these views can be correct since the concept of money is much deeper than the way it is c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Unit of Account: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e4c2fc4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/unit-of-account"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unit of Account
Unit of account is the thing that measures the value of goods and services. It's an essential function for something to be [or become?] money. In simple terms, it is a standard measure of value, a common scaling system through which the value of products can be calculated and compared.
Countries typically have distinct units of account, identified as the national or regional currency, such as the euro (EUR) or the British pound (GBP). At the same time, internationally, the U.S. dollar (USD) is the unit of account that is mainly used for global invoicing and setting prices internationally. 
Unit of account is one of money’s three universally agreed functions of money that Bitcoin Magazine is reviewing; the other two are store of value and medium of exchange.
What is a Unit o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Store of Value? A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e4c2fb5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/store-of-value"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Store of Value
The concept of a “store of value” refers to goods that are capable of retaining or increasing their worth over time rather than declining in value. This term is used to describe a mechanism that enables individuals to preserve their wealth without experiencing any loss in value over time. 
It is one of the three functions of money that Bitcoin Magazine is exploring; the other two are medium of exchange and unit of account.
What is a Store of Value
A store of value is an asset, a currency or a commodity that can be trusted to hold its value over time; ideally, it doesn’t bear much risk. Traditionally, people who are less tolerant to risk will invest in a store of value with an enduring lifespan, a stable demand and low volatility. 
Fiat currencies are weak stores of value sin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Medium of Exchange? A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e4c2fa8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/guides/medium-of-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medium of Exchange
As society’s structure and organization became more complex over time, the need for an evolving monetary system arose from the limitations of barter. Barter is not suitable as a means to exchange goods and services in an economic system larger than a tribe or family; barter was unsuitable for expanding societies that needed a more efficient method to exchange goods and services. 
Hence, about 2,600 years ago, a new and more sophisticated medium of exchange emerged in Lydia — a region recognized as modern Turkey — and materialized with stamped coins to face the challenges of barter and facilitate trade.
A medium of exchange is an intermediary item that is widely accepted to facilitate the trade of goods and services between two parties. It is one of money’s three universa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Faces Moving Averages Convergence: Here's How It Affects Price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184166/XRP-Faces-Moving-Averages-Convergence-Heres-How-It-Affects-Price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184166/XRP-Faces-Moving-Averages-Convergence-Heres-How-It-Affects-Price"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP might be set for proper recovery after taking consecutive hits on market]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini Expands Beyond US Borders Amid Regulatory Uncertainty With Upcoming Launch of New Crypto Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184129/Gemini-Expands-Beyond-US-Borders-Amid-Regulatory-Uncertainty-With-Upcoming-Launch-of-New-Crypto-Exchange</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184129/Gemini-Expands-Beyond-US-Borders-Amid-Regulatory-Uncertainty-With-Upcoming-Launch-of-New-Crypto-Exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American crypto exchange Gemini is expanding its operations overseas as US federal regulators create uncertainty in the industry at home. The exchange says it’s launching the Gemini Foundation, a non-US crypto derivatives platform that will initially offer customers with a perpetual Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering AI in Crypto: CCData’s Comprehensive Dataset and its Game-Changing Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184160/Empowering-AI-in-Crypto-CCDatas-Comprehensive-Dataset-and-its-Game-Changing-Impact</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184160/Empowering-AI-in-Crypto-CCDatas-Comprehensive-Dataset-and-its-Game-Changing-Impact"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores how CCData’s industry-leading institutional-grade comprehensive cryptocurrency dataset could serve as a game-changer for AI companies in the evolving cryptocurrency landscape. On March 30, 2023, London-based CryptoCompare, a leading provider of real-time digital asset data,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how much Bitcoin is up since Peter Schiff told investors to sell in January]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184123/Heres-how-much-Bitcoin-is-up-since-Peter-Schiff-told-investors-to-sell-in-January</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184123/Heres-how-much-Bitcoin-is-up-since-Peter-Schiff-told-investors-to-sell-in-January"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the turn of the year Bitcoin’s (BTC) rally has taken some investors by surprise, particularly following the prolonged bear … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Holders: The NIGHTMARE Is REAL!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184165/Bitcoin-Holders-The-NIGHTMARE-Is-REAL</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184165/Bitcoin-Holders-The-NIGHTMARE-Is-REAL"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price at critical point. Argentina inflation goes insane.🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY💸 BYBIT $30,030 BONUS & FEE DISCOUNT 👉 https://cryptolark.co/BYBIT💡💡💡 ESSENTIAL CRYPTO KNOWLEDGE 💡💡💡🔥 GET MY FREE NEWSLETTER 👉 https://cryptolark.co/WEALTHMASTERY👨‍🎓...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pan-European crypto regulation is almost here: Law Decoded, Apr 17–24]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184109/Pan-European-crypto-regulation-is-almost-here-Law-Decoded-Apr-1724</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184109/Pan-European-crypto-regulation-is-almost-here-Law-Decoded-Apr-1724"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Bank Of Korea Authorized To Conduct Inspections On Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e48aed0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bank-of-korea-inspections-on-crypto-firms/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Korea (BoK) can now investigate local crypto exchanges. According to a report, the bank has the authority to conduct on-site inspections and even request financial records from exchanges operating within the country.
 
The main objective of the Bank of Korea is to ensure the stability of prices throughout the nation. This responsibility, in turn, allows the bank to control and improve the economy.
 
South Korean Bank To Oversee Transaction Data Of Crypto Local Exchanges
 
The new rights will allow the central bank to monitor the activities of cryptocurrency exchanges more closely and take action if necessary. This includes the power to issue fines and even revoke licenses if exchanges violate digital asset regulations.
 
The move comes amid growing concerns over the potential r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Winter is over’ and bitcoin may hit $100,000 next year, says Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184093/Winter-is-over-and-bitcoin-may-hit-100000-next-year-says-Standard-Chartered</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184093/Winter-is-over-and-bitcoin-may-hit-100000-next-year-says-Standard-Chartered"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Chartered's head of crypto research says bitcoin is building toward $100,000 following the recent U.S. banking crisis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Bank Of Korea Authorized To Conduct Inspections On Crypto Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184086/Report-Bank-Of-Korea-Authorized-To-Conduct-Inspections-On-Crypto-Firms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184086/Report-Bank-Of-Korea-Authorized-To-Conduct-Inspections-On-Crypto-Firms"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bank of Korea (BoK) can now investigate local crypto exchanges. According to a report, the bank has the authority to conduct on-site inspections and even request financial records from exchanges operating within the country. The main objective of the Bank of Korea is to ensure the stability...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Price at Crossroads: $2K or $1.5K Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184117/Ethereum-ETH-Price-at-Crossroads-2K-or-15K-Next</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184117/Ethereum-ETH-Price-at-Crossroads-2K-or-15K-Next"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite recent ETH price correction, strong on-chain fundamentals suggest that investors remain confident in the long-term prospects of the Ethereum network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former OpenSea Executive Set for NFT Insider Trading Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184116/Former-OpenSea-Executive-Set-for-NFT-Insider-Trading-Trial</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184116/Former-OpenSea-Executive-Set-for-NFT-Insider-Trading-Trial"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-OpenSea product manager Nathaniel Chastain will face trial for non-fungible tokens (NFT) insider trading allegations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Euro Will Have ‘Maximum Level of Privacy’—But Not as Much as Cash: ECB Board Member]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137684</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137684/digital-euro-will-have-maximum-level-of-privacy-but-not-as-much-as-cash-ecb-board-member"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:29:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ECB board member Fabio Panetta stopped short of saying that the digital euro would have ‘the same level of privacy’ as cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three-way Bidding War for Celsius To Begin Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184061/Three-way-Bidding-War-for-Celsius-To-Begin-Tuesday</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184061/Three-way-Bidding-War-for-Celsius-To-Begin-Tuesday"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New bidders include Fahrenheit LLC and the Blockchain Recovery Investment Committee, backed by Gemini and Van Eck]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unit of Account: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184058/Unit-of-Account-A-Comprehensive-Guide</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184058/Unit-of-Account-A-Comprehensive-Guide"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unit of AccountUnit of account is the thing that measures the value of goods and services. It's an essential function for something to be [or become?] money. In simple terms, it is a standard measure of value, a common scaling system through which the value of products can be calculated and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Medium of Exchange? A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184060/What-is-a-Medium-of-Exchange-A-Comprehensive-Guide</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184060/What-is-a-Medium-of-Exchange-A-Comprehensive-Guide"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medium of ExchangeAs society’s structure and organization became more complex over time, the need for an evolving monetary system arose from the limitations of barter. Barter is not suitable as a means to exchange goods and services in an economic system larger than a tribe or family; barter was ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum price lower highs vs. Bitcoin hint at more downside in April]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184062/Ethereum-price-lower-highs-vs-Bitcoin-hint-at-more-downside-in-April</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184062/Ethereum-price-lower-highs-vs-Bitcoin-hint-at-more-downside-in-April"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Investment Funds See First Week of Outflows in 6 Weeks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e4ad891</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/24/crypto-investment-funds-see-first-week-of-outflows-in-6-weeks/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Net outflows totaled $30 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thetanuts Finance secures $17 million institutional funding round as expansion looms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184069/Thetanuts-Finance-secures-17-million-institutional-funding-round-as-expansion-looms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184069/Thetanuts-Finance-secures-17-million-institutional-funding-round-as-expansion-looms"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thetanuts Finance, a decentralized finance (DeFi) structured products protocol, has raised $17 million in an institutional funding round led by … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New phone rules, who dis? Judge approves restrictions for Sam Bankman-Fried’s parents]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184053/New-phone-rules-who-dis-Judge-approves-restrictions-for-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-parents</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184053/New-phone-rules-who-dis-Judge-approves-restrictions-for-Sam-Bankman-Frieds-parents"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joseph Bankman and Barbara Fried will be subject to strict cellphone monitoring while Sam Bankman-Fried is under house arrest at their home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bybit to introduce mandatory KYC requirements starting May 8]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184049/Bybit-to-introduce-mandatory-KYC-requirements-starting-May-8</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184049/Bybit-to-introduce-mandatory-KYC-requirements-starting-May-8"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users without Know Your Customer verification had a daily withdrawal limit of 20,000 USDT on Bybit prior to the announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar Network Launches First US Mutual Fund on Public Blockchain: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184054/Stellar-Network-Launches-First-US-Mutual-Fund-on-Public-Blockchain-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184054/Stellar-Network-Launches-First-US-Mutual-Fund-on-Public-Blockchain-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar reveals exciting milestone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers Could Still Nix Digital Euro, ECB’s Panetta Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e344e87</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/24/lawmakers-could-still-nix-digital-euro-ecbs-panetta-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:14:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ECB wants the CBDC to be universally accepted, and usable by those without bank accounts, the central banker said]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Investment Funds Have First Week of Outflows in 6 Weeks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184046/Crypto-Investment-Funds-Have-First-Week-of-Outflows-in-6-Weeks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184046/Crypto-Investment-Funds-Have-First-Week-of-Outflows-in-6-Weeks"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Treasury Sanctions 3 Lazarus Group Members]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184045/US-Treasury-Sanctions-3-Lazarus-Group-Members</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18184045/US-Treasury-Sanctions-3-Lazarus-Group-Members"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T16:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: LTC, LINK Rebound on Monday, Despite Crypto Market Red Wave]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e31d06f</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-ltc-link-rebound-on-monday-despite-crypto-market-red-wave/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T15:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin rose marginally higher to start the week, despite cryptocurrency markets mostly trading lower on Monday. The global crypto market cap is down 0.15% at the time of writing, as volatility remains high. Chainlink also moved higher in today’s session.
 
Litecoin (LTC)
 
Litecoin (LTC) bounced from a key point of support to start the week, as the token rallied, despite Monday’s crypto red wave.
 
Following a low of $84.92 on Sunday, LTC/USD raced to an intraday peak of $88.89 earlier in today’s session.
 
As a result of this move, litecoin moved further away from its price floor at $86.00, and is now trading at its highest point since last Friday.
 
 
From the chart, it appears that the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) has now risen to a point of resistance at 45.00, leading to LTC giving up earlier gains.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 44.33, with litecoin trading at $88.11.
 
Should price strength move beyond the 45.00 mark, there is a good chance that LTC will be back above $90.00.
 
 
Chainlink (LINK)
 
Chainlink (LINK) was also in the green in today’s session, and the token rose by as much as 2%.
 
LINK/USD climbed to a peak of $7.25 to start the week, following a low of $6.92 on Sunday.
 
Today’s rebound sees LINK move away from the three-and-a-half-week low registered over the weekend.
 
 
Looking at the chart, this coincides with the RSI bouncing from a floor of its own at the 44.00 mark.
 
Currently price strength is tracking at 45.09, with a resistance point at 47.00 a potential target for bulls.
 
Should it hit this mark, then it is likely that LINK will move above $7.30.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
What has been behind today’s bearish sentiment? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Regulator Ponders ‘Fast Track’ Route To MiCA Compliance For Registered Firms]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e31f8bf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/french-regulator-ponders-fast-track-mica-compliance/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T15:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the European Parliament’s recent adoption of the crypto-focused Markets in Crypto Assets Legislation also known as ‘MiCA’, other countries including Ukraine have been seen following the European Union (EU) steps and embracing MiCA. 
 
Notably, France is now the latest country that has also joined in on the increasing MiCA adoption. On Friday, French Regulator,  L’Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF) announced it’s pondering a “Fast Track” route to the MiCA compliance for registered companies in the region. 
 
AMF To ‘Fast Track’ MiCA For Registered Firms
 
On April 21, the French Financial Markets Authority (AMF) released a statement expressing its satisfaction with the European Parliament’s recent adoption of the Markets in Crypto Assets (MiCA) regulation, a groundbreaking cryp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is EtherMail? The ‘Read-to-Earn’ Web3 Email Service]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=126203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-ethermail-the-read-to-earn-web3-email-service-2"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T14:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EtherMail aims to deliver “anonymous and encrypted wallet-to-wallet communication” to power Web3 and upend the advertising market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Euny Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Slides Towards $27K, Down 9% Over the Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137662/bitcoin-slides-towards-27k-down-9-over-the-week"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T14:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Macroeconomic fears and the Fed’s hawkishness caused Bitcoin’s price to drop significantly over the past week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sanctions 3 North Koreans for Supporting Hacking Group Known for Crypto Thefts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e3a02c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/04/24/us-sanctions-3-north-koreans-for-supporting-hacking-group-known-for-crypto-thefts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T14:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Treasury Department's sanctions watchdog banned three North Korean individuals for supporting the Lazarus Group, a North Korean hacking team known for crypto thefts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De, Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price May Hit $100K by Year-End, Standard Chartered Bank Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e3a02a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/04/24/bitcoin-price-may-hit-100k-by-year-end-standard-chartered-bank-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T14:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The report noted that the crypto winter is finally over and bitcoin halving is set to be a positive catalyst for the price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 1,000 Ancient Bitcoins from 2010 and 2011 Moved in 2023, Valued at Over $27 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e3b0067</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/nearly-1000-ancient-bitcoins-from-2010-and-2011-moved-in-2023-valued-at-over-27-million/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T14:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on present data, within the last four months, a mere three block rewards from the year 2010 have been transferred after 13 years of dormancy. This is due to the fact that dormant wallets from that era are becoming a rarity to behold. The latest expenditure of a 2010 block took place on April 22, 2023, at 11:14 p.m. (UTC), when a miner spent 50 bitcoin that was valued at approximately $1.3 million. A historic moment occurred today, as a transfer of 400 bitcoin from 2011 took place, marking the first time in over a decade that these digital assets had been moved.
 
Rare Bitcoin Activity: 985 BTC from 2010 and 2011 Moved in 2023
 
Block rewards of antiquity from 2010 and 2011 have become increasingly scarce. Only three 2010 blocks were spent this year, along with several ancient bitcoin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Not Slowing Down: 305 Million Tokens Burned In A Week]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e3b6526</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-not-slowing-down/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T14:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu community has shown a strong commitment to reducing the overall token supply in the ecosystem. The Shiba Army aims to boost the value of SHIB by triggering a decline in its supply through an aggressive token-burning mechanism.
 
So far, the community has burned about 19 million SHIB coins in the last 24 hours. This number takes the total of burned SHIB tokens for the week to over 305.77 million.
 
Shiba Inu Weekly Burn Hit 305.77M Last Week
 
According to Shibburn, about 19,175,360 SHIB tokens entered the dead wallet in 24 hours. This burning operation occurred through four different transactions.
 
Shibburn report showed that SHIB burning increased by over 103% as against the past day, which recorded only 9.40 million SHIB coins through three separate transactions. Also, its…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Dambel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Messari Founder Weighs In On Crypto Exchanges Leaving US Shores]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e2cfbbe</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/messari-founder-weighs-crypto-exchanges-migration/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T13:36:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US and crypto, in recent weeks, have become hot topics of discussion among notable figures and expert analysts who evaluate the operational sustainability of US-based crypto exchanges. This is a result of the numerous crackdowns and regulatory scrutiny on crypto companies and exchanges operating within the shores of the US.
 
While popular exchanges such as Coinbase, and Gemini currently contemplate relocation of headquarters operations or even ceasing to operate in the US, these decisions could impact the industry’s growth as well as global crypto adoption.
 
Messari Founder Ryan Selkis in a recent post has aired his view on the ongoing crypto offshore movement situation.
 
Biggest Hub For Crypto Exchanges
 
Messari founder Ryan Selkis made a Twitter post on his official handle yester…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mudiaga Iritare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Protocol Thetanuts Finance Raises $17M for Expansion, New Partnerships]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e2a7c52</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/04/24/defi-protocol-thetanuts-finance-raises-17m-for-expansion-new-partnerships/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T13:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup offers multi-chain structured financial products with plans for a buy-side altcoin options market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandy Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC on Brink of ‘Death Cross’ on Moving Average Trendline]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e14e397</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-on-brink-of-death-cross-on-moving-average-trendline/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T12:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin started the week on the brink of a downwards crossover of two key moving average trend lines, which could signal an upcoming price drop. The 10-day and 25-day moving average look set to cross, potentially leading to a breakout of the $27,000 level. Ethereum is trading above a floor at $1,830 as of writing.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) is on the brink of registering a downward crossover of its 10-day (red) and 25-day (blue) moving averages.
 
A recent downtrend, which today pushed BTC/USD to an intraday low of $27,192.03, has also led to an overall shift in market momentum.
 
This latest low in bitcoin comes less than a day after the world’s largest cryptocurrency traded at a high of $27,979.98.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Overall, BTC is trading over 7% lower than at the same point last week, when the price was above $30,000.
 
In addition to the potential crossover of moving averages, the 14-day relative strength index (RSI) continues to hover close to a floor at 42.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 44.11, with BTC trading at $27,550.00.
 
 
Ethereum
 
In addition to BTC, ethereum (ETH) also started the week in the red, with prices hovering close to a key point of support.
 
Following a high of $1,888.19 on Sunday, ETH/USD slipped to an intraday low of $1,831.16 earlier in today’s session.
 
As a result of this move, ethereum fell close to its long-term price floor at $1,830, however bulls have so far rejected a breakout.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 
One of the reasons that a break has yet to occur seems to be due to the RSI, which continues to trend above support at 44.00
 
Price strength is now tracking at 45.58, with a ceiling at 52.00 a potential target for bulls hopeful of recapturing the $1,900 mark.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Could ethereum move above $1,900 this week? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT Thrives In Market Cap Growth, But Theft Risks Grow With Scams On The Rise]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e160240</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/usdt-theft-risks-grow/"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T12:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USDT, the largest stablecoin in the crypto market, is once again approaching its all-time high market capitalization of $82 billion, which it briefly touched during the collapse of LUNA last year. 
 
However, despite its current dominance, Tether’s stablecoin is not invulnerable to external threats, such as the possibility of theft, which could disrupt the market and impact the coin’s value.
 
Where is USDT headed next? Despite its recent return to almost all-time high market capitalization levels, there is still uncertainty about what the future holds for Tether’s stablecoin. 
 
 
USDT Treasury Composition And Market Performance
 
With a current price of $0.999949, USDT has experienced a minor 0.03% decline in the past 24 hours. To support the value of its stablecoin, Tether maintains a w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art Of The Orange Pill: Lessons On Pitching Bitcoin From A Third-Generation Salesman]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e16529b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/how-to-pitch-bitcoin-like-a-salesman"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T12:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former sales account manager describes pitching Bitcoin with a focus on influencing perspectives while maintaining honesty and integrity.
 
         
         
         
         
    
This is an opinion editorial by Source Node, a former sales account manager with a background in training and industrial-organizational psychology.
When I pitch Bitcoin to a relative, to a friend or to a complete stranger in the bathroom stall next to me, they will inevitably ask, "How is this benefiting you? Are you going to make money from me buying bitcoin?" 
In one sense, the honest answer is yes, but my main objective is actually to alleviate suffering. 
Will any single investor buying bitcoin make my bitcoin increase in value? Not unless I'm convincing a hyper-rich communist sympathizer like Charlie …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Source Node</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Seized Bitcoin Stack Could Be Bulgaria's Golden Ticket]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e751e165288</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/the-future-for-bulgaria-seized-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T12:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After seizing 213,000 bitcoin in 2017, Bulgaria now has an opportunity to become one of the wealthiest countries on earth.
 
         
         
         
         
    
This is an opinion editorial by Ahmed Botan, a marketing professional with a focus on Bitcoin-based projects.
Bulgaria, a small country located in Southeast Europe, nestled between Romania and Greece, is set to become one of the wealthiest countries in the world. 
The reason for this is its possession of 213,000 bitcoin, which its authorities seized from a group they labeled as criminals in 2017. According to the South East European Law Enforcement Center (SELC), the group hacked the Bulgarian customs agency’s computers and made changes to the system so that their partner companies could import goods while avoiding paying …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahmed Botan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin 'Frenzy' Cools As Dogecoin, PEPE Slip]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137655</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137655/memecoin-phenomenon-cools-as-dogecoin-pepe-slip"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T12:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wider market conditions have brought memecoins down to Earth over the past week, after a 'frenzy' of trading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFTs Come to Portfolio App Floor Amid Mad Lads Boom]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137634</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137634/solana-nfts-come-to-portfolio-app-floor-amid-mad-lads-boom"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Floor app will soon support Solana NFTs, with the feature debuting right after Solana’s buzziest mint in months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grimes Offers 50% Royalties on AI-Generated Music Using Her Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137649</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137649/grimes-offers-50-royalties-on-ai-generated-music-using-her-voice"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T10:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grimes likes the idea of "open sourcing all art and killing copyright" and has given creators permission to machine-generate her voice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Regulator Considers ‘Fast-Track’ to MiCA For Registered Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137648</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137648/french-regulator-considers-fast-track-to-mica-for-registered-firms"/>
        <updated>2023-04-24T10:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Markets in Crypto Assets law will ‘increase the competitiveness’ of French and European crypto businesses, the AMF said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trust Wallet Fixed Vulnerability But Warns $88,000 of User Funds Are Still at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137627/trust-wallet-vulnerability-fix-refund-88000-funds-still-at-risk"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T21:53:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Binance-backed crypto wallet project said hacks are still possible for users with older accounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Chinese Government Employees Will Be Paid in Digital Yuan: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137622</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137622/cbdc-salary-china-chinese-workers-digital-yuan-renminbi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T19:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public sector workers in the Chinese City of Changshu are the latest to be enlisted in China’s CBDC rollout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Normies Don’t 'Actually Care About Decentralization': Arthur Hayes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137619</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137619/average-person-doesnt-care-about-decentralization-centralization-arthur-hayes"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T18:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former BitMEX CEO says ease of use is more important to the average crypto user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Tom Emmer Grilling Gensler Goes Viral, US and EU Regulators Make Moves]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137603</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137603/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-tom-emmer-gary-gensler-mica-uk-souljaboy"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T18:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soulja Boy’s history of shilling crypto scams was brought to light this week by one crypto sleuth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Twitter Alternatives Bluesky and Nostr Are Growing, With Some Growing Pains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137589/decentralized-twitter-alternatives-bluesky-and-nostr-are-growing-with-some-growing-pains"/>
        <updated>2023-04-23T05:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early adopters are rejoicing in brand new social spaces, but wrestling with establishing new norms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Ape Creator Yuga Labs Claims 'Landmark Legal Victory' Over Copycat NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137577/bored-ape-creator-yuga-labs-claims-landmark-legal-victory-over-copycat-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T21:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga Labs declares victory over "scammers and counterfeiters" after winning a key legal battle over a Bored Ape Yacht Club copycat project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bored Apes, CryptoPunks Fall Below $100K as NFT Momentum Stalls]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137545/bored-apes-cryptopunks-fall-below-100k-nft-momentum-stalls"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T17:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Blue chip” NFT projects are losing value as some trading metrics across NFT marketplaces fell to nearly two-year lows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Market Slumps as Bitcoin and Ethereum Drop Over 10%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137574</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137574/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-ethereum-crash-bittrex-sec-gensler-hearings"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T17:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markets were cautious this week as regulators continued the debate over crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Copy Michael Saylor and Create Your Own Bitcoin Lightning Email Address]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137557</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137557/how-michael-saylor-create-bitcoin-lightning-email-address"/>
        <updated>2023-04-22T15:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wanna know how Saylor was able to start sending Bitcoin payments to his email address? Just follow these easy steps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Twitter Is All Good Vibes Again—On Bluesky]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137520</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137520/nft-twitter-all-good-vibes-again-bluesky"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T23:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buzzy Twitter rival Bluesky is attracting prominent Web3 creators, artists, and collectors, some of whom are praising its early atmosphere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson,Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scammers Used AI to Create Fake CEO, Regulators Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137519</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137519/crypto-scammers-used-ai-create-fake-ceo-regulators-say"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T23:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California regulators are stamping out alleged AI-tinged crypto scams—including a firm that supposedly generated a fake CEO for YouTube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Trades Soar as Pepe Mania Grips Meme Coin Market]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137509/uniswap-trades-soar-pepe-mania-meme-coin"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T22:27:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transactions on the decentralized exchange have spiked by more than 66% from the previous all-time high, according to a Uniswap researcher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes: Market Makers Knew They’d Be Front-Run on FTX—It Was 'Common Knowledge']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137506</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137506/arthur-hayes-market-makers-ftx-front-running"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T21:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BitMEX founder Arthur Hayes claims that "market makers did not want to trade on FTX," suggesting pro traders always knew the exchange was "a little bit shady."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto VC Funding Down 82% Compared to Last Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137503</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137503/crypto-vc-funding-down-82-percent"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T20:03:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The evaporating funding means "a lot of companies are doing their down rounds," said the founder of Delta Blockchain Fund.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Nation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves Nearly $8M After 10 Years of Inactivity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137493</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137493/bitcoin-whale-moves-nearly-8m-after-10-years-inactivity"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T18:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A holder who hadn’t touched their crypto for a decade just moved over 279 BTC, or $7.8 million worth of the crypto, to new wallets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas ‘Proof of Reserves’ Bill Passes House of Representatives]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137482</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137482/texas-proof-of-reserves-bill-passes-house-of-representatives"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T16:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill would require cryptocurrency exchanges to maintain reserves ‘in an amount sufficient to fulfill all obligations to customers.’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Bluesky? The Twitter Alternative With Promising Networking Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137463</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-bluesky-the-twitter-alternative-with-promising-networking-technology"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T13:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Bluesky seems like Twitter on the surface, the AT protocol architecture it is run on — and the functionality it enables — have the potential to be revolutionary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Euny Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Correction: Rewarded.tv Has No Channel With Rhett &#038; Link, Deal Was Misrepresented]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137442</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137442/youtube-stars-rhett-link-launch-web3-channel-with-token-rewards"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The channel was reportedly available on the service via syndication, but then pulled by Mythical once the news came to light.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Warns Advisers to Apply 'Heightened Scrutiny' When Recommending Crypto Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137461</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137461/sec-warns-advisers-to-apply-heightened-scrutiny-when-recommending-crypto-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T12:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting retail investors, including those seeking exposure to cryptocurrencies, remains a priority for the SEC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Now Measures Network Carbon Emissions Data in Real Time]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137441</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137441/solana-now-measures-network-carbon-emissions-data-in-real-time"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T12:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana Foundation claims that it is the first "major smart contract blockchain network" to broadcast its environmental impact as such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Merges AI Teams Under DeepMind Banner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137448</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137448/google-merges-ai-teams-under-deepmind-banner"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T11:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google parent company Alphabet is bringing its Brain and DeepMind AI teams under one roof with the launch of Google DeepMind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops to $28,000 as Macro Pressures Bite]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137449</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137449/bitcoin-drops-to-28000-as-marco-pressures-bite"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T10:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto market’s negative streak continued as prices dipped for a third consecutive day, with Bitcoin briefly slipping below $28,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Has Most Americans Scared About Privacy, Job Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137421</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137421/ai-has-most-americans-scared-about-privacy-job-losses"/>
        <updated>2023-04-21T01:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using AI is one thing, but having AI being used on you—when your job could be on the line—is another.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F1 Legend Michael Schumacher’s Family Threatens Lawsuit Over Faked AI Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137415</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137415/f1-legend-michael-schumachers-family-threatens-lawsuit-faked-ai-interview"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A German magazine promoted an exclusive interview with seven-time Formula 1 champion Michael Schumacher—but it was an AI-based fake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mining Pools Will Have Less Power With This Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137402</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137402/bitcoin-mining-pools-less-power-upgrade"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T22:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stratum v2 aims to change a key feature in the way Bitcoin mining is done, making it much harder for mining pools to collectively censor transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyssa Hertig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Monkey Business IP Acquired by DAO of NFT Holders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137393</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137393/solana-monkey-business-ip-acquired-dao-nft-holders"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T21:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent NFT project Solana Monkey Business is now owned by the independent collective of holders that formed around it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PUBG Creator to Launch NFT Metaverse Game This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137387</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137387/pubg-creator-to-launch-nft-metaverse-game-this-year"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T18:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Krafton, the studio behind the smash battle royale game PUBG, said that its metaverse gaming platform will launch in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CryptoPunks NFT in Centre Pompidou ‘Quite a Surprise’: Larva Labs Co-Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137094</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137094/quite-surprise-seeing-cryptopunks-nft-pompidou-larva-labs-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world-renowned art museum in Paris has made special room for the emerging NFT space, adding a exhibition of blockchain-related art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Leads Meme Coin Rally With Pepe and Baby Doge]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137372</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137372/dogecoin-surges-over-the-week-bringing-meme-coin-market-with-it-as-bitcoin-slumps"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:16:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is on a run this week—and so its meme coin compatriots, PEPE and BABYDOGE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Print Is Dead? Why NFT Platform Zora Is Launching a Magazine]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137327/print-is-dead-why-nft-platform-zora-is-launching-a-magazine"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T16:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only 2,500 copies of Print Issue 001 will be published, made redeemable via collectible NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Receives Bermuda License, Outlines Global Expansion Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137367</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137367/coinbase-receives-bermuda-license-outlines-global-expansion-plans"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T14:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The exchange is also in talks with Abu Dhabi Global Market regulators about opening a regulated exchange there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Arthur Hayes Says Crypto Failures Are A Sign of The System Cleansing Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZHyccGKp/gm-arthur-hayes-says-crypto-failures-are-a-sign-of-the-system-cleansing-itself</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ZHyccGKp/gm-arthur-hayes-says-crypto-failures-are-a-sign-of-the-system-cleansing-itself"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T13:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur Hayes says the speed at which projects like Terra grow and implode is a feature of the crypto industry, not a bug. He founded crypto exchange Bitmex in 2014 and then became the original crypto bad boy. In 2021 the DOJ charged him in with violating the U.S. Bank Secrecy Act for not implementing an anti-money laundering program at Bitmex. He plead guilty and was sentenced to two years probation and six months of home detention. In fact, he was still sporting an ankle bracelet on a recent cover of New York Magazine. Now he's living in Singapore, offering up his views on the crypto industry with long form, meme-filled essays, and still thinks the crypto industry will save investors from what he calls a broken banking system. "I don't care if you're capitalist or you're a communist. Everybody put on a lot of debt. We've passed the point where that debt is becoming useful," he said. "And therefore everyone is going to take an L unless they get some crypto or some gold—some hard asset that's outside of the traditional banking system."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch Court Agrees to Free Tornado Cash Dev Alex Pertsev Pending Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=137355</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/137355/dutch-court-agrees-to-free-tornado-cash-dev-alex-pertsev-pending-trial"/>
        <updated>2023-04-20T13:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developer of coin mixer Tornado Cash, Alex Pertsev, is set to be released on bail after nine months in detention without a trial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent on Web3 Games and the Problem with 'NFT Value']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/P97zCeID/brycent-on-web3-games-and-the-problem-with-nft-value"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T22:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET gamer and content creator Brycent tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the problem with gaming NFTs—and what needs to happen instead in the next generation of Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brycent on Meeting Gary Vaynerchuk through Web3 Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xL8pz64R/brycent-on-meeting-gary-vaynerchuk-through-web3-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xL8pz64R/brycent-on-meeting-gary-vaynerchuk-through-web3-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-04-19T22:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XSET gamer and content creator Brycent tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how entrepreneur and VeeFriends creator Gary Vaynerchuk first reached out to him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Anthony Scaramucci Is More Bullish on Bitcoin Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/PqLOXL47/gm-anthony-scaramucci-is-more-bullish-on-bitcoin-than-ever"/>
        <updated>2023-04-13T18:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anthony Scaramucci of hedge fund SkyBridge Capital got burned by Sam Bankman-Fried: he co-hosted SALT conferences with FTX and sold a 30% stake in SkyBridge to FTX Ventures. And yet "The Mooch" tells Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott "I'm more bullish now than I have ever been" on crypto as an investment case. He discusses his frustration with SBF, how wrong he thinks politicians like Elizabeth Warren and Gary Gensler are about crypto and how to regulate it, what he sees happening next with adoption, and talks about Trump. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer: The Problem With SEC's Howey Test Isn't Its Age]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal discussed the "Howey Test," which the SEC uses as its yard stick for whether a crypto asset should be regulated as a security, and told Decrypt's Stacy Elliott and Dan Roberts the issue with it isn't that it's old (the case is from 1946) but how it's being applied to modern technology. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures Plots Its Next Web3 Grant for Filmmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Matchett from Web3 film funding platform Decentralized Pictures tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about DCP's just announced iPhone Filmmaking Initiative, which will support aspiring filmmakers who create a short film on their iPhones, and will be determined via DCP's crypto-native on-chain voting system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kevin Owocki Wants to Regenerate DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, DeFi—ReFi is coming? Gitcoin founder Kevin Owocki has stepped away from DeFi grant-giving machine Gitcoin as it fully decentralizes and is now focused on regenerative finance (huh?) and ReFi incubator Supermodular. He aims to "regenerate the regenerators." He explained it all to Dan Roberts and Liam Kelly, and also talks DAO structure, crypto factions, NFT use cases, his book "Greenpilled," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aurory's Head of Production Left Ubisoft for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory executive producer and head of production Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about how the first-generation of Web3 games came out of DeFi and are now evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Really Do the Corporate Thing Very Well' Says Jason Brink on Gala Games Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With roughly 50 video games in its pipeline, Gala Games is all-in on Web3. Gala's President of Blockchain Jason Brink told Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about the studio's ethos and weighs in on the different approaches to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Coinbase's Top Lawyer Gets Real on SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal is the Chief Legal Officer at Coinbase and a former U.S. magistrate judge in Northern California. He gave Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott his candid takes on Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX, the SEC's crackdown on staking, the sanctioning of Tornado Cash, and more alpha on how Coinbase is approaching the current unfriendly US regulatory environment. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>