<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-02-06T19:12:12.849Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-02-06T19:12:12.849Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchanges Face Security Challenge With New AI-Generated Service]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efed5970</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-face-security-challenge-ai-generated-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T19:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent reports have shown the surge in popularity of Artificial Intelligence (AI) generated technology, which could present a significant challenge for crypto exchanges and the community in the never-ending battle against scams and illicit activity.
 
 
Can AI-Generated IDs Bypass Exchanges Verification Processes?
 
An underground website named OnlyFake has gained popularity for its realistic AI-generated fake ID services. The website, as reported by 404 Media, claims to use “neural networks” to generate convincing photos of fake IDs for $15. The investigation led by Joseph Cox, 404 Media co-founder, details the process of creating these fake documents.
 
The creation of the fake ID is done within minutes, and the service offers a variety of documents to choose from, including passports an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rubmar Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Triggers Jump for Solana-Based Altcoin After Placing it on Listing Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233103/Coinbase-Triggers-Jump-for-Solana-Based-Altcoin-After-Placing-it-on-Listing-Roadmap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233103/Coinbase-Triggers-Jump-for-Solana-Based-Altcoin-After-Placing-it-on-Listing-Roadmap"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T19:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top US-based crypto exchange Coinbase is potentially preparing to list a Solana-based (SOL) decentralized wireless provider, catalyzing a price spike for the network’s native altcoin. In a new announcement, Coinbase says it’s listing Helium Mobile (MOBILE) to its listing roadmap, which alerts...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Shiba Inu’s BONE Harnesses Liquid Staking on Shibarium]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233101/How-Shiba-Inus-BONE-Harnesses-Liquid-Staking-on-Shibarium</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233101/How-Shiba-Inus-BONE-Harnesses-Liquid-Staking-on-Shibarium"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[K9 and SHIB shake their paws to embark on a mutual mission to bring dynamic staking to Shibarians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchanges Face Security Challenge With New AI-Generated Service]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233094/Crypto-Exchanges-Face-Security-Challenge-With-New-AI-Generated-Service</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233094/Crypto-Exchanges-Face-Security-Challenge-With-New-AI-Generated-Service"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T19:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent reports have shown the surge in popularity of Artificial Intelligence (AI) generated technology, which could present a significant challenge for crypto exchanges and the community in the never-ending battle against scams and illicit activity. Related Reading: CFTC Issues Warning On...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whale Rapidly Accumulating Chainlink: What’s Going On With LINK?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233082/Whale-Rapidly-Accumulating-Chainlink-Whats-Going-On-With-LINK</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233082/Whale-Rapidly-Accumulating-Chainlink-Whats-Going-On-With-LINK"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T19:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mysterious whale is rapidly accumulating Chainlink (LINK). According to Lookonchain, the unknown entity, possibly an institution, withdrew over 2.2 million LINK (worth $42.38 million) via 47 new wallets from Binance, the world’s largest crypto exchange by trading volume, in two days. This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surprising Bitcoin Remarks from FED Member Kashkari: “It Turns Out to Be a Terrible Hedge Against Inflation”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233087/Surprising-Bitcoin-Remarks-from-FED-Member-Kashkari-It-Turns-Out-to-Be-a-Terrible-Hedge-Against-Inflation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233087/Surprising-Bitcoin-Remarks-from-FED-Member-Kashkari-It-Turns-Out-to-Be-a-Terrible-Hedge-Against-Inflation"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his statement, FED Member Kashkari described Bitcoin as 'another risky asset' and argued that it could not protect it from inflation. Continue Reading: Surprising Bitcoin Remarks from FED Member Kashkari: “It Turns Out to Be a Terrible Hedge Against Inflation”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Era Of Infrastructure: The Rise Of DePIN]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233098/A-New-Era-Of-Infrastructure-The-Rise-Of-DePIN</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233098/A-New-Era-Of-Infrastructure-The-Rise-Of-DePIN"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emergence of Decentralized Physical Infrastructure Networks (DePIN) marks a revolutionary shift in the way physical infrastructures are conceptualized, built, and operated. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DYM surges 40% following distribution to over one million users]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233073/DYM-surges-40-following-distribution-to-over-one-million-users</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233073/DYM-surges-40-following-distribution-to-over-one-million-users"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[App-chain infrastructure Dymension released its mainnet today, opening the claim period for its native token, the DYM. Two hours after its debut, the token jumped 40% after being listed on major centralized exchanges, such as Binance.Over one million addresses qualified for the airdrop of 70...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Crypto Gainers Today on Uniswap – AZR, YES, PANDORA]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233072/Biggest-Crypto-Gainers-Today-on-Uniswap-AZR-YES-PANDORA</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233072/Biggest-Crypto-Gainers-Today-on-Uniswap-AZR-YES-PANDORA"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conditions in blue-chip cryptocurrency markets are tepid on Tuesday, with major names largely within recent ranges, but the biggest crypto gainers today on Uniswap keep pumping. Bitcoin (BTC) was last up 1% in 24 hours, as per CoinMarketCap, and trading to the north of $43,000. Ether (ETH),...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero Suffers Binance Delisting as Crypto Titan Cracks Down]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233049/Monero-Suffers-Binance-Delisting-as-Crypto-Titan-Cracks-Down</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233049/Monero-Suffers-Binance-Delisting-as-Crypto-Titan-Cracks-Down"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The untraceable Monero blockchain gets torn apart by the crypto bears after Binance dropped XMR.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero’s Market Plummets 32% as Binance Announces Delisting, Sparking XMR’s Turbulence]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efe99a53</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/moneros-market-plummets-32-as-binance-announces-delisting-sparking-xmrs-turbulence/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leading privacy-focused cryptocurrency by market valuation, monero, experienced a sharp 32% decline within the last day after news broke that Binance intends to remove the coin from its platform. Citing non-compliance with its listing criteria, Binance announced that monero, along with three other cryptocurrencies, will be taken off its exchange on Feb. 20, 2024.
 
Monero Faces 32% Value Slash as Binance Cuts Ties With Privacy Coin
 
Monero (XMR) will soon vanish from the roster of the globe’s leading cryptocurrency exchange by trade volume, as confirmed by a company announcement on Tuesday. Binance’s list for removal also includes ANT, MULTI, and VAI, all scheduled for delisting on the same date, Feb. 20, 2024. Consequently, Binance will cease trading for pairs including XMR/BNB, XMR/…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Stocks Poised to Soar if China Turns its Economy Around]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233054/Three-Stocks-Poised-to-Soar-if-China-Turns-its-Economy-Around</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233054/Three-Stocks-Poised-to-Soar-if-China-Turns-its-Economy-Around"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a 3-year slump, first signs of a rally appear for China's stocks but which ones stand to gain the most from a revival?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BREAKING:  SEC Delays Invesco & Galaxy Spot Ethereum ETF Application]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233047/BREAKING-SEC-Delays-Invesco-Galaxy-Spot-Ethereum-ETF-Application</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233047/BREAKING-SEC-Delays-Invesco-Galaxy-Spot-Ethereum-ETF-Application"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Misunderstanding: What MiCA Really Means for Stablecoins in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233055/The-Big-Misunderstanding-What-MiCA-Really-Means-for-Stablecoins-in-Europe</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233055/The-Big-Misunderstanding-What-MiCA-Really-Means-for-Stablecoins-in-Europe"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI network Bittensor’s crypto token is up more than 90% as market cap hits $3 billion]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233035/AI-network-Bittensors-crypto-token-is-up-more-than-90-as-market-cap-hits-3-billion</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233035/AI-network-Bittensors-crypto-token-is-up-more-than-90-as-market-cap-hits-3-billion"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum founder Vitalek Buterin's apparent praise for Bittensor preceded the network's token passing $500 at one point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask and Robinhood join forces to enable in-wallet crypto purchases]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233025/MetaMask-and-Robinhood-join-forces-to-enable-in-wallet-crypto-purchases</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233025/MetaMask-and-Robinhood-join-forces-to-enable-in-wallet-crypto-purchases"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Rogan Has HODL’d Over 5 Bitcoin For Almost A Decade]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233026/Joe-Rogan-Has-HODLd-Over-5-Bitcoin-For-Almost-A-Decade</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233026/Joe-Rogan-Has-HODLd-Over-5-Bitcoin-For-Almost-A-Decade"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Famous podcaster Joe Rogan has held onto his Bitcoin (BTC) stash without selling any, as revealed by on-chain data dating back nearly a decade. Back in 2014, the mixed martial arts (MMA) commentator shared a QR code version of his public Bitcoin address over social media. Revisiting that same...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s volatility impact on merchant acceptance in El Salvador]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233058/Bitcoins-volatility-impact-on-merchant-acceptance-in-El-Salvador</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233058/Bitcoins-volatility-impact-on-merchant-acceptance-in-El-Salvador"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC adopts rule to have stricter oversight over dealers, looping in crypto and DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233018/SEC-adopts-rule-to-have-stricter-oversight-over-dealers-looping-in-crypto-and-DeFi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233018/SEC-adopts-rule-to-have-stricter-oversight-over-dealers-looping-in-crypto-and-DeFi"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short squeeze alert for February: Two cryptocurrencies about to skyrocket]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233003/Short-squeeze-alert-for-February-Two-cryptocurrencies-about-to-skyrocket</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19233003/Short-squeeze-alert-for-February-Two-cryptocurrencies-about-to-skyrocket"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing DeFi: Equalizer Introduces New Meta Aggregator and Airdrop Explorer Services]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efd62c1a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/enhancing-defi-equalizer-introduces-new-meta-aggregator-and-airdrop-explorer-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Road Town, British Virgin Islands, February 6th, 2024, Chainwire.
 
Equalizer Elevates Their DeFi Platform with Launch of DEX & Bridge Aggregator and Airdrop Explorer Features
 
In a significant leap forward for decentralized finance, Equalizer is proud to announce the launch of two innovative services: a Meta Aggregator and an Airdrop Explorer. These additions, combined with the platform’s existing Flash Loans service, cement Equalizer’s position as a multi-service player in the DeFi space.
 
Meta Aggregator: A One-Stop DeFi Solution
 
The Meta Aggregator is a multi-chain decentralized exchange (DEX) and a cross-chain bridge for top blockchain networks, enabling users to swap any token seamlessly with a single click. This service also features a unique gas function, assisti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Bitcoin Miner Blasts EIA’s Emergency Directive A Political Ploy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efd62171</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-bitcoin-miner-eia-directive-political-ploy/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a series of statements on X, Brian Morgenstern, Head of Public Policy at Riot Platforms Inc, the second-largest Bitcoin miner in the United States by market capitalization, has openly criticized the US Energy Information Administration’s (EIA) new mandate to collect data on energy usage by miners. This directive, which stems from a White House initiative, is part of a broader effort to understand the growing electricity demands and environmental impacts of the Bitcoin mining industry.
 
A Political Ploy Against Bitcoin
 
Morgenstern’s remarks suggest a deep-seated belief that the directive is less about environmental concern and more a politically motivated attack on the Bitcoin and crypto sector. Via X, he argues that the mandate is an indirect result of recommendations from the White …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankruptcy Was Crypto Winter’s Circuit Breaker]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efd64f7a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2024/02/06/bankruptcy-was-crypto-winters-circuit-breaker/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Societies have often frowned on bankruptcy, viewing it in moral terms as a breach of trust. But, in the wake of 2022's scandals, the process helped relaunch the crypto industry, says Michael Casey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael J. Casey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Crypto to Buy Now February 6 – Dymension, Ethereum Name Services, Pendle]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19232981/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-February-6-Dymension-Ethereum-Name-Services-Pendle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19232981/Best-Crypto-to-Buy-Now-February-6-Dymension-Ethereum-Name-Services-Pendle"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major cryptocurrencies are nudging higher on Tuesday but remain largely within recent ranges as investors monitor fresh commentary from Fed policymakers, who continue to hint at rate cuts later this year so long as inflation keeps easing, while Dymension (DYM), Ethereum Name Service (ENS) and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polkadot NFT Mint Breaks Records, Surpasses Solana, Polygon]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19232982/Polkadot-NFT-Mint-Breaks-Records-Surpasses-Solana-Polygon</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19232982/Polkadot-NFT-Mint-Breaks-Records-Surpasses-Solana-Polygon"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tokenized, Inc: BlackRock's Plan To Own The Fractionalized World]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efd79711</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/tokenized-inc-blackrocks-plan-to-own-the-fractionalized-world-"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T18:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just one day after the January 11 approval of 11 Bitcoin spot ETFs – including BlackRock’s iShares Bitcoin Trust (IBIT) – by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, BlackRock Chair and CEO Larry Fink sat down with Bloomberg's David Westin to discuss the implications of the world's largest asset manager entering the Bitcoin market. Not one to mince words, Fink articulated a clear framework for his company's approach to Bitcoin, and furthermore for BlackRock's intention to replicate similar ETF products for other assets. “If we can 'ETF' a Bitcoin, imagine what we can do with all financial instruments.” Fink continued, speaking about Bitcoin itself, stating “I don’t believe it’s ever going to be a currency. I believe it’s an asset class.”
Bitcoin: Commodity, Not Currency
While the Black…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Goodwin,Whitney Webb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter Rival Bluesky Opens to Public Right as Farcaster Gains Steam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=216106</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/216106/twiter-rival-bluesky-opens-public-farcaster"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bluesky, a decentralized social media platform, has gained 3 million users since it launched in beta last March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cleanspark Expands Bitcoin Mining Operations to Mississippi With $19.8 Million Acquisition]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efd2fa44</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cleanspark-expands-bitcoin-mining-operations-to-mississippi-with-19-8-million-acquisition/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The publicly traded bitcoin mining entity Cleanspark has unveiled plans to broaden its operational footprint into Mississippi through the purchase of three fully operational bitcoin mining sites in the area. Alongside these Mississippi locations, the firm also secured a site in Dalton, Georgia, which is in the midst of construction.
 
Nasdaq Traded Bitcoin Miner Cleanspark Expands Footprint
 
On Tuesday, Cleanspark (Nasdaq: CLSK) revealed its Mississippi expansion strategy, having completed a purchase agreement for three fully equipped bitcoin mining facilities, shelling out $19.8 million in cash. Cleanspark shared that these Mississippi data centers will contribute approximately 2.4 exahash per second (EH/s) to the firm’s total mining capabilities.
 
Furthermore, the company has acquired …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Recovery: Blockchain Restored Within 5 Hours After Shutdown]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efd2f200</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-blockchain-back-online/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the early hours of Tuesday, Solana (SOL) encountered a significant outage, adding to the growing list of incidents it has faced in the past 24 months. 
 
As reported by our sister website NewsBTC, the mainnet-beta of Solana experienced a nearly 5-hour disruption, which raised concerns within the cryptocurrency community. 
 
The incident was initially detected when block explorers Solscan and OKLink indicated a lack of new transactions on the network. The ongoing disruption prompted South Korean crypto exchange Upbit to suspend deposits and withdrawals for SOL and several other tokens.
 
Solana Blockchain Upgraded And Restarted
 
Solana’s team acknowledged the outage through an incident report, confirming the disruption but refraining from disclosing specific details about its cause.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Holders Fall Deeper Into Losses, Here’s How Many Holders Are In The Red]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efdf630b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-in-the-red/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data from IntoTheBlock has revealed an interesting dynamic among Shiba Inu holders. According to the on-chain analytics platform, 68% of SHIB holders are currently at a loss as the crypto continues to fail to register price growth in the early months of the year. Price action shows SHIB is currently trading at $0.000008918 and has been perambulating around the $0.000009 price level for the past week.
 
Shiba Inu Holder Profitability Percentages
 
The Shiba Inu community has grown exponentially from its days as an ordinary meme coin, with its team constantly working to elevate the SHIB token’s status. The crypto now has its own fully-fledged ecosystem with a layer-2 scaling solution and other tokens. Consequently, Shiba Inu has drawn in investors from all corners of the crypto market to for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury Secretary Yellen Says U.S. Needs Better Stablecoin Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efd8c396</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/02/06/treasury-secretary-yellen-says-us-needs-better-stablecoin-regulation/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["A federal regulator should have the ability to decide if a stablecoin issuer should be barred from issuing such an asset," she told lawmakers on Tuesday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Halving Nears and BTC Miner CleanSpark Is Preparing for Lower Fees]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=216101</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/216101/bitcoin-halving-nears-and-btc-miner-cleanspark-is-preparing-for-lower-fees"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new acquisitions will bump up CleanSpark's Bitcoin mining capacity to 2.4 exahashes per second, says the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farcaster Explained: The Blockchain-Powered Decentralized Social Media Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=216096</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/farcaster-explained-the-blockchain-powered-decentralized-social-media-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Farcaster leverages blockchain technology to provide a framework on which multiple social media apps can be built.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilan Hazan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood Adds MetaMask for Easier Ethereum Buys]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=216091</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/216091/robinhood-metamask-crypto-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration aims to make buying digital coins and tokens a seamless experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Mean 'Substitution' From Gold Into BTC Will Continue, Says Cathie Wood]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efc4f0f0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/02/06/bitcoin-etfs-mean-substitution-from-gold-into-btc-will-continue-says-cathie-wood/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:37:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While bitcoin's price is often denominated against fiat currencies, Wood pointed out that even relative to gold, BTC has risen consistently since its early days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Rebounds as Network Restarts After Outage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=216095</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/216095/solana-price-rebounds-network-restarts-after-outage"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana network was down almost five hours before a software patch brought it back online, marking the first major outage in nearly a year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citrea Launches First ZK Rollup on Bitcoin, Enhancing Blockspace Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efc5ed01</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/citrea-launches-first-zk-rollup-on-bitcoin-enhancing-blockspace-capabilities"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Citrea Team unveils Citrea, the inaugural ZK Rollup designed to elevate Bitcoin's blockspace capabilities through zero-knowledge technology. Departing from traditional scalability solutions that move security and demand off-chain, Citrea introduces an approach to scale Bitcoin comprehensively with zero-knowledge proofs, ensuring on-chain verifiability and data availability within the Bitcoin network. This positions Citrea as one of the first scaling solutions to enable more complex applications without compromising Bitcoin's security or altering its consensus rules.
The prevalent issue with creating new blockspace solutions lies in their inability to inherit Bitcoin's fundamental properties of security, decentralization, and censorship resistance. Citrea addresses this challenge by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nik Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Crypto Exchange CEO Gets 7 Years For $8 Million Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efc1fb90</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/south-korean-crypto-exchange-ceo-gets-7-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a blow to the South Korean cryptocurrency industry, the CEO of major exchange Bitsonic, Jinwook Shin, has been sentenced to seven years in prison for operating a sophisticated fraudulent scheme totaling 10 billion won, approximately $7.6 million.
 
Judge Lee Jong-chae of the Seoul Eastern District Court delivered the verdict, finding Shin guilty alongside Bitsonic’s vice president of technology, Bae, who received a one-year prison term. Both were charged with fraud, forgery of business records, and obstruction of business through computer manipulation.
 
 
Inflating Prices, Stealing Deposits
 
The court found that Shin, from January 2019 to May 2021, manipulated trading volumes using Bitsonic’s own funds to inflate the price of its self-issued digital currency, Bitsonic Coin (BSC). Addi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filecoin's Liquid Staker Glif Raises $4.5M, Hints at Token Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efce11ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/02/06/filecoins-liquid-staker-glif-raises-45m-hints-at-token-airdrop/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T15:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glif's "liquid leasing" gives FIL holders a way to earn yield on their assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Faces First Outage of the Year; Engineers Deploy Fix as SOL Dips 3%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efcfb2e9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/solana-faces-first-outage-of-the-year-engineers-deploy-fix-as-sol-dips-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T15:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Solana layer one (L1) blockchain is currently experiencing a service disruption, with the Solana Status website revealing that engineers are actively probing the cause. Validators on mainnet have received instructions to implement an upgrade to version 1.17.20 and to initiate a system reboot.
 
** Editor’s note: Solana Status notes that block production resumed at 14:57 UTC. A final paragraph has been added to reflect the update. 
 
Solana Network Experiences Disruption, Prompting Urgent Upgrade and Reboot
 
Presently grappling with its first outage of the year, Solana has otherwise maintained a 99.8% operational status over the preceding 90 days, notwithstanding the interruption. This setback is part of a series of disruptions that Solana has encountered in 2020, 2021, and 2022, durin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Archaeologists Tap AI to Decipher Ancient Scrolls Nearly Lost to Volcano]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215975</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215975/archaeologists-ai-ancient-scrolls-mount-vesuvius"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T15:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2,000-year-old documents were burnt, brittle, and could not be unrolled. But scientists were finally able to read some of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MetaMask Deal With Robinhood Broadens Crypto Access]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efcbc02a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/02/06/metamask-deal-with-robinhood-broadens-crypto-access/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T15:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-ramps like the one used in this partnership are a key piece of infrastructure serving as a bridge between traditional banking rails and blockchain-based crypto economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Jupiter Airdrop Allegedly Leaked: A User Received Almost $1 Million Using 9,246 Wallets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efb508cc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/solanas-jupiter-airdrop-allegedly-leaked-a-user-received-almost-1-million-using-9246-wallets/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T15:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent airdrop of JUP, the token of the Solana native Jupiter exchange, was allegedly gamed by an individual who avoided established controls. An unknown airdrop hunter received 1.85 million JUP (almost $1 million) using over 9,000 wallets for this task, with some users presuming an insider leaked the airdrop information beforehand.
Jupiter Airdrop Allegedly Leaked by an Insider
Some users have begun to question the fairness of the Jupiter airdrop, an event that distributed over $700 million in JUP tokens to users of the Solana native Jupiter exchange in January. While the airdrop has been recognized as one of the largest in its class, crypto sleuths have detected irregularities in the form in which some approached this event.
X user Open4profit stressed the airdrop was unfair, claimin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HIVE Digital Technologies And Bitcoin Magazine Announce FUD Fighters Educational Initiative]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efb5783a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/press-releases/hive-digital-technologies-and-bitcoin-magazine-announce-fud-fighters-educational-initiative-"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T15:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, February 6, 2024 – HIVE Digital Technologies Ltd (NASDAQ: HIVE) and Bitcoin Magazine announce “FUD Fighters”, a new initiative centered around education on the many false narratives articulated by critics of Bitcoin. The “FUD Fighters” series will consist of four in-depth research articles written by industry experts to counter erroneous, biased and misinformed narratives that seek to mislead the public about Bitcoin. Through this initiative, HIVE and Bitcoin Magazine aim to highlight, through a data-oriented approach, the tangible benefits of this technology, and consequently, to rebuke the unequivocally false reporting from traditional media outlets, pundits and biased researchers. “FUD Fighters” will provide the Bitcoin community with refutations of commonly circulated “FUD” …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin Magazine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Quick Look at Last Month's U.S. Crypto Crime Log]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efb57ebe</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/02/06/a-quick-look-at-last-months-us-crypto-crime-log/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T15:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While our attention was focused on exchange-traded funds earlier this month, federal regulators in the U.S. announced charges or sentences for various crypto parties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhilesh De</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crossover and Ouinex Collaborate for Crypto Market Advancements]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74efb19a74</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crossover-and-ouinex-collaborate-for-crypto-market-advancements/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T14:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ouinex, a crypto trading platform tailored for  
active and professional traders, has announced a strategic alliance with  
Crossover Markets, an institutional trading venue specializing in spot  
cryptocurrencies. The collaboration heralds a milestone within the crypto  
sphere, as Ouinex integrates Crossover's electronic communication network (ECN)  
technology, known as CROSSx.
CROSSx: Reshaping Digital Asset Trading Dynamics
Ilies Larbi, the CEO of Ouinex, expressed enthusiasm  
regarding the partnership: "By partnering with Crossover Markets and  
harnessing their state-of-the-art technology, we are propelling ourselves  
forward in delivering a unique and exceptional trading experience to our  
clients." 
CROSSx, heralded as a revolutionary ECN for  
digital assets, brings unpreceden…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOL Dips 4% Following Solana Network Outage]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=216059</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/216059/sol-dips-solana-network-outage"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T13:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of Solana's SOL token wavered after the network rolled out a software update to validators following a "major outage."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-time AI Chat Translation Comes to Roblox]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215967</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215967/roblox-ai-chat-translation"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new feature instantly translates chat messages between 16 languages, enabling players to connect globally in their native tongues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Arrests Haru Invest Executives Over Alleged $826M Embezzlement]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=216005</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/216005/south-korea-arrests-haru-invest-826m-embezzlement"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T10:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm, which claimed to offer double-digit yields on cryptocurrencies, abruptly shut down user withdrawals in June 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero Drops 17% as Binance Delists XMR]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215981/monero-binance-delists-xmr"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T09:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monero dropped 17% on news that Binance, the largest crypto exchange in the world, will delist it on February 20.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs Are Worthless? Why Gmoney Took Out a $1 Million Loan on His CryptoPunk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215932</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215932/cryptopunks-nft-million-dollar-loan-gmoney-rug-radio"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T02:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gmoney tells Rug Radio’s “FOMO Hour” why he opted to borrow against one of the most recognizable PFPs in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Vision Pro Doesn't Do VR Porn—And Users Are Already Trying to Hack It]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215935</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215935/apple-vision-pro-porn-vr-spatial-immersive-adult-content"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T02:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost every new technology finds early adoption in adult entertainment. Apple's new headset doesn't support immersive porn experiences out of the box—but just wait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ownership Doesn’t Need Blockchain or NFTs, Entertainment Execs Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215930</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215930/ownership-doesnt-need-blockchain-or-nfts-entertainment-execs-say"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T01:35:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At SEG3 Los Angeles, gaming leaders agree on the importance of ownership, but are split on the role of decentralized ledgers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gmoney Took Out a $1 Million Loan on a CryptoPunks NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mIE20tcG/why-gmoney-took-out-a-1-million-loan-on-a-cryptopunks-nft</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mIE20tcG/why-gmoney-took-out-a-1-million-loan-on-a-cryptopunks-nft"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T00:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pseudonymous NFT collector and entrepreneur Gmoney joined Rug Radio's live "FOMO Hour" show to discuss why he took out a $1 million loan on one of the most recognizable CryptoPunks NFTs around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Use Your .Com Domain as Your Ethereum Address With GoDaddy and ENS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215920</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215920/ethereum-name-service-godaddy-website-domains"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T23:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Name Service domains can now be tied to traditional web domains with no fees, adding more functionality in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Says Ripple Must Hand Over Financial Statements to SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215861/judge-says-ripple-must-hand-over-financial-statements-to-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T23:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. judge has sided with the SEC in a demanding Ripple answer questions about institutional sales of XRP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Spent the Weekend With the Apple Vision Pro—My Face May Never Be the Same]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215844/apple-vision-pro-headset-review"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T22:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Apple Vision Pro really worth $3,500 or more? I spent the weekend with a computer strapped to my face to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum's Vitalik Buterin Praises Farcaster, Disses Friend.Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215893</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215893/ethereum-vitalik-buterin-farcaster-friend-tech"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T22:21:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ethereum co-founder appears big on Farcaster, a decentralized social media network making waves in crypto.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Makes It Easier to Launch Crypto Games With Built-In NFT Shops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215855</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215855/solana-games-gameshift-tensor-nft-marketplaces"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T21:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana gaming toolkit GameShift is now available broadly with new features like in-game Tensor marketplaces and support for other NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Farcaster and Why Is Crypto So Excited About the Twitter Alternative?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215856/what-is-farcaster-ethereum-crypto-twitter-alternative"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T20:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized social media protocol Farcaster exploded in popularity recently after launching a powerful new feature. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Future: 5 Mind-Blowing Uses of the Apple Vision Pro]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215830</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215830/apple-vision-pro-5-mind-blowing-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Vision Pro isn’t cheap, but this headset has immense potential. Here are some of the early standout experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Power Law: A Mathematical Approach to Predicting Bitcoin's Price]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215807</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/the-bitcoin-power-law-a-mathematical-approach-to-predicting-bitcoins-price"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T18:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former physics professor claims to have developed a model that maps Bitcoin's long-term price. Here's how it (purportedly) works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilan Hazan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Flat, But There Could Be Turbulence on the Horizon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215782</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215782/bitcoin-price-flat-turbulence-on-horizon"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T17:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC and ETH have barely moved over the past day—but there could be some turbulence on the horizon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Hunger Games: Explained in One Minute or Less]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/9R1qQMVk/solana-hunger-games-explained-in-one-minute-or-less</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/9R1qQMVk/solana-hunger-games-explained-in-one-minute-or-less"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T16:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer AshleyDCan explains the latest sensation taking over timelines on Crypto Twitter, Solana Hunger Games. The new "crypto AR" game from GG.zip is backed by Delphi and plans to launch in the spring. Here's what going on, explained in one minute or less.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Put BlackRock and Fidelity Among January's Top 10 ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215730</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215730/bitcoin-etfs-blackrock-fidelity-top-10"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T14:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock and Fidelity's spot Bitcoin ETFs landed in the top 10 ETFs by net asset flows in January, according to a Morningstar report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform Labs Former CFO Extradited From Montenegro to South Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215744</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215744/terraform-labs-cfo-extradited-south-korea"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T13:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Terraform Labs CFO Han Chang-joon faces charges in South Korea including fraud that could carry a life sentence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Regulator Plans to Meet SEC Chair Gensler, Discuss Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215729/south-korea-regulator-plans-to-meet-sec-chair-gensler-discuss-bitcoin-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T13:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The governor of South Korea's FSS plans to meet with SEC chair Gary Gensler to discuss the "important" subject of spot Bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Champion Nayib Bukele Clinches Re-election in El Salvador]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=215712</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/215712/bitcoin-champion-nayib-bukele-clinches-reelection-in-el-salvador"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T10:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador President Nayib Bukele, who made Bitcoin legal tender  in 2021, has secured a second 5-year term according to exit polls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game On: The Hottest Upcoming Gaming Token Airdrops]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=211029</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/211029/game-on-hottest-upcoming-gaming-token-airdrops"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T20:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: The Heroes of Mavia airdrop is coming this week, with Portal, Pixels, Saga, WUFFI, and other gaming drops still on the horizon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Questions With SCENE: Gala Marija Vrbanic]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UcfnncpU/5-questions-with-scene-gala-marija-vrbanic</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UcfnncpU/5-questions-with-scene-gala-marija-vrbanic"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T03:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tribute Brand founder and CEO Gala Marija Vrbanic joins 5 Questions With SCENE to discuss not just fashion, but graffiti crimes, fishless aquariums, and the apparently emergent sport of wind chasing.

Video shot and edited by Vincent Roazzi Jr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is Everyone Talking About Jupiter on Solana?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/EiN2WqlF/why-is-everyone-talking-about-jupiter-on-solana</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/EiN2WqlF/why-is-everyone-talking-about-jupiter-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T19:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio Creator and crypto influencer AshleyDCan explains why the crypto world can't stop talking about Solana's Jupiter. What is JUP? Who qualified for the airdrop? And will there be another round?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jupiter Founder Meow Unloads on the Solana Airdrop 'FUD']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YSpISivs/jupiter-founder-meow-unloads-on-the-solana-airdrop-fud</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YSpISivs/jupiter-founder-meow-unloads-on-the-solana-airdrop-fud"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T18:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meow, the pseudonymous founder of Solana DEX aggregator Jupiter, made a surprise appearance today on Rug Radio's "FOMO Hour" to address the JUP airdrop "FUD,"  and explain why he believes the backlash to the team's launch liquidity pool is unfounded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future is Multichain w/ Jason Trikakis from Holograph]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QGJdd57G/the-future-is-multichain-w-jason-trikakis-from-holograph</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/QGJdd57G/the-future-is-multichain-w-jason-trikakis-from-holograph"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Jason from Holograph.xyz

They dive into the multichain future and what that means for NFTs, DeFi, RWAs, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Generative AI Makes for a More Inclusive Metaverse in 'Avalon']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J5j39bBG/how-generative-ai-makes-for-a-more-inclusive-metaverse-in-avalon</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/J5j39bBG/how-generative-ai-makes-for-a-more-inclusive-metaverse-in-avalon"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T04:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler speaks with Decrypt reporter Jason Nelson about the use of generative AI within the upcoming game and how it will help players from anywhere and everywhere truly see themselves represented in the online world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Perfume DAO Crafted a 'Scent of the Metaverse']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LIUXdAv0/how-a-perfume-dao-crafted-a-scent-of-the-metaverse</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LIUXdAv0/how-a-perfume-dao-crafted-a-scent-of-the-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rook Perfumes founder Nadeem Crowe and Melissa Gilmour of Web3 creative agency Lily & Piper join Stephen Graves to talk about how they created a fragrance with a DAO and brought it to the shelves of London department store Harvey Nichols.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trash-Fueled BTC Mining w/ Chris Bennet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uLy5Y1E7/trash-fueled-btc-mining-w-chris-bennet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uLy5Y1E7/trash-fueled-btc-mining-w-chris-bennet"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T19:09:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Chris Bennet from Spacestation Investments.

They discuss:
- Mining BTC with energy generated from landfills
- How to increase deal-flow
- Running an agency vs running a fund]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preview of Agoria's 'Le Code d’Orsay']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PK7ynKMB/preview-of-agorias-le-code-dorsay</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PK7ynKMB/preview-of-agorias-le-code-dorsay"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A first look at "Sigma Lumina," a sculpture by artist and musician Agoria in collaboration with Johan Lescure. It features in "Le Code d’Orsay," the first NFT exhibition at the Musée d’Orsay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you the one being farmed? w/ Frisson]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/i3sesrao/are-you-the-one-being-farmed-w-frisson"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Frisson from Tallyx.xyz

They reflect on:
- building in the bear market
- the points system meta
- will zoomers care about decentralization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Look Touch Own': OONA Discusses Her Performance Art Exhibition]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/79jpGlCe/look-touch-own-oona-discusses-her-performance-art-exhibition"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptual artist OONA joins moderator Raina Marie to discuss "Look Touch Own," her performance art exhibition featuring her own former breast implants, which have been tokenized. This conversation was recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genius Marketing by Genius Marketers: How Crypto Builders Can Reach the Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/YiQgzWJW/genius-marketing-by-genius-marketers-how-crypto-builders-can-reach-the-masses"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio founder Farokh Sarmad moderates a conversation between 9dcc founder and CEO Gmoney and Serotonin founder and CEO Amanda Cassatt about the challenges and opportunities in Web3 marketing and how they're navigating the ever-evolving space. Recorded at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel Miami in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative Art Across Mediums: Artists Discuss the Evolving Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GK3aN0zo/generative-art-across-mediums-artists-discuss-the-evolving-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-12T02:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this panel discussion from Rug Radio's R Haus at Art Basel Miami 2023, Sofia Garcia, Ismail Tazi, Emily Edelman, and Aleksandra Art discuss the expanding generative art space—and why "generative" doesn't necessarily have to mean digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Coin to Rule Them All with Mike Grantis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rkYpU8TJ/the-ai-coin-to-rule-them-all-with-mike-grantis"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reza is joined by Mike Grantis from Contango Digital to discuss
- The AI coin to rule them all
- The Solana Ecosystem 
- What's next for Solana airdrops]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conversation With Snowfro: Bringing 'Chromie Squiggle' #8107 to the Physical Space]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/DcrU04gG/conversation-with-snowfro-bringing-chromie-squiggle-8107-to-the-physical-space"/>
        <updated>2024-01-10T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Art Blocks founder and CEO and "Chromie Squiggle" project creator Erick "snowfro" Calderon spoke with Benny Redbeard Gross at Rug Radio's R Haus event at Art Basel 2023, to discuss how and why "Chromie Squiggle" NFT #8107 was given a special edition print run in collaboration with Avant Arte.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't Underestimate Mobile Gaming: Qualcomm's Matthew Grossman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/34Oil4Qu/dont-underestimate-mobile-gaming-qualcomms-matthew-grossman"/>
        <updated>2024-01-08T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm product marketing manager Matthew Grossman tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin why mobile esports is exploding in popularity around the world—and dispels some of the misconceptions around mobile gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>