<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-19T01:03:22.083Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-19T01:03:22.083Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ether rise; Toncoin leads crypto rebound]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912232/Bitcoin-Ether-rise-Toncoin-leads-crypto-rebound</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912232/Bitcoin-Ether-rise-Toncoin-leads-crypto-rebound"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin rose on Tuesday morning in Asia to around US$26,700, after briefly breaching the US$27,000 mark. Ether also logged gains but remained below US$1,650.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Co-Founder Urges Congress: Regulate Crypto To Retain America’s Rising Innovators]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547488671</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-co-founder-urges-congress-regulate-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with Fortune Magazine, Anatoly Yakovenko, renowned entrepreneur and co-founder of Solana, emphasized the urgent need for regulatory clarity in the blockchain industry to attract and retain top talent in the United States. 
 
Yakovenko, who experienced the stark contrast between limited opportunities under Soviet rule and other possibilities in America, believes that a well-functioning economy should not penalize an entire industry for the actions of a few bad actors.
 
Solana Co-founder Demands US Congress To Take Action
 
Per the report, Yakovenko’s passion for fostering innovation led him to co-found Solana, a blockchain platform designed for global accessibility and decentralization. He envisions a future where everyone has equal access to an open and interoperable…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Co-Founder Urges Congress: Regulate Crypto To Retain America’s Rising Innovators]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912228/Solana-Co-Founder-Urges-Congress-Regulate-Crypto-To-Retain-Americas-Rising-Innovators</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912228/Solana-Co-Founder-Urges-Congress-Regulate-Crypto-To-Retain-Americas-Rising-Innovators"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent interview with Fortune Magazine, Anatoly Yakovenko, renowned entrepreneur and co-founder of Solana, emphasized the urgent need for regulatory clarity in the blockchain industry to attract and retain top talent in the United States. Yakovenko, who experienced the stark contrast...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Altcoins UNDER $1 FOR MASSIVE GAINS]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912241/Top-3-Altcoins-UNDER-1-FOR-MASSIVE-GAINS</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912241/Top-3-Altcoins-UNDER-1-FOR-MASSIVE-GAINS"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altcoins under $1 can be a great deal. But not all of them actually are a great deal. However, we found three coins that have strong fundamentals and are under $1. They sure are the real deal and a great deal in September.Manage Your Crypto Portfolio with Regular Updates and Top Insights for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC sees temporary setback in request to access Binance.US software]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912221/SEC-sees-temporary-setback-in-request-to-access-BinanceUS-software</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912221/SEC-sees-temporary-setback-in-request-to-access-BinanceUS-software"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A federal magistrate judge has denied the SEC's request to gain immediate access to Binance.US's software, asking the regulator to provide more specific requests for discovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Goldman Sachs Executive Lays Out Bull Case for Ethereum Rival Solana, Says SOL Best Story Outside of ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912202/Ex-Goldman-Sachs-Executive-Lays-Out-Bull-Case-for-Ethereum-Rival-Solana-Says-SOL-Best-Story-Outside-of-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912202/Ex-Goldman-Sachs-Executive-Lays-Out-Bull-Case-for-Ethereum-Rival-Solana-Says-SOL-Best-Story-Outside-of-ETH"/>
        <updated>2023-09-19T00:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Goldman Sachs executive Raoul Pal says that Solana (SOL) is one of his top altcoin picks and is potentially the most promising project outside of Ethereum (ETH). In a new interview with Altcoin Daily, the Real Vision founder says Solana co-founder Anatoly Yakovenko, commonly referred to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Authorities Take Aim at Unregulated Crypto OTC Desks Amid Money Laundering Concerns]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75473512e6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/south-korean-authorities-take-aim-at-unregulated-crypto-otc-desks-amid-money-laundering-concerns/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean prosecutors and regulators are directing their attention toward reported issues concerning unregulated cryptocurrency-based over-the-counter (OTC) trading and deposit enterprises. During the third annual prosecutors’ conference, officials proposed the necessity for enhanced regulation in the crypto sphere, citing concerns that these enterprises facilitate money laundering and fraud. The Korea Customs Service estimates that unlawful cryptocurrency exchanges totaling 5.6 trillion won ($4 billion) transpired in 2022.
 
Unregulated Crypto OTC Firms in South Korea Draw Regulatory Focus
 
South Korean authorities are setting their focus on the crypto OTC market, according to a regional report published on Sunday. Essentially, over-the-counter (OTC) trading involves the direct buying…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Flashes Bearish Death Cross, How Low Can It Go?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754735989a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/xrp-price-bearish-death-cross/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Death crosses appearing in the chart of any digital asset can be bad and the XRP price is no different in this regard. The token presently looks to be heading toward another notable drop in price as an analyst points out a looming death cross.
 
XRP Death Cross Could See Price Fall
 
According to a crypto analyst who goes by Cheeky Crypto on social media platforms, the XRP price could see a price dip soon as a death cross forms on its chart. The analyst pointed out this formation to his over 152,000 subscribers on YouTube, explaining what this might mean for the digital asset.
 
 
The XRP price is currently finding support at the 200-day EMA, although with resistance at the 50 EMA, presenting a close tie between the two for dominance. He also points out a three-way pattern in the chart tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the XRP-BlackRock rumour and its implications]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912172/Understanding-the-XRP-BlackRock-rumour-and-its-implications</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912172/Understanding-the-XRP-BlackRock-rumour-and-its-implications"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a few days before this episode, Ripple also cracked a new partnership, one that can help further increase the blockchain’s adoption in Asia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PayPal Shares First PYUSD Report as Stablecoin Market Fades to $131 Billion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197688</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197688/paypal-pyusd-report-stablecoins-131-billion"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PYUSD’s $44 million market capitalization suggests the stablecoin’s initial adoption has been slow so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Regulator Takes Aim At OTC Crypto Trading]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912162/South-Korean-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-OTC-Crypto-Trading</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912162/South-Korean-Regulator-Takes-Aim-At-OTC-Crypto-Trading"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s customs agency recently highlighted crypto trading’s role in illegal forex transactions. The Financial Services Commission (FSC) has also taken note of OTC crypto trading’s role in financial crimes. Unlawful forex transactions via crypto assets reached a whopping $4 billion last...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Price Flashes Bearish Death Cross, How Low Can It Go?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912134/XRP-Price-Flashes-Bearish-Death-Cross-How-Low-Can-It-Go</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912134/XRP-Price-Flashes-Bearish-Death-Cross-How-Low-Can-It-Go"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Death crosses appearing in the chart of any digital asset can be bad and the XRP price is no different in this regard. The token presently looks to be heading toward another notable drop in price as an analyst points out a looming death cross. XRP Death Cross Could See Price Fall According to a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Will Dogecoin Trade At If It Attains The Market Cap Of Bitcoin Or Ethereum?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912126/How-Much-Will-Dogecoin-Trade-At-If-It-Attains-The-Market-Cap-Of-Bitcoin-Or-Ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912126/How-Much-Will-Dogecoin-Trade-At-If-It-Attains-The-Market-Cap-Of-Bitcoin-Or-Ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T23:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comparisons in the crypto market are not out of the norm, especially given the fierce rivalry that goes on between two or more tokens at a time. So this report will take a look at where the price of Dogecoin will realistically be if the meme coin’s market cap were to reach the current market cap...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I Just Want to Keep Things Moving’: Judge Makes No Ruling in SEC-Binance Document Dispute]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754731ae72</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/18/i-just-want-to-keep-things-moving-judge-makes-no-ruling-in-sec-binance-document-dispute/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. judge declined to order Binance.US to make its executives more available for depositions, or for the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to back down in its demands for more documents during a hearing Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ‘Spiderchain’ Plans to Build Ethereum on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197687/how-spiderchain-plans-to-build-ethereum-on-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following weeks of debate about Bitcoin drivechains, a similar project to unlock the network’s programming potential is picking up steam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ‘Spiderchain’ Plans to Build Ethereum on Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912122/How-Spiderchain-Plans-to-Build-Ethereum-on-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912122/How-Spiderchain-Plans-to-Build-Ethereum-on-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following weeks of debate about Bitcoin drivechains, a similar project to unlock the network’s programming potential is picking up steam.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: Binance "Won'T Comply" ?? Bitcoin And Crypto Holders Be Ready]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912123/WARNING-BINANCE-WONT-COMPLY-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-HOLDERS-BE-READY</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912123/WARNING-BINANCE-WONT-COMPLY-BITCOIN-AND-CRYPTO-HOLDERS-BE-READY"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crackdown: South Korea Targets OTC Market Amid Multi-Billion Scandals]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754733392d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-crackdown-south-korea-targets-otc-market/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In light of a surge in illicit activities associated with the over-the-counter (OTC) crypto trading market, South Korea is increasing its regulatory scrutiny. Financial regulators in this tech-forward nation are actively delving into the largely unregulated domain of OTC crypto trading in the Asian country. 
 
The report claims a sense of urgency to establish concrete regulatory measures amid mounting concerns regarding possible abuse in money laundering and other illegal endeavors. 
 
 
Increasing Pressure On OTC Crypto Exchanges
 
In a discussion titled “Criminal Legal Issues Related to Virtual Assets,” key regulatory authorities such as Deputy Chief Prosecutor Ki No-Seong and the Financial Services Commission’s Park Min-woo emphasized the potential dangers of the unregulated OTC crypto …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin’s Crypto Market Dominance Rises to 50% and It Could Go Higher, Say Analysts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75473348a1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/18/bitcoins-crypto-market-dominance-rises-to-50-and-it-could-go-higher-say-analysts/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hopes for a spot bitcoin ETF and the latest regulatory actions could prove a further catalyst.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I Just Want to Keep Things Moving’: Judge Makes No Ruling in SEC-Binance Document Dispute]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912117/I-Just-Want-to-Keep-Things-Moving-Judge-Makes-No-Ruling-in-SEC-Binance-Document-Dispute</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912117/I-Just-Want-to-Keep-Things-Moving-Judge-Makes-No-Ruling-in-SEC-Binance-Document-Dispute"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. judge declined to order Binance.US to make its executives more available for depositions, or for the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) to back down in its demands for more documents during a hearing Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge asks Binance.US and SEC to simmer down in dispute over documents]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912096/Judge-asks-BinanceUS-and-SEC-to-simmer-down-in-dispute-over-documents</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912096/Judge-asks-BinanceUS-and-SEC-to-simmer-down-in-dispute-over-documents"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A D.C. district judge encouraged Binance Holdings Limited and the SEC Commission to work together as the agency pushes for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin investors can look out for this bullish signal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912090/Bitcoin-investors-can-look-out-for-this-bullish-signal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912090/Bitcoin-investors-can-look-out-for-this-bullish-signal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Users on Ethereum’s Decentralized Polymarket Speculate on Biden’s Impeachment]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75473d94b6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/users-on-ethereums-decentralized-polymarket-speculate-on-bidens-impeachment/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the Republican House of Representatives speaker, Kevin McCarthy, directed the House to open an impeachment inquiry into Joe Biden, bettors on the cryptocurrency-powered Polymarket platform have started placing bets on whether Biden will be impeached by two specific dates. Currently, bettors are wagering against impeachment on or before two specific dates: September 30, 2023, and December 31, 2023.
 
Polymarket Bettors Predict Slim Odds for Biden’s Impeachment
 
In both traditional and decentralized betting circles, gamblers are placing bets on whether Joe Biden will be impeached after House speaker Kevin McCarthy initiated an inquiry into Biden on September 12, 2023. McCarthy and other GOP House members contend that U.S. president Biden may have misled Americans regarding his son Hun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Ethos Vs. Regulatory Compliance: Who Will Win The Battle For DeFi?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912086/Crypto-Ethos-Vs-Regulatory-Compliance-Who-Will-Win-The-Battle-For-DeFi</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912086/Crypto-Ethos-Vs-Regulatory-Compliance-Who-Will-Win-The-Battle-For-DeFi"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In light of the recent regulatory scrutiny on decentralized finance (DeFi) platforms, several industry experts emphasized the need for a balanced approach that respects the ethos of the crypto world while ensuring compliance with traditional fin read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum ICO Participant Moves $9.96 Million Of ETH To Kraken. Will He Sell?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912062/Ethereum-ICO-Participant-Moves-996-Million-Of-ETH-To-Kraken-Will-He-Sell</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912062/Ethereum-ICO-Participant-Moves-996-Million-Of-ETH-To-Kraken-Will-He-Sell"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Crackdown: South Korea Targets OTC Market Amid Multi-Billion Scandals]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912068/Crypto-Crackdown-South-Korea-Targets-OTC-Market-Amid-Multi-Billion-Scandals</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912068/Crypto-Crackdown-South-Korea-Targets-OTC-Market-Amid-Multi-Billion-Scandals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T22:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Predicts Ripple Suit Settlement Amid ‘Treasonous’ Insider Leaks]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912057/Expert-Predicts-Ripple-Suit-Settlement-Amid-Treasonous-Insider-Leaks</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912057/Expert-Predicts-Ripple-Suit-Settlement-Amid-Treasonous-Insider-Leaks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Bitcoin Hit $1,000,000 By 2025?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912063/CAN-BITCOIN-HIT-1000000-BY-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912063/CAN-BITCOIN-HIT-1000000-BY-2025"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC embroiled in court cases; Hester Peirce says crypto firms shouldn’t give up on US]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912039/SEC-embroiled-in-court-cases-Hester-Peirce-says-crypto-firms-shouldnt-give-up-on-US</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18912039/SEC-embroiled-in-court-cases-Hester-Peirce-says-crypto-firms-shouldnt-give-up-on-US"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spiderchains: A Proof Of Stake Second Layer]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547391c3d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/spiderchains-a-proof-of-stake-second-layer"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an extension to my previous article series discussing the different sidechain proposals that exist. Those articles can be found here: Spacechains, Spacechain Use Cases, Softchains, Drivechains, Federated Chains, and Trade Offs Of Sidechains. 
Botanix Labs has proposed a completely new sidechain design recently, called spiderchains, for the purposes of porting the Ethereum Virtual Machine to a platform anchored to the Bitcoin network. The architecture is a pretty large deviation from most prior proposals for concrete designs. Firstly, it does not involve miners directly in consensus or use merge-mining in any of its variant forms. Secondly, it uses multisig and escrow bonds to create a second layer proof-of-stake system on top of Bitcoin. Third, it does not require any changes to Bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shinobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citi Launches Crypto Platform For Institutional Clients]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75473946b5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/citi-launches-crypto-platform-institutional-clients/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banking giant Citi launched a new crypto and blockchain-based platform for its institutional clients. The Citi Token Services was released by the bank’s Treasury and Trade Solutions (TTS) with several new capabilities and features.
 
 
Citi Doubles Down On Crypto With New Platform
 
Per an official press release, the new crypto or token platform was created to provide institutions access to smart contracts and blockchain technology. In that way, Citi expects to address a demand for “tokenized deposits” and integrate these technologies into their global network.
 
Ultimately, the bank aims to “upgrade” its cash management and trading features for its clients. These institutions will have access to some advantages of smart contracts and blockchain, such as cross-border payments, programmable…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of Crypto 'Capitulation Phase' May Be Near: CoinShares Analyst]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197677</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197677/end-of-crypto-capitulation-phase-may-be-near-coinshares-analyst"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Token prices rose but institutions continue to sell digital assets, which for James Butterfill is an indicator of a change in phases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Earn Bitcoin by Playing Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197638</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-earn-bitcoin-playing-minecraft-satlantis-guide"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Satlantis server on Minecraft pays out real Bitcoin for playing. Here's how to get started, begin earning, and cash out your winnings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SoftBank Mulls Big Investment in OpenAI Following ARM IPO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197633</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197633/softbank-mulls-big-investment-in-openai-following-arm-ipo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T21:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of the Japanese multinational firm chats frequently with both Sam Altman and ChatGPT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC’s Call for Full Disclosure: Court Asked to Order Inspection of Binance US]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547272b9d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/secs-call-for-full-disclosure-court-asked-to-order-inspection-of-binance-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T20:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) filed a reply to support its motion to compel Binance Holdings Limited to comply with expedited discovery related to customer assets. The reply comes after months of alleged delays and incomplete responses from Binance as it fights a lawsuit alleging it violated federal securities laws. 
 
SEC Seeks Court-Ordered Probe of Binance US in Ongoing Crypto Custody Clash
 
In the 12-page document, the SEC argues Binance has failed to fully comply with a consent order requiring it to hand over documents and other information about the custody and control of customer crypto assets. The agency says recent depositions have revealed Binance likely withheld responsive documents and information without proper justification. The SEC’s court filing states:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s U.S. Exchange Bucks SEC’s Document Requests Amid Investigation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754727bc81</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/18/binances-us-exchange-bucks-secs-document-requests-amid-investigation/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T20:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange is fighting to avoid handing over certain documents to the regulator, arguing the SEC’s requests are “overbroad.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Begins New Week On A Bearish Note As Burn Rate Drops Double-Digits]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754727cfdf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-drops/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T20:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu remains a fan favorite after its massive run back in 2021. However, the meme coin has been having a tough go of it especially as the bears have continued to dominate the market. This time around, SHIB’s price is opening the new week on a rather bearish note that could set a negative tone for the rest of the week.
 
Shiba Inu Succumbs To Bears
 
As the market ushers in the new trading week, some cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Ethereum have seen positive movement. However, this positive movement has not rubbed off on the Shiba Inu meme coin which is showing very bearish tendencies at this time.
 
 
The SHIB token is still seeing losses across its hourly, daily, and weekly charts, despite minor gains being recorded by so many other large caps. This would suggest high selling p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Inches Toward Merger With USBTC as Court Approves Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197631</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197631/bitcoin-miner-hut-8-inches-toward-merger-with-usbtc-as-court-approves-deal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T20:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hut 8 Corp stands to be one of the largest Bitcoin miners across the continent, but the deal isn't finalized yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Regulators Ever Keep Up With Crypto Markets?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754722dcec</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/18/can-regulators-ever-keep-up-with-crypto-markets/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T20:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York’s finance watchdog's proposed token listing requirements give up the game before it starts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the 'Shared Vocabulary' of Generative Art's History]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=156690</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/156690/exploring-the-shared-vocabulary-of-generative-arts-history"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new exhibition in London highlights the connections between the early pioneers of generative art and their modern counterparts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Under Fire: SEC Files Strong Reply In Compelling Case Amidst Employee Exodus]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75472e4b3a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-reply-against-binance-amidst-employee-exodus/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:35:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ongoing legal battle between the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) and Binance, the SEC has filed a robust reply supporting its Motion to Compel. 
 
The agency emphasizes the increasing exodus of the exchange’s employees, who potentially hold crucial asset custody and control information.
 
SEC Raises Alarm Over Employee Exodus At Binance
 
According to the SEC filing, Binance.US’s alleged opposition to the motion exemplifies the “complexities” the SEC has faced in navigating this case. 
 
 
Despite initially agreeing to expedited discovery provisions outlined in the Consent Order, the exchange is now attempting to reevaluate its “scope and purpose,” according to the SEC. 
 
The SEC argues that Binance.US’s representations have been undermined by their documents and “incon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mila Kunis' Stoner Cats Banned From NFT Marketplaces After SEC Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197622</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197622/mila-kunis-stoner-cats-trading-banned-nft-marketplaces-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSea and Rarible both confirmed that they blocked Stoner Cats NFT trades, while Blur shows no active listings after the SEC settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Gives Up $27K in Sharp Tumble as Crypto Liquidations Top $100M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547285622</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/18/bitcoin-gives-up-27k-in-sharp-tumble-as-crypto-liquidations-top-100m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC price fell to $26,700 from $27,200 during Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['House of Mirrors': SEC Demands Urgent Inspection of Binance US Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197620/sec-demands-binance-us-inspection-in-house-of-mirrors-case"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The top regulator has slammed Binance US in Monday court documents for allegedly not cooperating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Outlook for September]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754729574e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-price-outlook-for-september-2/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T19:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After weeks of consolidation, bitcoin has started the second half of September in relatively bullish fashion. Prices have once again surged above the $27,000 level, which comes as traders attention turns to the upcoming Federal Reserve meeting. Prior to this, we explore how the price of bitcoin may move for the remainder of the month.
 
Current Market Status
 
The first fortnight of September has been largely non-eventful, with bitcoin mostly consolidating below $26,500.
 
This comes as volatility in the market hovered close to a five-year low in August, with trading volume amongst exchanges falling by $52 billion.
 
However, as we move into the fall, there has been a slight rise in volatility, mostly led by a rise in both inflation and retail sales in the United States.
 
Markets have used this as confirmation that the Federal Reserve will hike rates later this week, which could lead to dollar strength.
 

 
September Outlook
 
Bitcoin peaked at $27,414.73 earlier in today’s session, following a low of $24,900 exactly a week ago.
 
This has seen BTC/USD reach its highest level since August 31, 2023, and comes as the 10-day (red) and 25-day (blue) moving averages near an upward cross.
 
 
From the chart, the potential for this move has been on the cards for a while, however, it has finally taken place as volatility returned to the market.
 
Additionally, the relative strength index has now also moved past a key point of resistance at 53.00, which has been a thorn in the sight of bulls for the past few weeks.
 
The next real ceiling lies at 65.00, and should bulls be targeting this, there is a chance bitcoin (BTC) ends the month above $28,300.
 
Where will bitcoin end the month? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainlink’s LINK Soars, Outperforming Other Crypto Majors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75472aa167</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/09/18/chainlinks-link-soars-outperforming-other-crypto-majors/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The uptick comes as the company has secured a number of notable partnerships with traditional finance institutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I Learned Managing a Crypto Fund for Five Years]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75472bcdd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/09/18/what-i-learned-managing-a-crypto-fund-for-five-years/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jeff Dorman, chief investment officer at Arca, says crypto funds still need to find a balance between adopting professional Wall Street practices and taking advantage of crypto’s unique opportunities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Dorman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Is Supposedly Separate From Crypto Custodian Ceffu. The SEC Has Questions]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7547150750</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/09/18/binance-is-supposedly-separate-from-crypto-custodian-ceffu-the-sec-has-questions/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As regulators prepare to square off with one of the world’s biggest crypto exchanges in court, Ceffu has denied any ties to Binance or U.S. operations. The reality is murkier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firms In Hong Kong Prohibited From Identifying As ‘Banks,’ Regulator Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e75471554fa</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-firms-prohibited-from-identifying-as-banks/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T18:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto firms in Hong Kong have received a stern warning from the Hong Kong Monetary Authority (HKMA), urging them to refrain from using the term “bank” in their operations unless they hold the status of an authorized institution. 
 
The regulatory announcement addresses growing concerns about misleading terminology adopted by certain cryptocurrency companies, including self-designations as crypto banks, digital asset banks, or digital trading banks.
 
In a press release, the HKMA highlighted the alarming trend of certain digital entities using the term “deposits” when referring to funds entrusted to them by clients. The financial regulator made it clear that such practices constitute a gross violation of Hong Kong’s banking laws. The warning underscores the need for transparency and accura…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Elder Scrolls VI Isn't Coming to PlayStation 5, Won't Release Before 2026]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197609/the-elder-scrolls-vi-isnt-coming-playstation-5-wont-release-before-2026"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike Skyrim, The Elder Scrolls VI isn't planned for PlayStation. Instead, it'll be a PC and Xbox exclusive, like Starfield.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citigroup Will Let Rich Clients Use Private Blockchain to Transfer Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197602</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197602/citigroup-launches-smart-contract-digital-token-service-for-institutions"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T17:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citigroup is allowing big money clients to transform their deposits into digital tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising From Ashes: Berlin Bitcoin Veteran Bitwala Makes Surprise Comeback]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197596</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197596/rising-from-ashes-berlin-crypto-veterans-bitwala-make-surprise-comeback"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once known as Nuri, Berlin-based cryptocurrency startup Bitwala is relaunching under its old name—but German users will have to wait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How Much Bitcoin We Earned Playing Minecraft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/z8rit7yN/heres-how-much-bitcoin-we-earned-playing-minecraft</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/z8rit7yN/heres-how-much-bitcoin-we-earned-playing-minecraft"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T16:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now mine Bitcoin in Minecraft. Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shows us how.

Satlantis website: https://satlantis.net/
Minecraft server address: play.satlantis.net]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deepfake Pornography: Is Consent Over Your Image a Lost Cause?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197592</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/deepfake-pornography-is-consent-over-your-image-a-lost-cause"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T14:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many in the areas of cybersecurity, social justice, privacy law, and other fields, deepfake pornography is one of the greatest threats to emerge from the AI era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong Influencer Arrested Over JPEX Exchange Promotion]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197573</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197573/hong-kong-influencer-arrested-over-jpex-exchange-promotion"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joseph Lam’s arrest followed the suspension of trading on crypto exchange JPEX, which regulators allege was operating without a license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain's Unseen Backbone Securing Billions of Dollars in Value]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154993</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154993/blockchains-unseen-backbone-securing-billions-of-dollars-in-value"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T12:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chronicle Protocol aims to redefine the oracle space with Scribe, when it launches to the public this month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act Gets Nine New Sponsors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197565</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197565/elizabeth-warrens-digital-asset-anti-money-laundering-act-gets-nine-new-sponsors"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T10:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warren's controversial Digital Asset Anti-Money Laundering Act has received support from nine more U.S. senators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe is ‘Eating America’s Lunch’: U.S. Held Back by Bitcoin ETF Paralysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197538</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197538/europe-is-eating-americas-lunch-u-s-held-back-by-bitcoin-etf-paralysis"/>
        <updated>2023-09-18T01:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Europe is probably a bit ahead of the game,” says a Swiss CEO. "The U.S. still has work to do.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nature, Not Humans, Should Be the Model for AI, Says Artist Collective]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197514</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197514/ai-agi-nature-fungi-plants-not-humans-theta-noir"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Challenging conventional AI ethics, Theta Noir believes AI should mimic nature's sustainability rather than human excess.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Celebrities Settle Lawsuits Over FTX Deals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197509/first-celebrities-settle-lawsuit-over-ftx-deals"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T23:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among those who agreed to settle were Jacksonville Jaguars quarterback Trevor Lawrence, and YouTube influencers Tom Nash and Kevin Paffrath.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PolkaWorld Hits Pause as Founder Faults Polkadot Governance Change]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197507/polkaworld-hits-pause-as-founder-faults-polkadot-governance-change"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T22:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the center of the controversy is a new structure that grants every token holder a vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week on Crypto Twitter: Idris Elba Falls Flat, and Are We Near the End of Binance?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197480</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197480/this-week-on-crypto-twitter-idris-elba-stellar-binance-executive-turnover"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T18:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several crypto Twitter heads remarked on the shifty personnel changes over at Binance this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prosecutors Say SBF’s Lawyers Are Trying to Taint Juror Pool]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197479/prosecutors-say-sbfs-lawyers-are-trying-to-taint-juror-pool"/>
        <updated>2023-09-17T17:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahead of Sam Bankman-Fried's trial, the government objects to voir dire questions from the defense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Steady Week for Bitcoin and Ethereum, Toncoin Balloons 23%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197429</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197429/this-week-in-coins-bitcoin-steady-ethereum-invlationary-toncoin-rises"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not even a big-budget Idris Elba commercial could save Stellar’s XLM from taking a nose dive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Metaverse Token Coming From Animoca Game Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197441</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197441/bitcoin-metaverse-token-coming-from-animoca-game-studio"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animoca Brands' Darewise subsidiary will launch a metaverse token via Bitcoin Ordinals to power an ecosystem led by the game Life Beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mark Cuban Loses $870,000 In Crypto Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197439</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197439/mark-cuban-crypto-scam-metamask-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The owner of the Dallas Mavericks lost roughly $870,000, although the figures could have been much worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Google Ban AI Artists from Running Stable Diffusion on Its Cloud?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197428</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197428/google-colab-stable-diffusion-web-ui-ban"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T18:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users have claimed that Google banned them from Colab after they tried to run Stable Diffusion with the famous WebUI popularized by A1111.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Celebrities Are Embracing AI to Stay Ahead of Deepfake Makers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197412</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197412/celebrities-using-ai-to-get-ahead-of-deepfakes"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T17:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prominent actors are reportedly using Metaphysic Pro to take ownership of the data needed to reproduce their likenesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is KYC? How Crypto Exchanges Prevent Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=112290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-kyc-how-crypto-exchanges-prevent-money-laundering"/>
        <updated>2023-09-16T09:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Know-your-customer (KYC) requirements are a growing part of Web3, as crypto becomes more integrated with the existing financial system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea’s Lazarus Group Has Stolen $240M in Crypto in Just 104 Days: Elliptic]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197407/north-korea-lazarus-hacks-240m-crypto-just-104-days-elliptic"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T22:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding to the tally is the $54 million hack of crypto exchange CoinEx, which blockchain sleuths at Elliptic now believe Lazarus was likely behind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nouns Fork: Disgruntled NFT Holders Exit With $27 Million From Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197400/nouns-fork-disgruntled-nft-holders-exit-27-million-from-treasury"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T21:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Nouns NFT collective on Ethereum, which is building open-source IP by funding creative projects, fractures after a widely supported fork.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Grants SEC’s Motion to Unseal Key Documents in Binance Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197396</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197396/judge-sec-unseal-key-documents-binance-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T21:20:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The judge’s approval follows accusations that Binance US exhibited a “lack of transparency” in the SEC’s investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Gemini Poised to Take On AI Titans OpenAI and Microsoft]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197378/google-gemini-poised-to-take-on-ai-titans-openai-and-microsoft"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has reportedly started testing its most advanced AI model to date, Gemini, which it says has impressive multimodal capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London Design Museum Lets Visitors Test Iconic Runway Looks via AR]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197360/london-design-museum-lets-visitors-test-iconic-runway-looks-ar"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An augmented reality experience developed by Snapchat maker Snap is part of the museum's new "Rebel: 30 Years of London Fashion" exhibit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephanie Hirschmiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Companies Aren't Banks, Hong Kong Warns Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197359</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197359/crypto-companies-arent-banks-hong-kong-warns-investors"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T19:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Describing themselves as banks may mislead the public into entrusting the companies with their savings,” read the regulator's notice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PUBG Creator Krafton Unveils 'Overdare' NFT Game With AI Creation Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197345</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197345/pubg-creator-krafton-unveils-overdare-nft-game-ai-creation-tools"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T18:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overdare looks to deliver a Roblox-like game creation experience within an open-world metaverse, built on top of the Settlus blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Year After the Merge: Where Does Ethereum Stand?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197341</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197341/one-year-after-the-merge-where-does-ethereum-stand"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T18:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In terms of price, Ethereum is trading at approximately the same price it was when the merge happened in 2022. But that's just part of the story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Bitcoin Mining Really Greener? Here's What's Going On]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197344</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197344/is-bitcoin-mining-really-greener-heres-whats-going-on"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T17:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report says Bitcoin mining is mostly sustainable, and that environmental FUD is "overstated."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Yieldflow: the DeFi Protocol for Passive Growth of Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/how-to-use-yieldflow-the-defi-protocol-for-passive-growth-of-digital-assets"/>
        <updated>2023-09-15T16:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While centralized exchanges expose customers to security risk in the event that they collapse, and to unpredictable liquidity, inflexible staking rules, and more, YieldFlow aims for a smooth user experience governed by trust, security, and decentralization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained's Daniel Paez on the Future of NFT Gaming Interoperability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/obt7FGYr/gods-unchaineds-daniel-paez-on-the-future-of-nft-gaming-interoperability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-14T20:27:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, executive producer on NFT card-battling game Gods Unchained, speaks with Decrypt Culture Editor Andrew Hayward about what the future of NFT game interoperability will really look like—and what it won't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of AI Stardom and Robotics With SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>