<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-30T15:16:27.592Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-30T15:16:27.592Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here's How Cardano (ADA) Governance Will Look in Voltaire Era]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690540/Heres-How-Cardano-ADA-Governance-Will-Look-in-Voltaire-Era</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690540/Heres-How-Cardano-ADA-Governance-Will-Look-in-Voltaire-Era"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano (ADA) blockchain enthusiasts shared explanation of hotly anticipated CIP-1694 release]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Calls BlackRock, Fidelity Bitcoin ETF Applications Inadequate: WSJ]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146863</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146863/sec-calls-blackrock-fidelity-bitcoin-etf-applications-inadequate-wsj"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T15:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newspaper reported Friday claims that the top regulator has said the applications "aren’t sufficiently clear and comprehensive" enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu’s Shibarium Rumored for Launch in Surprising Location]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690536/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Rumored-for-Launch-in-Surprising-Location</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690536/Shiba-Inus-Shibarium-Rumored-for-Launch-in-Surprising-Location"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SHIB Token might be heading to Canada for a game-changing event in the Shiba Inu saga.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trending Crypto Coins – Pepe 2.0, Refund Token, Safemoon 3.0, Shib 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690534/Trending-Crypto-Coins-Pepe-20-Refund-Token-Safemoon-30-Shib-20</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690534/Trending-Crypto-Coins-Pepe-20-Refund-Token-Safemoon-30-Shib-20"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broader crypto market sentiment has taken a knock on Friday, with bitcoin (BTC) last down around 1.5% and back in the low $30,000s following reports the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has informed applicants like BlackRock that recent spot bitcoin ETF filings are “inadequate”. The...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Bullish Signal: HODLers Buying At A Rate Of 194,500 BTC Per Month]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690527/Bitcoin-Bullish-Signal-HODLers-Buying-At-A-Rate-Of-194500-BTC-Per-Month</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690527/Bitcoin-Bullish-Signal-HODLers-Buying-At-A-Rate-Of-194500-BTC-Per-Month"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain data shows the Bitcoin HODLers have continued to accumulate recently as they expand their holdings at a rate of 194,500 BTC per month. Bitcoin’s Illiquid Supply Has Continued To Go Up Recently According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the BTC illiquid supply is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today in Crypto: Mastercard to Start Testing Its Multi-Token Network This Summer, OKX's Liquid Marketplace Exceeds $3BN in Trading Volume, Binance’s Institutional Clients Remain Optimistic on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690535/Today-in-Crypto-Mastercard-to-Start-Testing-Its-Multi-Token-Network-This-Summer-OKXs-Liquid-Marketplace-Exceeds-3BN-in-Trading-Volume-Binances-Institutional-Clients-Remain-Optimistic-on-Crypto</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690535/Today-in-Crypto-Mastercard-to-Start-Testing-Its-Multi-Token-Network-This-Summer-OKXs-Liquid-Marketplace-Exceeds-3BN-in-Trading-Volume-Binances-Institutional-Clients-Remain-Optimistic-on-Crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Date That Celsius Can Sell Its Altcoins Has Been Announced: It Will Be Converted To BTC And ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690496/The-Date-That-Celsius-Can-Sell-Its-Altcoins-Has-Been-Announced-It-Will-Be-Converted-To-BTC-And-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690496/The-Date-That-Celsius-Can-Sell-Its-Altcoins-Has-Been-Announced-It-Will-Be-Converted-To-BTC-And-ETH"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Celsius Can Convert Altcoins to BTC, ETH Starting July 1 Following SEC Talks]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575d9ebce</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2023/06/30/bankrupt-celsius-can-convert-altcoins-to-btc-eth-starting-july-1-following-sec-talks/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creditor distributions will only be made in the two most popular cryptocurrencies, the company said]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Schickler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithm sets Stellar price for July 31, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690487/Machine-learning-algorithm-sets-Stellar-price-for-July-31-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690487/Machine-learning-algorithm-sets-Stellar-price-for-July-31-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM) has emerged as one of the top 5 altcoins in terms of price gains over the past week, … Continued]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humayun Sheikh, CEO of Fetch.ai, on AI, Machine Learning, Autonomous Agents, and Blockchains | Ep. 243]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690483/Humayun-Sheikh-CEO-of-Fetchai-on-AI-Machine-Learning-Autonomous-Agents-and-Blockchains-Ep-243</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690483/Humayun-Sheikh-CEO-of-Fetchai-on-AI-Machine-Learning-Autonomous-Agents-and-Blockchains-Ep-243"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an exclusive interview with cryptonews.com, Humayun Sheikh, Founder and CEO of Fetch.ai, talks about building the infrastructure required for autonomous software agent, connecting smart agents to automate web3 systems, and the intersection of AI and Crypto.... Read More: Humayun Sheikh, CEO...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US SEC deems spot Bitcoin ETFs filings as inadequate: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690468/US-SEC-deems-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-filings-as-inadequate-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690468/US-SEC-deems-spot-Bitcoin-ETFs-filings-as-inadequate-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the eyes of the SEC, the recent filings from BlackRock, ARK Invest, Fidelity and other asset managers are not "sufficiently clear and comprehensive."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Presidential Candidate Ron DeSantis Supports Plan to Eliminate IRS and ‘Break the Swamp’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575db7eae</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-presidential-candidate-ron-desantis-supports-plan-to-eliminate-irs-and-break-the-swamp/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interview this week, Ron DeSantis, the Republican governor of Florida and a presidential candidate, revealed his support to eliminate several federal agencies should he win the general election. Among the entities he mentioned were the U.S. departments of Education, Commerce and Energy, and the Internal Revenue Service (IRS).
 
If Elected, DeSantis Administration Would Abolish the Departments of Commerce and Energy, Education, and the IRS
 
During an interview with Fox News television host Martha MacCallum on Wednesday, Ron DeSantis, the Republican governor of Florida and a candidate in the 2024 U.S. presidential race, shared his idea to streamline the federal government by eliminating certain agencies. DeSantis expressed his firm support for reducing the overall size of government a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin dives after WSJ report on ‘inadequate’ spot bitcoin ETF filings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690437/Bitcoin-dives-after-WSJ-report-on-inadequate-spot-bitcoin-ETF-filings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690437/Bitcoin-dives-after-WSJ-report-on-inadequate-spot-bitcoin-ETF-filings"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin shed more than 4% in just 20 minutes after the Wall Street Journal reported that the SEC told the Nasdaq and Cboe exchanges that recent filings for spot bitcoin ETF funds weren’t “clear and comprehensive.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin dominance surging amid changing market dynamics and regulatory crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690430/Bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690430/Bitcoin-dominance-surging-amid-changing-market-dynamics-and-regulatory-crackdown"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Takeaways Bitcoin dominance measures the ratio of the Bitcoin market cap to the cumulative cryptocurrency sector market cap It is currently at 58%, the highest mark since April 2021 Market dynamics are changing as institutions consider Bitcoin, while rest of crypto market still struggles...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sabre56 Partners With Arkon Energy For Ohio Data Center Consultancy Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690426/Sabre56-Partners-With-Arkon-Energy-For-Ohio-Data-Center-Consultancy-Deal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690426/Sabre56-Partners-With-Arkon-Energy-For-Ohio-Data-Center-Consultancy-Deal"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leading hosting provider Sabre56 deepens its strategic partnership with Arkon Energy, consulting on their new Ohio data center acquisition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's Commitment to Compliance: An Inside Look at the Program]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690471/Binances-Commitment-to-Compliance-An-Inside-Look-at-the-Program</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690471/Binances-Commitment-to-Compliance-An-Inside-Look-at-the-Program"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: SEC Demand Clarity And Comprehensive Information For Spot Bitcoin ETF Filings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c44b71</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/markets/sec-demand-clarity-and-comprehensive-information-for-spot-bitcoin-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has raised concerns over the recent surge of applications for spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs), stating that the filings are lacking clarity and comprehensive information, according to a report by the Wall Street Journal.

A variety of firms have submitted the applications such as BlackRock and Fidelity Investments. 
Following BlackRock's lead, a wave of traditional and crypto asset managers, including Fidelity Investments, Ark Investment Management, Invesco, WisdomTree, Bitwise Asset Management, and Valkyrie, have reactivated or amended their applications for spot bitcoin ETFs in recent days. The approval of such an ETF would mark a significant milestone for the industry, providing broader institutional access to bitcoin and allowing investors to trade bitcoin as easily as stocks, albeit at the loss of some of bitcoin’s properties.
Experts predicted BlackRock's application would address the SEC's concerns through an agreement to share surveillance of a spot bitcoin-trading platform with Nasdaq, the proposed ETF's listing exchange.
Nevertheless, the SEC informed the exchanges that the filings lacked key details, such as the precise surveillance-sharing agreement that would be implemented. A spokesperson for Cboe told the Wall Street Journal that they plan to update and refile the application. 
The SEC's critique has once again highlighted the regulatory challenges surrounding the launch of spot bitcoin ETFs. Market participants await updates from the asset managers and exchanges to address the concerns raised by the SEC. As the industry eagerly anticipates the potential approval of a spot bitcoin ETF, stakeholders hope that the revised filings will provide the clarity and comprehensive information necessary to gain regulatory acceptance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Litecoin Halving Is Due In 33 Days, What To Expect Now]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c4591e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/litecoin-halving-is-due-in-33-days/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a price increase of over 18% within the last 24 hours, Litecoin (LTC) is sending out a reminder today that the halving of the block reward is only 33 days and a few hours away. Based on current estimates, the Litecoin halving will take place on August 3, 2023, 10:01 am UTC (6:01 am EST), ushering the “digital silver” into a new era.
 
Litecoin Halving Is Just Around The Corner
 
Here’s the deal with the halving. Miners in the network get rewarded with Litecoin for producing blocks. At the beginning, it was 50 LTC per block. But every 4 years or so (around 840,000 blocks), that reward gets cut in half. Currently at 12.5 LTC, it will drop to 6.25 LTC after the August 2023 halving.
 
Like Bitcoin, Litecoin was designed to be deflationary, like gold or silver. As time goes on, the number …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Takes Hit As SEC Reportedly Brands ETF Filings 'Inadequate']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690434/Bitcoin-Takes-Hit-As-SEC-Reportedly-Brands-ETF-Filings-Inadequate</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690434/Bitcoin-Takes-Hit-As-SEC-Reportedly-Brands-ETF-Filings-Inadequate"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has raised concerns about recent applications for spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs).  The agency found that the applications, submitted by asset managers like BlackRock and Fidelity through exchanges Nasdaq and CBOE Global Markets, lacked...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Sees Rare 300% Quarterly Increase in Transaction Fees, Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690410/Bitcoin-BTC-Sees-Rare-300-Quarterly-Increase-in-Transaction-Fees-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690410/Bitcoin-BTC-Sees-Rare-300-Quarterly-Increase-in-Transaction-Fees-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin transaction fees increased 4x compared to last quarter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claim: Users Cannot Close Their Positions in This Cryptocurrency Exchange: The Exchange Has Response!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690414/Claim-Users-Cannot-Close-Their-Positions-in-This-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-The-Exchange-Has-Response</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690414/Claim-Users-Cannot-Close-Their-Positions-in-This-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-The-Exchange-Has-Response"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Goldman Sachs Executive Craig Broderick Joins Stablecoin-Issuer Circle's Board]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690435/Former-Goldman-Sachs-Executive-Craig-Broderick-Joins-Stablecoin-Issuer-Circles-Board</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690435/Former-Goldman-Sachs-Executive-Craig-Broderick-Joins-Stablecoin-Issuer-Circles-Board"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana, others caught in SEC crackdown ‘don’t deserve it,’ Buterin says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690398/Solana-others-caught-in-SEC-crackdown-dont-deserve-it-Buterin-says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690398/Solana-others-caught-in-SEC-crackdown-dont-deserve-it-Buterin-says"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little less a month after Binance and Coinbase were sued, Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin defends rival chains that have been targeted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Tokenized Assets Are Safer During a Banking Crisis]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c60167</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/30/why-tokenized-assets-are-safer-during-a-banking-crisis/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent U.S. bank failures exposed a strange truth: depositing your money on-chain is safer than trusting banks to make good on your holdings, argues Copper’s Fadi Aboualfa.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fadi  Aboualfa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azuki offers minor changes to similar NFTs after botched collection launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690408/Azuki-offers-minor-changes-to-similar-NFTs-after-botched-collection-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690408/Azuki-offers-minor-changes-to-similar-NFTs-after-botched-collection-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ‘overreacting’ as SEC returns ETF filings, BTC price dives 6%]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690399/Bitcoin-overreacting-as-SEC-returns-ETF-filings-BTC-price-dives-6</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18690399/Bitcoin-overreacting-as-SEC-returns-ETF-filings-BTC-price-dives-6"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Tumbles on Report of SEC Saying Spot BTC ETF Filings Inadequate]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c23a2f</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/30/bitcoin-tumbles-on-report-of-sec-saying-spot-btc-etf-filings-inadequate/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin ETF applications from BlackRock and Fidelity, among others, had helped drive bitcoin higher over the past two weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What New York Can Learn From Hong Kong in Regulating Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c23a20</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/30/what-new-york-can-learn-from-hong-kong-in-regulating-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A small number of unelected individuals in Washington D.C. are exercising alarming authoritarian power as regulators, counter to the Big Apple’s stated desire to move from antiquated financial systems to digital ones, writes Omer Ozden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Ozden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WebX Conference Welcomes Distinguished Guests: Japan PM, Yuga Labs CEO, Kabosu (Doge), Desdemona (AI Robot)]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c27314</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/webx-conference-welcomes-distinguished-guests-japan-pm-yuga-labs-ceo-kabosu-doge-desdemona-ai-robot/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. WebX, Asia’s leading Web3 conference (July 25-26), is thrilled to announce the participation of more esteemed guests at this year’s event: Japan prime minister Fumio Kishida, Yuga Labs CEO Daniel Alegre, the Dogecoin dog Kabosu, and the groundbreaking AI robot Desdemona (Made by Hanson Robotics, sister to Sophia the Robot).
 
WebX is a conference dedicated to bridging divides – Web2 and Web3, Japanese and English, Japan and the rest of the world. Japan has the potential to become Asia’s Web3 hub, and this inaugural WebX conference is both a recognition of and a launchpad for that potential.
 
Prime Minister Kishida speaking at WebX underscores the Japanese government’s recognition of the significance of Web3 technology in shaping Japan’s digital future. Their involvement sig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Association Backs Coinbase In SEC Regulatory Battle]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575ccba7b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/blockchain-association-backs-coinbase/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Blockchain Association has released a comprehensive document backing Coinbase option on the legal rationale behind its argument calling for the recusal of Securities and Exchange Commission Chair Gary Gensler from any decision-making processes. This is regarding the initiation or continuation of an enforcement action based on the assertion that a digital asset qualifies as a security.
 
The association said Chair Gensler’s consistent public assertion that ‘everything other than bitcoin’ should be considered a security, raises concerns and creates, at the very least, an appearance of a closed-minded approach to this matter.
 
By repeatedly expressing this viewpoint, Chair Gensler has essentially pre-judged the core issue involved in enforcement proceedings related to digital assets.
 
C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ebo Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OKX Overcomes FTX-Related Concerns Around Crypto Industry to Expand Sponsorship With Man City]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575cdf751</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/30/okx-overcomes-ftx-related-concerns-around-crypto-industry-to-expand-sponsorship-with-man-city/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:27:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manchester City and OKX's other partners have been auditing the exchange's proof of reserves to ease concerns that it won't go the same way as FTX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Potential of Crypto to Drive Economic Growth and Development in Emerging Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575cee6ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/the-potential-of-crypto-to-drive-economic-growth-and-development-in-emerging-markets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent  
years, cryptocurrency, a digital form of currency that runs independently of  
central banks, has received a lot of attention and appeal. While the impact of  
bitcoin on established economies is frequently addressed, the potential of  
cryptocurrency to fuel economic growth and development in emerging markets  
requires special consideration. 
This article  
investigates cryptocurrencies' revolutionary power in emerging markets and how  
they can contribute to long-term economic growth and development.
Financial  
Inclusion and Banking Service Access
One of the most  
important benefits of cryptocurrencies in emerging nations is their ability to  
increase financial inclusion. Due to hurdles such as insufficient  
infrastructure and high transaction costs, traditional banking …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FM Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New UK Law Recognizes Crypto Trading as Regulated Financial Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146857</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146857/new-uk-law-recognizes-crypto-trading-as-regulated-financial-activity"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:12:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The amended Financial Services and Markets Bill enables the regulation of digital assets to support their safe adoption in the UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Backed Loans and Lending Platforms: Unlocking the Potential of Digital Assets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c8497b</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/innovation/crypto-backed-loans-and-lending-platforms-unlocking-the-potential-of-digital-assets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of  
cryptocurrencies in recent years has resulted in the emergence of novel  
financial services that use the potential of digital assets. Crypto-backed  
loans, which allow individuals to unlock the value of their cryptocurrencies  
without having to sell them, are one such business that is growing popularity. 
These loans are  
made possible through lending platforms, which connect borrowers and lenders in  
a decentralized fashion. This article delves into the concept of crypto-backed  
loans, their advantages, and how lending platforms are changing the financial  
environment.
Understanding  
Bitcoin-Backed Loans
Crypto-backed  
loans are a type of borrowing in which individuals offer their digital assets  
as collateral to secure a loan, such as Bitcoin or Ethereum. This  
c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FM Contributors</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: BTC Remains in the Green, Ahead of US Consumer Sentiment Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c84eb8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-btc-remains-in-the-green-ahead-of-us-consumer-sentiment-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin remained close to the $31,000 level on Friday, as momentum in the market continued to be bullish heading into the weekend. This comes ahead of the anticipated consumer sentiment report from the United States, which is expected to show an increase in overall consumer confidence. Ethereum also edged higher today, climbing above $1,900.
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin (BTC) remained close to $31,000 in today’s session, as traders prepared for the consumer sentiment report from the United States.
 
After dropping to a low of $30,273.22 on Thursday, BTC/USD raced to an intraday peak of $31,256.86 earlier today.
 
As a result of the move, bitcoin neared a recent one-year high at $31,443, which was last Friday’s high.
 
 
Bitcoin chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Friday’s surge also led to a breakout of a key price ceiling at $30,800.
 
This appears to be due to the relative strength index (RSI) running into its own resistance level at the 70.00 mark.
 
At the time of writing, BTC is trading at $30,831.12.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) climbed above the $1,900 mark earlier in the day, however traders have already moved to consolidate gains.
 
ETH/USD briefly rose to an intraday high of $1,906.37 on Friday, but has since tailed off, and is now trading at $1,891.36.
 
Friday’s peak saw the world’s second largest cryptocurrency come close to a collision with the resistance level at $1,910.
 
 
Ethereum chart by TradingView
 

 
 

 
Looking at the chart, the RSI also neared a ceiling of its own, as it approached the 58.00 point of resistance.
 
In the event this level is broken, there is a strong possibility that ethereum could move beyond $1,930.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will this bullish sentiment continue throughout the weekend? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Fidelity Joins the Rush for Spot Bitcoin ETF]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c88364</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/30/first-mover-americas-fidelity-joins-the-rush-for-spot-bitcoin-etf/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for June 30, 2023. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Adopts Crypto and Stablecoins as Regulated Financial Activity]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575c9cc26</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/uk-adopts-crypto-and-stablecoins-as-regulated-financial-activity/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bill that aims to regulate cryptocurrencies and  
stablecoins in the UK has been approved by King Charles. Dubbed the Financial  
Services and Markets Act 2023, the new law classifies the trading of  
cryptocurrencies as a regulated activity and brings stablecoins under the scope  
of payment rules.
The Financial Services  
and Markets Act 2023 gives regulators more power to govern financial systems,  
including the digital assets. The bill, which got the approval of the upper house  
last week, permits the regulators, including the Financial  
Conduct Authority (FCA), the  
Bank of England, and the Payments Systems Regulator, to introduce new rules in  
the digital asset sector.
Unlocking Innovation
Andrew Griffith, the  
Economic Secretary to the Treasury, said that the new law present…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea Unveils Crypto Protection Bill Following Series Of Debacles]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575b532db</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/south-korea-unveil-crypto-protection-bill-following/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T12:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The South Korean government has ushered in an era of stricter regulation for digital assets with its latest Virtual Asset User Protection legislation. The law has been enacted as a response to a series of scandals that rocked the crypto market, including the implosion of coins created by Korean tech entrepreneur Do Kwon that aggravated a $2 trillion crypto-market downturn.
 
The landmark legislation, approved on Friday, is South Korea’s first comprehensive crypto regulation framework. It was formulated by integrating 19 pre-existing crypto-related bills. The law formally characterizes digital assets and sets out punitive measures for various offenses, including insider trading, market manipulation, and illicit trading practices.
 
Strengthening Oversight, Protecting Investors
 
The new leg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citigroup Reviews Partnership With Metaco, in Talks With Other Crypto Custodians: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575b65db6</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/30/citigroup-reviews-partnership-with-metaco-in-talks-with-other-crypto-custodians-bloomberg/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T12:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Banking giant Citigroup (C) is reviewing its partnership with crypto custody firm Metaco one month after Ripple Labs announced that it agreed to acquire Metaco for $250 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Knight</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crypto Industry’s New Favorite Punching Bag – Prometheum – Asks for a Chance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575b65dac</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk/2023/06/30/the-crypto-industrys-new-favorite-punching-bag-prometheum-asks-for-a-chance/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T12:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No new crypto rules are needed, said Aaron Kaplan, co-CEO of Prometheum Inc., and his company means to demonstrate it – even as the issuers whose tokens it seeks to trade say no thanks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linking Bitcoin To The Fentanyl Trade, Elizabeth Warren Demonstrates Concerning Bias Against Innovation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575b21c2e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/elizabeth-warren-mischaracterizes-bitcoin-as-criminal-tool"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an opinion editorial by Lee Bratcher, the president of the Texas Blockchain Council, and Mark Shut, the director of administrative affairs at the Texas Blockchain Council.
Senator Elizabeth Warren has expressed concerns regarding the use of cryptocurrencies in illicit activities, specifically in relation to the fentanyl and opioid crisis in the United States. In a recent hearing at the Senate Banking Committee, she cited a report from blockchain analytics firm Elliptic, indicating that digital currencies, particularly bitcoin, are being used to fund the fentanyl trade in China. But this is a clear obfuscation of the facts and a willful disregard for concepts in logic. 
Let's put this into perspective: Any technology can be used for good or ill but we do have a responsibility to add…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Bratcher,Mark Shut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investor Enthusiasm for Coinbase Shares May Prove Short-Lived: Berenberg]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7575b2cb14</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/30/investor-enthusiasm-for-coinbase-shares-may-prove-short-lived-berenberg/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange is faced with several risks that could trigger a reversal of the stock’s recent gains, the report said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Canny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Bitcoin Cash?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=5717</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/bitcoin-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash was a hard fork of Bitcoin. The split took place in 2017 and since then, Bitcoin Cash has become one of the largest cryptocurrencies to emerge from Bitcoin. It has made a number of subtle but significant changes to distinguish itself from Bitcoin, namely larger block size and faster transaction times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Hussey,Joseph O'Neill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash (BCH) Surges 33.9% in 24 Hours on EDX Listing, S. Korean Trading Spike]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146851</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146851/bitcoin-cash-bch-surges-33-9-in-24-hours-following-edx-listing-s-korean-short-squeeze"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After its listing on EDX, the digital asset exchange backed by Wall Street giants Fidelity, Citadel and Charles Schwab, the trading activity around the token has surged significantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sodexo Drops NFTs With a Twist: They’re for Employees, Not the Public]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146830</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146830/sodexo-drops-nfts-twist-employees-not-public"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T11:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European food services and facilities management firm’s Pluxee division launches NFTs on Internet Computer, but they’re not for everyone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucy Harley-McKeown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CME Group to Launch Ethereum-to-Bitcoin Ratio Futures Next Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146841</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146841/cme-group-to-launch-ethereum-to-bitcoin-ratio-futures-next-month"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T10:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world's leading derivatives exchange is set to expand its digital assets offering with a new product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Startup Typeface Now Worth $1 Billion Thanks to Salesforce, Google]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146820</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146820/generative-ai-startup-typeface-worth-1-billion-thanks-salesforce-google"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T23:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typeface, which offers a generative content platform for businesses, raised $100 million to secure its AI “unicorn” valuation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Steam Rejecting PC Games Created With Generative AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146819</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146819/steam-rejecting-pc-games-created-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T23:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers claim that their games were denied due to copyright concerns over AI-generated elements. Is a proper Steam ban on the horizon?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase's Ethereum Layer-2 Network Base Preps for Mainnet Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146815</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146815/coinbase-ethereum-layer-2-base-mainnet"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experts have conducted an external security audit and couldn’t find any significant flaws in the network built by Coinbase and Optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuga's HV-MTL Forge Beginner's Guide: Do You Need Bored Ape NFTs to Play?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146795</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/yugas-hv-mtl-forge-beginners-guide-need-bored-ape-nfts-play"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:32:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HV-MTL Forge, the Bored Ape creator's latest game, blends Tamagotchi-style pet care with world building and social strategy. Here's how to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump NFTs Are Back—This Time, It's $50 Melania July 4 Collectibles]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146791</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146791/trump-nfts-back-time-melania-july-4"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T20:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melania Trump starts the Independence Day celebrations early with $50 Solana collectibles, following the former president's NFT trading cards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Chatbot Startup Rockets to $4 Billion Valuation With Microsoft, Nvidia Backing]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146757</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146757/ai-chatbot-startup-rockets-to-4-billion-valuation-with-microsoft-nvidia-backing"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup is now backed by Microsoft, Nvidia, and notable tech figureheads: Bill Gates, Eric Schmidt, and Reid Hoffman.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steam Bans CS:GO Accounts With $2 Million Worth of Skins—Do NFTs Fix This?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146773</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146773/steam-bans-csgo-accounts-with-2-million-worth-of-skins-do-nfts-fix-this"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CS:GO accounts tied to at least $2 million worth of assets were just banned—but players could have more options with an NFT game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fidelity Refiles Bitcoin ETF Application With SEC as BlackRock Renews Hope]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146432</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146432/fidelity-files-bitcoin-etf-application-with-the-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T17:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After BlackRock's filing, the Boston-based investment giant is trying its luck with the SEC—again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Carolina Reps Suggest Adding Bitcoin, Gold to State Treasury]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146746</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146746/north-carolina-reps-suggest-adding-bitcoin-gold-to-state-treasury"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T17:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bill’s Republican sponsor described it as an important step toward “protecting” the state’s assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Is Like Mario Kart for NFT Degens]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146725</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146725/rumble-racing-star-like-mario-kart-nft-degens"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T17:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PREVIEW: In the simple but polished racing game, you can play as a Bored Ape or a Pudgy Penguin—no NFTs or crypto required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian Lawmakers Want to Help Blockchain Businesses 'Flourish']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146747/canadian-lawmakers-want-to-help-blockchain-businesses-flourish"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T17:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In their own words, the lawmakers say Canada has fallen behind the U.S. and Europe in its progress towards establishing crypto regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble Racing Star Game Preview: Is This Mario Kart With NFTs?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/lXVkuaeq/rumble-racing-star-game-preview-is-this-mario-kart-with-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin shares a first look at Delabs' upcoming lawn mower racing game Rumble Racing Star, which offers a large cast of quirky characters pulled from the worlds of Bored Ape Yacht Club, Pudgy Penguins, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon 2.0 Aims to Provide 'Unified Liquidity' Across Ethereum Scaling Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146739/polygon-2-unified-liquidity-across-its-chains-say-co-founders"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company said Polygon 2.0 will better connect separate blockchains and do away with wrapped tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Candy Digital Confirms Layoffs, Reveals Merger With Palm NFT Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146734</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146734/candy-digital-confirms-layoffs-reveals-merger-palm-nft-studio"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T15:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The combined company will operate under the Candy banner, albeit with fewer employees amid layoffs this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany’s BaFin Rejects Binance Crypto Custody License: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146699</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146699/germanys-bafin-rejects-binance-crypto-custody-license-report"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T12:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance maintains it is “committed” to working with regulators amid reports of BaFin denying its application for a crypto custody license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Coinbase Thinks the SEC Lawsuit Should Be Dismissed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146695</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146695/why-coinbase-thinks-the-sec-lawsuit-should-be-dismissed"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T12:23:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto exchange argued that the case falls outside the regulator's purview, as tokens are not investment contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin-Friendly Damus Will Remain on Apple App Store—With ‘Core Feature’ Removed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146687/bitcoin-friendly-damus-will-remain-on-apple-app-store-with-core-feature-removed"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Damus, a Bitcoin-friendly social media app, has won a reprieve in its battle to remain in the Apple App Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Loses European Banking Partner Paysafe]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146681</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146681/binance-loses-european-banking-partner-paysafe"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance's European banking partner Paysafe Payment Solutions will terminate support for the world’s largest crypto exchange in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lacoste Reveals Gamified, Tokenized Ecosystem for NFT Holders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146672</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146672/lacoste-reveals-gamified-tokenized-ecosystem-for-nft-holders"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The program, UNDW3, will reward engaged users with rarity-related NFT perks that the fashion brand says will increase those digital assets’ value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Bitcoin ETF, and Why Does Everyone from Blackrock to Fidelity Want One?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=12006</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-bitcoin-etf-explained-guide-learn-easy"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T09:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Bitcoin ETF creates a simple, legally compliant way to trade the price of Bitcoin, accessible on markets that investors are already familiar with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Stevens,Ki Chong Tran,Daniel Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETF Race: Ark Amends SEC Filing to Match BlackRock]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146645</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146645/bitcoin-etf-race-ark-amends-sec-filing-to-match-blackrock"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T05:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ARK added a surveillance-sharing agreement that appears to address potential market manipulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flirting With Algorithms: Men Are Harnessing AI to Win at the Dating Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146646</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146646/ai-dating-men-messaging-study"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T05:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithms are turning male suitors into virtual Casanovas—or at least they think so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humans Are More Likely to Believe Disinformation Generated By AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146662</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146662/humans-more-likely-to-believe-disinformation-generated-by-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T04:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even before GPT-4's launch, a new study finds disinformation created with GPT-3 was harder to detect than human-made falsehoods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s A 'Forgone Conclusion' That Ethereum Is A Commodity, Says Joe Lubin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146661/forgone-conclusion-ethererum-is-a-commodity-joe-lubin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T03:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ConsenSys Founder says Gary Gensler may not be able to admit it, but that his hesitancy doesn’t matter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Did Citadel-Backed EDX List Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin, and Bitcoin Cash?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146642</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146642/why-did-citadel-backed-edx-list-bitcoin-ethereum-litecoin-and-bitcoin-cash"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T23:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators appear to have said enough about these four digital assets to assuage Wall Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TUSD Brags About Volume 'Milestone' After Stablecoin Depegs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146637</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146637/tusd-trading-volume-stablecoin-depegs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T22:10:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TrueUSD team touts its high trading activity while holders fret over troubles at custodian Prime Trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Rejected 'Game of Thrones' to Make 'Crypto Unicorns']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146609</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146609/why-laguna-games-rejected-game-thrones-make-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T22:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We didn't start this company [...] to just get jobs at WB," Laguna CEO Aron Beierschmitt said of the decision to make Crypto Unicorns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Farren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Ate Ramen That Was 'Imagined' in the Metaverse—Here's What That Means]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=145627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/145627/ate-ramen-imagined-metaverse-heres-what-that-means"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chef Esther Choi is bringing noodles from the metaverse to the real world. Decrypt tried them and spoke to KPR's creators about their vision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diablo IV Fashion Line Can Summon an AR Demon]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146616</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146616/diablo-iv-augmented-reality-fashion-line-launches-in-london"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The game-themed denim collection, available at a department store pop-up, focuses on Diablo IV's Lilith and her dark aesthetic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Laguna Games Turned Down 'Game of Thrones' for Crypto Unicorns]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/IqET3GYs/why-laguna-games-turned-down-game-of-thrones-for-crypto-unicorns"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin chats with Laguna Games about why the team chose to move away from an offer with WB Games to develop a Game of Thrones licensed title—and made Crypto Unicorns instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firms Swan, Coinbits Disclose Prime Trust Ties as Fallout Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146601</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146601/swan-coinbits-disclose-prime-trust-ties-fallout-continues"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T20:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Swan got their users' funds out of Prime Trust in time, Coinbits has been forced to suspend most of its services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digital Asset Manager 3IQ Adds Ethereum Staking to Two of Its Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146571</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146571/digital-asset-manager-3iq-adds-ethereum-staking-two-funds"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T20:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm’s two Ethereum ETFs will now be the first investment vehicles to offer a staking service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Trader Ordered to Pay $54 Million CFTC Fine Over Crypto Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146591</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146591/ex-trader-finally-ordered-to-pay-54-million-fine-by-cftc"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T20:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ohio resident Michael Ackerman was charged in 2020 for defrauding victims with a bogus crypto trading algorithm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donovan Choy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTX 'Reboot' Talks Begin and Send FTT Token Soaring 15%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=146543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/146543/ftx-reboot-talks-begin-and-send-ftt-token-soaring-15"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T19:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt crypto exchange FTX  would likely rebrand as part of any restart, according to reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games CEO John Linden on NFL Rivals Topping 1M Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nDhvMd8r/mythical-games-ceo-john-linden-on-nfl-rivals-topping-1m-downloads"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T23:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mythical Games just raised a $37 million Series C1 round on the back of the early success of NFL Rivals, which has already topped a million downloads in two months. Mythical CEO John Linden joins Decrypt's Andrew Hayward to discuss the launch and impact of NFL Rivals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ava Labs Is Approaching Gaming on Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/M4TqVEkK/how-ava-labs-is-approaching-gaming-on-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 3XP, Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin to discuss some of the biggest Avalanche-based games on the horizon and how the company is approaching and thinking about Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi Founder David Gull on Why AI Should Be Your Meditation Coach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/DnNqBruk/ogimi-founder-david-gull-on-why-ai-should-be-your-meditation-coach"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T18:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ogimi founder David Gull speaks with Decrypt's Jason Nelson about its AI-driven meditation guides and how the technology can enable a more unique, custom-tailored meditation experience for users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VaynerSports Gaming VP Discusses Web3 Content Creators, Decentralized Streaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/1MvGbnK5/vaynersports-gaming-vp-discusses-web3-content-creators-decentralized-streaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darren Glover, VP of Gaming at talent management agency VaynerSports, sat down with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss the challenges faced by Web3-centric content creators, the current state of the esports market, and how decentralized streaming platforms can challenge centralized leaders like Twitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYXL Co-Founder on the State of Esports and Crypto Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xDHUNFLB/nyxl-co-founder-on-the-state-of-esports-and-crypto-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohit Gupta, co-founder of esports team NYXL, chats with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo to discuss challenges faced by the esports industry and opportunities and experiments in Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is GameBridge? Inside Shrapnel's Gaming Innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/xqVjzGLr/what-is-gamebridge-inside-shrapnels-gaming-innovation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marc Mercuri, Head of Platform for Web3 shooter Shrapnel, speaks with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at the 3XP expo about GameBridge, a feature that simplifies blockchain item composability and interoperability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gods Unchained Executive Producer Discusses Epic Games Store Move]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hjLymzUL/gods-unchained-executive-producer-discusses-epic-games-store-move"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Paez, Executive Producer on Immutable X-based card-battler Gods Unchained, discusses the long-running NFT game's launch on the Epic Games Store and the opportunity it provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Play-to-Earn Is Not Dead. It Will Never Die' Says Words with Friends Creator Paul Bettner]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/znmOo9vp/play-to-earn-is-not-dead-it-will-never-die-says-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner"/>
        <updated>2023-06-20T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard Creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on Axie Infinity and Web3 games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages Game Review: A Tough But Rewarding Card Battler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/2PfzFDVY/cross-the-ages-game-review-a-tough-but-rewarding-card-battler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-18T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross the Ages is a digital collectible card game that challenges players to duel online opponents—and you can even mint your cards as tradable NFTs. It's complex and difficult to grasp at first, but this mobile-first game has some serious strategic upside. GG contributor Ryan Gladwin puts Cross the Ages through its paces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI Is Game-Changing But Needs Fact-Checking": AlchemyAI Project Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HXlThlXv/ai-is-game-changing-but-needs-fact-checking-alchemyai-project-lead"/>
        <updated>2023-06-15T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, Decrypt's Jason Nelson chats with Alchemy product manager and AlchemyAI project lead Elan Halpern on blockchain analysis using ChatGPT, what AI means for better user experience, and the need to fact-check AI. Halpern also gives a demo of the new AlchemyAI ChatGPT plugin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal Is Like an Arcade, Says Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6r6Mdwt6/fractal-is-like-an-arcade-says-twitch-co-founder-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Kan was a co-founder of Twitch and now works on Fractal, a Web3 gaming startup. Kan tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his new company and what he's up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Co-Founder Said There Was No ‘Aha Moment’ When Launching DAO Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CCO and co-founder of Collab.Land Anjali Young explained at this year’s NFC Lisbon the origins of the crypto community tool kit, which industry niches are turning to its suite of products, and what’s next for the project since its token distribution event last February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Slice of H.R. Giger's 'Alien' Is Fine Art, Not Memorabilia: Particle CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With H.R. Giger's original "Alien" statue on full display at this year's NFC Lisbon, Particle CEO Harold Eytan told Decrypt that owning an NFT-ified slice of the piece isn't just for fans of the iconic creature and movie series but also for fine art collectors. Interested in owning a piece? Be prepared to cough up half an ETH for one of the 500 tranches of the digitized sculpture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Co-Creation 'Is a Big Step for Fashion Brands' Entering the Metaverse: BNV Founder and CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder and CEO of metaverse fashion platform BNV Richard Hobbs said big brands are still nervous to let fans and community members customize their favorite garments. Still, he believes that as long as you can meet a firm's commercial bottom lines while stirring engagement, there's nothing to lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>