<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-06-14T19:12:04.948Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-06-14T19:12:04.948Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT Dominance Hits Highest Level Since May 2021, While USDC Slumps]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e1ed21d</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/usdt-dominance-hits-highest-level-2021-usdc-slumps/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows Tether (USDT) has recently observed growth in its dominance, while USD Coin (USDC) and others have lost market share.
 
USDT Dominance Has Grown To A Value Of 67.6% Now
 
According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the relative supply dominance of USDT has continued to increase recently. The “supply dominance” here refers to the percentage of the total supply of the largest stablecoins being contributed by a given stable.
 
The stablecoins included here are Tether (USDT), USD Coin (USDC), Binance USD (BUSD), Dai (DAI), and TrueUSD (TUSD). As is apparent, all of these assets are pegged to the US dollar.
 
These coins all having the same value is also why it’s possible to directly compare their supplies, as their market caps (the metric generally used for making …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hououin Kyouma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Pain: Bitcoin Price Remains Sideways Following Fed Rate Hike Pause]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e1ed219</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/max-pain-bitcoin-price-fed-rate-hike-pause/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:05:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the first pause in a historic series of interest rate hikes by the US Federal Reserve, Bitcoin price appears unaffected, maintaining a steady price range between $25,000 and $28,000. 
 
Amid the market digesting the Fed’s interest rate decision, the leading cryptocurrency has so far exhibited a muted reaction to the central bank’s latest, less-hawkish move. But why?
 
Federal Reserve Puts Rate Hikes — And Bitcoin — On Pause
 
Minutes ago, the Federal Reserve, in a remarkable decision, held its key interest rate steady, temporarily halting what had been the sharpest flurry of rate hikes in four decades. While a pause was expected to provide some direction to the market, Bitcoin, currently trading at $25,800, has remained stable within its current price range.
 
 
In their fight against rampant inflation, Federal Reserve officials have hinted at the possibility of two more rate hikes later this year. This projection surpasses the expectations of many market analysts and economists.
 
Typically, such monetary policy adjustments by central banks have the potential to jolt global financial markets. Yet, the cryptocurrency’s muted response to the recent Federal Reserve actions remains noteworthy. Despite numerous potential catalysts for price fluctuations, the leading cryptocurrency is demonstrating a degree of price stability that belies its reputation for volatility.
 

 
 
Looking Ahead At The Fed’s Fight Against Inflation And Impact On Crypto
 
Looking ahead, the Fed’s continued effort to combat inflation through more rate hikes could introduce further variables into the crypto market landscape. As a potential yet thus unproven hedge against inflation, Bitcoin might yet see movement that bucks the trend.
 
 
Investors and observers will be watching closely as the year unfolds. The prevailing question is whether Bitcoin will maintain its current uncharacteristic stability, or whether the anticipated Federal Reserve actions will eventually trigger a more substantial response.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony &amp;quot;The Bull&amp;quot;</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[USDT Dominance Hits Highest Level Since May 2021, While USDC Slumps]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576299/USDT-Dominance-Hits-Highest-Level-Since-May-2021-While-USDC-Slumps</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576299/USDT-Dominance-Hits-Highest-Level-Since-May-2021-While-USDC-Slumps"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data shows Tether (USDT) has recently observed growth in its dominance, while USD Coin (USDC) and others have lost market share. USDT Dominance Has Grown To A Value Of 67.6% Now According to data from the on-chain analytics firm Glassnode, the relative supply dominance of USDT has continued to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EigenLayer deploys restaking protocol on Ethereum mainnet]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576277/EigenLayer-deploys-restaking-protocol-on-Ethereum-mainnet</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576277/EigenLayer-deploys-restaking-protocol-on-Ethereum-mainnet"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Initial tokens supported in the mainnet launch are stETH, rETH and cbETH — native staking will also be available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puma launches metaverse experience: Nifty Newsletter, June 7–13]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576300/Puma-launches-metaverse-experience-Nifty-Newsletter-June-713</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576300/Puma-launches-metaverse-experience-Nifty-Newsletter-June-713"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Puma launches Black Station, a 3D metaverse experience allowing Puma Pass NFT holders access to exclusive products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is BNB price up today?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576275/Why-is-BNB-price-up-today</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576275/Why-is-BNB-price-up-today"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BNB price has rebounded more than 10% from its six-month low of $220 as short traders were squeezed alongside rising open interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Pain: Bitcoin Price Remains Sideways Following Fed Rate Hike Pause]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576273/Max-Pain-Bitcoin-Price-Remains-Sideways-Following-Fed-Rate-Hike-Pause</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576273/Max-Pain-Bitcoin-Price-Remains-Sideways-Following-Fed-Rate-Hike-Pause"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the first pause in a historic series of interest rate hikes by the US Federal Reserve, Bitcoin price appears unaffected, maintaining a steady price range between $25,000 and $28,000. Amid the market digesting the Fed’s interest rate decision, the leading cryptocurrency has so far...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto prime brokerage FPG halts withdrawals following $15 million cyber attack]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576268/Crypto-prime-brokerage-FPG-halts-withdrawals-following-15-million-cyber-attack</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576268/Crypto-prime-brokerage-FPG-halts-withdrawals-following-15-million-cyber-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Floating Point Group (FPG) has ceased trading, deposits and withdrawals following a "cyber security incident" on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spark Protocol is re-thinking stablecoin stability mechanisms]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576263/Spark-Protocol-is-re-thinking-stablecoin-stability-mechanisms</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576263/Spark-Protocol-is-re-thinking-stablecoin-stability-mechanisms"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The protocol will eventually become a “sub-DAO” in MakerDAO’s Endgame update]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase tells SEC that DEXs can’t be regulated as exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576269/Coinbase-tells-SEC-that-DEXs-cant-be-regulated-as-exchanges</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576269/Coinbase-tells-SEC-that-DEXs-cant-be-regulated-as-exchanges"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase has sent the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission a fresh letter, arguing that it's impossible to regulate DEXs like a central exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers Introduce Bill To Remove Gary Gensler As SEC Chair Following ‘Long Series of Abuses’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576270/Lawmakers-Introduce-Bill-To-Remove-Gary-Gensler-As-SEC-Chair-Following-Long-Series-of-Abuses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576270/Lawmakers-Introduce-Bill-To-Remove-Gary-Gensler-As-SEC-Chair-Following-Long-Series-of-Abuses"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two crypto-friendly Republican lawmakers in the US introduced legislation this week that would remove Gary Gensler as Chair of the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). House Majority Whip Tom Emmer of Minnesota and Representative Warren Davidson of Ohio rolled out the “SEC...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Union AI Act passes in parliament]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576264/European-Union-AI-Act-passes-in-parliament</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576264/European-Union-AI-Act-passes-in-parliament"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Member states will have the opportunity to negotiate final details before the act becomes law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Short term technical headwinds for Bitcoin heading into FOMC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576236/Short-term-technical-headwinds-for-Bitcoin-heading-into-FOMC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576236/Short-term-technical-headwinds-for-Bitcoin-heading-into-FOMC"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Take Currently, Bitcoin is trading around $26,000, but there are a few short-term resistance levels that it is currently facing. The short-term cost holder basis is around $26,400, the average cost basis of investors who hold Bitcoin for 155 days or less. Bitcoin is also trading below the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securitize takes contrarian view in crypto’s war with the SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576242/Securitize-takes-contrarian-view-in-cryptos-war-with-the-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576242/Securitize-takes-contrarian-view-in-cryptos-war-with-the-SEC"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securitize doesn't buy the argument that crypto companies don't know how to register with U.S. regulators — it's done it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU lawmakers vote for landmark Artificial Intelligence regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576233/EU-lawmakers-vote-for-landmark-Artificial-Intelligence-regulation</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576233/EU-lawmakers-vote-for-landmark-Artificial-Intelligence-regulation"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Union Parliament has voted in favour of an AI Act. If ratified, the law will require AI systems like ChatGPT to first undergo review before release to the public. The regulation also seeks a ban on real-time biometric recognition. The European Parliament has yet again made a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO votes to decrease GUSD held in DAI stablecoin reserve]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576202/MakerDAO-votes-to-decrease-GUSD-held-in-DAI-stablecoin-reserve</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576202/MakerDAO-votes-to-decrease-GUSD-held-in-DAI-stablecoin-reserve"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO could soon remove $390M of Gemini’s GUSD stablecoin from its reserves. The DAO is currently voting to decrease the maximum amount of GUSD held in Maker’s DAI stablecoin reserve to $110M. MakerDAO’s reserve currently holds roughly 88% of total GUSD supply. MakerDAO, a decentralized...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed holds interest rates, markets dip into the red]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576201/Fed-holds-interest-rates-markets-dip-into-the-red</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576201/Fed-holds-interest-rates-markets-dip-into-the-red"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto and equities dipped lower Wednesday after the central bank said interest rates wouldn’t be budging]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it Too Late to Buy Binance Coin? BNB Token Blasts Up 12% From Recent Crash and Traders Say This New AI Crypto Signals Platform May Be the Next Best Performer – Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576194/Is-it-Too-Late-to-Buy-Binance-Coin-BNB-Token-Blasts-Up-12-From-Recent-Crash-and-Traders-Say-This-New-AI-Crypto-Signals-Platform-May-Be-the-Next-Best-Performer-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576194/Is-it-Too-Late-to-Buy-Binance-Coin-BNB-Token-Blasts-Up-12-From-Recent-Crash-and-Traders-Say-This-New-AI-Crypto-Signals-Platform-May-Be-the-Next-Best-Performer-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Coin (BNB), the cryptocurrency that powers the Binance Smart Chain, has seen a decent 9% bounce from its recent lows. BNB/USD was last changing hands around $247, having crashed to lows around $220 earlier this week. The cryptocurrency was sent tumbling last week after the US Securities...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price swings as Federal Reserve opts to hold interest rates in place]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576197/Bitcoin-price-swings-as-Federal-Reserve-opts-to-hold-interest-rates-in-place</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576197/Bitcoin-price-swings-as-Federal-Reserve-opts-to-hold-interest-rates-in-place"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Postpones Asset Freeze as Binance US and SEC Agree to Work on Deal]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e057562</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/judge-postpones-asset-freeze-as-binance-us-and-sec-agree-to-work-on-deal/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A judge in Washington decided to give Binance US and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) time to work out a deal to avoid the freezing of the exchange’s assets. The two sides are close to an agreement that will protect customer funds without paralyzing the crypto trading platform.
 
Crypto Exchange Binance US and SEC Near Compromise to Avoid Asset Freeze
 
Binance US, the United States-based subsidiary of the world’s leading digital asset exchange, Binance, and the U.S. securities regulator, the SEC, have agreed to work on a deal which would spare the court from the need to decide whether to freeze the platform’s assets.
 
During a hearing on Tuesday, U.S. District Judge Amy Berman Jackson announced that the exchange and the Commission “aren’t that far apart” on a compromise ensur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Leaves Policy on Hold, Ending Long String of Rate Hikes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e05c36b</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/14/fed-leaves-policy-on-hold-ending-long-string-of-rate-hikes/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. central bank signaled it might restart rate hikes in coming months if inflation doesn't continue to recede.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Reacts to Latest Fed Rate Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576272/Bitcoin-BTC-Reacts-to-Latest-Fed-Rate-Decision</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576272/Bitcoin-BTC-Reacts-to-Latest-Fed-Rate-Decision"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Very costly side effects’: Blockchain Australia hits back at banks limiting crypto payments]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576155/Very-costly-side-effects-Blockchain-Australia-hits-back-at-banks-limiting-crypto-payments</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576155/Very-costly-side-effects-Blockchain-Australia-hits-back-at-banks-limiting-crypto-payments"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country’s preeminent industry body for crypto and blockchain technology said banks should educate their customers on scams instead of restricting access]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Central Bank Would Need To Set Limits on Use of Digital Euro Under Draft Proposal: Bloomberg]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576167/European-Central-Bank-Would-Need-To-Set-Limits-on-Use-of-Digital-Euro-Under-Draft-Proposal-Bloomberg</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18576167/European-Central-Bank-Would-Need-To-Set-Limits-on-Use-of-Digital-Euro-Under-Draft-Proposal-Bloomberg"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judge Denies SEC’s Request To Freeze Binance.US Assets, Calls For Collaborative Compromise]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e063841</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/judge-denies-sec-request-to-freeze-binance-assets/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T18:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent development, US District Judge Amy Berman Jackson has rejected the Securities and Exchange Commission’s (SEC) request to freeze the assets of Binance.US, the American arm of the cryptocurrency trading platform Binance. The court has instead directed both parties to work together in finding a solution that would protect customer funds while allowing Binance.US to continue its operations without interruption and gave the parties until Thursday, June 15 to work out the final details.
 
The SEC’s initial lawsuit against Binance.US, filed on June 5th, included a plea to freeze all assets of the platform, alleging potential commingling of customer funds and offshore transfers. 
 
However, such a freeze would have had severe consequences not only for Binance.US but also for the broade…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler’s Catch-22 Vision of ‘Regulated’ Crypto Brokers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e072d5e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/06/14/gary-genslers-catch-22-vision-of-regulated-crypto-brokers/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T17:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC-registered trading platform Prometheum pitched the House on Gary Gensler's vision. But skeptical legislators highlighted that the platform won't offer major assets, including Bitcoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Z. Morris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MakerDAO Weighs Ditching $390M of Gemini Dollars from DAI Reserve]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e02d956</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/14/makerdao-weighs-ditching-390m-of-gemini-dollars-from-dai-reserve/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T17:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The result could have a significant impact on Gemini and its stablecoin as MakerDAO’s reserve holds roughly 88% of total GUSD supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitstamp Joins FCA’s List of Registered Crypto Companies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e0c69bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitstamp-joins-fcas-list-of-registered-crypto-companies/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T17:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UK arm of cryptocurrency exchange, Bitstamp, has  
been registered by the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) as one of the digital asset  
exchanges that comply with the country’s anti-money laundering (AML) and counter-terrorism  
financing (CTF) regulations. With the registration, Bitstamp UK can provide  
services such keeping custody of crypto assets, facilitating fiat purchases of  
cryptocurrencies and enabling cryptocurrency trading, the company  
said in a statement.
FCA Registers 42 Crypto Firms 
The Luxembourg-based company's registration brings the number of the registered crypto firms compliant with FCA's AML/CTF regulations to  
42. Moreover, the registration brings Bitstamp’s licenses and  
registrations globally to 52.  
Bitstamp is one of the digital  
asset exchanges th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why XRP Failed To Move Following The Release Of Hinman’s Emails]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e0e58b6</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/heres-why-xrp-failed-to-move/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T17:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last week, the XRP community was abuzz with the expectation that the Hinman documents were finally going to be released. The fight to release these documents had waxed on for a long between Ripple and the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) before a judge ruled that the documents be unsealed. However, once the documents were finally released, XRP remained stagnant, which begs the question of why?
 
Hinman Documents Did Not ‘Favor’ Ripple
 
The Hinman documents are emails from William Hinman, the previous SEC director, which contained his opinions about cryptocurrencies such as Ethereum. These documents had reportedly been in favor of cryptocurrencies such as ETH not being classified as securities and the deduction was the documents would help make a case against…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Best Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BCB Group Abandons Sutor Bank Acquisition on Regulatory Delay]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e0861c0</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2023/06/14/bcb-group-abandons-sutor-bank-acquisition-on-regulatory-delay/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The payments processor also cited crypto market conditions as a reason for the exit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lyllah Ledesma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['NFTs Can't Scale' in Current Form, Say Superduper Co-founders]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144579</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144579/nfts-cant-scale-current-format-say-superduper-founders"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC, the Superduper founders stressed that getting NFTs to mass adoption won’t be easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey’s #startsmall Pledges $5 Million Over 5 Years To Bitcoin Nonprofit Brink]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757e0a5eb9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/startsmall-pledges-5-million-over-5-years-to-bitcoin-nonprofit-brink"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin development nonprofit, Brink, has received a significant financial boost with a pledge of $5 million from Jack Dorsey's #startsmall organization. The pledge, totaling $1 million per year for the next five years, aims to support Brink's efforts in funding Bitcoin developers and ensuring the long-term sustainability of Bitcoin's core codebase.
Brink aims to provide fellowship and support to Bitcoin and Bitcoin-adjacent developers. The organization offers developer grants, mentorship programs and funding opportunities to promote open-source development for Bitcoin and related technologies. By nurturing new contributors and decentralizing Bitcoin's protocol development, Brink hopes to strengthen the Bitcoin network and developer ecosystem.
Expressing his gratitude for the generous pledge, Mike Schmidt said, "Brink is very grateful for this extended pledge to support our Bitcoin developer funding efforts. $1,000,000 a year for each of the next 5 years means that we can help make Bitcoin development a sustainable career for the talented developers that are building, securing, testing, and reviewing the Bitcoin Core codebase."
The support from #startsmall will contribute significantly to Brink's mission of supporting Bitcoin development and fostering open-source decentralized systems. This substantial funding injection will enable Brink to provide ongoing support to Bitcoin developers and facilitate their crucial work in maintaining and enhancing the Bitcoin ecosystem.
Brink is actively engaged in creating a sustainable environment for Bitcoin development. With the additional funding, they can attract more talent, further educate developers, and expand their fellowship and grant programs. This financial backing not only demonstrates the commitment of #startsmall to open-source initiatives but also highlights the growing importance of Bitcoin and its underlying technology.
To learn more about Brink and its programs, visit their website at brink.dev.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BtcCasey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Ecosystem Is Getting Busier, Not Quieter, Amid Layer 2 Shift]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff69f9c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/06/14/ethereum-ecosystem-is-getting-busier-not-quieter-amid-layer-2-shift/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many transactions are getting offloaded onto layer-2 blockchains, and those should be included in any analysis of the Ethereum ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Kunke, Brian Rudick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Crypto Lesson From George Soros Amid Binance and Coinbase Accusations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff69f88</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/06/14/a-crypto-lesson-from-george-soros-amid-binance-and-coinbase-accusations/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Positioning and expectations explain why the Binance case drove prices down but markets rebounded after Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Groth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Graph Starts Migrating its Settlement Layer to Arbitrum from Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff69f77</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/06/14/the-graph-starts-migrating-its-settlement-layer-to-arbitrum-from-ethereum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transition is aimed at reducing barriers of entry for The Graph’s users by decreasing gas costs and speeding up transactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bittrex Gets Green Light: Court Order Allows Withdrawals Starting June 15]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff6dd30</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bittrex-green-light-court-order-allows-withdrawals/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 15, clients of the United States division of the bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange Bittrex will be able to withdraw their assets, following a court ruling by a Delaware bankruptcy court. 
 
The exchange had declared bankruptcy in May, but the United States Justice Department had opposed Bittrex’s efforts to restore customer access to their assets, citing millions in unpaid penalties for sanctions breaches.
 
Bittrex Withdrawals Unlocked
 
A Delaware bankruptcy court has issued an order by Judge Brendan Shannon allowing the US division of Bittrex to begin facilitating customer withdrawals.
 
The order was issued in response to a motion filed by Bittrex’s debtors in possession and allows the exchange to permit customers with “undisputed, noncontingent, and liquidated claims” to withdr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adoption: Belgian Fast Food Chain To Accept Crypto Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff6dd27</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/fast-food-chain-to-integrate-crypto-payments-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto industry is rapidly expanding and gradually creeping into crypto payment systems as more businesses adopt cryptocurrencies as a payment option. In the latest development, French fast food chain Black & White Burger’s Belgian franchise has added support for crypto payments.
 
The fast food chain announced that its 12 stores nationwide would accept cryptocurrencies as payments. A June 13 tweet revealed that Black & White Burger is bringing this payment feature through a partnership with a French crypto app developer, Lyzi. 
 
Customers Can Pay for Burgers In Seventy Cryptocurrencies
 
Media outlet L’Echo reported that the partnership would allow Black & White Burger customers to pay in 70 cryptocurrencies, including Bitcoin and Ethereum. The report also noted that this development…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: XRP 9% Lower, as Price Falls From 10-Week High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff73161</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-xrp-9-lower-as-price-falls-from-10-week-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XRP plunged by over 9% on Wednesday, as traders moved to secure profits following a recent ten-week high. This decline comes as overall market sentiment remains bearish, following last week’s actions by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). Cardano was also back in the red today.
 
XRP
 
XRP, formerly ripple, dropped by over 9% in today’s session, as traders seemingly moved to secure recent gains.
 
XRP/USD rose to a ten-week high of $0.5614 on Tuesday, however today’s sell-off has sent the token to a bottom at $0.5009.
 
The decline comes as bulls were unable to maintain yesterday’s breakout of a key resistance level at $0.5490.
 
 
Looking at the chart, the shift in sentiment came as the relative strength index (RSI) retreated to a floor of its own at 52.00
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking marginally above this point at 52.11, with a ceiling of 58.00 the possible target for bulls.
 
In the event it reaches this level, it is likely that XRP will once again be trading above $0.5500.
 
 
Cardano (ADA)
 
Cardano (ADA) was another notable token to move into the red on Wednesday, with the price remaining close to a key support point.
 
Following a high of $0.2895 on Tuesday, ADA/USD dropped to an intraday low of $0.2699 today.
 
As a result of the move, cardano remained near its long-term price floor at $0.2700, which was broken over the weekend.
 
 
Saturday’s drop sent ADA to its weakest point since January, however this decline was short lived, with bulls sweeping in to buy the dip.
 
Despite rebounding in recent days, the RSI continues to track below 30.00, which is a sign of current bearish pressure.
 
Bulls are likely looking at the $0.3000 level as a short-term target, however there will likely be a high level of volatility preventing this point from being hit.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will there be a price recovery in cardano this week? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Distributed Validator Technology’ Marks Last Key Milestone in Ethereum’s Current Era]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff77fbd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2023/06/14/distributed-validator-technology-marks-last-key-milestone-in-ethereums-current-era/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T16:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The technology known as DVT involves splitting a validator's private key across several node operators. The goal is to increase the network's resilience – while also protect the individual validators – by reducing single points of failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sage D. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Hard Fork to Stave Off SEC? Devs Say It's Not Happening]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144576/solana-hard-fork-devs-say-its-not-happening"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I work on the largest Solana project, with more than 10 developers, and nobody is discussing [a hard fork]” said Matías Kudelski, a cyber security researcher who audits Solana’s code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US and the SEC Negotiate to Avoid Total Asset Freeze]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ffc653c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/binanceus-and-the-sec-negotiate-to-avoid-total-asset-freeze/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T15:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance.US, the US affiliate of cryptocurrency  
exchange, Binance, and the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) are working  
on an agreement to avoid a total freeze of the exchange's assets. The  
negotiations are currently before a magistrate court.  According to the  
information shared with Bloomberg today (Wednesday), US District Judge Amy  
Berman Jackson said the agreement is important to protect investors' funds  
without closing the exchange's operations while the case proceeded.
Temporary Restraining  
Order
Finance Magnates  
reported on May 7 that the SEC had filed  
a motion to obtain a  
temporary restraining order to freeze the assets of BAM Management US Holdings  
and BAM Trading Services, the holdings and operating company affiliated with  
Binance.US. The motion was…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jared Kirui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators Turn Up The Heat On Crypto: Binance Asks To Exit Cyprus]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e757ff80dc0</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/regulators-turn-up-heat-crypto-binance-exit-cyprus/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T15:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to CoinDesk’s report, the Cyprus Securities and Exchange Commission (CSEC) received a petition to deregister Binance’s subsidiary in the country. If approved, the crypto company will no longer operate as a service provider in the country. 
 
 
The application has been uploaded to the CSEC’s official website. The crypto company was granted registration in Cyprus in 2022 under 427114.
 
The company could offer crypto trading, management, transfer, custody, and other financial services. This included the “provision of investment advice.” As of this writing, the application for deregistration is under examination.
 
 
Binance Under Pressure From All Sides
 
Less than a year ago, Binance celebrated securing a registration to operate in Cyprus. At that time, the crypto company was gran…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reynaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Firms Should Start Preparing for MiCA ‘Now–Maybe Even Yesterday’: Chainalysis]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144572</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144572/crypto-firms-should-start-preparing-mica-now-maybe-even-yesterday-chainalysis"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T13:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiCA comes into effect next year, but that doesn't mean crypto firms should wait to become compliant, said Chainalysis' EU policy lead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Drops 5% as Markets Digest Hinman Documents, SEC Court Case]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144569/xrp-drops-markets-digest-hinman-documents-sec-court-case"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T13:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A day after the so-called Hinman documents were unsealed, XRP hasn't enjoyed the bullish effect that many enthusiasts had hoped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fashion Brands Still ‘Nervous’ to Set IP Loose in Metaverse: BNV CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144555/fashion-brands-still-nervous-set-ip-loose-in-metaverse-bnv-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T10:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Allowing users to create their own versions of products is a “big step” for brands, BNV CEO Richard Hobbs told Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Legal Chief Calls for Investigation Into Former SEC Director Hinman]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144543/ripple-legal-chief-calls-investigation-former-sec-director-hinman"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T09:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any “serious discussion” about whether a token is a security should never again refer to Hinman’s speech, argued Ripple's legal chief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaverse Tokens Lead Weekly Crypto Losses Amid SEC’s Securities Allegations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144537/metaverse-tokens-lead-weekly-crypto-losses-sec-securities-allegations"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T09:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tokens powering various metaverse projects have failed to pump even after the highly anticipated launch of Apple’s new headset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Reverends Lead a Church Congregation of 300 in Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144502</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144502/ai-reverends-lead-a-300-people-congregation-in-germany"/>
        <updated>2023-06-14T00:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because it’s about the message, and not about the messenger—or is it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Mint This Ridiculous Song About Vitalik Buterin as a Free NFT]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144498</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144498/you-can-mint-this-ridiculous-song-about-vitalik-buterin-as-a-free-nft"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T23:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As music NFT platform Sound.xyz adds support for Ethereum layer-2 Optimism, the projects' co-founders deliver a rousing tribute to Vitalik.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Refuses to Respond to Coinbase’s Rulemaking Petition Following Lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144454</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144454/sec-refuses-respose-coinbase-rulemaking-petition-lawsuit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T23:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit had asked the SEC to clarify its position on a rulemaking petition from Coinbase.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US 'Has Not Yet Determined Whether It Will Pursue a CBDC,' Says Treasury Official]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144476</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144476/the-u-s-has-not-yet-determined-whether-it-will-pursue-a-cbdc-says-treasury-official"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T21:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Treasury is leading an interagency group that is researching a “potential” U.S. central bank digital currency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Much Energy Does Bitcoin Really Use? Less Than You Might Think]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144438</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144438/how-much-energy-does-bitcoin-really-use-less-than-you-might-think"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T21:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The study uses ASIC model "fingerprints" to understand Bitcoin’s energy use, saying it's wrong to assume the same efficiency across mining rigs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will ‘10X’ With Regulatory Clarity, Says Michael Saylor]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144465</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144465/bitcoin-will-10x-with-regulatory-clarity-says-michael-saylor"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The head of MicroStrategy says it’s time to accept that ‘Bitcoin is the next Bitcoin.’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas Reveals Sneaker Collab With NFT Artist Fewocious]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144457</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144457/adidas-reveals-sneaker-collab-nft-artist-fewocious"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fewocious, a prominent Web3 artist, has teamed with the apparel giant to launch the Adidas Originals Campus 00s via NFT redemption ticket.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Farren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are NFTs the Next SEC Target?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YaGgY87J/are-nfts-the-next-sec-target"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin discusses the current regulatory climate in the U.S. with Gala Games' President of Blockchain Jason Brink.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Pocketed More Than $100M in Atomic Wallet Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144444</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144444/north-korean-hackers-pocket-over-100-m-in-atomic-wallet-heist"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T19:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazarus Groupe hacked crypto wallet service Atomic Wallet earlier this month, Elliptic said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg's NFT Tour Pass Lets Fans 'Travel the World' With Him Virtually]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144446</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144446/snoop-dogg-nft-tour-pass-fans-virtual-travel-world-tour"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T19:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Arbitrum-based NFT pass will let fans join the rapper’s summer tour via exclusive benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong's New Crypto Rules Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144436</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144436/hong-kong-new-crypto-rules-explained"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T19:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulators say they'll welcome firms with "genuine operations and genuine business practices," which could mean an office or employees in Hong Kong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Meta AI Music Tool Is Trained on 10,000 Hours of ‘Licensed Music’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144425</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144425/new-meta-ai-music-tool-musicgen-trained-hours-licensed-music"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T18:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Google's MusicLM, MusicGen can turn a descriptive text prompt into short clips of music.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul McCartney Says 'Final' Beatles Song Coming Soon—Thanks to AI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144415</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144415/paul-mccartney-says-final-beatles-song-coming-soon-thanks-ai"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T17:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The track will be out later this year with the help of AI technology developed in the making of Peter Jackson’s “Get Back” documentary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's in the SEC's Hinman Emails and Do They Really Help Ripple?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144404</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144404/whats-in-the-secs-hinman-emails-and-do-they-really-help-ripple"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T16:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The emails about former SEC director Williiam Hinman's 2018 speech saying Ethereum is not a security have been released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Morgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Makes No Sense’ to Tether Crypto Users to Desktops, Says Zerion on Mobile Wallet Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144399</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144399/makes-no-sense-tether-crypto-users-desktops-says-zerion-mobile-wallet-launch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zerion’s head of growth unpacked the strategy of launching a mobile-first crypto wallet in an industry dominated by desktop competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple App Store Says Damus Has 2 Weeks to Cut Bitcoin Tipping or Get Booted]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144374</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144374/apple-app-store-says-damus-has-2-weeks-cut-bitcoin-tipping-get-booted"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Damus has been given 14 days to remove Bitcoin payments and implement in-app purchases or it will be removed from the App Store.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guy Fieri and Sammy Hagar's Tequila Brand Launches NFT Loyalty Program]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144378</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144378/guy-fieri-sammy-hagar-tequila-brand-launches-nft-loyalty-program"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The celebrity stars’ Santo Spirits Club will reward users with “mystery” NFTs alongside real-world rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XRP Jumps After Highly Anticipated Hinman Docs Are Unsealed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144375</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144375/xrp-jumps-unsealing-highly-anticipated-hinman-documents"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T13:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Hinman documents, referring to a speech from a former director, are finally released, the price of the XRP token has soared.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Update Means 'The Possibilities Are Pretty Endless,' Says Developer]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144307</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144307/uniswap-v4-open-source-hooks-singleton"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The platform has announced its fourth version, open sourcing the draft core code for others to build upon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Sui? The Latest 'Solana Killer' From Former Diem Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=138597</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-sui-the-latest-solana-killer-from-former-diem-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T12:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sui sets itself apart from other Layer 1 chains with its focus on instant transaction finality, reduced latency in smart contract deployment, and overall transaction speed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Rise as Inflation Eases to 4% in May]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144362</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144362/bitcoin-ethereum-rise-inflation-eases-4-may"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T12:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve is watching, with a key meeting later this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee's Key Focus for Big Brands? Building 'a Better NFT', Says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144358</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144358/arianee-key-focus-big-brands-building-better-nft-says-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T11:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NFTs are becoming more dynamic, letting brands join Web3 to integrate their digital assets into their marketing stack, said Arianee’s CEO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Earn Platform Haru Invest Freezes Withdrawals, Citing Service Partner Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144354</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144354/crypto-earn-platform-haru-invest-freezes-withdrawals-citing-service-partner-issue"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The South Korea-based crypto earn platform Haru has halted withdrawals for a reported 80,000 users across 140 countries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Tokenization Was Not Created to Evade Laws': Ava Labs CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144346</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144346/tokenization-was-not-created-evade-laws-ava-labs-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto stalwart Emin Gün Sirer will come up in defense of blockchain technologies at today’s testimony before the House Financial Services Committee.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUI Leads Crypto Market Rebound With 8% Rise Overnight]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144347</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144347/sui-leads-crypto-market-recovery-rise-overnight"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to a recent project update and a few contrarian bets in the futures market, the token powering Sui has led the latest rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collab.Land Co-Founder Said There Was No ‘Aha Moment’ When Launching DAO Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kcBRKFGk/collabland-co-founder-said-there-was-no-aha-moment-when-launching-dao-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T09:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CCO and co-founder of Collab.Land Anjali Young explained at this year’s NFC Lisbon the origins of the crypto community tool kit, which industry niches are turning to its suite of products, and what’s next for the project since its token distribution event last February.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying a Slice of H.R. Giger's 'Alien' Is Fine Art, Not Memorabilia: Particle CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/VACG0WVg/buying-a-slice-of-hr-gigers-alien-is-fine-art-not-memorabilia-particle-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With H.R. Giger's original "Alien" statue on full display at this year's NFC Lisbon, Particle CEO Harold Eytan told Decrypt that owning an NFT-ified slice of the piece isn't just for fans of the iconic creature and movie series but also for fine art collectors. Interested in owning a piece? Be prepared to cough up half an ETH for one of the 500 tranches of the digitized sculpture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community Co-Creation 'Is a Big Step for Fashion Brands' Entering the Metaverse: BNV Founder and CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/z6NSMnNm/community-co-creation-is-a-big-step-for-fashion-brands-entering-the-metaverse-bnv-founder-and-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T08:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The founder and CEO of metaverse fashion platform BNV Richard Hobbs said big brands are still nervous to let fans and community members customize their favorite garments. Still, he believes that as long as you can meet a firm's commercial bottom lines while stirring engagement, there's nothing to lose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaverse Beauty Week Aims to Showcase the Branding Potential of the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144327</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144327/metaverse-beauty-week-aims-showcase-branding-potential-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T02:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immersive games and events across Decentraland, Spatial, and Roblox this week will invite users to experience cosmetic brands in new ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Fights Back Against SEC Lawsuit Over Alleged Securities Violations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144334</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144334/binance-fights-back-against-sec-lawsuit-over-securities-law"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T01:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange filed more than 20 motions and declarations late Monday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rishi Sunak’s £100 Million Plan to Make the UK an AI Hub]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144318</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144318/richi-sunaks-100-million-plan-to-make-the-uk-an-ai-hub"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T01:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prime Minister wants early access to OpenAI and Google’s new LLMs “for safety purposes.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Ordinals Hype Lures Meme Token Traders Into Wallet Drainer Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144320</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144320/bitcoin-ordinals-hype-lures-meme-token-traders-wallet-drainer-attack"/>
        <updated>2023-06-13T01:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A convincing-looking BRC-20 token mint on Friday apparently swiped some $63,000 worth of Bitcoin from unsuspecting traders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Solo Bitcoin Miner Hits the Jackpot for $160,000]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144309</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144309/another-solo-bitcoin-miner-hits-the-jackpot-for-160000"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T23:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beating one-to-5,500 odds, the miner solved a block by renting six-year-old hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto-Friendly Congressmen Draft Bill to Reform SEC, Fire Gary Gensler]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=144280</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/144280/congressmen-draft-bill-to-fire-gary-gensler"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T23:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The congressman aims to decentralize the structure of the SEC, and free the agency from its "tyrannical Chairman."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standard Crypto VC Co-Founder on NFTs and Their Stigma in Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bmtrrLio/standard-crypto-vc-co-founder-on-nfts-and-their-stigma-in-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-12T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alok Vasudev is a co-founder of venture capital firm Standard Crypto. In an interview with Decrypt's Kate Irwin, he shares his thoughts on NFT marketing, NFT utility in gaming, and the stigma that pervades the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Announces Avalanche Arcad3 for Game Developers at 3XP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XPHp9r4j/ava-labs-announces-avalanche-arcad3-for-game-developers-at-3xp"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T15:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs Head of Gaming Ed Chang shares news with Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the crypto firm's latest push to help traditional game developers break into blockchain gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Like a Middle Finger to Western Culture’: YuYu Unpacks Inspiration Behind NFT Expo GAG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Vuoplr6a/like-a-middle-finger-to-western-culture-yuyu-unpacks-inspiration-behind-nft-expo-gag"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this year’s NFC Lisbon, multimedia artist and photographer YuLiang "YuYu" Liu broke down how themes from traditional painting and BDSM informed his latest NFT exhibition called “GAG.” He also shared exclusively with Decrypt a yet-to-be-launched drop for fans of his work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Competition Was Rather Low' in Mobile Wallet Space, Says Zerion Head of Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/vCg8O2oy/competition-was-rather-low-in-mobile-wallet-space-says-zerion-head-of-growth"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zerion's move to launch a mobile-first crypto wallet not only helped NFT users swap jpegs on the go but was also a play to get away from crypto's desktop-centric user experience. And with such little competition, Zerion's head of growth Alexander Guy told Decrypt at NFC Lisbon it's managed to rake in 150,000 funded wallets. Next step? Taking on MetaMask and contending as a browser-extension wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘We’ve Never Seen Anything Like This in VR’, Says The Sandbox COO on Apple’s Vision Pro Headset]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/GQ29RaHw/weve-never-seen-anything-like-this-in-vr-says-the-sandbox-coo-on-apples-vision-pro-headset"/>
        <updated>2023-06-09T13:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sandbox COO Sebastien Borget told Decrypt at this year’s NFC Lisbon that despite the high price point, Apple’s new VR headset is nonetheless “groundbreaking.” And though the tech giant never used the term “metaverse” in its reveal, Borget is sure that the technology will be key in growing participation in various digital worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Gala Safe? Gala Games Head of Blockchain on GALA, Crypto, and SEC Regulatory Turmoil]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5bcrE8nL/is-gala-safe-gala-games-head-of-blockchain-on-gala-crypto-and-sec-regulatory-turmoil"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gala Games President of Blockchain shares his thoughts on the GALA token upgrade and the latest SEC turmoil with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artists Adopting NFTs Has Been ‘Really Market Dependent’, Says NFT Club Berlin’s Rebekka Revel]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/QKlIVlj3/artists-adopting-nfts-has-been-really-market-dependent-says-nft-club-berlins-rebekka-revel"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T15:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting non-crypto artists to make the leap into Web3 comes in ebbs and flows according to the market’s bear and bull waves, says co-founder of NFT Club Berlin and Superteam Germany Rebekka Revel. But she’s hoping to change that by changing the narrative around digital collectibles, regardless of the market, one word at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Exploring Web3 to ‘Scale Up Their Super-fan Base’: Superduper Co-founder]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/he6UzJwz/big-brands-exploring-web3-to-scale-up-their-super-fan-base-superduper-co-founder"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T14:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Co-founder and co-CEO of Web3 media brand Superduper Dom Smith says big brands are eager to enter the space—they just don’t know how. Still, they all maintain a thesis of turning their communities into “super fans” that generate value for users as well as a firm’s bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How 1 Simple Question Kickstarted Performance Artist Foodmasku's Plunge Into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/w86DMn3p/how-1-simple-question-kickstarted-performance-artist-foodmaskus-plunge-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As his food mask creations went viral on the Internet during the COVID lockdowns, reposted on TikTok and Instagram without his consent, he soon asked: "How do I protect my digital files?" Performance artist Foodmasku describes at this year's NFC Lisbon how that simple question spiraled into a minting collection after collection of his edible works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pegs Wine and Spirits as Next 'Exciting' Industry to Make Web3 Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Bo2NeG9Z/arianee-ceo-pegs-wine-and-spirits-as-next-exciting-industry-to-make-web3-leap"/>
        <updated>2023-06-08T09:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEO and co-founder of Arianee Pierre Nicolas Hurstel unpacks the wide spectrum of digital collectibles from 10,000 PFP collections to access passes for exclusive events. And with an unannounced big brand soon joining, Hurstel revealed at NFC Lisbon which kind of NFTs big brands are moving towards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam J. Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Words With Friends' Creator Paul Bettner is 'Allergic' to Pay-to-Win NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JkfOleb4/why-words-with-friends-creator-paul-bettner-is-allergic-to-pay-to-win-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Words With Friends and Wildcard creator Paul Bettner tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about his perspective on what to do when NFTs become in-game characters and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch Co-Founder Justin Kan: 18 Months is 'Several Decades' in Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rKVvsPFb/twitch-co-founder-justin-kan-18-months-is-several-decades-in-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-06-07T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fractal and Twitch co-founder Justin Kan gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin an update on all things Fractal and his perspective on blockchain technology in gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing for Money in Web3 Games Not 'Durable,' Says Fractal's Justin Kan]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MQG3SaBM/playing-for-money-in-web3-games-not-durable-says-fractals-justin-kan"/>
        <updated>2023-06-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitch and Fractal co-founder Justin Kan and Fractal co-founder Dan Borstelmann share their perspectives on Web3 gaming's changing landscape with Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Cyber Cafe to Web3: How Everquest Dev Jeffrey Butler Got Into Game Development]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/hRlI4WXe/from-cyber-cafe-to-web3-how-everquest-dev-jeffrey-butler-got-into-game-development"/>
        <updated>2023-06-05T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everquest developer turned Avalon Chief Product Officer Jeffrey Butler tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he got into game development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Machines Arena Game Preview: Is This the Next Overwatch?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/tT0qWy4s/the-machines-arena-game-preview-is-this-the-next-overwatch"/>
        <updated>2023-06-02T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt contributor Ryan S. Gladwin shares an inside look at The Machines Arena, an upcoming top-down 4v4 shooter from Directive Games that will offer NFTs minted on Ethereum sidechain network Ronin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You 'Have' to Be on Mobile: InfiniGods Cofounders on Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/l3KBurz4/you-have-to-be-on-mobile-infinigods-cofounders-on-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-06-01T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[InfiniGods developers Damon Gura and Owen O’Donoghue share their stance on why mobile gaming is essential to Web3 adoption and general success in the video games industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>