<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-11T22:15:11.679Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-06-11T22:15:11.679Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Stock Surges as Roaring Kitty Skewers Recent Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234856/gamestop-stock-surges-roaring-kitty-skewers-losses"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two days of rough declines, GameStop (GME) shares shot up Tuesday—and influencer Roaring Kitty poked fun at his recent paper losses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin potential upside muted by hedge funds shorting futures, Glassnode reports]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578199/Bitcoin-potential-upside-muted-by-hedge-funds-shorting-futures-Glassnode-reports</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578199/Bitcoin-potential-upside-muted-by-hedge-funds-shorting-futures-Glassnode-reports"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the impressive flows registered by spot Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) in the US have seen impressive inflows, the expected positive impact on the market prices is being hindered by a strategy called "cash-and-carry." According to on-chain analysis firm Glassnode, investors are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Unveils $1 Billion Warchest For Deals And Investments In Key Markets]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741721bcd3</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/tether-1-billion-warchest-investments-key-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Tether and its investment arm, Tether Investments, have revealed their intention to allocate more than $1 billion to various investment opportunities over the next 12 months. 
 
According to a Bloomberg report, Paolo Ardoino, Chief Executive Officer behind the USDT stablecoin, shared insights into the company’s next investment strategies and areas of focus in a recent interview.
 
Tether’s Expansion Plans
 
According to the report, the firm is particularly interested in alternative financial infrastructure for emerging markets, artificial intelligence (AI), and biotechnology, with approximately $2 billion invested in these sectors.
 
 
Tether has invested most of its reserves, which back USDT, in US Treasury bills and other securities. This strategy has resulted in signif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Unveils $1 Billion Warchest For Deals And Investments In Key Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578188/Tether-Unveils-1-Billion-Warchest-For-Deals-And-Investments-In-Key-Markets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578188/Tether-Unveils-1-Billion-Warchest-For-Deals-And-Investments-In-Key-Markets"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoin issuer Tether and its investment arm, Tether Investments, have revealed their intention to allocate more than $1 billion to various investment opportunities over the next 12 months. According to a Bloomberg report, Paolo Ardoino, Chief Executive Officer behind the USDT stablecoin,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Holders Flee to This Bitcoin ICO – 1,000% Gains Ahead?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578166/Shiba-Inu-Holders-Flee-to-This-Bitcoin-ICO-1000-Gains-Ahead</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578166/Shiba-Inu-Holders-Flee-to-This-Bitcoin-ICO-1000-Gains-Ahead"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu is followed market trends by dropping a total of 6.69% as of Tuesday afternoon, with investors exploring new opportunities like successful Bitcoin ICO 99bitcoins as they hunt for 1,000% gains. The excitement for 99bitcoins comes on the heels of April's halving event and the approval of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micheal Saylor on Why Bitcoin Development is Slow #bitcoin #bitcoinnews #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578100/Micheal-Saylor-on-Why-Bitcoin-Development-is-Slow-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578100/Micheal-Saylor-on-Why-Bitcoin-Development-is-Slow-bitcoin-bitcoinnews-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micheal Saylor is an ossification maxiBrought to you by Bitcoinwell.com a bitcoin-only platform on a mission to enable independence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Altcoin Assets Also Melted With The Decline – Here is Trump’s Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578093/Donald-Trumps-Altcoin-Assets-Also-Melted-With-The-Decline-Here-is-Trumps-Loss</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578093/Donald-Trumps-Altcoin-Assets-Also-Melted-With-The-Decline-Here-is-Trumps-Loss"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:19:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the latest decline in the cryptocurrency market, former US President Donald Trump's assets also melted. Continue Reading: Donald Trump’s Altcoin Assets Also Melted With The Decline – Here is Trump’s Loss]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Meeting Highlights Shift to Local Currencies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74172f5586</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-meeting-highlights-shift-to-local-currencies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Ministers of Foreign Affairs have emphasized using local currencies in trade, reaffirming economic resilience and financial sovereignty. At their meeting on Monday, the Ministers underscored the importance of the enhanced use of local currencies in financial transactions between the BRICS countries. BRICS Ministers Push for Use of Local Currencies The BRICS Ministers of Foreign […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoins Get Hit]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578079/Memecoins-Get-Hit</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578079/Memecoins-Get-Hit"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fed Meeting anxiety is causing traders to jettison their riskiest crypto holdings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Struggling With MEV Bots, Executive Argues That Solana Has Succeeded]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417290262</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-mev-bots-solana-has-succeeded/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike Bitcoin, where transactions are ordered on a first-come, first-served basis, Ethereum and Solana rely on a pool of validators to confirm transactions and add them to the next block. This process allows for flexibility, as users can expedite their transactions by paying higher fees.
 
At the protocol level, prioritizing transactions based on gas fees has inadvertently led to the rise of complex Maximal Extractable Value (MEV) bots on Solana and Ethereum. By exploiting the system, these bots have become a significant factor in the ongoing debate about gas fees.
 
MEV Bots Pushing Gas Fees Higher On Ethereum?
 
Now, the debate surrounding validators, gas fees, and the impact of MEV bots on Solana and Ethereum is escalating. Mert Mumtaz, the co-founder of Solana RPC provider Helius, tak…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$1 Billion in Bitcoin Just Moved from Coinbase — Are Whales Massively Buying the Dip?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578076/1-Billion-in-Bitcoin-Just-Moved-from-Coinbase-Are-Whales-Massively-Buying-the-Dip</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578076/1-Billion-in-Bitcoin-Just-Moved-from-Coinbase-Are-Whales-Massively-Buying-the-Dip"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:02:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The major transaction occurred as the price of the premier digital currency dropped below $67k earlier today, a -3% change in the last 24 hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 BTC Layer 2 Coins! #shorts]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578081/Top-3-BTC-Layer-2-Coins-shorts</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578081/Top-3-BTC-Layer-2-Coins-shorts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 BTC Layer 2 Coins!Check out Tectum: https://x.com/tectumsocialIntroducing the ALTCOINBUZZ ALPHA x DECUBATE Special Offer! Decubate Bronze+ Tier Members can now claim a full refund on your 1st month of Altcoin Buzz Alpha Membership!Eligibility✅ Submit your Bronze+ Member email ID to #Alpha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Struggling With MEV Bots, Executive Argues That Solana Has Succeeded]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578063/Ethereum-Struggling-With-MEV-Bots-Executive-Argues-That-Solana-Has-Succeeded</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578063/Ethereum-Struggling-With-MEV-Bots-Executive-Argues-That-Solana-Has-Succeeded"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike Bitcoin, where transactions are ordered on a first-come, first-served basis, Ethereum and Solana rely on a pool of validators to confirm transactions and add them to the next block. This process allows for flexibility, as users can expedite their transactions by paying higher fees. At the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Bill Miller believes Bitcoin is ‘significantly undervalued’ at current market cap]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578044/Billionaire-investor-Bill-Miller-believes-Bitcoin-is-significantly-undervalued-at-current-market-cap</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578044/Billionaire-investor-Bill-Miller-believes-Bitcoin-is-significantly-undervalued-at-current-market-cap"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire investor Bill Miller IV, Chairman and CIO of Miller Value Partners, reiterated his unwavering belief in Bitcoin in a June 11 blog post titled “Why I’m Still Betting on Bitcoin.” Despite Bitcoin’s significant gains against fiat currencies, Miller argued that the flagship crypto...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CBDCs' threat to freedom put under the microscope at Oslo conference]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578030/CBDCs-threat-to-freedom-put-under-the-microscope-at-Oslo-conference</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578030/CBDCs-threat-to-freedom-put-under-the-microscope-at-Oslo-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attendees of the 2024 Oslo Freedom Forum were united in addressing the threat that central bank digital currencies (CBDCs) pose to freedom around the globe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation, Interest Rates, and Bitcoin: What Traders Are Watching]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578046/Inflation-Interest-Rates-and-Bitcoin-What-Traders-Are-Watching</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578046/Inflation-Interest-Rates-and-Bitcoin-What-Traders-Are-Watching"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A significant week awaits the cryptocurrency market, with incoming Consumer Price Index (CPI) data and Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) interest rate decisions. Michaël van de Poppe, founder of MN Trading, emphasizes the importance of these events for market dynamics. Bitcoin and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Presidential Election Comes Down To Crypto, Mark Cuban Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578004/US-Presidential-Election-Comes-Down-To-Crypto-Mark-Cuban-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578004/US-Presidential-Election-Comes-Down-To-Crypto-Mark-Cuban-Says"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Mark Cuban claims that Biden and Trump's stances towards cryptocurrencies may be costly when it comes to making it to the Oval Office. The billionaire's take comes as the two White House hopefuls remain neck and neck in official polls despite the election being less than six months away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwala and Curve Announce Partnership for Digital Wallet Integration]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741715b30b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitwala-and-curve-announce-partnership-for-digital-wallet-integration/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwala, a blockchain banking service based in Berlin, has entered into a partnership with Curve, a digital wallet provider. The partnership is aimed at integrating Bitwala’s services with Curve’s digital wallet. Users can add Bitwala to their Curve Wallet and avail a 1% cashback offer on their purchases for 30 days. The Curve card can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bonk Price Prediction as Crypto Prices Crash – Can BONK Recover?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577998/Bonk-Price-Prediction-as-Crypto-Prices-Crash-Can-BONK-Recover</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577998/Bonk-Price-Prediction-as-Crypto-Prices-Crash-Can-BONK-Recover"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:23:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today BONK has experienced growth despite a market crash that saw major meme coins fall 5-10%, hinting towards a potential recovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PleasrDAO files lawsuit against Martin Shkreli]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577996/PleasrDAO-files-lawsuit-against-Martin-Shkreli</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577996/PleasrDAO-files-lawsuit-against-Martin-Shkreli"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized autonomous organization claimed Shkreli’s livestream of a one-of-a-kind Wu-Tang Clan album owned by the DAO caused undue damage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum, Dogecoin Dump Before FOMC Wednesday: Here's What They Did After Prior Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578031/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Dump-Before-FOMC-Wednesday-Heres-What-They-Did-After-Prior-Meetings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578031/Bitcoin-Ethereum-Dogecoin-Dump-Before-FOMC-Wednesday-Heres-What-They-Did-After-Prior-Meetings"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency markets have sold off prior to the CPI data release on Wednesday, with major meme coins being hit particularly hard. Prices as of 3.30 p.m. ET: read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brett Coin Soars as Dogecoin Rival Raises $3.7M – Next Crypto to Watch?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577975/Brett-Coin-Soars-as-Dogecoin-Rival-Raises-37M-Next-Crypto-to-Watch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577975/Brett-Coin-Soars-as-Dogecoin-Rival-Raises-37M-Next-Crypto-to-Watch"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, the Brett coin has surged to a new all-time high, establishing itself as Coinbase’s first multi-billion market cap Base meme coin. This article will provide an analysis of Brett’s current price trends and look to see whether an innovative new meme coin, PLAY, represents a more...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin, Shiba Inu Continue To Drive High Trading Volume, Report Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578000/Dogecoin-Shiba-Inu-Continue-To-Drive-High-Trading-Volume-Report-Finds</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19578000/Dogecoin-Shiba-Inu-Continue-To-Drive-High-Trading-Volume-Report-Finds"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coins remain a major force in the cryptocurrency market and drive major trading volume, according to a new research report. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europol Criticizes Bitcoin Mining, Says It Attracts Criminal Actors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577959/Europol-Criticizes-Bitcoin-Mining-Says-It-Attracts-Criminal-Actors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577959/Europol-Criticizes-Bitcoin-Mining-Says-It-Attracts-Criminal-Actors"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stance of Europol regarding Bitcoin mining centres on the threat that mining activities might be exploited to hide illicit gains, rendering them appealing to scammers and ransomware creators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Security Risk? Elon Musk Ban oO Apple Devices Looms If They Embrace OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417109a05</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-security-risk-elon-musk-ban-on-apple-looms/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a shocking turn of events that has stirred the tech and crypto communities, business mogul and the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of SpaceX and Tesla, Elon Musk has issued a stark warning to tech company Apple, threatening to forbid Tesla from using Apple devices if the tech giant integrates OpenAI into its operating system.
 
Musk, who has been outspoken about his worries about Artificial Intelligence (AI) and its possible hazards made this claim amid mounting rumors that Apple may include OpenAI’s capabilities in upcoming releases of its iOS and macOS operating systems.
 
Apple Intelligence To Send Data In A Cryptoghically Way
 
On Monday, tech behemoth Apple during its annual Worldwide Developers Conference WWDC 2024 announced its foray into artificial intelligence dubbed Apple Intell…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[British Columbia Officials, RCMP Issue Warning To International Crypto “Money Mules”]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577952/British-Columbia-Officials-RCMP-Issue-Warning-To-International-Crypto-Money-Mules</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19577952/British-Columbia-Officials-RCMP-Issue-Warning-To-International-Crypto-Money-Mules"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British Columbia Securities Commission (BCSC) and Royal Canadian Mounted Police's (RCMP) Integrated Marketing Enforcement Team (IMET) have issued a warning to ten British Columbia residents over their reported criminal transfer of digital asset funds. The province has been grappling with the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has AI Already Changed Gaming Forever?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mZlR3He5/has-ai-already-changed-gaming-forever"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt’s Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Puke sat down with Simon Davis of Mighty Bear Games and VC Kyle Klemmer to discuss how AI has already remade the gaming industry—for better and for worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funding Open-Source Generative AI With Crypto]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417129f86</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/06/11/funding-open-source-generative-ai-with-crypto/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto infrastructure could help address one of the biggest challenges in open source generative AI, says Jesus Rodriguez.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesus Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Largest Bank in Brazil Itau Unibanco Opens Cryptocurrency Trading to All Users]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741713f4bd</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/largest-bank-in-brazil-itau-unibanco-opens-cryptocurrency-trading-to-all-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Itau Unibanco, the largest bank in Brazil and all of Latam, has reported the availability of cryptocurrency trading services for all its users. Through Ion, the bank’s in-house investment platform, customers can purchase bitcoin (BTC) and ether (ETH), a feature previously available to selected users. Brazilian Banking Giant Itau Unibanco Opens Cryptocurrency Trading Services for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Alliance Merger Delayed for a Month As Token Prices Fall]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234802</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234802/ai-token-merger-delay-asi"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The three tokens set to become one are down over 20% for the week, along with much of the crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BODEN Solana Meme Coins Soar on Hunter Biden Guilty Verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234823</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234823/boden-solana-meme-coins-soar-hunter-biden-guilty-verdict"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hunter Biden was found guilty on three felony gun charges Tuesday—and Solana meme coins inspired by the Bidens pumped afterwards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floki Name Service Is Live on BNB Chain]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74171805f6</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/floki-name-service-is-live-on-bnb-chain/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Floki Name Service, a decentralized domain name service by the popular meme coin, is now live exclusively on the BNB Chain mainnet. This service allows users to create a unique .floki domain name, which can be used as an on-chain identity and for other purposes such as launching a decentralized website, blog, or résumé. Built […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 135 - BTC FALLS ON OUTFLOWS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bA3jJ5aA/fomo-hour-135-btc-falls-on-outflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls as ETFs see first outflow in 19 days. Short positions grow on downwards move in BTC. BTC short-term realised price now at $64k. ETH ETF issuers still waiting for SEC response. UK ETNs continue to see tiny volume. SOL validators get kicked out for sandwich attacks. ZKsync airdrop happening next week. ZKsync to give 17.8% to the community. OP launches Fraud Proofs. Bitfarms plans poison pill to counter takeover bid. OKX sees outflows after security incidents. Bybit considers shutting China offices. COIN may get added to S&P500.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Exchange Lykke Confirms Platform Breach; Reports Theft of Assets Valued at $22 Million]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417196f63</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-exchange-lykke-confirms-platform-breach-reports-theft-of-assets-valued-at-22-million/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency exchange Lykke confirmed on June 10 that it fell victim to a breach, resulting in a hacker stealing digital assets valued at $22 million. Lykke stated that it had shut down the affected systems to contain the damage and assured users that their funds remained secure. Lykke Faces Accusations of Delayed Breach Confirmation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Founder Charles Hoskinson Teases Major Change For ADA – Here’s What We Know]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417047ec8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-founder-change-for-ada/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cardano Chang hard fork is finally within reach, promising historic changes for the blockchain. Cardano founder, Charles Hoskinson, has teased significant updates and major changes set to take place for ADA. 
 
Cardano To Record Historic Moment With Chang Hard Fork
 
In an X (formerly Twitter) post on June 9, Hoskinson announced the imminent release of the highly anticipated Chang hard fork. The Cardano founder declared that June will be the month that the Cardano Node will reach 9.0, signaling the network’s readiness for the new hard fork. 
 
 
The Chang hard fork is an upgrade designed to empower the Cardano community with greater influence over the network’s governance. This update will grant ADA holders voting rights on proposals and introduce important tools and infrastructure to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr. Advocates for Father as Leading Bitcoin Proponent]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741705a39c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/donald-trump-jr-advocates-for-father-as-leading-bitcoin-proponent/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Donald Trump Jr. shared an opinion article on the social media platform X and declared that his father Donald Trump is “the best choice for bitcoin.” Trump Jr. Endorses Father as Prime Candidate for Bitcoin, Highlights Bitcoin Magazine Editorial The eldest child of former U.S. President Donald Trump and his first wife Ivana […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Plunges as $245 Million in Crypto Longs Are Liquidated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234815</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234815/bitcoin-price-plunges-245-million-crypto-longs-liquidated"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto liquidations are soaring Tuesday as Bitcoin sinks 5% to a price of nearly $66,000, with long positions seeing the biggest impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's Value Is ‘Many Multiples’ Above Its Current Price: Billionaire Investor Bill Miller]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234803</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234803/bitcoin-value-many-multiples-above-current-price-bill-miller"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The famed investor predicts Bitcoin deniers will suffer over the next decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be Warned, AI Crypto Scams Are on the Rise]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74170c6ab8</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/opinion/2024/06/11/be-warned-ai-crypto-scams-are-on-the-rise/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Elliptic report found five ways AI is being used to rob crypto users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon Unveils $1 Billion Grant Program to Foster Blockchain Development Over Next Decade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74170d4244</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/polygon-unveils-1-billion-grant-program-to-foster-blockchain-development-over-next-decade/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polygon has announced a $1 billion Community Grants Program, set to roll out over the next ten years, aimed at supporting developers on its platform. This initiative promises to allocate about $100 million annually to fund innovative projects that enhance the Polygon and Ethereum ecosystems. Polygon Community Treasury to Release $1B in Grants Over the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just Don’t Call It Blockchain: Apple's New AI Privacy Tech Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234801</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234801/apple-blockchain-ai-privacy-cloud-compute"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple says its new AI model uses “blockchain-ish” tech to preserve privacy. But what does that really mean?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Pullback to $66K Triggers $250M in Crypto Liquidations as Traders Brace for 'Wild Wednesday' of FOMC, CPI Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74170f3c6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/11/bitcoin-pullback-to-66k-triggers-250m-in-crypto-liquidations-as-traders-brace-for-wild-wednesday-of-fomc-cpi-report/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow's Fed "dot plot" of interest rate projection and forward guidance by Chairman Powell will be key for what's next for the digital asset market, K33 Research said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Trump Trounce Biden? Polymarket Traders Are Betting on It.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7417085a18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/06/11/will-trump-trounce-biden-polymarket-traders-are-betting-on-it/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:13:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a 56% chance of winning, according to the prediction market's traders, the former president has a 22-point lead over the incumbent, far bigger than what the polls indicate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Reynolds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple Completes Standard Custody Acquisition, Appoints New Stablecoin Lead]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741708b7c1</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-standard-custody-acquisition-stablecoin-lead/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple has officially finalized its acquisition of Standard Custody & Trust Company, a regulated entity providing high-grade digital asset custody solutions. This acquisition, first announced earlier this year, has received the green light from all necessary regulatory bodies, including the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS), which oversees the operation of limited-purpose trust companies. This approval marks a significant step forward for Ripple, further strengthening its compliance framework across its existing and future product lines.
 
Ripple Closes Second Acquisition In One Year
 
The closure of this transaction extends Ripple’s already considerable portfolio of regulatory licenses. The company holds nearly 40 money transmitter licenses across the United States, a Majo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRON DAO Announces HackaTRON Season 6 Qualifiers]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e741709d208</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/tron-dao-announces-hackatron-season-6-qualifiers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. Geneva, Switzerland, June 11, 2024 – With HackaTRON Season 6 coming to a close, the TRON DAO team, alongside HTX DAO, BitTorrent Chain (BTTC), and JustLend DAO hosted a series of innovations that has taken the blockchain landscape by storm. This season, participants redefined the digital landscape across multiple tracks. Web3, DeFi, Artistry, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Good Hands: Bitcoin Builds A Better Future]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74170ab6ee</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/culture/in-good-hands-bitcoin-builds-a-better-future"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin is still a young protocol by every measure. These adolescent years are arguably more formative than any other period in its short history because the stakes are already quite high for a groundbreaking project with less than two decades of testing and growth. As I have watched new investors, developers, users and marketers flock to Bitcoin over the past 18 months, the fundamental reasons why a so-called Bitcoin Renaissance matters seems to be given a backseat. 
Over this period of time I have been asked countless questions like “What do you think of this new L2?” or “Will this new L2 actually work?” In almost every case, my answer has been, “I don’t know.” Building on Bitcoin is hard, and many people do not know how. Thus, it is hard to know what exactly someone is building, let alo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Willem Schroe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinmetrics: Meme Coins Reshape Crypto Landscape Despite Centralized Token Holdings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410f221fe</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinmetrics-meme-coins-reshape-crypto-landscape-despite-centralized-token-holdings/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meme coin sector has exploded to a staggering $60 billion market capitalization, reshaping the digital asset landscape and outperforming traditional crypto assets. Researchers Tanay Ved and Matías Andrade from Coinmetrics provide insights into the implications of this trend on networks like Ethereum and Solana. The Cultural Impact of Meme Coins on Crypto According to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Mixers, Privacy Coins, Layer 2s Complicate Tracing for Law Enforcement, EU Innovation Hub Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7410fc2d4c</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/06/11/crypto-mixers-privacy-coins-layer-2s-complicate-tracing-for-law-enforcement-eu-innovation-hub-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Separately, France's markets regulator said crypto remains a high risk for money laundering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doxxing and Conspiracy Theories: GameStop Hero Roaring Kitty's Fans Are Getting Carried Away]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234769</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234769/doxxing-conspiracy-theories-roaring-kitty-gamestop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit moderators have urged fans of the GameStop bull to stop posting photos of Roaring Kitty’s family on the social media site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Break 19-Day Inflow Streak As Net Outflows Hit $65 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234780</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234780/bitcoin-etfs-break-19-day-inflow-streak-as-net-outflows-hit-65-million"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale’s GBTC has seen net outflows of over $113 million across the past three days, as Bitcoin's price dipped below $67,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No More Betting With Crypto on Australian Gambling Sites, Says Regulator]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234770</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234770/no-more-betting-with-crypto-on-australian-gambling-sites-says-regulator"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T12:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Failure to comply could see companies fined up to $155,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Lightning Network and Layer 2 Scaling Could Be 'Abused by Criminals', Says EU]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234748</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234748/bitcoin-lightning-network-and-layer-2-scaling-could-be-abused-by-criminals-says-eu"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T11:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An EU Innovation Hub for Internal Security report argues that layer 2 solutions could cause "problems for law enforcement investigations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Drops 3% Ahead of Interest Rate Decision and US Inflation Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234754</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234754/bitcoin-drops-3-ahead-of-interest-rate-decision-and-us-inflation-report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin has dropped by 3% ahead of tomorrow's Federal Open Markets Committee interest rates decision and new U.S. inflation data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZkSync Will Airdrop 3.7 Billion ZK Tokens to User Wallets Next Week]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234747</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234747/zksync-will-airdrop-3-7-billion-zk-tokens-to-user-wallets-next-week"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There'll be no lock-up period for the community airdrop, but distribution has been capped at 100,000 tokens per wallet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sora Who? Kling Is the New AI Video Generator Everyone Is Talking About]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234706</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234706/kling-ai-video-generator-china-beats-pika-runwayml-openai-sora"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hailing from China, the Kling AI video model is a potential game changer, blasting past mainstays like Pika or RunwayML. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call of Duty: Black Ops 6 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=214893</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/214893/call-of-duty-2024-preview-leaks-rumors-release-date"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Activision just shared a ton of details about Call of Duty: Black Ops 6—including some big changes from last year's entry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says He Will Ban Apple Devices From His Companies If They Integrate OpenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234689/elon-musk-apple-device-ban-chatgpt-security-privacy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“That is an unacceptable security violation,” the Tesla CEO declared, asserting that Apple can't guarantee that OpenAI will keep user data secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Hamster Kombat? The Telegram Crypto Game and Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=233407</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/what-is-hamster-kombat-telegram-game-token-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat is the latest Telegram-based crypto game to go viral, just like Notcoin. Here's what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Is Down Over $350 Million on GameStop Since Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234687/roaring-kitty-down-350-million-gamestop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme stock influencer Roaring Kitty says he's still in the black on his massive GameStop (GME) options gamble—just barely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia's Rumored GPU Upgrades Will Fuel More Demanding AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234675</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234675/nvidia-rtx50-leak-gpu-vram-upgrades"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An alleged leak suggests the top chipmaker is bolstering its position as the top provider of AI hardware—but prices could also rise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Taps OpenAI to Bring Big AI Updates to iPhones and Macs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234661</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234661/apple-ai-openai-chatgpt-siri-wwdc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Siri will plug into ChatGPT, but the tech giant emphasized that its AI features will be private and secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Treasury Strategy Boosts Stock Price of Canadian Firm DeFi Technologies]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234642</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234642/bitcoin-treasury-strategy-boosts-stock-price-defi-technologies"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeFi Technologies, a Canadian firm and parent company of ETF provider Valour, has adopted Bitcoin as a treasury reserve asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Base Meme Coin Normie Removes Video Depicting Suicide, Following Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234588</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234588/base-meme-coin-normie-removes-suicide-video-backlash"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The creators of Normie, a meme coin minted on Ethereum layer-2 network Base, said they weren't trying to "trivialize a sensitive topic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop Dumps 15% as Roaring Kitty Jokes About His Plunging Position]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234649</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234649/gamestop-dumps-15-roaring-kitty-jokes-plunging-position"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop's share price continued to fall Monday as the meme stock influencer Kieth Gill made light of his own losses on paper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Meme Coin Michi Pumps After Ariana Grande Shares the Cat's Photo]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234635</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234635/solana-meme-coin-michi-pumps-ariana-grande"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:57:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pop star Ariana Grande reposted a Michi meme ahead of the Monday surge, prompting debate over whether she knows of its crypto connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Layer-2 ZkSync Unveils ZK Nation Ahead of Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234619</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234619/zksync-unveils-zk-nation-ahead-of-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The community will be responsible for governing the protocol via the upcoming ZKsync token.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Stock Nears All-Time High Price Ahead of Expected AI Push]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234620/apple-stock-nears-all-time-high-price-ahead-of-expected-ai-push"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's stock price has been on a bullish streak for seven weeks, with its expected focus on AI at WWDC fueling investor optimism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Cipher Guide: How to Use Morse Code to Earn a Million Free Coins in the Telegram Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234027</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/hamster-kombat-daily-cipher-guide-morse-codeearn-million-free-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now there’s another way to rack up free coins ahead of the Hamster Kombat airdrop. Here’s how to do it and where to find the latest code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap Labs Acquires 'Crypto: The Game' Ahead of Next Season]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234608</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234608/uniswap-labs-acquires-crypto-game-next-season"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto: The Game, the Survivor-inspired reality game built around on-chain activities, will continue on under the Uniswap Labs umbrella.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 134 - EU SNAP ELECTIONS LAND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pZksMKIV/fomo-hour-134-eu-snap-elections-land"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volatility remains low, TL continues to be divisive. 2nd highest weekly close ever for BTC. Crypto funds saw $2bn inflows last week. Rumour that BlackRock will apply for SOL ETF. Base TVL hits $8bn, top of L2s for activity. zk Sync hint at TGE this week. PENDLE enters top 5 for DeFi TVL. Berachain v2 testnet goes live.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Funds Added $2 Billion in Biggest Week for Crypto ETFs Since March]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234599</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234599/bitcoin-funds-added-2-billion-biggest-week-crypto-etfs-march"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:17:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto funds added more than $2 billion worth of assets last week with the largest combined inflows since March—most of it for Bitcoin ETFs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaring Kitty Posts on Twitter Again. Does It Mean He's Buying AMC?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234559/roaring-kitty-posts-on-twitter-again-does-it-mean-hes-buying-amc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T12:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop legend Roaring Kitty is back to posting movie references on Twitter. Could this mean he owns meme stock AMC?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Makes 'Crypto President' Play at Fundraiser: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234556</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234556/trump-makes-crypto-president-play-at-fundraiser-report"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T12:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Republican presidential hopeful doubled down on his pro-crypto stance, according to attendees of the fundraising event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin Token Pumps 6% as Telegram Game Hits 40 Million Players]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234557</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234557/notcoin-pumps-40-million-players"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T10:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Players have earned $1.5 million across 20 campaigns, according to the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarang Khaitan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friend.tech Token Down 22% After Migration Off Base L2 Gets Panned]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234545/friend-tech-token-down-22-after-migration-off-base-l2-gets-panned"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T09:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News of Friend.tech's plans to launch a blockchain for decentralized social projects has not been well received.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Has Put a Weird New Face on an Old Amazon Prime Video Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=234361</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/234361/ai-weird-new-face-old-amazon-prime-video-problem"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thumbnail for the classic 12 Angry Men has had a terrifying makeover.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ali Shutler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 133 - RUGGED BY HOGEN?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MSvAS9qX/fomo-hour-133-rugged-by-hogen"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC still just below ATH after $218m ETF inflows. BTC OI hits record $37bn as long-short ratio rises. Amount of ETH on exchanges lowest since 2015. Franklin Templeton explores broader crypto fund. Mining stocks rise on takeover frenzy. Kraken considers $100m funding round. Binance reinstates crypto buys with Mastercard. Phantom & Jito partner for native staking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 132 - CRYPTO STRENGTH IS GROWING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/bQBFWC0w/fomo-hour-132-crypto-strength-is-growing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto consolidates near ATH, $488m ETF inflow. BTC correlation to tech stocks highest since 2023. BTC options anticipate $74-80k move. ETH to $22k by 2030: VanEck. Robinhood to acquire Bitstamp.
Coinbase launches Smart Wallet. ByBit opens up explicitly to China users. Global liquidity breaks out to $94T. US President given new powers to block crypto. Cramer & Gensler continue to bash crypto. Gensler hints at prolonged ETH ETF process. Stand with Crypto PAC hits 1m advocates. Turkey denies plans to tax crypto. EigenLayer surpasses $20bn TVL. IONET to launch on Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Unleashing The Power Of Permissionless Markets With Vega Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OvA845JA/webinar-unleashing-the-power-of-permissionless-markets-with-vega-protocol"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T08:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join our expert panel for an insightful discussion on Vega Protocol's revolutionary approach to decentralized derivatives trading. Discover how Vega's permissionless markets enable anyone to create and trade futures and perpetuals on a fully decentralized network. Explore the potential of Vega's innovative features, such as the ability to add new assets, transfer network assets, and adjust network parameters—as well as the protocol's active markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 131 - BIG BITCOIN INFLOWS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/a37DNT7n/fomo-hour-131-big-bitcoin-inflows"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs see large $900M inflows, biggest in weeks. $800M of shorts would be liquidated above $72K. BTC to $100K if it breaks $73K in a week: Novogratz. BNB hits new ATH, breaks $100B market cap. FTX reaches $200M tax settlement with IRS. Most investors should hold BTC: Fidelity. Tether CEO criticises EU on stablecoin regulation. Japanese exchange raises $320M to recover funds. ETH ETFs could see $4B inflows in 5 months: K33. Paradigm propose MEV taxes. StarkWare plans ZK scaling for BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 130 - $DOG TARGETS 1B MC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ke2mFBwr/fomo-hour-130-dog-targets-1b-mc"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Runes & Ordinals soar as DOG passes $900M. rekt Brands opens up its shares claim for NFT holders. BTC led NFT trading volume with $6.3M on the day. NodeMonkes +10% 0.289, Puppets +35% at 0.198. Runes up by DOG which soared 23% to $922M mc. BUS won the Blast Jackpot last night for a 3% win. Memecoin majors are mostly red this AM. Trader buys 10k SOL of GME. Base brings back Onchain Summer. Dapper settles massive lawsuit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 129 - ROARING RETURNS, AGAIN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ABOejLBT/fomo-hour-129-roaring-returns-again"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto bounces, BTC breaks 2-week downtrend. BTC low volatility points to trend continuation. BTC will top at $150k in September 2025: Brandt. $3bn ETH withdrawn from exchanges since ETF. ETH ETF inflows imply ‘base case’ price $5.3k. ETH ETF inflows won’t be like BTC: Fireblocks. BTC logo projected on ECB building. Ethena USDe hits $3bn market cap in 4 months. Maple launches DeFi institutional lending platform. OKX launches in the Netherlands. Matter Labs drops ZK ticker. Linea shuts down chain after hack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 128 - PUMP DOT FUN KEEPS PUMPING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/cziNL3TF/fomo-hour-128-pump-dot-fun-keeps-pumping"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto nears break-out then falls on Trump verdict. 13 straight days of BTC ETF inflows, BTC whale accumulation ‘echoes 2020’. Crypto apps next year will onboard millions: Burniske. Elon denies talking crypto policy with Trump. RFK has bought 21 BTC during campaign. TON market cap falls after updating supply data. a16z donates $25m to crypto PAC. Vitalik sends 30ETH to Tornado devs. DBS Bank in Singapore custodies $650m ETH. Backlash grows over zkSync using ZK ticker. Implementing FIT21 a slow process: CFTC. Pierce recommends UK & US cross-border sandbox. Vitalik writes blog on block size wars. Hong Kong government expresses support for web3. Do Kwon & Terraform reach settlement with SEC. Large unlocks for a number of alts next month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 127 - CELEB COINS CRASH!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mGbE2GHV/fomo-hour-127-celeb-coins-crash"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYSE to launch BTC options. CME has ‘no plans’ to offer SOL futures. Stablecoin market cap rises to 2 year high. Inflation below 3.3% ‘means BTC ATH’. Crypto market cap heading to $200T: Yat Siu. Gemini recovers $2.2bn for Earn users. PayPal stablecoin will offer ‘confidential transfers’. Mastercard launches Crypto Credential pilot on BTC. Layer Zero launches on SOL. L2s are cultural extensions of ETH: Vitalik. FTX’s Salame says he will share story. SEI announces 27m SEI airdrop. ASI merger complete, to launch June 13th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 126 - MEMECOIN MADNESS!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/eA3xqKLr/fomo-hour-126-memecoin-madness"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF flips Grayscale in size. BTC ETFs see 11 straight days of inflows. ZKasino gives 72hours for ETH withdrawals. ENS to migrate to L2. ADA drops out of top 10 coins. Salame sentenced to 7.5 years in jail. Riot Platforms attempts takeover of Bitfarms. Ripple donates $25m to Fairshake PAC. Pump(.)fun launches live streaming. Iggy Azelea MOTHER coin leads celeb tokens. Beeple Everyday features many coins. Runes bounce, DOG hits $560m. PEPE active wallets double during rally. Cristiano Ronaldo launches 4th NFT. Friend Tech announces club wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum DN-404 Tokens Are a Sensation in Asia. Are They the West’s Next Big Trend?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/drcV3Zte/ethereum-dn-404-tokens-are-a-sensation-in-asia-are-they-the-wests-next-big-trend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz and Rug Radio creator Pukerainbow sat down for a conversation with some of the biggest adopters involved in Ethereum’s newest trend: dividing NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying Crypto Simplified with Mika]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Z9rxTcnJ/buying-crypto-simplified-with-mika"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our series turning crypto beginners into crypto pros, Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of purchasing cryptocurrency using crypto exchange Kraken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 125 - ETH NEARS 4K]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BrgFfEe8/fomo-hour-125-eth-nears-4k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T17:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH leads rally on continued bullish ETF sentiment. Previous anti-crypto Trump comments highlighted. Wave of influencers and celebrities hacked, release coins. Phantom becomes no.1 finance app in the US. Argentina & El Salvador hold talks on BTC adoption. LINK to have large announcement on May 30th. PEPE, MOG, TURBO, TRUMP hit ATHs in ETH memes. MOG up 60%, mentioned in Beeple Everyday. Caitlyn Jenner hacker releases JENNER coin. Garga outlines future plans for BAYC. Friend Tech founder offers $200k to migrate off Base.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 124 - THE ETH ETF IS APPROVED!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5ELzjWt4/fomo-hour-124-the-eth-etf-is-approved"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs get approved 19b-4 forms. ETFs won’t trade until July or August: Galaxy. ETF means many coins not securities: Coinbase CLO. Coinbase relists XRP in US. SOL ETF coming: Scaramucci. US House passes vote to ban CBDC. Building a pro-crypto army in congress: Sen. Lummis. Polymarket backlash over if ETH ETF truly approved. Expect ETH ETFs to be 10-15% of BTC: Bloomberg. BTC ETFs see $1.75bn inflows over 9 days. BTC to $150k in 2024 is base case: Tom Lee. ETH co-founder moves $37m ETH to exchanges. Grayscale launches trusts for STX & NEAR. Coinbase loses against SEC on DOGE sweepstakes. ALGO ad attacks BTC, SOL, ETH. Phantom now no.2 finance App on Google Play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 123 - ETHEREUM KEEPS GOING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JE3lB00G/fomo-hour-123-ethereum-keeps-going"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH soars, ETF S1 approvals expected in hours. US house greenlights FIT21 bill with broad support. Gensler says SEC already has rules for crypto. Hong Kong set to allow ETH staking for ETFs. ETH OI continues to soar. SOL mentioned as next ETF candidate on CNBC. SOL ETF will take years: Bloomberg. MetaMask plans BTC integration. Fed says only 7% of Americans own crypto. SBF heads to a new prison. Hong Kong orders WLD shutdown. TON added to Binance ahead of potential listing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 122 - ETH ETF MOVES CLOSER!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/FlTuDkm9/fomo-hour-122-eth-etf-moves-closer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETFs move closer to approval, drop staking. Blackrock ETF see biggest inflow in 6 weeks. Grayscale ETH discount narrows under 10%. BTC & ETH heading for ATH: StanChart. Banana zone squared coming for ETH: Raoul Pal. Trump accepts crypto donations including DOGE. Pelosi mulls support of crypto bill. Farcaster raises $150M, DEGEN up 20%. Coinbase to launch gold & oil futures trading. Uniswap ‘ready to fight’ against SEC. Vitalik proposes solutions to MEV problems. Phantom may soon support email sign-up. Jupiter announces initiative to tokenise RWAs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 121 - ETHEREUM GOD CANDLES!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/EE1S4Hf4/fomo-hour-121-ethereum-god-candles"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ETH ETF suddenly seems likely, flurry of amendments. ETH biggest daily gain ever, gains SOL market cap. ETF approval shifted due to political pressure. ETF approval may come as soon as tomorrow. Squeeze liquidates $230M of shorts. ETH OI hits record of $14B on exchanges. BTC nears ATH amid 6th straight day of ETF inflows. SOL flips ETH in Google search trends. House Democrats will not whip against crypto bills. Anti-crypto FDIC chair Gruenberg to step-down. Grayscale CEO steps down, ETHE discount narrows. Genesis settles for $2B with creditors. Binance to focus launchpad on higher float projects. SEI v2 launch coming next week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Chikai]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BGCnTbKb/we-do-a-little-with-chikai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we sit down with our good friend and one of the biggest supporters of the pod, Chikai Ohazama. Chikai is the co-founder of Keyhole which was acquired by Google and became Google Earth. He is one of the most caring art collectors in our space, as well as an extremely talented AI artist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>