<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-13T19:14:37.390Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-09-13T19:14:37.390Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DailyCoin Bitcoin Regular: BTC Soars 3.6% Overnight, Is the Bull Back On?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900702/DailyCoin-Bitcoin-Regular-BTC-Soars-36-Overnight-Is-the-Bull-Back-On</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900702/DailyCoin-Bitcoin-Regular-BTC-Soars-36-Overnight-Is-the-Bull-Back-On"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price is showing subtle yet intriguing shifts, fueled by market sentiment changes, economic data, and key resistance levels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moonpay Secures Registration to Offer Digital Currency Exchange Services in Australia]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745305cf4b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/moonpay-secures-registration-to-offer-digital-currency-exchange-services-in-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Moonpay has successfully registered with the Australian Transaction Reports and Analysis Centre (AUSTRAC) to provide digital currency exchange services in Australia. This registration will enable Moonpay to establish local payment processing relationships and offer Australian users alternative payment methods such as Osko and Pay ID. As a registered entity, Moonpay will comply with Australia’s AML/CTF […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Analyst Dives Into Why BinaryX and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino Are Performing Strong, BNX Investors Add Mpeppe (MPEPE) To Holdings]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745305d377</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-analyst-dives-into-why-binaryx-and-mpeppe-mpepe-casino-are-performing-strong-bnx-investors-add-mpeppe-mpepe-to-holdings/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BinaryX (BNX) and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino have become standout performers in the cryptocurrency market, attracting investors with their innovative approaches to decentralized finance (De-Fi) and online gaming. As both projects continue to grow, top analysts are taking note of their impressive performance, particularly highlighting how BinaryX (BNX) has solidified its position in De-Fi gaming while Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino is redefining decentralized gambling. Many BinaryX (BNX) investors are now adding Mpeppe (MPEPE) to their portfolios, recognizing the synergies between these two promising projects.
 
The Key to Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Success 
One of the primary reasons Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino is gaining traction is its commitment to enhanced security and privacy. By utilizing cryptocurrency transacti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Rival Mpeppe (MPEPE) Doubles Down On Mobile Gaming Developments, SOL Investors Flock Into Presale]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745305d376</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-rival-mpeppe-mpepe-doubles-down-on-mobile-gaming-developments-sol-investors-flock-into-presale/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE), a rising competitor to Solana (SOL), has recently doubled down on its mobile gaming developments, creating significant excitement in the crypto world. Known for its decentralized casino platform and meme-driven appeal, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is now expanding into the mobile gaming market, which has attracted a wave of Solana (SOL) investors. The presale of Mpeppe (MPEPE) is already drawing substantial interest as investors look to capitalize on this next phase of growth.
 
Why Mobile Gaming Is a Game-Changer for Mpeppe (MPEPE) 
The mobile gaming sector has seen explosive growth in recent years, and Mpeppe (MPEPE) is seizing the opportunity to expand its reach by integrating its blockchain-based casino and gaming offerings into mobile platforms. By combining its decentralized featur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Investors Back BinaryX As New BNX Rival Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino  Takes Centre Stage]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745305d375</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binance-investors-back-binaryx-as-new-bnx-rival-mpeppe-mpepe-casino-takes-centre-stage/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino, a new decentralized casino platform, is quickly gaining traction in the cryptocurrency market, positioning itself as a strong competitor to BinaryX (BNX). As investors on Binance look for the next big project, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is becoming an attractive option. Its unique use of blockchain technology in online gambling has caught the attention of many, while BinaryX (BNX) continues to be a leader in De-Fi and gaming. With Mpeppe (MPEPE) now in the spotlight, Binance investors are carefully watching the growing rivalry between these two projects.
 
BinaryX (BNX): A Long-Standing Favorite for Binance Investors 
BinaryX (BNX) has been a favorite among Binance investors due to its integration of decentralized finance (De-Fi) and gaming. With BinaryX (BNX) leading the charge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Performing Altcoins Uniswap, BinaryX and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Gain Major Whale Investor Support]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745305d374</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-performing-altcoins-uniswap-binaryx-and-mpeppe-mpepe-gain-major-whale-investor-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI), BinaryX (BNX), and Mpeppe (MPEPE) have all seen significant growth, attracting large-scale investors who recognize the potential of these projects to deliver strong returns. With their focus on decentralized finance (De-Fi) and innovative use cases, these altcoins are positioning themselves as leaders in the next wave of crypto adoption.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE): Revolutionizing De-Fi with Innovative Financial Services 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) has captured the attention of whale investors thanks to its integration with De-Fi protocols, which allows users to access a range of financial services. Through Mpeppe (MPEPE), users can participate in lending, borrowing, trading, and yield farming without the need for traditional intermediaries. This decentralized approach not only enhances the platf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BinaryX Investors Add Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino To Investment Portfolio With BNX Profits, Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745305d373</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/binaryx-investors-add-mpeppe-mpepe-casino-to-investment-portfolio-with-bnx-profits-heres-how/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the cryptocurrency market continues to grow and diversify, BinaryX (BNX) investors are exploring new opportunities to expand their portfolios. One of the latest trends among BinaryX (BNX) holders is reinvesting their profits into Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino, an innovative decentralized casino platform. Mpeppe (MPEPE) combines the power of blockchain technology with the excitement of online gaming, offering investors an enticing opportunity to maximize returns.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino: A Perfect Fit for BinaryX (BNX) Investors 
BinaryX (BNX) investors, who are well-versed in the advantages of decentralized platforms, are finding Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino to be a valuable addition to their portfolios. Mpeppe (MPEPE) offers transparency, security, and the opportunity to capitalize on the growing dem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil lifts freeze on Starlink, X accounts after $3M fine payment]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900698/Brazil-lifts-freeze-on-Starlink-X-accounts-after-3M-fine-payment</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900698/Brazil-lifts-freeze-on-Starlink-X-accounts-after-3M-fine-payment"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fines are tied to a legal dispute involving X’s failure to comply with court orders in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s crypto platform launch, Uniswap denies charging for protocol deployment: Finance Redefined]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900683/Trumps-crypto-platform-launch-Uniswap-denies-charging-for-protocol-deployment-Finance-Redefined</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900683/Trumps-crypto-platform-launch-Uniswap-denies-charging-for-protocol-deployment-Finance-Redefined"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump is launching the World Liberty Financial DeFi platform, Uniswap’s CEO denies charging for protocol deployment, and the Sonic blockchain hits 720ms finality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Analyst Dives Into Why BinaryX and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino Are Performing Strong, BNX Investors Add Mpeppe (MPEPE) To Holdings]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900686/Top-Analyst-Dives-Into-Why-BinaryX-and-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-Are-Performing-Strong-BNX-Investors-Add-Mpeppe-MPEPE-To-Holdings</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900686/Top-Analyst-Dives-Into-Why-BinaryX-and-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-Are-Performing-Strong-BNX-Investors-Add-Mpeppe-MPEPE-To-Holdings"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BinaryX (BNX) and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino have become standout performers in the cryptocurrency market, attracting investors with their innovative approaches to decentralized finance (De-Fi) and online gaming. As both projects continue to grow, top analysts are taking note of their impressive...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Rival Mpeppe (MPEPE) Doubles Down On Mobile Gaming Developments, SOL Investors Flock Into Presale]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900685/Solana-Rival-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Doubles-Down-On-Mobile-Gaming-Developments-SOL-Investors-Flock-Into-Presale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900685/Solana-Rival-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Doubles-Down-On-Mobile-Gaming-Developments-SOL-Investors-Flock-Into-Presale"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE), a rising competitor to Solana (SOL), has recently doubled down on its mobile gaming developments, creating significant excitement in the crypto world. Known for its decentralized casino platform and meme-driven appeal, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is now expanding into the mobile gaming...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNX Price Prediction: Mpeppe (MPEPE) Presale Raises 500K In 24Hrs With BNX Whales]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900690/BNX-Price-Prediction-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Presale-Raises-500K-In-24Hrs-With-BNX-Whales</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900690/BNX-Price-Prediction-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Presale-Raises-500K-In-24Hrs-With-BNX-Whales"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an impressive display of investor confidence, the Mpeppe (MPEPE) presale has raised $500,000 in just 24 hours, largely driven by BinaryX (BNX) whales. The success of this presale has caught the attention of the wider crypto community, with Mpeppe (MPEPE) emerging as a significant player in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino Attracts Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA) Whales To Play With The Chance Of Major Profits!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900688/Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-Attracts-Solana-SOL-and-Cardano-ADA-Whales-To-Play-With-The-Chance-Of-Major-Profits</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900688/Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-Attracts-Solana-SOL-and-Cardano-ADA-Whales-To-Play-With-The-Chance-Of-Major-Profits"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of online gambling is seeing a new wave of excitement, and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino is at the center of it. This meme-driven casino platform is quickly gaining popularity, especially among large investors or “whales” from major blockchain networks like Solana (SOL) and Cardano (ADA). With...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Investors Back BinaryX As New BNX Rival Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino  Takes Centre Stage]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900684/Binance-Investors-Back-BinaryX-As-New-BNX-Rival-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-Takes-Centre-Stage</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900684/Binance-Investors-Back-BinaryX-As-New-BNX-Rival-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-Takes-Centre-Stage"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino, a new decentralized casino platform, is quickly gaining traction in the cryptocurrency market, positioning itself as a strong competitor to BinaryX (BNX). As investors on Binance look for the next big project, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is becoming an attractive option. Its unique use...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Performing Altcoins Uniswap, BinaryX and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Gain Major Whale Investor Support]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900682/Top-Performing-Altcoins-Uniswap-BinaryX-and-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Gain-Major-Whale-Investor-Support</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900682/Top-Performing-Altcoins-Uniswap-BinaryX-and-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Gain-Major-Whale-Investor-Support"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI), BinaryX (BNX), and Mpeppe (MPEPE) have all seen significant growth, attracting large-scale investors who recognize the potential of these projects to deliver strong returns. With their focus on decentralized finance (De-Fi) and innovative use cases, these altcoins are positioning...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BinaryX Investors Add Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino To Investment Portfolio With BNX Profits, Here’s How]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900681/BinaryX-Investors-Add-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-To-Investment-Portfolio-With-BNX-Profits-Heres-How</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900681/BinaryX-Investors-Add-Mpeppe-MPEPE-Casino-To-Investment-Portfolio-With-BNX-Profits-Heres-How"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the cryptocurrency market continues to grow and diversify, BinaryX (BNX) investors are exploring new opportunities to expand their portfolios. One of the latest trends among BinaryX (BNX) holders is reinvesting their profits into Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino, an innovative decentralized casino...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe Skyrockets Past Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) 150% Despite New Gaming Web3 AI Agent Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900654/Mpeppe-Skyrockets-Past-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-150-Despite-New-Gaming-Web3-AI-Agent-Integration</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900654/Mpeppe-Skyrockets-Past-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-150-Despite-New-Gaming-Web3-AI-Agent-Integration"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-volatile cryptocurrency market, few things are certain, except perhaps the unpredictability of it all. This truth has never been more evident than in the current showdown between Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET), a sophisticated AI-powered blockchain platform, and Mpeppe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nubank Suspends Trading of Nucoin, Offers Conversion Options]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900656/Nubank-Suspends-Trading-of-Nucoin-Offers-Conversion-Options</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900656/Nubank-Suspends-Trading-of-Nucoin-Offers-Conversion-Options"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian digital bank Nubank has announced the immediate suspension of trading for its native cryptocurrency, Nucoin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Coin Artificial Superintelligence Alliance (FET) Loses Ground After Mpeppe Spikes 100x]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900652/Artificial-Intelligence-Coin-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-Loses-Ground-After-Mpeppe-Spikes-100x</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900652/Artificial-Intelligence-Coin-Artificial-Superintelligence-Alliance-FET-Loses-Ground-After-Mpeppe-Spikes-100x"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving world of cryptocurrency, competition among tokens is fierce, with each striving to capture the attention and investment of the market. Recently, Mpeppe (MPEPE), a meme-based cryptocurrency, has made significant waves, overshadowing even the prominent AI-focused coin,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Hack Weekly Report: Indodax Heist, Caterpillar Coin Collapse, and Apple’s Deepfake Incident]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900646/Crypto-Hack-Weekly-Report-Indodax-Heist-Caterpillar-Coin-Collapse-and-Apples-Deepfake-Incident</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900646/Crypto-Hack-Weekly-Report-Indodax-Heist-Caterpillar-Coin-Collapse-and-Apples-Deepfake-Incident"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies have become the new norm in the world of digital currencies and, in the last one week, there have been various security threats across the dominant platforms. Ranging from millions of dollars heists to deepfake cons, hackers carried on to exploit weaknesses in both CeXs and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet approves new staking mechanism with dynamic STRK minting curve]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900647/Starknet-approves-new-staking-mechanism-with-dynamic-STRK-minting-curve</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900647/Starknet-approves-new-staking-mechanism-with-dynamic-STRK-minting-curve"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet community approved a dynamic minting curve for STRK tokens. The minting curve adjusts token supply based on staking participation levels. Starknet Foundation can modify minting parameters to manage inflation and rewards. The Starknet community has successfully passed a proposal to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Says He Will Only Promote Sufficiently Decentralized Ethereum Layer-2s Starting in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900636/Vitalik-Buterin-Says-He-Will-Only-Promote-Sufficiently-Decentralized-Ethereum-Layer-2s-Starting-in-2025</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900636/Vitalik-Buterin-Says-He-Will-Only-Promote-Sufficiently-Decentralized-Ethereum-Layer-2s-Starting-in-2025"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) creator Vitalik Buterin says that starting next year, he will only publicly mention layer-2 projects that he believes are en route to optimal decentralization. Addressing his 5.4 million followers on the social media platform X, Buterin says that in 2025, he plans to only publicly...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Eyes $60K and Likely Haa More Room to Rally, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7453004fc7</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/09/13/bitcoin-eyes-60k-and-likely-have-more-room-to-rally-analyst-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The key variable for risk assets is the U.S. economy as concerns of a recession linger, crypto investment firm Ryze Labs said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Goes on Biggest Bitcoin (BTC) Buying Spree Since 2021: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900622/MicroStrategy-Goes-on-Biggest-Bitcoin-BTC-Buying-Spree-Since-2021-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900622/MicroStrategy-Goes-on-Biggest-Bitcoin-BTC-Buying-Spree-Since-2021-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software firm MicroStrategy is reportedly accumulating Bitcoin (BTC) at the highest rate it has since 2021. According to a new report by Bloomberg, MicroStrategy purchased 18,300 Bitcoin for about $1.1 billion between August 6th and September 12th, the highest amount the firm has bought since...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin liquidations won’t be enough to break $70K+ range high — Here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900615/Bitcoin-liquidations-wont-be-enough-to-break-70K-range-high-Heres-why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900615/Bitcoin-liquidations-wont-be-enough-to-break-70K-range-high-Heres-why"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin bulls stampede toward $60,000 but is there enough energy to break above to 200-day moving average?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nervos Network (CKB) Dominates Crypto Market on Upbit Listing]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900612/Nervos-Network-CKB-Dominates-Crypto-Market-on-Upbit-Listing</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900612/Nervos-Network-CKB-Dominates-Crypto-Market-on-Upbit-Listing"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nervos Network's CKB token outshines the competition, spiking 70% while the broader crypto market remains flat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat Scores Binance Listing, Updates HMSTR Supply Before Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7453015966</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hamster-kombat-scores-binance-listing-updates-hmstr-supply-before-airdrop/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamster Kombat, one of the world’s most successful Web3 games, has announced that Binance will list its HMSTR token and will include the project as the 58th initiative part of its Launchpool structure. Hamster Kombat’s team also stated that HMSTR would have a total supply of 100 billion tokens instead of the already announced 10 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Says Bitcoin 4-Year Cycles Are Over, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7453016710</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-4-year-cycles-are-over/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular analyst Justin Bennett has explained why the Bitcoin four-year cycle might be over for the foreseeable future. He indicated that the crypto’s projected price surge in this market cycle might not happen as planned and that Bitcoin could suffer a severe price crash soon enough. 
 
Why The Bitcoin Four-Year Cycle Might Be Over
 
In an X (formerly Twitter) post, Bennett asserted that Bitcoin follows business cycles while explaining why the leading crypto might be on the verge of a new era. He noted that the leading crypto has been following the perfect four-year cycles since its inception, witnessing two years of a bear market and a bull market. 
 
 
However, he suggested that this could be set to change since Bitcoin’s correlation with business cycles means that a contraction would en…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Eyes $60K and Likely Haa More Room to Rally, Analyst Says]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900614/Bitcoin-Eyes-60K-and-Likely-Haa-More-Room-to-Rally-Analyst-Says</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19900614/Bitcoin-Eyes-60K-and-Likely-Haa-More-Room-to-Rally-Analyst-Says"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin price on Sept. 13 (CoinDesk)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Game ‘Catizen’ Set to Reveal Airdrop Allocations as Binance Rewards Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249385</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249385/telegram-game-catizen-airdrop-allocations-binance-rewards"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram game Catizen will take a snapshot and tell players how many tokens they can claim, with a Binance rewards campaign underway too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Analyst Explains Why Solana and Internet Computer Whales Are Adding Mpeppe (MPEPE) To Their Investments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530d59bb</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/top-analyst-explains-why-solana-and-internet-computer-whales-are-adding-mpeppe-mpepe-to-their-investments/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE), a rising star in the cryptocurrency market, has quickly attracted the attention of large investors from the Solana (SOL) and Internet Computer (ICP) communities. Top analysts are now exploring why whales from these major blockchain platforms are adding Mpeppe (MPEPE) to their investment portfolios. With its unique blend of blockchain innovation, sports culture, and meme-driven appeal, Mpeppe (MPEPE) offers a dynamic new opportunity for growth and wealth creation.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Sports Passion and Blockchain Innovation 
At the core of Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s appeal is its fusion of sports passion, meme culture, and blockchain technology. Inspired by the global popularity of soccer, Mpeppe (MPEPE) unites crypto enthusiasts with sports fans in a community-driven project that aims…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) Bulls Purchase The Fastly Growing Casino ICO Mpeppe (MPEPE) As Eyes $0.00235]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530d59b9</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/uniswap-uni-bulls-purchase-the-fastly-growing-casino-ico-mpeppe-mpepe-as-eyes-0-00235/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uniswap (UNI) bulls are always on the lookout for promising new projects, and Mpeppe (MPEPE) has emerged as one of the most exciting opportunities in the cryptocurrency market. As Mpeppe (MPEPE) gains momentum in the casino and gaming space, Uniswap (UNI) investors are flocking to the fast-growing ICO, anticipating explosive gains as the token eyes a price of $0.00235.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE): Where Sports Fandom Meets Blockchain Innovation 
Introducing Mpeppe (MPEPE), the meme cryptocurrency that unites sports enthusiasts and crypto fans through blockchain innovation. Inspired by the legendary Pepecoin and the talents of professional soccer player Mbappé, Mpeppe (MPEPE) combines sports-related memes with the power of decentralized technology. Uniswap (UNI) investors are drawn to the unique appea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why Solana and Internet Computer Investors Are Buying A.I Cryptocurrency Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530d59b8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/heres-why-solana-and-internet-computer-investors-are-buying-a-i-cryptocurrency-mpeppe-mpepe-casino/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mpeppe (MPEPE) has captured the attention of investors from major cryptocurrency platforms like Solana (SOL) and Internet Computer (ICP). The AI-driven online casino is pioneering a new era of gaming by combining decentralized technology with cutting-edge AI, making it an attractive investment for those looking to diversify into the booming blockchain gaming market. With its transparent, secure, and decentralized structure, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is quickly becoming the go-to option for investors seeking innovative opportunities in crypto gambling.
 
Why Solana and Internet Computer Investors Are Eyeing Mpeppe (MPEPE) 
Solana (SOL) and Internet Computer (ICP) investors are always on the lookout for projects that push the boundaries of blockchain technology. Mpeppe (MPEPE) offers exactly that by in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Computer (ICP) Whales Use Decide AI (DCD) Profits To Join New A.I Crypto Casino Priced 0.0021 USD]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530d59b5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/internet-computer-icp-whales-use-decide-ai-dcd-profits-to-join-new-a-i-crypto-casino-priced-0-0021-usd/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Computer (ICP) whales, who have been reaping significant profits from Decide AI (DCD), are now turning their attention to Mpeppe (MPEPE), the fast-growing AI-powered crypto casino. Priced at just $0.0021 USD, Mpeppe (MPEPE) is quickly becoming the go-to choice for these high-stake investors. With its innovative use of AI and blockchain technology, Mpeppe (MPEPE) offers the perfect opportunity for Internet Computer (ICP) and Decide AI (DCD) investors to diversify their portfolios while capitalizing on the growing trend of decentralized online casinos.
 
Mpeppe (MPEPE)’s Integration of AI and Blockchain: A Game-Changer for Online Casinos 
Mpeppe (MPEPE) is revolutionizing the online gambling industry by combining artificial intelligence with the decentralized nature of blockchain te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Double Solana Holdings In ICP and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino, SOL Struggles To Join Altcoin Momentum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530d59b4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/double-solana-holdings-in-icp-and-mpeppe-mpepe-casino-sol-struggles-to-join-altcoin-momentum/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana (SOL) has been a major player in the crypto market for its speed and efficiency, but as new altcoins gain momentum, it is facing increasing competition from Internet Computer (ICP) and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino. Both ICP and Mpeppe (MPEPE) are carving out their own spaces in the decentralized ecosystem, providing unique advantages that are drawing attention from investors who have traditionally favored Solana (SOL). As SOL struggles to keep pace, ICP and Mpeppe (MPEPE) continue to capitalize on their decentralized, community-driven platforms.
 
Why Investors Are Doubling Their Holdings in Internet Computer (ICP) and Mpeppe (MPEPE) Casino 
As Internet Computer (ICP) and Mpeppe (MPEPE) demonstrate their potential for rapid growth, many investors are choosing to double their holdings in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Left Out as Stocks, Bonds and Gold Party on Global Monetary Easing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7453084939</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/09/13/bitcoin-left-out-as-stocks-bonds-and-gold-party-on-global-monetary-easing/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markets are rallying as might be expected on a new rate cut cycle, but crypto continues to struggle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen  Alpher, Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saudi Minister Hints at 86 Million Tonnes of Petroyuan Adoption, States Country Is ‘Open to New Ideas’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530901a5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/saudi-minister-hints-at-86-million-tonnes-of-petroyuan-adoption-states-country-is-open-to-new-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bandar Alkhorayef, Saudi Minister of Industry and Mineral Resources, stated that while the petroyuan – the use of the Chinese currency to settle oil shipments – was not “substantial to the ministry,” the country was open to new ideas, trying not to mix politics and commerce. This hints at the yuan’s adoption for this purpose. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Nears $60,000 as Traders Anticipate Jumbo Rate Cut]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249381</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249381/bitcoin-price-nears-60000-traders-anticipate-jumbo-rate-cut"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's price rose as reports indicated that the Fed could begin lowering interest rates with a 50-basis-point cut.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tether Hires PayPal Government Affairs Ace as U.S. Scrutiny Unresolved]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74530bae18</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/09/13/tether-hires-paypal-government-affairs-ace-as-us-scrutiny-unresolved/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tether hired a government-affairs veteran from PayPal and Chainalysis, Jesse Spiro, to head its own shop as the issuer of the leading {{USDT}} stablecoin has long been under a cloud of reported U.S. investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floki and GoodEgg Become Meme Favorites As GEGG Develops A.I Dating Platform Using Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c213</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/floki-and-goodegg-become-meme-favorites-as-gegg-develops-a-i-dating-platform-using-cryptocurrency/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of cryptocurrencies, where innovation meets humor, two memecoins have captured the attention of investors and enthusiasts alike: Floki (FLOKI) and GoodEgg (GEGG). While Floki (FLOKI) has already made a name for itself as a fan favorite in the meme coin space, GoodEgg (GEGG) is quickly rising through the ranks, thanks to its development of a groundbreaking A.I-powered dating platform that utilizes cryptocurrency. These two coins are now in the spotlight as potential meme coin giants, each with unique strengths and appeal to different sections of the crypto community.
 
The Rise of Floki (FLOKI)
 
Floki (FLOKI), inspired by Elon Musk’s Shiba Inu dog named Floki, has been one of the most well-known meme coins in the cryptocurrency space. From its humble beginnings, it has built a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Market In Jeopardy? Rising Stablecoins Dominance Signals Instability]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c212</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/stablecoins-dominance-signals-crypto-instability/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The general cryptocurrency market has been quite unpleasant as major crypto assets have seen extended negative trends, fueling uncertainty within the sector. With the recent upsurge in the stablecoins dominance, which is considered a negative sign for cryptocurrencies, the broader ecosystem could be poised for additional pessimistic behavior.
 
Stablecoin Dominance Growth Poses Risk To Cryptocurrencies
 
Recent reports from Alphractal, an advanced platform for investment data analysis, show that the dominance of stablecoins is increasing rapidly amidst price fluctuations. Historically, a drop in stablecoin dominance is a bullish indication for cryptocurrencies, as observed from late 2022 to early 2024, while an increase in dominance is a definite signal of a bearish trend.
 
 
As market vo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum and Bitcoin Investors Add Future A.I Dating Cryptocurrency To Future Investment Portfolios, Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e745cf4c211</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-and-bitcoin-investors-add-future-a-i-dating-cryptocurrency-to-future-investment-portfolios-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T17:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the cryptocurrency market continues to evolve, a new contender is emerging that has caught the attention of Ethereum (ETH) and Bitcoin (BTC) investors—GoodEgg (GEGG), a revolutionary AI-driven dating platform that promises to integrate artificial intelligence with blockchain technology for a game-changing experience. Both ETH and BTC investors, known for seeking strategic, long-term opportunities, are diversifying their portfolios by adding GoodEgg (GEGG), a project set to reshape online dating.
 
GoodEgg (GEGG) — A Game-Changer in AI and Blockchain 
The GoodEgg (GEGG) platform combines the power of artificial intelligence with the security of blockchain to create a next-level dating experience. By using advanced AI algorithms, GoodEgg (GEGG) matches users more efficiently while ensurin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoinist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘Rocky Rabbit’ Enigma and SuperSet Daily Combo Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=245981</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/here-are-todays-rocky-rabbit-enigma-superset-daily-combo-solutions"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T16:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can earn millions of free in-game coins in the Telegram game Rocky Rabbit. Here are the solutions for Friday, September 13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Government Intensifies Pressure on Nigeria to Free Detained Binance Exec: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249331</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249331/us-officials-pressure-nigeria-free-detained-binance-exec"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officials have reportedly stepped up attempts to advocate for the release of Binance executive Tigran Gambaryan from Nigerian prison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer Watchdog Calls Tether a 'Disaster for Consumers Waiting to Happen']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249323</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249323/consumer-watchdog-calls-tether-a-disaster-for-consumers-waiting-to-happen"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Tether has many of the same issues that FTX and Celsius had before their collapse," the watchdog wrote on its letter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Just Bought Another $1.1 Billion Worth of Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249319</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249319/microstrategy-just-bought-another-1-1-billion-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor's software firm MicroStrategy now holds over $14 billion worth of Bitcoin after four years of buying up BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Pushes for Jury Trial in SEC Lawsuit, Rails Against 'Crypto Asset Securities' Claims]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249313</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249313/kraken-pushes-for-jury-trial-in-sec-lawsuit-rails-against-crypto-asset-securities-claims"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T14:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken accused the SEC of blocking efforts to register or cooperate, saying they were "stonewalled" by inconsistent rulings and guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money, Get Away: Fake Celebrity Meme Coin Linked to Pink Floyd and Neymar Is 'Saddest Launch' Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249290</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249290/money-get-away-fake-celebrity-meme-coin-linked-to-pink-floyd-and-neymar-is-saddest-launch-ever"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The celebrity meta is officially dead," Bubblemaps CEO says after celeb-pushed token fails to break $20,000 market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘X Empire’ Elon Musk Game Daily Combo and Riddle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the X Empire daily combo and riddle solution for Friday, September 13? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today's ‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo and Cipher Code]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=239305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-hamster-kombat-daily-combo-cipher-code"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the daily combo and cipher code for Friday, September 13? Here’s what you need to make bank in Telegram game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Defines 'Stage 1+' Layer-2 Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249281/how-ethereum-founder-vitalik-buterin-defines-stage-1-layer-2-networks"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T12:43:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It doesn't matter if I invested, or if you're my friend; stage 1 or bust,” he said in a recent tweet. Here's what that means.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Stagnates as Analysts Forecast Potential Bottom For Ethereum Before End of Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249278/bitcoin-stagnates-as-analysts-forecast-potential-bottom-for-ethereum-before-end-of-year"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T10:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Traders should monitor medium-term reversal indicators such as RSI and Stochastics," to catch signs of assets being oversold, said 10X Research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Launches New ‘01’ Model That Outperforms ChatGPT-4o]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249227</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249227/openai-launches-new-01-model-that-outperforms-chatgpt-4o"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T01:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI developer said it is “resetting the counter” for its product names as its latest set of models excel across its tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill to Fight AI Deepfakes Reaches US House as Entertainment Industry Cheers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249254</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249254/entertainment-industry-celebrates-as-no-fakes-act-moves-to-congress"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T00:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With backing from both parties, the legislation follows the intrduction of its counterpart in the U.S. Senate earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ and ‘Catizen’ Telegram Token Demand Could Disrupt TON, Devs Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249203</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249203/hamster-kombat-catizen-token-airdrops-ton-issues"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T23:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrop season on The Open Network is nearly here, and developers admit that demand could get the better of the Telegram-linked network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why CEO Jack Lu Is Pushing Magic Eden Beyond NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/x4A4U9Z4/why-ceo-jack-lu-is-pushing-magic-eden-beyond-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/x4A4U9Z4/why-ceo-jack-lu-is-pushing-magic-eden-beyond-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Eden's grip on the NFT market has been cemented by a multi-chain approach under co-founder and CEO Jack Lu. Now the marketplace is pushing forward with a digital wallet that bridges Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Solana as it eyes other future expansions. Lu discusses Magic Eden's evolution since its early days, along with valuable lessons learned in the turbulent crypto industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe Pushes Into Generative Video With Firefly Amid AI Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249181</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249181/adobe-pushes-into-generative-video-with-firefly-amid-ai-controversy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adobe’s Firefly Video Model, set for release in beta later this year, introduces new generative AI capabilities to its Premiere Pro video suite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Magic Muffins’ Game Launches on Telegram to Take on ‘Hamster Kombat’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249215</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249215/magic-muffins-game-telegram-take-on-hamster-kombat"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earn Alliance’s Telegram game Magic Muffins delivers a tap-based combat experience that’s tied to the platform’s upcoming ALLY token launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kalshi's US Election Prediction Markets Go Live as CFTC Seeks Appeal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249204</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249204/kalshi-us-election-prediction-markets-go-live-cftc-seeks-appeal"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legal and regulated U.S. prediction markets platform Kalshi has launched its first election pools after the court win over the CFTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Dollar Is Taking Over the World Thanks to Stablecoins: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249197</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249197/stablecoins-drive-us-dollar-dominance-globally"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Survey data shows that stablecoins are inciting net flows into dollar instruments where U.S. dollar banking is unavailable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Wrapped Bitcoin Sparks Pushback from Justin Sun]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249189</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249189/coinbase-wrapped-bitcoin-sparks-pushback-from-justin-sun"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T20:31:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TRON founder's connection to  WBTC has driven interest in alternatives, and Sun is not a fan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Hamster Kombat’ Will Give Out Billions of Tokens via Binance in Telegram Game Airdrop]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249171</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249171/hamster-kombat-give-out-billions-tokens-binance-telegram-game-airdrop"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T18:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance users will be able to earn a share of 3 billion HMSTR in the lead-up to Hamster Kombat’s token launch on TON.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana’s Pump.Fun Has Launched Millions of Tokens—Fewer Than 100 Are Worth Much at All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249107</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249107/fewer-than-100-pump-fun-tokens-above-1m-market-cap-amid-meme-coin-lull"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T17:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pump.fun is “stale,” traders believe, as the protocol fails to keep more than 100 tokens above a $1 million market cap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuse Plugs Solana Token Into Energy Distribution DePIN Play]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=248985</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/248985/fuse-plugs-solana-token-energy-distribution-depin-play"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T17:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a new $12 million fundraising round, the renewable energy company aims to reward customers for supporting the power grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Central Bank Drops Interest Rates Again as Bitcoin, Stocks Bounce Back]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249154</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249154/european-central-bank-drops-interest-rates-again-bitcoin-up"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed is likely to drop rates next, potentially setting up Bitcoin for another "Uptober" after a shaky start to September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 198 - THE GREAT APE HEIST!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RJ6YcMxP/fomo-hour-198-the-great-ape-heist</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/RJ6YcMxP/fomo-hour-198-the-great-ape-heist"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto rises with stocks after CPI falls again. Bitfinex BTC longs continue to grow. SUI again leads L1s, up 18%. FTX estate unstakes $24m SOL, still has $943m. Binance introduces SOL liquid staking. SWIFT introduces infrastructure for RWA transfers. Pendle launches Bitcoin yield pools. UK makes crypto legal property. India leads crypto adoption for second year. Vitalik won’t advertise L2s with multi-sig security. Based rollups seen as alternative future for ETH. Blockchain music start up raises $50m. Ford & Toyota file blockchain patents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Debuts XRP Trust Following Bitcoin and Ethereum ETF Launches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249124</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249124/grayscale-debuts-xrp-trust-bitcoin-ethereum-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto asset manager Grayscale launched the XRP Trust, a new product giving investors exposure to the Ripple-aligned asset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Eve Frontier’ Survival Game Is Being Built on Ethereum, CCP Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249126</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249126/eve-frontier-survival-game-ethereum-ccp-reveals"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T15:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eve Online maker CCP Games has rebranded Project Awakening, which is being built on Ethereum layer-2 network Redstone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Will Hit New High Price If Trump or Harris Wins, Says Analyst—But Bettors Favor Kamala]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249073</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249073/bitcoin-hit-new-high-price-trump-or-harris-wins-bettors-favor-kamala"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris has pulled ahead of Donald Trump on Polymarket, but Standard Chartered sees a new Bitcoin peak if either candidate wins the election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Under Fire for Alleged Political Favoritism in SEC Appointments]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249095</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249095/gary-gensler-under-fire-for-alleged-political-favoritism-in-sec-appointments"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The SEC appears to be unlawfully considering an applicant’s political ideology when hiring bureaucrats," the lawmakers wrote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vismaya V</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eToro Will Only Offer Bitcoin, Ethereum, and Bitcoin Cash in US After Settling SEC Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249074</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249074/etoro-only-offer-bitcoin-ethereum-bitcoin-cash-us-settling-sec-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC announced that eToro has settled securities charges, and will pay a penalty alongside curtailing offered crypto assets in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward,André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gameloft Reveals 'Claynosaurz' Mobile Game Based on Solana NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=249031</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/249031/gameloft-claynosaurz-mobile-game-solana-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana NFT collection Claynosaurz is expanding into gaming via a team-up with mobile giant Gameloft. Here's what to expect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fomo Hour 197 - Debate Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rMxl1cgJ/fomo-hour-197-debate-disaster</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rMxl1cgJ/fomo-hour-197-debate-disaster"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T19:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls slightly after Presidential debate. Exchanges see highest BTC outflow since May. Be wary of Yen move for BTC: Hayes. SOL active addresses hit ATH. At least 5 massive SOL announcements coming: Mert. Binomial to introduce restaking on BNB. Indonesian exchange hacked for $22m. Atomic Wallet wins lawsuit over $100m hack. Lawyers argue Ellison shouldn’t go to jail. ENS integrated with Venmo & PayPal. Galaxy & State Street launch 3 crypto ETFs. Standard Chartered begins UAE crypto custody. AAVE leads resurgence in DeFi coins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 196 - THE INFLOWS RETURN!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/e9F8zYRp/fomo-hour-196-the-inflows-return</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/e9F8zYRp/fomo-hour-196-the-inflows-return"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$29m, ETH ETFs: -$5m. BTC rallies, ETF has first inflow in 9 trading days. BTC may have put in first higher low in 6 months. Saylor predicts $13m price for BTC. Wealth advisors quickly adopting BTC: BitWise CEO. Binance among few firms to get Indonesia license. Spot trading on CEXs up 30% in August. SEC made $4.68bn from crypto firms in 2023. $5.6bn lost to scams in 2023. XRP security status may be unchallenged in appeal. EtherFi announces credit card on Scroll. Base has more DEX users than other L2s combined. Tether & Tron create taskforce against crime. TIA still only making $585 in daily fees. WLD investigated by Singapore police.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 195 - CAN WE GET A BOUNCE?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/m7JRnQJc/fomo-hour-195-can-we-get-a-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/m7JRnQJc/fomo-hour-195-can-we-get-a-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 55.3k (+2%), ETH: 2320 (+1%), SOL: 130 (0%). Top Gainers: FTM, TAO, BTT, AAVE, TON, ATOM. Crypto mini-bounce continues, BTC reclaims $55k. BTC RSI hits lowest level since July 2021. Bitfinex longs continue to grow aggressively. BTC hashrate hits another ATH. BTC could hit $90k on Trump election: Bernstein. BlackRock settles intraday BTC trades off-chain. Spot BTC ETFs have been a failure: Bianco. Power giant Tepco explores Bitcoin mining. ETH Foundation & Vitalik continue to sell ETH. Farcaster DAU’s down 95%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting MYRIAD, a prediction market and digital media engagement ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Rwj71okY/presenting-myriad-a-prediction-market-and-digital-media-engagement-ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/Rwj71okY/presenting-myriad-a-prediction-market-and-digital-media-engagement-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T14:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Media company DASTAN, the parent company of Decrypt and Rug Radio, is embarking on the next stage of its evolution with the launch of MYRIAD, a prediction market and engagement ecosystem that aims to “transform the digital media landscape.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 194 - ARE NFTS BACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5oNbWn5H/fomo-hour-194-are-nfts-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5oNbWn5H/fomo-hour-194-are-nfts-back"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T12:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto weak after continued ETF outflows. Durov breaks silence, TON bounces 3%. Telegram will start moderating private chats. Hayes & Brandt flip bearish on BTC. Coinbase shares hit 7 month lows. 90% of crypto firm applications rejected in UK. Japan’s 3 largest banks to trial stablecoins. Trump promises again to embrace crypto. INJ launches BlackRock BUIDL index. DWF to launch synthetic stablecoin. Vitalik to donate all L2 tokens to charity. Most VCs in crypto ‘will disappear’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Researcher Explains Meme Coin Mania]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tC2Oz5H9/crypto-researcher-explains-meme-coin-mania</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tC2Oz5H9/crypto-researcher-explains-meme-coin-mania"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T18:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Head of Research at CoinMarketCap, Alice Liu, breaks down the highs and lows of meme coin mania in 2024. We’ve seen meme coins like Dogwifhat (WIF) soar to huge market caps and we’ve seen political meme coins crash as the candidate drops out (BODEN). Liu explains the data behind all of this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 193 - NVIDIA DROPS-OFF]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LxNEmmjX/fomo-hour-193-nvidia-drops-off</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LxNEmmjX/fomo-hour-193-nvidia-drops-off"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls on macro wobble, Yen fears. OI wiped in BTC drop to $56k, funding negative. Altcoins down 13% YTD, stablecoin supply up 30%. BTC mining profitability at record low: JP Morgan. FBI says North Korea targeting BTC ETF issuers. Trump family to launch DeFi project on ETH. Trump project linked to AVAX’s Dough Finance. Trump family members hacked during launch. AI coins underperform after Nvidia investigation. MATIC upgrade to POL begins. TON falls as Telegram faces issues in many countries. VC funding & BTC correlation breaks down. We have entered crypto’s ‘corporate phase’. Gensler will leave regardless of election: Ripple CEO. Harris campaign has asked Coinbase for advice. Penpie DeFi project hacked for $27m. Galois Capital settles with SEC over FTX custody.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 192 - WTF IS ETHERVISTA]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xOt72jL2/fomo-hour-192-wtf-is-ethervista</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xOt72jL2/fomo-hour-192-wtf-is-ethervista"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T19:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OI continues to rise as BTC stabilises. BTC still best performing assets class this year. FTX to distribute $16bn to creditors starting in Q4. Qatar introduces regulatory framework for crypto. ETH L1s fees down 90%, L2 activity ATH. Base hits 14m monthly users, many may be Sybil. ETH is in death spiral: Krueger. SOL to see significant unlocks in Q1. Japan considers dropping crypto tax to 20%. Rate cuts won’t help BTC: Hayes. BTC should double after rate cuts: Tapiero. Mr 100 linked back to Upbit wallet. WazirX hacker moves funds to Tornado. SUI to launch handheld gaming device. Sony & PYTH announce collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin Millionaire Explains How Neiro United Meme Coins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LjhyvMyI/dogecoin-millionaire-explains-how-neiro-united-meme-coins</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LjhyvMyI/dogecoin-millionaire-explains-how-neiro-united-meme-coins"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T13:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kabosu, the dog many know as Doge and the mascot of Dogecoin, sadly passed away earlier this year. Its owner later adopted another Shiba Inu called Neiro which caused a long blockchain civil war with multiple tokens battling it out for liquidity. Now a month later SlumDOGE, the man who became a millionaire off Dogecoin (but never sold), explains why Neiro is a moment for the dog coin community to unite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 191 - CRYPTO STABLE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VM5OAovR/fomo-hour-191-crypto-stable</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/VM5OAovR/fomo-hour-191-crypto-stable"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T17:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: -$72m, ETH ETFs: -$2m. BTC weekly volatility returns to multi-year lows. BlackRock BTC ETF sees first outflow in months. ETH dominance hits 4-year low. Vitalik linked wallet sells $2m ETH. Bukele talks up BTC impact in Time interview. CBoE files for ETH & BTC ETF options. Elon & Tesla win DOGE manipulation lawsuit. Macron denies inviting Durov to France. Trump promises to make US the ‘crypto capital’. Trump advertises Liberty Financial DeFi project. DeFi mindshare continues to grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 190 - OPENSEA VS SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g3scPNlK/fomo-hour-190-opensea-vs-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/g3scPNlK/fomo-hour-190-opensea-vs-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC: 59.7k (0%), ETH: 2545 (0%), SOL: 146 (-1%). Top Gainers: HNT, IMX, ICP, ADA, KCS. BTC ETFs: -$105m, ETH ETFs: +$6m. Bitcoin in tight liquidation range, ETH outperforms. ETH ETF sees first in flow in 10 days. Funding rates all turn negative. Mr 100 buys 500 BTC in dip. France formally charges Durov, can’t leave country. TON jumps 6% after Durov release. TON faces another outage related to DOGS. AI coins fall after Nvidia earnings. Crypto payments about to soar: Armstrong. Binance denies freezing Palestinian accounts. CryptoCom & Standard Chartered partner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 189 - TRUMP LAUNCHES MORE NFTS]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xUt5dSH4/fomo-hour-189-trump-launches-more-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/xUt5dSH4/fomo-hour-189-trump-launches-more-nfts"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: -$127m, ETH ETFs: -$3m. BTC hits $58k after ETF outflows, then bounces. BTC sees largest exchange outflow in a year. Divergence between BTC & stocks grows. TON stops producing blocks briefly, price bounces. TON outage linked to DOGS launch. Maker DAO rebrands as Sky. USDS upgrade from DAI will have freezing function. Robinhood readds SOL support. SEC charges 2 brothers with $60m crypto scam. Nasdaq pitches options on BTC ETFs. Full-time open source devs under 8k in crypto. Crypto owners more likely to be ‘psychopaths’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 188 - TON CONTINUES TO FALL]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UhURASRQ/fomo-hour-188-ton-continues-to-fall</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UhURASRQ/fomo-hour-188-ton-continues-to-fall"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock ETF sees biggest inflow in 35 days. BTC ETFs have 12 straight days of inflows. ETH ETFs have 8 straight days of outflows. ETH/BTC ratio continues to hit new lows. Russia to start using crypto for trade this week. Stablecoin TVL hits ATH of $168bn. Durov faces several serious charges in France. Telegram also under investigation in India. TRX flips TON, enters top 10 crypto coins. Crypto is the currency of AI: Naval. 84k new crypto millionaires created this year. SEC lawsuit against Kraken to proceed to trial. Aave proposes integration with BlackRock BUIDL. Celsius has repaid $2.5bn in assets so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 187 - AI TOKENS LEADING]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M7IhK60K/fomo-hour-187-ai-tokens-leading</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/M7IhK60K/fomo-hour-187-ai-tokens-leading"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI tokens lead ahead of Nvidia earnings. Crypto funds saw $533m inflows last week. BTC ‘bull market’ back on in IFP index. BTC close to ‘parabolic zone’ soon. Many coins ‘flipping back to bullish’ indicators. Open Interest begins to creep back up again. Binance Labs to focus on AI investments. 51 L2s now built on OP stack alone. Some exchanges rejected for Hong Kong license. Vitalik questions DeFi yields in crypto. New malware steals crypto on MacOS. Avalanche Discord hacked after Polygon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Meme Coin That Became a REAL Religion!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/szDuQcIw/the-meme-coin-that-became-a-real-religion</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/szDuQcIw/the-meme-coin-that-became-a-real-religion"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T17:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pastor Kelby created a meme coin on Pumpdotfun which has since registered a church and developed its own religious theories and philosophies. Twice a day Kelby heads a sermon on Twitter where he spreads lessons from books that have personally helped him achieve happiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 186 - AVAX LEADS PUMP]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JRqyT8vz/fomo-hour-186-avax-leads-pump</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/JRqyT8vz/fomo-hour-186-avax-leads-pump"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$65m, ETH ETFs: -$1m. Crypto stays range-bound ahead of Powell speech. Russia plans stablecoins of BRICS countries. El Salvador buys 162 BTC with daily buys. AVAX up 15% as Grayscale launches trust. Tron removes 12k BTC from USDD reserves. Trump promotes crypto DeFi project. Crypto half of corporate political donations. Tether abandons plan to launch its own blockchain. Sony backed L2 set to launch in weeks. Babylon launches BTC staking. CZ leaves prison for ‘halfway house’. PayPal & Anchorage partner for bank crypto rewards. Bitcoin mining market worth $74bn: JP Morgan. Bitfarms buys Stronghold in ‘strategic defence’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 185 - KAMALA 'SUPPORTS' CRYPTO?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u48y6NBU/fomo-hour-185-kamala-supports-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/u48y6NBU/fomo-hour-185-kamala-supports-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$40m, ETH ETFs: -$18m. BTC breaks channel, ripe for ‘short squeeze’. BTC OI rises $1.3bn post Fed minutes. Kamala ‘supports crypto policies’ says advisor. Vitalik ‘bull posts’ ETH. Story Protocol raises $80m for L1. WazirX halts open orders after problems with Rupee. Coinbase & Ripple lead political donations. Salame claims government reneged on plea deal. EigenLayer team claimed coins despite being in US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 184 - PUNKS ARE FLYING!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ILpzl0Wk/fomo-hour-184-punks-are-flying</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ILpzl0Wk/fomo-hour-184-punks-are-flying"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T17:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$88m, ETH ETFs: -$7m. BTC funding negative in ‘short squeeze’ setup. BTC dominance up 18% in 2 years. TRX leads L1s as memecoin activity soars. Chance of SOL ETF is zero in 2024: Bloomberg. Another SOL ETF approved in Brazil. Binance & CZ face new class action lawsuit. Tether to launch UAE-Dirham stablecoin. Mt Gox moves $700m in BTC. CRV founder faces backlash on DAO proposal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>