<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-27T08:19:05.690Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-07-27T08:19:05.690Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Ethereum Trust ETF hits historic net outflow of $1.5B]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731173/Grayscale-Ethereum-Trust-ETF-hits-historic-net-outflow-of-15B</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731173/Grayscale-Ethereum-Trust-ETF-hits-historic-net-outflow-of-15B"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T08:05:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the present rate of outflows, ETHE's ether reserves may be exhausted in a relatively short timeframe, potentially within weeks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How This Short Seller Who Is a Crypto Critic Hit a Legal Snag with the SEC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74711d9faf</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/heres-how-this-short-seller-who-is-a-crypto-critic/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T08:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Left, a controversial figure behind Citron Research, renowned for his critical stance on crypto and often bearish stance on various high-profile stocks, has found himself on the other side of the law.
 
Recently charged by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Left is accused of orchestrating a deceptive $20 million scheme that manipulated stock prices for personal gain.
 
This turn of events casts a long shadow over his career, particularly ironic given his past accusations that the cryptocurrency sector was “a complete fraud.”
 
 
Details of the Allegations
 
In Left’s case, federal prosecutors said he carried out a “systematic scheme to drive market prices in the stock markets” by issuing public recommendations.
 
In its complaint, the SEC detailed a scheme in which Le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How This Short Seller Who Is a Crypto Critic Hit a Legal Snag with the SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731170/Heres-How-This-Short-Seller-Who-Is-a-Crypto-Critic-Hit-a-Legal-Snag-with-the-SEC</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731170/Heres-How-This-Short-Seller-Who-Is-a-Crypto-Critic-Hit-a-Legal-Snag-with-the-SEC"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T08:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Left, a controversial figure behind Citron Research, renowned for his critical stance on crypto and often bearish stance on various high-profile stocks, has found himself on the other side of the law. Recently charged by the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), Left is accused of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Goldman Sachs Exec Shifts Most of His Assets to Solana, Moving Away from Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731158/Ex-Goldman-Sachs-Exec-Shifts-Most-of-His-Assets-to-Solana-Moving-Away-from-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731158/Ex-Goldman-Sachs-Exec-Shifts-Most-of-His-Assets-to-Solana-Moving-Away-from-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T08:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raoul Pal, CEO of Real Vision, has dramatically revised his investment strategy by shifting the bulk of his liquid assets into Solana (SOL), moving away from Bitcoin (BTC) and other cryptocurrencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WienerAI Raises $8M in Presale, Less than 5 Days to Go]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731132/WienerAI-Raises-8M-in-Presale-Less-than-5-Days-to-Go</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731132/WienerAI-Raises-8M-in-Presale-Less-than-5-Days-to-Go"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:42:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WienerAI ($WAI) has already raised over $8 million in presale funds, and with less than five days left, the window to become an early investor is rapidly closing. This meme coin, featuring an irresistibly cute wiener dog mascot, is set to shake up the meme coin scene, offering more than just...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Steal 70% of Crypto Ransomware Money]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731134/Russian-Hackers-Steal-70-of-Crypto-Ransomware-Money</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731134/Russian-Hackers-Steal-70-of-Crypto-Ransomware-Money"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report reveals that Russian-speaking hackers dominate the ransomware market, stealing nearly 70% of all illicit cryptocurrency earnings in 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Set to Surpass Gold in Market Value, According to SkyBridge Captal Founder]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731123/Bitcoin-Set-to-Surpass-Gold-in-Market-Value-According-to-SkyBridge-Captal-Founder</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731123/Bitcoin-Set-to-Surpass-Gold-in-Market-Value-According-to-SkyBridge-Captal-Founder"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Bitcoin 2024 conference in Nashville, Anthony Scaramucci, founder of SkyBridge Capital, projected that Bitcoin will soon eclipse gold in market capitalization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[X faces controversy over using user data for training AI chatbot Grok: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731126/X-faces-controversy-over-using-user-data-for-training-AI-chatbot-Grok-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731126/X-faces-controversy-over-using-user-data-for-training-AI-chatbot-Grok-Report"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several X accounts have made comments on the default setting on the social media platform that allows user's data "to train Grok."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘There’s a Very Big Move To Come’: Raoul Pal Says One Indicator Signaling Solana Will Vastly Outperform Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731104/Theres-a-Very-Big-Move-To-Come-Raoul-Pal-Says-One-Indicator-Signaling-Solana-Will-Vastly-Outperform-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731104/Theres-a-Very-Big-Move-To-Come-Raoul-Pal-Says-One-Indicator-Signaling-Solana-Will-Vastly-Outperform-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Macro guru and Real Vision CEO Raoul Pal believes that Solana (SOL) will furiously outpace Bitcoin (BTC) this cycle. In a new YouTube strategy session, Pal says that Solana could be printing a classic bullish inverse head and shoulders pattern (I-HNS) pattern against Bitcoin. “That’s a killer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana – Why network activity ALONE won’t work for SOL’s price]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731096/Solana-Why-network-activity-ALONE-wont-work-for-SOLs-price</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731096/Solana-Why-network-activity-ALONE-wont-work-for-SOLs-price"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can these factors help Solana decouple from the rest of the market?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pi Network New Update: Launched Social Profiles in Pi2Day]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731087/Pi-Network-New-Update-Launched-Social-Profiles-in-Pi2Day</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731087/Pi-Network-New-Update-Launched-Social-Profiles-in-Pi2Day"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Pi2Day 2024, Pi Network took a big step forward in connecting its community by launching Social Profiles. This new feature lets users personalize their presence on the network, making it easier to engage with the community. It is a key part of building useful tools before the Pi Network...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly review calendar week 30 – 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731102/Weekly-review-calendar-week-30-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731102/Weekly-review-calendar-week-30-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened this week in the world of blockchain and cryptocurrencies? Current events and background reports in the weekly review.The article Weekly review calendar week 30 – 2024 was first published on Crypto Valley Journal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s Why VanEck’s CEO Holds ‘Way Over 30%’ of His Portfolion in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731078/Heres-Why-VanEcks-CEO-Holds-Way-Over-30-of-His-Portfolion-in-Bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731078/Heres-Why-VanEcks-CEO-Holds-Way-Over-30-of-His-Portfolion-in-Bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck recently outlined a scenario in which BTC can skyrocket to $2.9M within the next 26 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackRock’s Crypto Focus: Bitcoin vs. Ethereum—Who’s Winning the ETF Battle?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731069/BlackRocks-Crypto-Focus-Bitcoin-vs-EthereumWhos-Winning-the-ETF-Battle</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731069/BlackRocks-Crypto-Focus-Bitcoin-vs-EthereumWhos-Winning-the-ETF-Battle"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the recent Bitcoin Conference in Nashville, Tennessee, BlackRock’s head of digital assets, Robert Mitchnick, shared the firm’s focused approach to cryptocurrency exchange-traded funds (ETFs). As BlackRock navigates the evolving crypto landscape, it remains centered on Bitcoin and Ethereum,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Philippines Plans to Introduce Wholesale CBDC by 2029]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747104be08</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/philippines-plans-to-introduce-wholesale-cbdc-by-2029/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP) plans to introduce its wholesale central bank digital currency (CBDC) by 2029. The Philippine central bank’s CBDC initiative is near its proof-of-concept completion. “This is an innovative payment instrument,” said the BSP deputy governor. “This is an entirely new thing, and we have to make sure that we can offer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr. Questions Trump's Pro-Crypto Stance As 2024 Presidential Race Heats Up: 'I Hope...Commitment To Bitcoin Is More Than Political Expediency']]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731079/Robert-F-Kennedy-Jr-Questions-Trumps-Pro-Crypto-Stance-As-2024-Presidential-Race-Heats-Up-I-HopeCommitment-To-Bitcoin-Is-More-Than-Political-Expediency</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731079/Robert-F-Kennedy-Jr-Questions-Trumps-Pro-Crypto-Stance-As-2024-Presidential-Race-Heats-Up-I-HopeCommitment-To-Bitcoin-Is-More-Than-Political-Expediency"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert F. Kennedy Jr., an independent U.S. presidential candidate, raised questions about the recent pro-cryptocurrency stance of GOP nominee Donald Trump. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Elizabeth Warren Doubles Down on Crypto Criticism Amid Loss of Support]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731046/Senator-Elizabeth-Warren-Doubles-Down-on-Crypto-Criticism-Amid-Loss-of-Support</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731046/Senator-Elizabeth-Warren-Doubles-Down-on-Crypto-Criticism-Amid-Loss-of-Support"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Senator Elizabeth Warren has continued her vocal opposition to cryptocurrencies, despite losing some of her legislative backing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Discussion, July 27, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731005/Daily-Discussion-July-27-2024</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731005/Daily-Discussion-July-27-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please utilize this sticky thread for all general Bitcoin discussions! If you see posts on the front page or /r/Bitcoin/new which are better suited for this daily discussion thread, please help out by directing the OP to this thread instead. Thank you! If you don't get an answer to your...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto News: Crypto Prices Hold Steady Amidst Market Trends]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731003/Crypto-News-Crypto-Prices-Hold-Steady-Amidst-Market-Trends</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731003/Crypto-News-Crypto-Prices-Hold-Steady-Amidst-Market-Trends"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VanEck observed that many Bitcoin conference attendees were curious about SOL, suggesting a Solana ETF could be on the horizon. The SEC has approved Grayscale's Bitcoin Mini Trust ETF, launching next week with a low 0.15% fee, following the successful Ethereum Mini Trust model. Crypto Fear and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Bitcoin, HODLing is the best bet: Marathon Digital tells us why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731000/For-Bitcoin-HODLing-is-the-best-bet-Marathon-Digital-tells-us-why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731000/For-Bitcoin-HODLing-is-the-best-bet-Marathon-Digital-tells-us-why"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital will turn to a HODL strategy, indicating confidence in Bitcoin's long-term value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Announced an Important Update for One Popular Altcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19730991/Binance-Announced-an-Important-Update-for-One-Popular-Altcoin</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19730991/Binance-Announced-an-Important-Update-for-One-Popular-Altcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance, the world's largest cryptocurrency exchange, has officially completed the token exchange and rebranding of Render (RNDR) to Render (RENDER).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Airdrop della crypto AVAIL: tutti i dati post-launch]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731036/Airdrop-della-crypto-AVAIL-tutti-i-dati-post-launch</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19731036/Airdrop-della-crypto-AVAIL-tutti-i-dati-post-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avail has just introduced in mainnet the first modular level of DA while simultaneously launching its own crypto airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study: AI Success in Africa Depends on Availability of Local Language Data and AI Talent]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e747101af10</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/study-ai-success-in-africa-depends-on-availability-of-local-language-data-and-ai-talent/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T05:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the latest Global System for Mobile Communications (GSMA) study report, the success of artificial intelligence (AI) in Africa hinges largely on the availability of local language data and addressing the AI skills gap. The report urges African countries to prioritize investment in domain-specific and local language data. It also recommends adopting participatory approaches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is This Solana Meme Coin The Next Dogwifhat (WIF)? $2.4 Million Buy Stuns Community]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74710c090c</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-meme-coin-dogwifhat/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T05:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meme coin trading on the Solana network has exploded over the last year, with the likes of BONK, Dogwifhat, and POPCAT going from below $1 million to over $1 billion in market cap. There have been other successful coins as well running into the hundreds of millions in market cap. However, one meme coin is standing out currently after a Dogwifhat whale completed a massive $2.4 million purchase that triggered a surge in the price.
 
Solana Trader Puts $2.4 Million Into MUMU The Bull
 
MUMU The Bull is another Solana meme coin that has been slowly making its way toward the $100 million market cap level. It finally reached $100 million this week, which is when fear of missing out (FOMO) seems to have set in for some investors.
 
 
On Thursday, the on-chain data tracker for the Solana network, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fintech Company Tecban Pilots Tokenization Platform for Brazil’s Drex CBDC]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74710e47b9</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fintech-company-tecban-pilots-tokenization-platform-for-brazils-drex-cbdc/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T04:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tecban, a fintech that provides interconnection technology for banks, has launched a tokenization and associated services platform called Nexchain. This platform facilitates the process of placing assets on the blockchain for third parties as part of the Drex pilot. The platform will be launched in tandem with the second pilot phase of the Brazilian CBDC, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Advances Cryptocurrency Mining Bill]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74710ae2cc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russia-advances-cryptocurrency-mining-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T03:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s State Duma has advanced a bill to regulate cryptocurrency mining, aiming to curb illegal activities and promote investment and employment. Proposed by the chairman of the Duma Committee on Financial Markets and supported by key deputies, the bill mandates strict guidelines for miners, including registration and government oversight. If passed, the law will take […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Rising: Next Most “Hated” Range Will Be Between $75,000 And $95,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74710ae1ca</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-rising-most-hated-range-75000-and-95000/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T03:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After concerns early this week, Bitcoin has rebounded sharply at spot rates. At the time of writing, the world’s most valuable coin is up 20% from July 2024 lows. 
 
Considering the upsurge from July 25, there is a high chance it will pierce $70,000 over the weekend and even break above the all-important liquidation level of $72,000.
 
Analyst: Expect Bitcoin To Range Between $75,000 And $95,000
 
As Bitcoin regains footing, much to the excitement of bulls, some analysts now believe this is the beginning of the next leg up. This preview is positive, at least based on the recent price action. 
 
 
Taking to X, one analyst said the zone between $75,000 and $95,000 will be the next “hated” region. At this zone, the coin would have broken above all-time highs at $74,000, last printed in March,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Poised to Dominate World Bank and IMF, Says Russian Executive Director]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472f75af7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-poised-to-dominate-world-bank-imf-says-russian-executive-director/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T02:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank Executive Director for Russia forecasts that BRICS nations will soon dominate the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund (IMF), attributing this shift to inevitable macroeconomic and demographic changes away from Western dominance. He emphasized the importance of working patiently toward this goal and resisting provocations from those upholding the old global […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comrades In Crime: Russian-Speaking Hackers Bag 70% Of Crypto Proceeds – Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472f14e8e</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/russian-speaking-hackers-bag-70-of-crypto-proceeds/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T02:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study from TRM Labs says that Russia’s involvement in illegal crypto operations grew a lot in 2023. Almost 70% of all cryptocurrency earnings from ransomware came from groups of people who spoke Russian. This makes them big players in this field.
 
 
It is clear that Russia plays a significant part in the worldwide hacking sector, as these entities have stolen almost half a billion US dollars, the report disclosed.
 
The study puts in the spotlight ALPHV/BlackCat and Lockbit, two ransomware operators that profited over $320 million. Sanctioned hacker Lockbit has targeted Boeing and the Royal Mail in the UK.
 
The MGM Resorts and the Fortune 500 dental and medical supply wholesaler Henry Schein are targets for BlackCat/ALPHV. Not only do these assaults show how far-reaching and sophistica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS Considers Iran’s Proposal to Link Payment Systems of All Member Countries, Says Russian Official]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472f38ac8</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/brics-considers-irans-proposal-to-link-payment-systems-of-all-member-countries-says-russian-official/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T01:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BRICS economic bloc is considering Iran’s proposal to link all member nations’ payment systems, according to Russian Deputy Foreign Minister Andrey Rudenko. The proposal aims to enhance BRICS countries’ financial sovereignty by establishing a resilient and sanctions-resistant payment infrastructure. Discussions include integrating financial markets, payments in national currencies, and new mechanisms for mutual financial […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investors Won’t Sell BTC Even if Price Drops to $3K, Peter Schiff’s Poll Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472ffc2b7</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-investors-wont-sell-btc-even-if-price-drops-to-3k-peter-schiffs-poll-shows/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T00:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gold advocate Peter Schiff has conducted two polls regarding bitcoin’s value and investors’ actions if the crypto’s price falls significantly. Despite his consistent criticism of bitcoin, the majority of respondents expressed strong commitment to holding their BTC even if the price drops drastically. Schiff maintains that bitcoin’s value proposition is flawed and anticipates a significant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu, Solana, And Litecoin Lead The Charge For Crypto Payments]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472ffdbcc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-solana-litecoin-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T00:36:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency payment gateway CoinGate has released a report outlining the current stage of crypto payments on its platform. The crypto platform has also declared Shiba Inu (SHIB), Solana (SOL) and Litecoin (LTC) as leading coins for crypto payments. 
 
CoinGate Crypto Payments Surge With Solana And Litecoin
 
The crypto payments sector continues to grow rapidly, driven by the rising popularity of altcoins and meme coins, and their increasing integration in the financial sector. In light of this rapid growth, CoinGate has released an official report, providing a comprehensive overview of the current state of its crypto payments and industry insights for the first half (H1) of 2024.  
 
 
In its July 25 report, CoinGate revealed that it had processed a total of 404,674 orders in the second…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Bing Adds AI to Search Results, Following Google’s Lead]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241927</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241927/microsoft-bing-adds-ai-to-search-results-following-googles-lead"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T00:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bing search results organized by AI, now in limited release, will feature prominent links to external sites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jitendra Soni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edward Snowden Tells Bitcoin Fans to Vote—But ‘Don’t Join a Cult’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241978</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241978/edward-snowden-bitcoin-vote-cult-nashville"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T23:46:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The outspoken privacy advocate said elections historically haven't changed much, and meanwhile railed against the threat AI poses to citizens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor: US Government Should Own Majority of Bitcoin in the World]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472e4cc59</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/michael-saylor-us-government-should-own-majority-of-bitcoin-in-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T23:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor, executive chairman of Microstrategy, believes the U.S. government should hold the majority of the world’s bitcoin, arguing this would strengthen the U.S. dollar. Drawing parallels to historic acquisitions, he views bitcoin as a critical asset for the future. Saylor emphasized: “The country gotta look to the future, and the future of the country […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cardano Sets Stage For Chang Hard Fork With Node Upgrade]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472e79d37</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/cardano-sets-stage-chang-hard-fork-node-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T23:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cardano network is on the brink of the Chang hard fork which will usher in the Voltaire era. The transition is enabled by the latest release of node validator software, version 9.1.0, which incorporates crucial updates essential for the hard fork. Charles Hoskinson, the founder of Cardano, declared via X, “This is it. End of the line, node 9.1 is Voltaire. Happy upgrading SPOs. Welcome to Chang.”
 
Additionally, Intersect, a member-based organization within the ADA ecosystem that focuses on the blockchain’s continuity and future enhancements, confirmed the announcement, stating via X, “Node 9.1.0 is here! The final version to bring on-chain decision-making to Cardano is here. As with all hard-forks, Cardano upgrades when the community is ready.”
 
Cardano Chang Hard Fork Is Ready
 
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA Discovers Potential Signs of Ancient Life on Mars]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241946</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241946/nasa-discovers-potential-signs-of-ancient-life-on-mars"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T23:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We have thrown all of our instruments at this,” a NASA scientist tells Decrypt, but more study is needed to determine the origin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe Injects $50M in Forex Market to Stabilize Currency]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472e333bc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/zimbabwe-injects-50m-in-forex-market-to-stabilize-currency/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T22:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zimbabwe’s central bank, the Reserve Bank of Zimbabwe (RBZ), has injected over US$50 million into the interbank foreign exchange market to stabilize the economy. This move comes as the parallel market exchange rate is significantly higher than the official rate, causing economic instability. The RBZ aims to increase foreign currency supply, reduce pressure on banks, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key U.S. Senate Republican Tim Scott Makes Crypto-Fan Debut]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472e3fea4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/07/26/key-us-senate-republican-tim-scott-makes-crypto-fan-debut/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T22:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sen. Tim Scott (R-S.C.), the top Republican on the Senate Banking Committee who may be in position to be its next chairman, argued at a Bitcoin 2024 appearance on Friday that the government should "make it easy" for the crypto industry to innovate in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polymarket Crypto Bettors Place Parlays on the Paris Olympics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241932</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241932/polymarket-crypto-bettors-place-parlays-on-the-paris-olympics"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T22:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The popular prediction market is taking wagers on the world’s biggest sports event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram’s Catizen (CATI) Game Raises $16 Million, Helps Save Stray Cats]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472e843c5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/telegrams-catizen-cati-game-raises-16m/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T21:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The imaginative gaming bot Catizen on Telegram has earned a solid $16 million from in-game purchases in the last few days. This game boasts a massive fan base and has a good impact by helping stray animals – cats, specifically. In addition to being very profitable, it also gives a percent of its profits to animal welfare groups. This combination of giving and fun is adding a whole new dimension for the gaming industry.
 
 
One of the most often used games on the Telegram platform, Catizen is a virtual realm dedicated just to feline-themed adventures and has drawn an amazing 26 million users. These ideas come together in this small app that blends games, Artificial Intelligence, crypto and the metaverse.
 
 
Catizen: Technical Triumph
 
Catizen stands out because it works perfectly with The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polymarket Bettors Predict 84% Chance of Trump-Harris Debate Before Election]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472e90a27</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/polymarket-bettors-predict-84-chance-of-trump-harris-debate-before-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T21:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the blockchain-based prediction market Polymarket, there is an 84% likelihood that former President Donald Trump and current Vice President Kamala Harris will debate before the election. Trump has shown hesitation to debate Harris until her official nomination, citing significant confusion within the Democratic party. High Stakes: $142,846 Wager on Trump-Harris Debate Before Election […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today's ‘Hamster Kombat’ Daily Combo and Cipher Code]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=239305</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-hamster-kombat-daily-combo-cipher-code"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T21:15:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the daily combo and cipher code for Friday, July 26? Here’s what you need to make bank in Telegram game Hamster Kombat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Saylor Predicts Bitcoin Will Hit $280 Trillion in Market Cap by 2045]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241910</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241910/michael-saylor-bitcoin-280-trillion-market-cap-2045"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T20:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin bull turned the dial up to 10 before thousands of conference attendees in Nashville.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salvadoran Basic Goods Basket Rose to Historic Highs in June]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472d69554</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/salvadoran-basic-goods-basket-rose-to-historic-highs-in-june/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T20:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The price of the Salvadoran basic goods basket, a group of foods and vegetables considered essential, rose to all-time high levels in June. The increase was pushed due to the price hikes in vegetables, going over the $260 barrier and reaching $262.17. President Bukele recently expanded the action of the Farmers’ Markets and slashed import […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Speaks Saturday at the Bitcoin Conference. Here's What Attendees Like 'The Crypto Patriot' Hope He Says.]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7472d6c8f4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/07/26/trump-speaks-saturday-at-the-bitcoin-conference-heres-what-attendees-like-the-crypto-patriot-hope-he-says/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T20:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I want to hear [Trump] give a bold statement on the future of crypto and spark up what we all want," one person said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Nelson, Bradley Keoun, George Kaloudis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Long Bitcoin Hashtag Emoji: Elon Musk Axes 'Special' Hashtags on Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241897</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241897/twitter-kills-bitcoin-hashtag-emoji-elon-musk"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T20:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bitcoin emoji hashtag on Twitter is no more, just days after Elon Musk said he pushed to kill the broader feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to Expect From Trump’s Bitcoin Nashville Speech]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241895</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241895/what-to-expect-from-trumps-bitcoin-nashville-speech"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T18:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former U.S. President Donald Trump is set to speak for 30 minutes onstage at Bitcoin’s biggest gathering. Here’s what you need to know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TALON Partners With XP.GG]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241887</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241887/talon-partners-with-xp-gg"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T17:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne, Australia, 26th July 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GameStop, Nvidia Short Seller Hit With SEC and Criminal Fraud Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241875</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241875/gamestop-nvidia-short-seller-sec-criminal-fraud-charges"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T16:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew Left and Citron Capital have been charged by the SEC and DOJ for a multi-million-dollar fraud scheme—and GameStop fans are celebrating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ledger Reveals New E Ink Touchscreen Flex Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241575/ledger-reveals-new-e-ink-touchscreen-flex-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T15:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new hardware wallet is part of Ledger's bid to "secure a world that’s embracing AI," by providing "Proof of You," the firm said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Get Digital IDs for the Republic of Palau on Solana]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241856</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241856/you-can-now-get-digital-ids-for-the-republic-of-palau-on-solana"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T15:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For $248, Solana users will be able to mint their Republic of Palau digital IDs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Are Today’s ‘Musk Empire’ Stock Exchange Daily Combo and Riddle]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241078</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/todays-musk-empire-stock-exchange-daily-combo"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T14:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the Musk Empire daily combo and riddle solution for Friday, July 26? Here are the latest boosts for the Telegram crypto game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vanta DAO is Making its Members ‘Owner-Operators’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241140</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241140/how-vanta-dao-is-making-its-members-owner-operators"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T14:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investment syndicate Vanta is decentralizing and handing over control to its NFT holders, DAO member Jax Dwyer told Rug Radio’s FOMO Hour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Jafery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Adds OpenAI Exec and Former US Solicitor General to Its Board]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241845</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241845/coinbase-openai-former-us-solicitor-general-board"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T12:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase has added three new board members that vary in political philosophies in an attempt to make crypto bipartisan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise Ethereum ETF Banner Hung on New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241844/bitwise-ethereum-etf-banner-hung-on-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T12:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wall Street now has a banner from one of nine new spot Ethereum ETFs hanging over it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Says Foreign Adversaries Use 'Cryptomines' to Spy on US Military]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241832</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241832/elizabeth-warren-says-foreign-adversaries-use-cryptomines-to-spy-on-u-s-military"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warren claimed that crypto mining operations based in the U.S. have used crypto to "secretly send millions of dollars back to China."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP Morgan Built Its Own AI Chatbot That Acts Like a 'Research Analyst': Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241834</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241834/jp-morgan-ai-chatbot-llm-suite"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T10:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chatbot’s technology was reportedly developed without leaning on external technology, like OpenAI or Google Gemini.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will McCurdy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[XP.GG Selects Shrapnel as First Web3 Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241831</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241831/xp-gg-selects-shrapnel-as-first-web3-game"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T07:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne, Australia, 26th July 2024, GamingWire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GamingWire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Regain Footing Even as Demand for ETFs Sour]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241825</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241825/bitcoin-ethereum-regain-footing-even-as-demand-for-etfs-sour"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T06:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though the market has shown signs of resiliency, oscillating sentiment between risk-on and risk-off among investors weighs heavily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrity Meme Coins Tank Following June Debut as Interest Fades]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241822</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241822/celebrity-meme-coins-tank-following-june-debut-interest-fades"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T04:17:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some celebrities involved have stepped back from promoting the coins on social media, raising questions over their authenticity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Sainsbury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marshall Becomes First US Senator to Walk from Controversial Crypto Bill He Co-Sponsored]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241806</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241806/marshall-first-us-senator-walk-controversial-crypto-bill-he-co-sponsored"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T01:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marshall, who helped introduce the bill a year ago, has been vocal in his criticism against crypto, including stablecoin issuer Tether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exoskeleton Technology Shines at Paris Olympics]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241745</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241745/robotic-exoskeleton-olympics-paraplegic-wandercraft"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T00:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paraplegic tennis player Kevin Piette, outfitted with a robotic exoskeleton, participated in the Olympic torch relay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris Offers ‘Fresh Opportunity’ to Make Inroads With Democrats, Says Blockchain Association CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241781</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241781/kamala-harris-fresh-opportunity-make-inroads-democrats-blockchain-association"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T23:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The non-profit organization’s leader spoke about advocating for the crypto industry ahead of the U.S. presidential election in an exclusive interview with Decrypt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Napolitano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Fever Dominates Bitcoin Nashville Ahead of Appearance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241750</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241750/trump-fever-dominates-bitcoin-nashville-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T22:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former president Donald Trump’s Saturday speech is already defining the annual Bitcoin Conference’s look from day one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video Game Actors and Performers to Strike Over AI Protections]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241734</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241734/video-game-strike-ai-protections"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T22:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SAG-AFTRA video game strike begins tomorrow, although members at San Diego Comic-Con can still participate in the event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’Bitcoin Won’: Jersey City Mayor Says Pension Fund to Invest in Bitcoin ETFs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241737</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241737/jersey-city-pension-fund-to-invest-in-bitcoin-etfs"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mayor Steven Fulop said the city will apportion around 2% of the fund toward Bitcoin as he eyes a run for governor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 166 - CRYPTO AND STOCKS FALL]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pCSPFk3B/fomo-hour-166-crypto-and-stocks-fall</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/pCSPFk3B/fomo-hour-166-crypto-and-stocks-fall"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: +$44m, ETH ETFs: -$133m. ETH falls as Grayscale ETF outflows continue. ETH ETFs still see $1bn of daily volume. Liquidations hit $250m in sell-off. ETH Open Interest hits ATH at CME. BTC whales have bought $23bn in July. SOL weekly active addresses hits ATH. Bitstamp to distribute Mt. Gox BTC today. Russia to legalise crypto mining & payments. Lummis set to introduce BTC strategic reserve bill. Harris will not be at Bitcoin Nashville. BTC going to $52m by 2050: VanEck. Hashdex file for mixed BTC & ETH ETF. Coinbase to make tokenised treasuries fund. Polymarket partners with Moonpay for on-ramp. Ferrari accepts crypto in Europe. Bitfarms stopped in poison-pill strategy. Riot buys another miner for $93m.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Reveals SearchGPT, Threatening to Upend Google's Dominance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241718</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241718/openai-search-searchgpt-google-bing"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reveal of the prototype of an AI-powered search engine saw Google and Microsoft stock drop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-Awaited ‘Illuvium’ Ethereum Games Launch on Epic Store]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241678</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241678/long-awaited-illuvium-ethereum-games-launch-epic-store"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T20:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illuvium has officially launched three interconnected Ethereum games following extensive beta testing and a play-to-airdrop campaign.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interpol Issues Red Notice for Hong Kong Crypto Promoter 'Coin Young Master']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241631</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241631/interpol-red-notice-hong-kong-coin-young-master"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T20:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Coin Young Master" Wong Ching-kit is wanted on counts of fraud and theft, while his associate Mok Tsun-ting faces money laundering charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Protocol Solend Rebrands as ‘Save’, Launches New Stablecoin and Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241709</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241709/solend-save-rebrand-susd-savesol-dumpy-fun"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T20:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The team also launched dumpy.fun, a platform designed to short meme coins, saying, “What goes up must come down.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Zmudzinski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Owners Don't Lean Toward One Political Ideology: Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241680</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241680/bitcoin-owners-political-spectrum-survey"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T19:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoiners in the U.S. trend young, male, and moderate, favoring liberty and equality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Murtuza Merchant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['No Bears Allowed'? Bullish Vibes Abound at Bitcoin Nashville]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241668</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241668/no-bears-allowed-bullish-vibes-bitcoin-nashville"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T19:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 2024 has landed in Nashville, packed with political intrigue and attendees from all around the world—and the mood is positive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Says He'd Make the Government Buy $615 Billion in Bitcoin]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241670</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241670/rfk-government-buy-615-billion-in-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T18:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If elected, Kennedy says he wants the United States’ Bitcoin reserves to match its gold reserves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Could Skyrocket to $52 Million by 2050, Says VanEck—Here's Why]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241663</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241663/bitcoin-price-52-million-by-2050-vaneck"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T17:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin could top a price of $52 million if it becomes a reserve asset around the world, VanEck argued in a report this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Shooter ‘Planet-X’ Launching on Xai With Real Prizes—Like a Tesla Cybertruck]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241651</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241651/ethereum-shooter-planet-x-xai-prizes-tesla-cybertruck"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T17:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile extraction shooter Planet-X is building on Ethereum layer-3 network Xai and offering up some serious prizes for players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marathon Digital Buys $100 Million in Bitcoin, Adopts 'Full HODL Strategy']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241645</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241645/marathon-digital-buys-100-million-bitcoin-full-hodl-strategy"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T16:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid an improving macro environment and growing institutional adoption, Bitcoin miner Marathon will no longer sell its BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Hit With $4.5 Million Fine in UK for Serving 'High-Risk Customers']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=241630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/241630/coinbase-4-5-million-fine-uk-high-risk-customers"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T15:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FCA has fined a Coinbase subsidiary in the UK for breaching a regulatory agreement to improve its defenses against financial crime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 165 - ETH ETFs TAKE IN 107M]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/z9zsSjQy/fomo-hour-165-eth-etfs-take-in-107m</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/z9zsSjQy/fomo-hour-165-eth-etfs-take-in-107m"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T08:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETFs: -$78m, ETH ETFs: +$107m. BTC falls amid ETF outflows & Mt. Gox movements. ETH ETFs see ‘very solid’ first day $107m inflows. Grayscale ETH trust sees $484m outflow. ETH ETF volumes come out at 23% of BTC. Debate about whether strong flows will continue. SOL DEX volume continues to rise above ETH. Harris may also speak at Bitcoin Nashville. Harris could be far more open to Bitcoin: Cuban. BTC symbol lights up Vegas Sphere. Coinbase continues to pursue Gensler emails. dYdX explores sale of derivatives tech. dYdX site recovers after DNS attack. JD to create Hong Kong stablecoin. Bitwise uses ENS addresses for ETH ETFs. BlackRock applies for ENA cash allocation. Uber CEO wants to accept BTC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 164 - ETH ETF DAY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Qn97IvaR/fomo-hour-164-eth-etf-day</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Qn97IvaR/fomo-hour-164-eth-etf-day"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T22:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: +$534m. ETH outperforms slightly as 9 ETFs set to launch. Grayscale moves $1bn ETH to Coinbase for outflows. Biggest BlackRock ETF inflow day in 4 months. Mt Gox moves $2.8bn BTC for distributions. US government moves $4m BTC to Coinbase. Bedford FC buys $4.5m BTC. Hamilton Lane launches private credit fund on SOL. CNBC discusses BTC reserve currency rumour. Polymarket sets another trading record. BlockFi administrator submits plan to repay customers. WLD denies insider trading and manipulation claims. India keeps high crypto taxes unchanged. Gate exchange exits Japan. Marathon Digital fined $138m for breaching NDA. HyperLend launches lending on HyperLiquid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mika Shares How to Sell Crypto Using Kraken Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6e7AC9Po/mika-shares-how-to-sell-crypto-using-kraken-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/6e7AC9Po/mika-shares-how-to-sell-crypto-using-kraken-wallet"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T09:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rug Radio creator Mika guides you through the process of selling crypto and transferring it back to your bank account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 163 - JOEVER FOR BYEDEN]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0GxuImTw/fomo-hour-163-joever-for-byeden</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0GxuImTw/fomo-hour-163-joever-for-byeden"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T16:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto dips then bounces on Biden-Harris switch. SOL again leads, DEX volume eclipses ETH + BNB. Biden news had led to $67m liquidations. Democrats have chance to ‘regain crypto vote’. Mt Gox transfers to Bitstamp expected soon. Crypto sees $3.2bn fund inflows in 3 weeks. China company Boyaa buys $100m BTC. Polymarket saw $80m bets on Biden withdrawal. Polymarket 2024 volumes hit $500m. Elon appearance at Bitcoin Nashville rumoured. Combined SOL, BTC & ETH ETF coming: Geraci. Call skew heads to 2024 extremes in bullish sign. Plan B points to bullish setup in S2F model. Coinbase premium moves back to positive. Gensler likely resigns next year: 10x. Germany already lost $124m profit selling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Meta? Do Crypto Degens Care About Being Scammed?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nNFxaZd6/whats-the-meta-do-crypto-degens-care-about-being-scammed</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/nNFxaZd6/whats-the-meta-do-crypto-degens-care-about-being-scammed"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T15:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Meta? With the rise of Pumpdotfun and rug pulls becoming a daily occurrence, why do crypto degens keep investing? Do these investors enjoy being scammed? It appears that people very often invest in meme coins that are very obviously going to rug pull. Once it happens, they just laugh it off on Twitter, is being scammed fun?!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 162 - SOLANA LEADS THE CHARGE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/695Aw43b/fomo-hour-162-solana-leads-the-charge</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/695Aw43b/fomo-hour-162-solana-leads-the-charge"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T21:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$85m. SOL leads majors ahead of ETH ETF. Rumours Trump may want BTC in strategic reserve. Trump BTC round-table tickets going for $845k. Polymarket hits volume record of $20m. ETH ETFs will get steady capital: Binance CEO. Winklevii donate $1m to try and unseat Warren. Tornado sees $1.9bn volume resurgence. New overlay attacks growing in crypto. Messari co-founder faces backlash on views. Raydium integrates with Moonpay. Tencent leads investment round in Chainbase. ZA Bank partners with stablecoin issuers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 161 - THE BIG WIF COMEBACK?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wDunKbUD/fomo-hour-161-the-big-wif-comeback</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/wDunKbUD/fomo-hour-161-the-big-wif-comeback"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T17:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$53m. Crypto remains stable despite macro sell-off. ETH ETF providers undercut each other on fees. Grayscale keeps 2.5% high fee, launches mini-fund. Grayscale launches ‘Decentralised AI Fund’. Dimon may be ‘changing tune’ on Bitcoin. Many alts now bounced 50-90% from lows. Vote implies 55% of Mt. Gox depositors won’t sell. BlockFi to make creditor distributions this month. WazirX exchanges sees $230m suspected breach. Vitalik warns against voting ‘pro-crypto’. Vitalik & Autism Capital trade barbs. Bitcoin Magazine to hold pro-Trump fundraiser. State Street explore blockchain payments. UPbit sees 44% monthly drop in volume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 160 - CHATTING TO ROBINHOOD!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mwCkRYNA/fomo-hour-160-chatting-to-robinhood</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mwCkRYNA/fomo-hour-160-chatting-to-robinhood"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$423m. Crypto pushes higher, biggest ETF inflow in 6 weeks. Mt. Gox FUD ‘overestimated’ as whales accumulate. Kraken to begin Mt. Gox repayments in 7-14d. ETH spot ETFs will push ETH to $5k: Bitwise. SOL ETF will be next: Bloomberg. XRP up 35% this week ahead of potential settlement. Aethir reports $36m H1 customer revenue. Craig Wright now under threat of perjury & forgery. FTX & CFTC in $12.7bn settlement. WLD up 40% after delaying unlock schedule. Helio announces instant crypto fiat commerce. Phantom pauses cross-chain swaps amid exploit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 159 - MEMECOINS GO MAD!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ynyia4ZI/fomo-hour-159-memecoins-go-mad</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ynyia4ZI/fomo-hour-159-memecoins-go-mad"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Inflows: +$301m. BTC dips from $65k as $6bn moves from Mt. Gox. Coinbase & MicroStrategy surge with BTC. Genesis sells another $38m BTC. ETH ETF timeline delayed until July 23rd. Trump chooses crypto friendly Vance as VP. Old clip shows Vance bashing Gensler on crypto. Bitcoin is good during debasement: Larry Fink. Michael Dell calls Fink video ‘fascinating’. Fear & Greed index shifts to Greed. Tether mints $1bn USDT on Tron. Stripe expands crypto integration to the EU.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 158 - A WILD WEEKEND FOR BITCOIN]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BcG2gbdq/fomo-hour-158-a-wild-weekend-for-bitcoin</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/BcG2gbdq/fomo-hour-158-a-wild-weekend-for-bitcoin"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T17:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump response optimism takes BTC to $63K. Bitcoin whales accumulate most since April 2023. Trump still set to talk at Bitcoin Nashville. ETH ETF approval this week: Geraci. XRP vs SEC press conference rumoured on 18th. Crypto funds saw $1.44B inflows last week. Rumours China is to ‘unban BTC’ in Q4. S. Korea may delay crypto taxes until 2028. Russia to allow crypto trading on stock exchange. All altcoin categories outperform BTC over 7d. BitConnect infamous promoter convicted. Scroll becomes 8th L2 with TVL over $1bn. ETHFI Season 2 claims available this week. Base hits record 1m UserOps in a week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoltan Istvan on AI and Human Immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/4BsXkpuA/zoltan-istvan-on-ai-and-human-immortality</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/4BsXkpuA/zoltan-istvan-on-ai-and-human-immortality"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T21:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transhumanist Party founder Zoltan Istvan chats with Decrypt's Emerging Technology report Jason Nelson about his journey with transhumanism, running for office, and why he fears AI is outpacing life science and poses a threat to the quest for immortality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 157 - ROLLBIT FRIDAY!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/COVjTRpj/fomo-hour-157-rollbit-friday</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/COVjTRpj/fomo-hour-157-rollbit-friday"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T16:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The German state sells $2bn+ BTC and has under $300m left. BTC ETF sees $800M of inflows, Mr 100 keeps buying. SOL ETF deadline set for 2025, election could be key. SOL stablecoin TVL soars on Tether & PYUSD growth. Firedancer sees the first accepted block on SOL testnet. ETH ETFs finally expected next week. Monthly active crypto addresses top 100m. Trump to speak at Bitcoin Nashville conference. Golman Sachs to launch 3 tokenization projects. Short squeeze in altcoins sees TIA rise 80% from lows. MOG leads top memes coins, BONK flips WIF. Farming interest shifts to Berachain & Monad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the Meta? Meet the Solana Dev Who Suffered Third Degree Burns to Pump a Token]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OgJCZDWk/whats-the-meta-meet-the-solana-dev-who-suffered-third-degree-burns-to-pump-a-token</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OgJCZDWk/whats-the-meta-meet-the-solana-dev-who-suffered-third-degree-burns-to-pump-a-token"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T12:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Mikol: the Dare dev that doused himself in isopropyl alcohol and had fireworks shot at him. He instantly went up in flames and was rushed to hospital, where it became apparent he suffered third degree burns.

In this episode, Mikol reflects on the biggest night of his life, details his injuries, and the grueling recovery process he’s still in. Despite the traumatic incident, Mikol isn’t done with the project. Instead, he’s planning to build a decentralized app where community members can take on dares in exchange for DARE tokens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 156 - ETH ON THE RISE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/soJHVe7R/fomo-hour-156-eth-on-the-rise</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/soJHVe7R/fomo-hour-156-eth-on-the-rise"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:34:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: +$147m. ETH outperforms with ETF optimism. Germany government moves 2375 BTC again. Tether mints another $250m USDT on SOL. Trump to speak at Bitcoin Nashville. Goldman Sachs to launch 3 tokenisation projects. Realised losses similar to COVID period. Staked ETH nears ATH. CEX stablecoin volume hits 7-month low. CFTC says 70-80% of crypto not securities. Base hardfork improves compression 20-30%. BitMEX pleads guilty to AML violation. APTOS & SEI see weak attendance at ETHcc event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 155 - ETFs SAVE THE DAY]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MLhJXkd3/fomo-hour-155-etfs-save-the-day</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/MLhJXkd3/fomo-hour-155-etfs-save-the-day"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T17:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: $216m. $654m of inflows into ETFs over 3 days. BTC transaction fees hit 4-year low. German state moves $300m BTC, holdings $1bn. SOL flips ETH for 7d DEX volumes. SOL Firedancer sees first accepted block on testnet. Tether mints another $250m USDT on SOL. Crypto monthly active addresses tops 100m. Biden crypto veto now expected to be upheld. Tech coalition urges Biden to back crypto. People face security threats at ETHCC. DBS sees 300% growth in crypto trading. PYUSD now 7th largest stable coin. China may have already sold BTC holdings. Elliptic exposes $11bn USDT scam network. StanChart in talks to buy Howard’s crypto fund. Polychain accuses former employee of side deals. SEI leads altcoins as it launches v2 mainnet beta. TIA rises 80% from lows on short squeeze. TON to release L2 based on Polygon’s tech stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 154 - THE CELEBS ARE BACK...]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/D9FImiB3/fomo-hour-154-the-celebs-are-back</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/D9FImiB3/fomo-hour-154-the-celebs-are-back"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T18:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: +$295m. ETF inflows fight German selling, BTC unchanged. German government sells $900m BTC, moves more. Rate of sales implies German supply sold this week. ETH ETFs set to launch next week. Election may affect SOL ETF decision March 2025. Raydium beats ETH for 24hr fees. BTC ‘power law’ points to 300% gain by 2025. BTC in 80 day post-halving re-accumulation phase. BlackRock treasury fund hits $500m. Republicans release pro-crypto policy. Senate urges blockchain tests for national security. Drop in BTC mining difficulty ‘comparable to FTX’. MetaMask introduces delegation toolkit. 25 major projects to launch tokens in H2 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 153 - A WEAK WEEKEND]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5YSiCw7F/fomo-hour-153-a-weak-weekend</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5YSiCw7F/fomo-hour-153-a-weak-weekend"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T23:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC sinks 5% then bounces back to unchanged. $58-60k the main area for ‘shorts to defend’. Crypto funds saw $441m inflows last week. German government transfers 1000 BTC to sell. Crypto sentiment at lowest in over a year. ETH spot premium hits local highs. Japanese firm Metaplanet buys $2.5m BTC. Expect more miners merging: TeraWulf CEO. SOL Firedancer bug bounty goes live. GLM transfers $117m of ETH treasury to exchanges. 98% of coins have topped this cycle: Kang. ETH ETF should come in next 2 weeks: Geraci. Crypto progress disheartening: Copeland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 152 - JOINED BY DEEZE!]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oLurNfIh/fomo-hour-152-joined-by-deeze</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/oLurNfIh/fomo-hour-152-joined-by-deeze"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC hits $54k, set for worst week in over year. Mt. Gox begins to move BTC & make distributions. German government continues to sell holdings. Worst day for BTC liquidations since FTX. Justin Sun says he is willing to buy German BTC. German MP calls on it to stop selling BTC. $52k super-trend support line eyed for BTC. Funding rates turn extremely negative across majors. Only 6 mining machines profitable below $56k. Coinbase spot buyers emerge to counter drop. Total3 hits RSI lows only hit 4 times in last 4 years. Fear & Greed index hits lowest since Jan 2023. Capo remains bullish. Real selling begins at $38k: Schiff. Coinbase continue to fight for Gensler’s emails. Circle mints $250m USDC on SOL. Symbiotic hits $1bn TVL. Taiwan Mobile may open crypto exchange. Unisat completes funding round with Binance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FOMO HOUR 151 - BTC TAPS THE 60K LINE]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HP5x5DDr/fomo-hour-151-btc-taps-the-60k-line</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/HP5x5DDr/fomo-hour-151-btc-taps-the-60k-line"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T18:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC ETF Flows: -$14m. BTC drops to $60k, CME gap filed again. $1bn shorts liquidated if we rally to $62.6k. Pump(.)fun surpasses ETH for revenue. ETH will outperform BTC after ETF launch: K33. ETH ETF may be delayed even further. BTC heading to $150k: Fundstrat. Chainlink & Fidelity partner for fund data on-chain. USDC protects the dollar: Circle ad. Robinhood considers crypto futures in US & EU. Another BTC miner looks to IPO in US. Vitalik bullish on prediction markets. Sentient Labs raises $85m for AI on SOL. Mantra to tokenise $500m of real estate. TAO falls 15% after security breach. Crypto scams & hacks hit $572m in Q2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>