<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-09-09T23:13:05.415Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-09-09T23:13:05.415Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Ethereum Outshining Bitcoin in Terms of Fees? Crypto Voices Share Thoughts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754db4ac58</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/is-ethereum-outshining-bitcoin-in-terms-of-fees-crypto-voices-share-thoughts/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T22:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, the crypto sphere, with bitcoin aficionados in particular, has been buzzing with chatter about the fees pocketed by BTC miners. They’re pondering if these fees will adequately offset the impending 2024 halving and the accompanying drop in revenue. On the other hand, Ethereum, the runner-up in the crypto world, is raking in significantly higher weekly fees. Here’s an insight into the leading blockchain networks and where users are truly shelling out for block space.
 
Bitcoin Proponents Discuss the 2 Leading Blockchains and Transfer Fees
 
Many of today’s leading blockchain networks come with transfer fees, designed to motivate miners or validators to oversee and validate transactions, fortifying the network. Besides ensuring security, these fees deter spam, prioritize transactions,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[S14 E12: Sam Lee on Bitcoin in Hong Kong]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18892013/S14-E12-Sam-Lee-on-Bitcoin-in-Hong-Kong</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18892013/S14-E12-Sam-Lee-on-Bitcoin-in-Hong-Kong"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T22:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past 4 years, Sam Lee has been the main organizer of the Bitcoin meetup in Hong Kong. In this episode, Sam tells us what it's like to be a bitcoiner in Hong Kong and how the experience differs from the one in Mainland China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ApeCoin DAO weighs 4 proposals to “expand ecosystem” – details inside]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18892012/ApeCoin-DAO-weighs-4-proposals-to-expand-ecosystem-details-inside</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18892012/ApeCoin-DAO-weighs-4-proposals-to-expand-ecosystem-details-inside"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T22:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The members of the ApeCoin DAO have begun voting on a series of proposals on the floor of the governance forum. However, one proposal has received strong resistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economic Collapse & Shift To Bitcoin Standard 'Months Away' | Max Keiser]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18892005/ECONOMIC-COLLAPSE-SHIFT-TO-BITCOIN-STANDARD-MONTHS-AWAY-MAX-KEISER</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18892005/ECONOMIC-COLLAPSE-SHIFT-TO-BITCOIN-STANDARD-MONTHS-AWAY-MAX-KEISER"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T22:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We discuss the global financial upheaval caused by a weakening dollar and dive deep into some grim macro and fiat world predictions from Max Keiser. How has Bitcoin emerged as the potential savior amidst a crumbling fiat system? From the alarming rates of inflation to the potential for Bitcoin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JPMorgan Mulls Blockchain-Based Deposit Token, Report]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754db021e4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/jpmorgan-mulls-blockchain-based-deposit-token-report/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T22:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America’s biggest bank by assets, JPMorgan Chase, is exploring a blockchain-based deposit token for cross-border payments and interbank transfers. If approved by regulators, the banking giant may create the digital asset, which would be different from its existing JPM Coin as it could be used to send money to accounts in other banks. 
 
JPMorgan Considers Digital Token for Cross-Border Payments and Settlement
 
JPMorgan is in the early stages of exploring a blockchain-based digital deposit token, Bloomberg reported quoting a person with knowledge of the matter. The token could be used to speed up cross-border payments and settlement.
 
According to the source who chose to remain anonymous, most of the underlying infrastructure that would be necessary to run the new means of payment has bee…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Financial Settles With SEC Out of Court]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891984/Linus-Financial-Settles-With-SEC-Out-of-Court</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891984/Linus-Financial-Settles-With-SEC-Out-of-Court"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T21:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to the prompt action and initiative, the SEC has decided that no penalties will be enforced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s XRP Primed For Ballistic Rally Amid Adoption By Banks in Indonesia, Philippines, Vietnam]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891976/Ripples-XRP-Primed-For-Ballistic-Rally-Amid-Adoption-By-Banks-in-Indonesia-Philippines-Vietnam</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891976/Ripples-XRP-Primed-For-Ballistic-Rally-Amid-Adoption-By-Banks-in-Indonesia-Philippines-Vietnam"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T21:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Says Lack of Clear Crypto Rules Has Caused ‘Terrible Things,’ Calls for Regulatory Clarity in US]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891943/Coinbase-CEO-Says-Lack-of-Clear-Crypto-Rules-Has-Caused-Terrible-Things-Calls-for-Regulatory-Clarity-in-US</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891943/Coinbase-CEO-Says-Lack-of-Clear-Crypto-Rules-Has-Caused-Terrible-Things-Calls-for-Regulatory-Clarity-in-US"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T21:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance’s exec exodus, Nasdaq to trade AI orders and SBF loses bail appeal: Hodler’s Digest, Sept. 3-9]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891938/Binances-exec-exodus-Nasdaq-to-trade-AI-orders-and-SBF-loses-bail-appeal-Hodlers-Digest-Sept-3-9</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891938/Binances-exec-exodus-Nasdaq-to-trade-AI-orders-and-SBF-loses-bail-appeal-Hodlers-Digest-Sept-3-9"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:42:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Eight Exchanges Handle Majority Of Crypto Trading Volume: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891940/Only-Eight-Exchanges-Handle-Majority-Of-Crypto-Trading-Volume-Report</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891940/Only-Eight-Exchanges-Handle-Majority-Of-Crypto-Trading-Volume-Report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the dynamic world of cryptocurrency trading, a handful of exchanges have emerged as dominant forces, holding a substantial share of market liquidity. What Happened: Recent data sheds light on this concentration, revealing that a mere eight platforms control the lion's share of the market...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Seeks Expansion in Markets With Clear Crypto Rules Unlike US]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754dbed9c5</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-seeks-expansion-in-markets-with-clear-crypto-rules-unlike-us/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America’s leading cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase, plans to expand its business in jurisdictions that are adopting clear regulations for the sector. These include markets in Europe, Asia and the Americas as opposed to the United States which, the company says, is enforcing existing rules and new regulation through courts.
 
Coinbase Eyes ‘Crypto-Forward Markets’ Like EU, Singapore, Brazil for Expansion
 
Crypto exchange Coinbase announced it’s executing the second phase of its “Go Broad, Go Deep” strategy for international expansion. The company shared details about its plans in a blog post analyzing the regulatory environment in key markets around the world.
 
The leading U.S. trading platform for digital assets will focus on acquiring licenses, registering, and establishing operations …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key crypto industry figures see promise in Privacy Pools proposal]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891931/Key-crypto-industry-figures-see-promise-in-Privacy-Pools-proposal</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891931/Key-crypto-industry-figures-see-promise-in-Privacy-Pools-proposal"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are the Stories of the Biggest Ethereum Whales? One Burned Over $500 Million Worth of ETH]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891934/What-Are-the-Stories-of-the-Biggest-Ethereum-Whales-One-Burned-Over-500-Million-Worth-of-ETH</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891934/What-Are-the-Stories-of-the-Biggest-Ethereum-Whales-One-Burned-Over-500-Million-Worth-of-ETH"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple v. SEC: 3 major developments since positive XRP ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891921/Ripple-v-SEC-3-major-developments-since-positive-XRP-ruling</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891921/Ripple-v-SEC-3-major-developments-since-positive-XRP-ruling"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ted Cruz Says He Is a ‘Big Believer’ In Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155694</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155694/ted-cruz-texas-senator-bitcoin-mining-dennis-porter-satoshi-act-fund"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Appearing on Fox News Radio, the Texas senator said Bitcoin mining is good for his state’s stressed power grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ted Cruz Says He Is a ‘Big Believer’ In Bitcoin Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891913/Ted-Cruz-Says-He-Is-a-Big-Believer-In-Bitcoin-Mining</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891913/Ted-Cruz-Says-He-Is-a-Big-Believer-In-Bitcoin-Mining"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former JPMorgan Chase Executives Sentenced to Prison Over Market Manipulation Scheme That Triggered $10,000,000 in Losses]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891905/Former-JPMorgan-Chase-Executives-Sentenced-to-Prison-Over-Market-Manipulation-Scheme-That-Triggered-10000000-in-Losses</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891905/Former-JPMorgan-Chase-Executives-Sentenced-to-Prison-Over-Market-Manipulation-Scheme-That-Triggered-10000000-in-Losses"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G20 calls for ‘swift’ creation of crypto tax reporting rules and info exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891904/G20-calls-for-swift-creation-of-crypto-tax-reporting-rules-and-info-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891904/G20-calls-for-swift-creation-of-crypto-tax-reporting-rules-and-info-exchange"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[G20 leaders are moving rapidly toward a Crypto Asset Reporting Framework, according to a report from The Times of India on Sept. 9. That framework would see G20 member countries collect and share information about the use of cryptocurrency and digital assets. This data would be used to ensure...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whales Sell 43,000 ETH on Coinbase, While 'Smart Money' Bought ETH on Dip This Week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891906/Whales-Sell-43000-ETH-on-Coinbase-While-Smart-Money-Bought-ETH-on-Dip-This-Week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891906/Whales-Sell-43000-ETH-on-Coinbase-While-Smart-Money-Bought-ETH-on-Dip-This-Week"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chainalysis Denounces Bitcoin Core Contributor As “Unqualified”]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754dbbc31b</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/technical/chainalysis-denounces-bitcoin-core-contributor-as-unqualified"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T19:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you haven’t had a good laugh at Chainalysis’ attempts to defend the use of its blockchain forensics software for law enforcement purposes in light of recent court proceedings, now may be the time.
After having to admit to the lack of scientific evidence for the accuracy of its software and the publication of an expert report describing the use of Chainalysis’ heuristics as “reckless”, Chainalysis finds itself trying to evade an audit of its software’s source code.
Chainalysis’ source code is requested by the defense in the case US vs. Sterlingov, an early Bitcoin adopter currently awaiting trial for the alleged operation of the custodial bitcoin mixer Bitcoin Fog, to reproduce the software’s findings in light of the lack of corroborating evidence.
Sterlingov’s defense defines access to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L0la L33tz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ARK Invest CEO Cathie Wood: ‘Convergence Between Bitcoin and AI Could Transform the Way Companies Organize’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891880/ARK-Invest-CEO-Cathie-Wood-Convergence-Between-Bitcoin-and-AI-Could-Transform-the-Way-Companies-Organize</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891880/ARK-Invest-CEO-Cathie-Wood-Convergence-Between-Bitcoin-and-AI-Could-Transform-the-Way-Companies-Organize"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T19:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$100 Billion Exits US Banking System in Three Months As Kevin O’Leary Warns People Are ‘Very Nervous About Putting Their Money in the Bank’]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891876/100-Billion-Exits-US-Banking-System-in-Three-Months-As-Kevin-OLeary-Warns-People-Are-Very-Nervous-About-Putting-Their-Money-in-the-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891876/100-Billion-Exits-US-Banking-System-in-Three-Months-As-Kevin-OLeary-Warns-People-Are-Very-Nervous-About-Putting-Their-Money-in-the-Bank"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T19:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘I’m Bullish on Bitcoin’ — Ted Cruz Champions Bitcoin’s Boon for Texas and Power Grid Boosts]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754da5f705</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bullish-on-bitcoin-ted-cruz-champions-bitcoins-boon-for-texas/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T19:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ted Cruz, the U.S. Republican senator from Texas, expressed his optimism on Friday, stating he’s “bullish on bitcoin,” after a recent interview with Forbes released on September 8. During the conversation, Cruz highlighted emerging reports indicating that bitcoin mining is positively impacting Texas’ power grid, commonly referred to as the Electric Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT).
 
Senator Cruz Celebrates Bitcoin’s Surge in Texas Energy
 
On Friday, Ted Cruz shared his most recent conversation with Forbes journalist Mickey Koss and expressed a keen enthusiasm for bitcoin (BTC).
 
“I’m bullish on Bitcoin,” Cruz broadcasted on the social network platform X (formerly known as Twitter). “Texas is the natural home for the digital asset industry since Texans love freedom and so do digital …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Fake News: BlackRock Not Buying Voyager Digital]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891863/Beware-of-Fake-News-BlackRock-Not-Buying-Voyager-Digital</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891863/Beware-of-Fake-News-BlackRock-Not-Buying-Voyager-Digital"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T19:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst the whirlwind of cryptocurrency rumors, separating fact from fiction is paramount in the case of BlackRock and Voyager Digital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Lawmaker Sponsors Bill to Restrict SEC’s Crypto Enforcement Funding]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891878/US-Lawmaker-Sponsors-Bill-to-Restrict-SECs-Crypto-Enforcement-Funding</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891878/US-Lawmaker-Sponsors-Bill-to-Restrict-SECs-Crypto-Enforcement-Funding"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[United States lawmaker and House Majority Whip Tom Emmer plans to sponsor a new bill imposing new restrictions on the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC). The initiative follows the financial regulator’s efforts to bring the crypto industry into compliance. In a September 8 post on X...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visa’s Head of Crypto on the Future of Blockchain Technology]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891852/Visas-Head-of-Crypto-on-the-Future-of-Blockchain-Technology</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/18891852/Visas-Head-of-Crypto-on-the-Future-of-Blockchain-Technology"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent blog post, Cuy Sheffield, the Head of Crypto at Visa, explored the transformative potential of blockchain technology. Drawing parallels between the early skepticism surrounding the internet and the current state of blockchain, Sheffield outlined what he sees as Visa’s ongoing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Responds to Ripple Filing, Doubles Down on Appeal Bid]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155689</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155689/sec-ripple-appeal-xrp-securities"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The regulator claims judge's summary judgment order raises "knotty legal problems" worthy of appellate review]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt AI, Edited by Ryan Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Week in Coins: Green Candles—But Barely—for Bitcoin and Ethereum as Global Adoption Grows]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155665</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155665/this-week-in-coins-green-candles-but-barely-for-bitcoin-and-ethereum-as-global-adoption-grows"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T18:01:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also, a member of the European Central Bank’s executive board criticized PayPal USD and shilled the digital euro.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Hakki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Greenlights Nasdaq’s First AI-Powered Order Type]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754dad56cb</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/sec-greenlights-nasdaqs-first-ai-powered-order-type/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T17:44:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) has approved a new artificial intelligence (AI)-powered order type for Nasdaq’s stock exchange. This marks the first AI order type approved for an exchange. Nasdaq says the latest technology aims to improve efficiency and performance on its platform.
 
Nasdaq’s AI-Powered Trading Mechanism Gets SEC Nod
 
Nasdaq announced on Friday that it received approval from the SEC to launch its “Dynamic Midpoint Extended Life Order.” This new order type uses artificial intelligence (AI) to match buyers and sellers who plan to hold stocks for longer periods.
 
Traditionally, Nasdaq matched buyers and sellers using set waiting periods. But the company found using AI to adjust waiting times based on current market conditions improved results. The AI-power…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MicroStrategy To Release Quarterly Updates On Bitcoin Holdings, Ignoring Impairment Losses]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754daf7e16</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/microstrategy-to-release-btc-updates-sans-impairment-losses/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T17:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developer MicroStrategy is set to revamp its reporting of Bitcoin (BTC) holdings each quarter, thanks to a recent decision by the Financial Accounting Standards Board (FASB).
 
Greater transparency into their financial health will be possible owing to this reform, which will permit businesses like MicroStrategy to declare the fair value of their Bitcoin holdings without disclosing impairment losses if the cryptocurrency’s price declines during the quarter.
 
Impairment loss disclosure is a financial reporting requirement where a company must acknowledge and reveal that its assets have significantly decreased in value, typically when their market value falls below their recorded value. It’s important for transparency and informs stakeholders about the impact on the company’s financ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuna Rin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple to Acquire Crypto Custodian Fortress Trust]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155658</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155658/ripple-fortress-trust-brad-garlinghouse-scott-purcell"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T17:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortress was founded two years ago by former Prime Trust CEO Scott Purcell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Senator Applauds Bitcoin Mining’s Role In Bolstering The Economy And Grid]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d959081</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-mining-profits-us-economy-and-grid/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T16:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an interview with Forbes, Texas Senator Ted Cruz voiced support for Bitcoin mining and affirmed that mining operations benefit the Texas economy and grid. Cruz admired the decentralized nature of cryptocurrency technology and talked about the financial freedom achieved through the uncontrollable nature of Bitcoin. 
 
The senator highlighted the distinctive quality of Texas during his speech, emphasizing the profound affection its residents have for their freedom. He underscored this unique attribute by drawing attention to the role of Bitcoin. 
 
Similarly, Cruz cited financial freedom as a focal point for creating crypto regulations implied by the world’s jurisdictions with their own point of view. He admitted China’s ban on cryptocurrencies as an example. 
 
 
The Texas senator also s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kent Glory</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fourth Consecutive Week of Decline: NFT Sales Dip 6.75%]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d973942</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/fourth-consecutive-week-of-decline-nft-sales-dip-6-75/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T16:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-fungible token (NFT) sales took yet another dip this week, marking the fourth consecutive week of decline, albeit a slight one, with a decrease of 6.75%. From September 2, 2023, to September 9, the total sales for this week amounted to approximately $80.69 million, with a notable chunk of $42.61 million originating from the Ethereum blockchain.
 
NFT Sales Drop 6.75% in Weekly Decline
 
NFT sales took a 6.75% dip this week, as reported by data from cryptoslam.io. Over the past seven days, NFT transactions also slid by 4.33%. Despite this decline in sales, the number of NFT buyers surged to 569,407, marking a 17.77% increase compared to the previous week.
 
Presently, Ethereum leads the pack among 22 different blockchain networks, accounting for $42.61 million in NFT sales, which repres…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Congressman Intends To Limit SEC’s Authority Over Crypto Space]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d9a4d53</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/us-congressman-to-limit-sec-authority-over-crypto/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T14:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Congressman and popular crypto advocate Tom Emmer has stated his intentions to introduce an appropriations amendment that limits the ability of the US Securities and Exchange Commission to deploy funds on digital asset enforcement.
 
SEC Chairman Abused His Authority, Emmer Says
 
Through an X post on Friday, Emmer, who is also serving as the US House Majority Whip, once again voiced his displeasure on the SEC’s regulatory actions in the nation’s crypto space.
 
Emmer stated that Gary Gensler, incumbent chairman of the SEC, was misusing his authority at the expense of the American people. The US congressman believes the commission should be restricted from further “weaponizing taxpayer dollars” in its crusade against the digital asset industry. 
 
 
That is why I'm planning to sponsor a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Semilore Faleti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biggest Movers: DOGE Moves Away From Support Level, XLM Nears 1-Month High]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d9bd0e3</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/biggest-movers-doge-moves-away-from-support-level-xlm-nears-1-month-high/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T14:04:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin moved away from a key price floor on Saturday, as the meme coin ended a three-day winless run. Price has traded in the red since Wednesday, leading to a collision with a support point of $0.0620. Stellar also rallied, nearing a one-month high in the process.
 
Dogecoin (DOGE)
 
Dogecoin (DOGE) snapped a three-day losing streak on Saturday, as bulls pushed price away from a recent support level.
 
Following a low of $0.06284 on Friday, DOGE/USD moved to a peak of $0.06382 earlier in the day.
 
Today’s gain in price saw the meme coin continue to move beyond its aforementioned floor at the $0.0620 region.
 
 
However, momentum has not fully shifted to the bulls, as a result of the relative strength index (RSI) tracking below a ceiling of 44.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at 42.18, which comes as a crossover of moving averages looms.
 
Should the 10-day (red) moving average move beyond its 25-day (blue) counterpart, this could be the sign bulls are waiting for to reenter the market.
 
 
Stellar (XLM)
 
Stellar (XLM) extended recent gains to a fourth straight day, as price broke out of a key ceiling in the process.
 
XLM/USD peaked at $0.1328 to start the weekend, following a low of $0.1242 during Friday’s session.
 
Today’s move saw stellar climb to its highest point since August 16, when price peaked at $0.1364.
 
 
As a result of the gain in price, the moving averages of 10-days and 25-days respectively, now also sit on the cusp of an upward cross.
 
This could further push the token higher, with bulls seemingly targeting a higher point of resistance at $0.1400.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Will stellar bulls hit their target this weekend? Let us know your thoughts in the comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Bitcoin Miners Forced To Stop Operations Due To Energy Crunch]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d808fc4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/texas-bitcoin-miners-forced-to-stop-operations/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin miners in Texas are facing a temporary setback as they power down their operations in response to the state’s ongoing energy crisis. The scorching heatwave that gripped the Lone Star State forced the Electric Reliability Council of Texas (ERCOT) to take drastic measures to ensure uninterrupted power supply to its 25 million customers, accounting for a staggering 90% of the state’s grid load.
 
To alleviate the energy strain, ERCOT invoked emergency procedures, compelling specific power consumers, including Bitcoin miners, to curtail their energy consumption. The relentless heatwave pushed several mining outfits to temporarily suspend their operations. 
 
 
Riot Platforms and Marathon Digital are among those who recently announced a pause in their mining activities. Marathon Digital…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Super Mario Bros. Wonder: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155605</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155605/super-mario-bros-wonder-nintendo-switch-everything-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mario and friends enter the fantastical Flower Kingdom. But what else is new in Super Mario Bros. Wonder on Nintendo Switch?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin, Ethereum Technical Analysis: Price Movement in BTC, ETH Stalls to Start the Weekend]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d834aef</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-ethereum-technical-analysis-price-movement-in-btc-eth-stalls-to-start-the-weekend/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T12:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin consolidated for yet another week, as price entered Saturday around the same point at which it stood on Monday. Despite a brief rally on Thursday, which saw the price move above $28,000, the cryptocurrency has largely been unchanged. 
 
Bitcoin
 
Bitcoin started the weekend trading close to the $26,000 level, as bulls attempted to break into this price zone.
 
Friday saw bitcoin peak at $26,414.01, however as the day progressed, price slipped, after bulls were unable to move past a key resistance point.
 
BTC/USD was trading at a low of $25,730.12 earlier in today’s session, however it has marginally risen, and now sits at $25,862.51.
 
 
The slight increase comes as the relative strength index (RSI) moved closer to a key resistance level of 45.00.
 
At the time of writing, the index is tracking at a reading of 39.66, after making a move towards a floor of 35.00 on Friday.
 
The 10-day (red) and 25-day (blue) moving averages look set for a cross in the near future, which could trigger a rise in bullish sentiment.
 
 
Ethereum
 
Ethereum (ETH) has been hovering near a key support point of $1,630 to start the weekend, as market volatility eased on Saturday.
 
Following a low of $1,624.48 on Friday, ETH/USD made marginal gains in today’s session, hitting a peak of $1,637.98 in the process.
 
Despite several attempts by bears to move beyond the aforementioned price floor, bulls have rejected these advances for the majority of the week.
 
 
However, in order for sentiment in the market to shift closer to being bullish, a breakout of the 42.00 level on the RSI would be needed.
 
Price strength is now sitting at 38.67, with ethereum somewhat flatlining around the $1,634 region.
 
Register your email here to get weekly price analysis updates sent to your inbox:
 
Do you expect a rally in price this weekend? Leave your thoughts in the comments below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliman Dambell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Vs. Ripple: Commission Urges Court To Grant Appeal Request In Latest Filing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d74e9a5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/sec-urges-court-to-grant-appeal-request-in-filing/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T11:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States Securities and Exchange Commission has submitted a new filing pushing for the approval of its request to appeal the court’s judgment in the lawsuit against Ripple Labs. This comes exactly a week after the payment technology platform argued that the court should not certify the commission’s interlocutory appeal.
 
On September 1, Ripple asked the court to deny the SEC’s request to appeal the court’s ruling, as the summary judgment “does not present a controlling question of law suitable for interlocutory appeal.” The financial technology company also stated that the commission’s appeal request lacked the “exceptional circumstances required for interlocutory appeal.”
 
Ripple Trying To Delay Resolution To Continue Selling XRP, SEC Fires Shots
 
In a new filing submitted on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Sule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Cracks Down on 3 Defi Platforms for Offering Illegal Derivatives]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d709548</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cftc-cracks-down-on-3-defi-platforms-for-offering-illegal-derivatives/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has issued orders against the operators of three decentralized finance (defi) protocols. The regulator accused them of committing various violations of commodity laws including illegal trading of digital asset derivatives.
 
U.S. Commodities Regulator Settles Charges Against Defi Protocols Opyn, Zeroex, Deridex
 
The CFTC has taken action regarding three Delaware-registered companies doing business in the defi space — California-based Opyn and Zeroex as well as Deridex which is based in North Carolina. The Commission said it had issued orders filing and settling charges against them.
 
According to the announcement published on Thursday, Deridex and Opyn have been charged with failing to register as a swap execution facility (SEF) or des…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lubomir Tassev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Plunge: Analyst Warns Of Looming Liquidity Crisis Amid ETF Hopes]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d72ce58</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-analyst-warns-of-looming-liquidity-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T10:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) has recently sent a cautionary signal to cryptocurrency investors, with Bloomberg Intelligence’s senior macro strategist, Mike McGlone, issuing a stark warning amid the renewed hopes for exchange-traded funds (ETFs). 
 
Despite the BTC’s resilience, McGlone suggests that its recent price decline could foreshadow an impending liquidity crisis, especially in a financial landscape characterized by rapidly shifting monetary policies.
 
 
Bitcoin: Uneasy Stance Despite ETF Expectations
 
Bitcoin, the pioneering cryptocurrency, has experienced a rather unexpected dip of during the third quarter leading up to Sept. 6. This decline has taken place even as the prospects for the approval of US spot ETFs have grown brighter and the traditional stock market continues to demonstrate remar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Commissioner Proposes ‘First-Ever’ US Pilot Program for Crypto Regulation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d799667</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/cftc-commissioner-proposes-first-ever-us-pilot-program-for-crypto-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T09:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A commissioner with the Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) has proposed the “first-ever” pilot program in the U.S. “to support the development of compliant digital asset markets and tokenization.” The regulator emphasized: “Our principles-based framework is built for innovation in technology, new products, and market structure.”
 
‘Time-Limited CFTC Pilot Program’ for Crypto
 
Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) Commissioner Caroline D. Pham unveiled her proposal for a regulatory sandbox program to regulate crypto assets on Thursday. She posted on social media platform X:
 

It’s time to take action. I propose the first-ever U.S. pilot program for digital asset markets as a regulatory sandbox to test, gather data, & examine innovation. This creates a safe framework for new…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Court Orders Collapsed BTC Investment Firm to Pay Over $1.7 Billion in Restitution for Forex Fraud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d624e2c</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/us-court-orders-collapsed-btc-investment-firm-to-pay-over-1-7-billion-in-restitution-for-forex-fraud/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T07:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A United States Federal Court Judge has ordered the collapsed bitcoin investment platform Mirror Trading International to pay over $1.7 billion in restitution. Commodity Futures Trading Commission director of enforcement Ian McGinley said the CFTC will not hesitate to go after fraudsters who target U.S. citizens. The Commission again warned that court rulings are not a guarantee that victims will recover all their funds.
 
Forex Fraud Allegations
 
United States Federal Court Judge David A. Ezra recently ordered the now-defunct South African bitcoin investment platform Mirror Trading International (MTI) to pay over $1.7 billion in restitution. The order, which stems from the Commodity Futures Trading Commission’s (CFTC) June 2022 complaint, was issued after the judge determined that MTI ha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesia Expands De-Dollarization Efforts With National Task Force Formation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d6a28e4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/indonesia-expands-de-dollarization-efforts-with-national-task-force-formation/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T06:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indonesia’s central bank has established a national task force to expand the use of local currency with partner countries. Malaysia, Thailand, Japan, and China are already trading with Indonesia using local currencies. In addition, Singapore and South Korea have signed cooperation agreements to build a local currency transaction framework with Indonesia, according to the central bank.
 
Indonesia’s De-Dollarization Efforts
 
Bank Indonesia (BI), the Indonesian central bank, announced on Tuesday that it has “formed a National Task Force to expand the use of local currency transactions (LCT) in Indonesia with partner countries.” The Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) concerning the National LCT Task Force was signed on the sidelines of this year’s ASEAN Summit in Jakarta on Tuesday.
 
Besides…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palau Finishes Distribution Phase of Stablecoin Pilot, Organizes Feedback Survey]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e754d50c6a4</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/palau-finishes-distribution-phase-of-stablecoin-pilot-organizes-feedback-survey/"/>
        <updated>2023-09-09T04:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palau is preparing to close the distribution phase of its stablecoin pilot after having extended it for 30 additional days to examine additional use cases and growing popular demand. Palau Ministry of Finance board member Jay Hunter Anson explained that the pilot was a “temporary, research and development pilot,” and that the entity will now compile data to deliver a report to the government.
Palau Concludes Stablecoin Pilot Distribution Phase
Palau has informed about the completion of the distribution phase of its first stablecoin pilot, prompting users to spend their Palau Stablecoins (PSC) before September 15, when they will be frozen. Jay Hunter Anson, a board member of Palau’s Ministry of Finance, thanked the participants in this first phase and explained the steps the organization wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT Plus vs Claude Pro: Choose The Best Paid AI Chatbot For You]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155600</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155600/chatgpt-plus-vs-claude-pro-choose-the-best-paid-ai-chatbot-ally-for-you"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T23:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI’s ChatGPT Plus and Anthropic’s Claude Pro come at similar price points, but they have very different strengths and weaknesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fed's Michael Barr: No Word on CBDC and 'Deeply Concerned' About Stablecoins]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155576</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155576/feds-michael-barr-no-cbdc-decision-deeply-concerned-about-stablecoins"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T23:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He also said that the central bank was "a long way" from any decision on issuing a CBDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Harry Potter' Actors Protest London Dream Home Plans of Ripple Exec]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155620</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155620/harry-potter-actors-protest-london-dream-home-plans-ripple-exec"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T22:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emma Thompson, Imelda Staunton, and Jim Broadbent appear to be seriously aggrieved about their crypto executive neighbor's remodeling plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Donation Company Says Gifted Crypto Should Require Less Paperwork]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155601</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155601/bitcoin-donation-company-says-gifted-crypto-should-require-less-paperwork"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T20:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's ridiculous to require an appraisal of donations made in dollar-pegged stablecoins, like USDC or USDT, the company argues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LBRY Will Appeal 'Unjust and Incorrect' SEC Lawsuit Ruling, Says CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155569</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155569/lbry-will-appeal-unjust-and-incorrect-sec-lawsuit-ruling-says-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company had previously said it plans to wind down operations and the SEC dropped its financial penalty from $44 million to around $111,000.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France Now Has Crypto Influencer Training to Encourage Paid Ad Disclosures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155575</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155575/france-now-has-crypto-influencer-training-to-encourage-paid-ad-disclosures"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T19:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France requires investment communications to be non-misleading and balanced. “It appears that some influencers are unaware of this," said an official.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox Is Finally Coming to PlayStation This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155564</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155564/roblox-finally-coming-playstation-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox, which hosts a wide variety of different metaverse game experiences, is finally releasing on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 5 consoles in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Salvador's Bitcoin Curriculum Will Teach Students the 'Dark Side of Fiat']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155559</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155559/el-salvadors-bitcoin-curriculum-will-teach-the-dark-side-of-fiat"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T18:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students learn about currency debasement, a nod to Saifedean Ammous's "The Bitcoin Standard" book. But he didn't help write the curriculum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIP TCG: How Deadfellaz Is Rethinking Card-Battler Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155545</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155545/rip-tcg-how-deadfellaz-rethinking-card-battler-games"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T17:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deadfellaz founders Psych and Betty share how the digital trading card game will help grow the lore of the zombie-themed Ethereum NFT brand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance NFT Marketplace Ends Support for Polygon in Effort to ‘Streamline']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155535</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155535/binance-nft-marketplace-ends-polygon-support"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users have until the end of the year to withdraw their Polygon NFTs from the exchange's NFT Marketplace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: Should You Spend $20 per Month for the Claude Pro AI Chatbot?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155361</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155361/review-should-you-spend-20-per-month-for-the-claude-pro-ai-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t pull out your credit card just yet. Here’s a guide to help you decide whether upgrading to Anthropic's Claude Pro is the right move for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How This African Non-Profit Is Building an Army of Bitcoin Devs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155537</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155537/how-this-african-non-profit-is-building-an-army-of-bitcoin-devs"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newly renamed Btrust Builders has placed developers with SphinxChat, Galoy, Bitnob, Chaincode Labs, HeartBit, Ibex, and Rigly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only Up Developer Removes Hit Game From Steam Citing 'Stress']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155540</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155540/only-up-developer-removes-hit-game-steam-citing-stress"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T16:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only Up is now gone forever, apparently, just months after hitting it big with Twitch streamers and intriguing crypto fans with NFT art.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Brushes Off 'Negative News' Amid Executive Departures]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155530</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155530/binance-ceo-brushes-off-negative-news-amid-executive-departures"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T13:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Twitter post, Changpeng ‘CZ’ Zhao confronted “FUD” surrounding employee turnover at the crypto exchange.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler,Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thodex CEO Gets 11,000-Year Jail Sentence Over $2B Crypto Exchange Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155522</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155522/thodex-ceo-gets-11000-year-jail-sentence-over-2b-crypto-exchange-collapse"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once the biggest crypto exchange in Turkey, Thodex collapsed in 2021, leaving 400,000 users without access to their crypto deposits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFTC Charges Three DeFi Protocols With Violating AML Rules, Operating Without Licenses]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155509</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155509/cftc-charges-three-defi-protocols-with-violating-aml-rules-operating-without-licenses"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T11:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized exchanges Opyn, ZeroEx and Deridex settled with the CFTC on charges that included failing to geoblock U.S. users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly Half Of Institutions Are Holding Digital Assets For Clients: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155507</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155507/nearly-half-of-institutions-are-holding-digital-assets-for-clients-report"/>
        <updated>2023-09-08T10:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of 60 institutions surveyed in the U.S., Europe and the U.K., an astounding 48% reported currently managing digital assets for their clients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drake and The Weeknd AI Song Went Viral—Could It Win a Grammy?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155479</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155479/drake-weeknd-ai-song-went-viral-now-could-win-grammy"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T23:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostwriter created "Heart on My Sleeve" with help from AI. It was pulled from streaming services, but it could it really win music's highest honor?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaq Played Active Role in Solana NFT Project Before Abandoning It, Lawsuit Alleges]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155470</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155470/shaq-played-active-role-solana-nft-project-before-abandoning-lawsuit-alleges"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T23:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Basketball legend Shaquille O'Neal bailed after FTX's collapse, the amended complaint claims, allegedly tanking the NFT project's value.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bitcoin Miners in Texas Are Making Millions Without Mining at All]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155460</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155460/how-bitcoin-miners-in-texas-are-making-millions-without-mining-at-all"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T21:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miners “either mine BTC or curtail energy when prices are high to sell it back to the grid,” Compass Mining told Decrypt, giving them a better return than mining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Solimano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EA Sports UFC 5: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155400</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155400/ea-sports-ufc-5-everything-you-need-know"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to rumble? EA Sports UFC 5 will be the first Mature-rated entry in the MMA fighting series, coming to PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former FTX Exec Ryan Salame Forfeits $1.5 Billion in Plea Deal]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155340</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155340/former-ftx-exec-ryan-salame-plead-guilty"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T20:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salame, co-CEO of FTX Digital Markets, pleaded guilty to campaign finance violations and fraud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basketball Title Rumble Kong League and Stance Launch In-Game and IRL HyperSocks]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=154226</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/154226/basketball-title-rumble-kong-league-and-stance-launch-in-game-and-irl-hypersocks"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The partnership will kick off with the launch of NFT HyperSocks by Stance, alongside IRL counterparts and an augmented reality filter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Says North Korea’s Lazarus Group Was Behind $41 Million Stake Hack]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155360</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155360/fbi-says-north-koreas-lazarus-group-was-behind-41-million-stake-hack"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hacker group is one of crypto’s most prolific, allegedly responsible for stealing $2 billion worth of assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skyrim Creator's Starfield Tops One Million Concurrent Players on Launch Day]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155330</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155330/skyrim-creators-starfield-tops-million-concurrent-players-launch-day"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bethesda Game Studios' Starfield is making waves with a huge player turnout on day one and broadly positive reviews.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Irwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFL All Day Has Fumbled: NFT Sales Down 87% From a Year Ago]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155347</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155347/nfl-all-day-has-fumbled-nft-sales-down-87-from-a-year-ago"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T18:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dapper Labs may be hoping for a Hail Mary as NFL All Day’s sales flounder compared to its 2022 football preseason rally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenyan Official Calls Worldcoin a 'Gang of Criminals Who Are Coming to Harvest Data']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155283</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155283/kenyan-official-calls-worldcoin-gang-of-criminals-coming-to-harvest-data"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T16:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worldcoin CEO Alex Blania refuted the claim, saying "Worldcoin is designed to be privacy-preserving."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic Debuts Claude Pro to Rival ChatGPT's AI Chatbot]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155331</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155331/anthropic-debuts-claude-pro-rival-to-chatgpt-ai-chatbot"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T15:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new service competes against ChatGPT Plus and offers 5X more interactions, priority of computing power and access to early features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Vitalik Buterin, Ethereum Creator?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155291</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/resources/who-is-vitalik-buterin-ethereum-creator"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buterin’s interest in broadening Bitcoin’s scope led him to pursue a Turing-complete programming language to realize his vision. The young programmer created an initial white paper for this concept, which he called Ethereum, in 2013.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Reiff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MyLugano Crypto Payment App Adds Support for Internet Computer’s Multi-Chain Bitcoin ‘Twin’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155275</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155275/mylugano-crypto-payment-app-adds-support-for-internet-computers-multi-chain-bitcoin-twin"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Swiss city of Lugano will see more crypto adoption thanks to a partnership with the DFINITY Foundation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Asmakov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF, FSB Lay Out Roadmap To ‘Address Risks’ Posed by Crypto to Financial Stability]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155281</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155281/imf-fsb-lay-out-roadmap-to-address-the-risks-posed-by-crypto-to-financial-stability"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The international bodies warned of threats to monetary policy and financial stability if crypto adoption becomes widespread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Pushes for ‘Privacy Pools’ to Balance Anonymity With Regulatory Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155278</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155278/vitalik-buterin-pushes-for-privacy-pools-to-balance-anonymity-with-regulatory-compliance"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T13:18:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A research paper co-authored by the Ethereum co-founder explores a privacy-preserving blockchain protocol that complies with global regulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivesh Rustgi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texas Paid Riot Platforms $31.7M to Slash Bitcoin Mining in August Heatwave]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155272</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155272/texas-paid-riot-platforms-31-7m-to-slash-bitcoin-mining-in-august-heatwave"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T11:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mining company reduced its energy demand by 95% during the August heatwave, receiving credits for the energy it would have consumed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mattis Meichler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK’s Frontier AI Taskforce Appoints Advisors to ‘Start-Up Inside Government’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=155268</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/155268/uks-frontier-ai-taskforce-appoints-advisors-to-start-up-inside-government"/>
        <updated>2023-09-07T10:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AI heavyweights joining the taskforce include a former OpenAI researcher, a Turing Award winner, and the Director of GCHQ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alys Key</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mino Games is Using Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SrT1Afj7/how-mino-games-is-using-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2023-09-05T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha McKinnon tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about how the studio's upcoming game Dimensionals will use real-time AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERVIEW: How Will Aurory Use NFTs and Crypto?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qv3VwNmM/interview-how-will-aurory-use-nfts-and-crypto"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Natoli, Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how the Aurory games will use NFTs and crypto and shares the studio's broader stance on the tech.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud's James Tromans on the Intersection of AI and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/OeD4uoLj/google-clouds-james-tromans-on-the-intersection-of-ai-and-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-09-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Global Head of Google Cloud for Web3 James Tromans sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson to discuss how AI can help Web3 companies come to market faster and the real value of Web3 tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering NFT Trading - Degen U]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/HQGt1Vrq/mastering-nft-trading-degen-u"/>
        <updated>2023-08-29T07:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take Degen U's new course, Mastering NFT Trading, and earn an on-chain certificate. A top instructor will help you identify trends, seize the right moment to trade, weed out scams—and have fun while doing it!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space Nation CEO on Working With 'Independence Day' Director Roland Emmerich]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LpznLhtx/space-nation-ceo-on-working-with-independence-day-director-roland-emmerich"/>
        <updated>2023-08-28T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jerome Wu, CEO of Space Nation, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the upcoming Space Nation Online game in development and shares details on Space Nation Cofounder Roland Emmerich's role in the project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GAME REVIEW: Champions Arena from Gala Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qUE1RlDx/game-review-champions-arena-from-gala-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Champions Arena is a turn-based fantasy RPG from Gala Games, where characters can become NFTs and crypto can be used to purchase gems, one of the game's synthetic currencies. Decrypt's Kate Irwin takes us inside the game for her thoughts on the fun, mobile-first title.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor Ben Prendergast on the Future of Gaming]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/X3RKdsaG/apex-legends-voice-actor-ben-prendergast-on-the-future-of-gaming"/>
        <updated>2023-08-24T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice actor Ben Prendergast, who's voiced characters in games like Apex Legends and God of War Ragnarok, shares his opinions on the tech space's history of "bubbles" and whether blockchain gaming has a future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The future of AI Stardom and Robotics with SingularityNET COO Janet Adams and Desdemona]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yVQaZI71/the-future-of-ai-stardom-and-robotics-with-singularitynet-coo-janet-adams-and-desdemona"/>
        <updated>2023-08-23T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this interview, SingularityNET COO Janet Adams explains the intricate details that went into creating the Desdemona robot AI from Hanson Robotics and future plans for the AI Diva.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto a 'No-Brainer' for Video Games, Says Mino Games CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rdynom8C/crypto-a-no-brainer-for-video-games-says-mino-games-ceo"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mino Games CEO Sasha MacKinnon, developer of the upcoming Dimensionals game, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin about the studio's approach to digital collectibles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Wagner's 'Controversial Take' on Crypto in Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tc2nKeqA/michael-wagners-controversial-take-on-crypto-in-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-21T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Solana's PlayGG, Star Atlas CEO Michael Wagner shares his "controversial take" on crypto in games, shares the challenges of developing the upcoming scifi game, and how crypto's volatility has changed his perspective with Decrypt's Jason Nelson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: Angelic CEO on Building the Sci-Fi RPG on Solana and Ethereum]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/uCzW3K7P/interview-angelic-ceo-on-building-the-sci-fi-rpg-on-solana-and-ethereum"/>
        <updated>2023-08-18T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Angelic is a sci-fi roleplay game in development that will be free-to-play and offer optional, opt-in crypto features on Solana and Ethereum and a governance token. Metaverse Game Studios CEO and Founder Erkan Bayol tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson about how he sees AAA traditional games as Angelic's main competitors and shares his vision for the game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apex Legends Voice Actor on AI's Impact on Video Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IOIrmb0N/apex-legends-voice-actor-on-ais-impact-on-video-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-16T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Prendergast is an actor who has voiced characters like Apex Legends' Fuse, God of War Ragnarok's Tyr, and Patroclus in Hades. But as debates swirl around the use of artificial intelligence in entertainment in light of the SAG-AFTRA and WGA strikes, Prendergast gives Decrypt's Kate Irwin his honest take on the potential use of AI actors in games.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Atlas CEO on Developing an MMO Game]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/WQCaahmH/star-atlas-ceo-on-developing-an-mmo-game"/>
        <updated>2023-08-15T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson speaks with Star Atlas Founder and CEO Michael Wagner about the MMO game's approach to development, marketing, and blockchain integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory's Origin Story: How JRPGs Inspired the Games]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/O0S201TB/aurorys-origin-story-how-jrpgs-inspired-the-games"/>
        <updated>2023-08-14T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson talks to Aurory's Head of Marketing and Business Development Michael Natoli about the origins of the Aurory crypto games at the Solana PlayGG event.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel TCG: Inside the Sci-Fi Card Game’s Closed Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/q8YVWJh4/parallel-tcg-inside-the-sci-fi-card-games-closed-beta"/>
        <updated>2023-08-11T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Kate Irwin goes hands-on with Parallel’s closed beta on Windows PC to find out what sets it apart from other crypto card-battlers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>