<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-08T15:15:47.485Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2024-05-08T15:15:47.485Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero-Backed Short Film Tackles Injustice on the Mexican-American Border]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229739</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229739/monero-backed-film-limite-injustice-mexican-american-border"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:12:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Límite” director George Nicolas explains how privacy-preserving cryptocurrency Monero gives him “hope for the future.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Next Big Leap? Buterin Proposes Transformative EIP-7702]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fe757d5</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ethereum-buterin-eip-7702/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin, along with collaborators Sam Wilson, Ansgar Dietrichs, and Matt Garnett, has proposed a new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) numbered 7702, designed to significantly enhance the functionality of Ethereum’s externally owned accounts (EOAs). EIP-7702 aims to integrate smart contract functionalities temporarily into EOAs, a transformative concept that might redefine user interactions on the Ethereum network.
 
Evolution Of Account Abstraction On Ethereum
 
Ethereum’s account model includes two primary types: externally owned accounts (EOAs) and contract accounts. EOAs are controlled by private keys and have limited capabilities and security features, which restrict their use in more complex transactions typically reserved for smart contracts.
 
To addre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Veterans Secure $28 Million in Funding Round for Arbelos Markets Led by Dragonfly]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470884/Crypto-Veterans-Secure-28-Million-in-Funding-Round-for-Arbelos-Markets-Led-by-Dragonfly</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470884/Crypto-Veterans-Secure-28-Million-in-Funding-Round-for-Arbelos-Markets-Led-by-Dragonfly"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Crypto Veterans Secure $28 Million in Funding Round for Arbelos Markets Led by Dragonfly Currently, Arbelos operates offshore through the British Virgin Islands. The company is also seeking a regulatory license from financial authorities in the region to enable it to operate without...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PEPE's 7-Day Bull Run Put on Hold, Explained by On-Chain Data]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470873/PEPEs-7-Day-Bull-Run-Put-on-Hold-Explained-by-On-Chain-Data</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470873/PEPEs-7-Day-Bull-Run-Put-on-Hold-Explained-by-On-Chain-Data"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do on-chain data essentials help explain the pause in PEPE coin's 25% weekly run?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Coinbase, Another Cryptocurrency Exchange Is Listed on the American Stock Exchange Nasdaq!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470838/After-Coinbase-Another-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Is-Listed-on-the-American-Stock-Exchange-Nasdaq</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470838/After-Coinbase-Another-Cryptocurrency-Exchange-Is-Listed-on-the-American-Stock-Exchange-Nasdaq"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of Japan's leading cryptocurrency exchanges is listed on the Nasdaq exchange through its Special Purpose Acquisition Company listing. Continue Reading: After Coinbase, Another Cryptocurrency Exchange Is Listed on the American Stock Exchange Nasdaq!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum’s Next Big Leap? Buterin Proposes Transformative EIP-7702]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470853/Ethereums-Next-Big-Leap-Buterin-Proposes-Transformative-EIP-7702</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470853/Ethereums-Next-Big-Leap-Buterin-Proposes-Transformative-EIP-7702"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum co-founder Vitalik Buterin, along with collaborators Sam Wilson, Ansgar Dietrichs, and Matt Garnett, has proposed a new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) numbered 7702, designed to significantly enhance the functionality of Ethereum’s externally owned accounts (EOAs). EIP-7702 aims to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget The Price Dip: Ethereum Network Activity Hints At Imminent Takeoff]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470824/Forget-The-Price-Dip-Ethereum-Network-Activity-Hints-At-Imminent-Takeoff</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470824/Forget-The-Price-Dip-Ethereum-Network-Activity-Hints-At-Imminent-Takeoff"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum, the world’s second-largest cryptocurrency by market cap, finds itself in a curious position. While the price struggles for direction, its underlying network is experiencing a surge in activity. Related Reading: Whispers In The Deep: Why Are Ethereum Whales Disappearing? Ethereum...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina to Mine Bitcoin with Stranded Gas]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fe18649</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinmagazine.com/business/-argentina-to-mine-bitcoin-with-stranded-gas"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina's energy sector is increasingly turning to Bitcoin, this time with a state-owned facility using stranded natural gas from oil fields that would otherwise be wasted.

JUST IN: 🇦🇷 Argentina state-owned company’s subsidiary will mine $BTC with Stranded Gas: Forbes
Eventually, every country will be mining #Bitcoin pic.twitter.com/bu6sCXEUJ1
— Bitcoin Magazine (@BitcoinMagazine) May 8, 2024
 
 
 
State-owned energy firm YPF's subsidiary, YPF Luz, recently partnered with Genesis Digital Assets (GDA) to launch a gas flare-powered mining facility. It will harness 1,200 machines to monetize gas currently being flared into the atmosphere.
This comes as Argentina embraces Bitcoin with the election of Bitcoin-friendly President Javier Milei in late 2023. 
By repurposing stranded gas that i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet Foundation Announces Seed Grant Program to Enhance Growth on its Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470816/Starknet-Foundation-Announces-Seed-Grant-Program-to-Enhance-Growth-on-its-Ecosystem</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470816/Starknet-Foundation-Announces-Seed-Grant-Program-to-Enhance-Growth-on-its-Ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starknet Foundation just rolled out a seed grant program in an initiative to provide teams with the capacity to build and grow on the Starknet ecosystem. The program aims to enhance the growth of the Starknet ecosystem. The Starkent Foundation set aside $5 million in grants, which will be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Trading Firm Purchased $1B Worth Of Bitcoin ETFs In Q1]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470881/Major-Trading-Firm-Purchased-1B-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Q1</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470881/Major-Trading-Firm-Purchased-1B-Worth-Of-Bitcoin-ETFs-In-Q1"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quantitative trading firm Susquehanna has invested over $1 billion in Bitcoin-related ETFs, including Grayscale, Fidelity, and ProShares, among others. read more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stellar (XLM) Readies for Game-Changing Upgrade: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470808/Stellar-XLM-Readies-for-Game-Changing-Upgrade-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470808/Stellar-XLM-Readies-for-Game-Changing-Upgrade-Details"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade comes after successful mainnet launch of Soroban, Stellar's smart contracts platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard and US banks collaborate to streamline settlement of tokenized assets.]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470799/Mastercard-and-US-banks-collaborate-to-streamline-settlement-of-tokenized-assets</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470799/Mastercard-and-US-banks-collaborate-to-streamline-settlement-of-tokenized-assets"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard, in collaboration with major US banks, is pioneering a new frontier in financial technology by testing shared-ledger technology as per Bloomberg report. This innovation aims to enable the seamless settlement of tokenized assets, including commercial bank money and various securities...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ripple’s Planned Stablecoin Draws SEC Scrutiny for Unregistered Status]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470802/Ripples-Planned-Stablecoin-Draws-SEC-Scrutiny-for-Unregistered-Status</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470802/Ripples-Planned-Stablecoin-Draws-SEC-Scrutiny-for-Unregistered-Status"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinspeaker Ripple’s Planned Stablecoin Draws SEC Scrutiny for Unregistered Status The SEC says Ripple's intention to issue a stablecoin, an unregistered asset, is further proof that it will continue to break the law. Ripple’s Planned Stablecoin Draws SEC Scrutiny for Unregistered Status]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Doggy (SOLDOGGY) Will Rally Over 6,000%, as Shiba Inu and Dogecoin Lose Momentum]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470800/Solana-Doggy-SOLDOGGY-Will-Rally-Over-6000-as-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin-Lose-Momentum</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470800/Solana-Doggy-SOLDOGGY-Will-Rally-Over-6000-as-Shiba-Inu-and-Dogecoin-Lose-Momentum"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Doggy (SOLDOGGY) could become a viral memecoin, like Shiba Inu (SHIB) and Dogecoin (DOGE)....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mixed Fortunes for US Bitcoin Funds as GBTC Losses Offset Other Gains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fec78bc</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/mixed-fortunes-for-us-bitcoin-funds-as-gbtc-losses-offset-other-gains/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following two days of positive inflows, U.S. spot bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) experienced a decline, with $15.7 million exiting on Tuesday. Grayscale’s Bitcoin Trust (GBTC) saw $29 million leave during the day’s trading sessions, overshadowing the break-even and positive reports from the other spot bitcoin funds. Fidelity, Ark Invest, Invesco Report Gains While GBTC Struggles […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sell signal for two overbought cryptocurrencies this week]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470762/Sell-signal-for-two-overbought-cryptocurrencies-this-week</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470762/Sell-signal-for-two-overbought-cryptocurrencies-this-week"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptocurrency market has recently gone through a tumultuous phase, leaving many investors uncertain. Amid this turmoil, most cryptocurrencies quickly … Continue reading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public blockchain ledgers ‘not fit for purpose,’ says JPMorgan]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470760/Public-blockchain-ledgers-not-fit-for-purpose-says-JPMorgan</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470760/Public-blockchain-ledgers-not-fit-for-purpose-says-JPMorgan"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the criticism, TradFi institutions still prefer using public blockchains for real-world asset tokenization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockworks expands ‘House of Brands’ model with acquisition of The Breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470814/Blockworks-expands-House-of-Brands-model-with-acquisition-of-The-Breakdown</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470814/Blockworks-expands-House-of-Brands-model-with-acquisition-of-The-Breakdown"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:34:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a momentous step for Blockworks, and we are excited about the opportunities this collaboration unlocks for our community]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lagrange Labs closes $13.2M to build out ZK proofs based on EigenLayer]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470749/Lagrange-Labs-closes-132M-to-build-out-ZK-proofs-based-on-EigenLayer</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470749/Lagrange-Labs-closes-132M-to-build-out-ZK-proofs-based-on-EigenLayer"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lagrange Labs, a cryptography startup specializing in zero-knowledge (ZK) proofs, has raised $13.2 million in a seed funding round led by Peter Thiel's Founders Fund.The startup is based on Ethereum's EigenLayer restaking platform and is aimed at providing decentralized applications with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX heritage auction for the third locked Solana tranche has begun]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470788/The-FTX-heritage-auction-for-the-third-locked-Solana-tranche-has-begun</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470788/The-FTX-heritage-auction-for-the-third-locked-Solana-tranche-has-begun"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FTX asset has started the auction of its third tranche of locked Solana (SOL) tokens. This move is part of a broader strategy to liquidate assets following the infamous collapse of the FTX exchange platform. The auction, which involves approximately 41 million locked SOL tokens, has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Chain Analyst Willy Woo Says Bitcoin Setting Up To Potentially Reach ‘Escape Velocity’ – Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470727/On-Chain-Analyst-Willy-Woo-Says-Bitcoin-Setting-Up-To-Potentially-Reach-Escape-Velocity-Heres-Why</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470727/On-Chain-Analyst-Willy-Woo-Says-Bitcoin-Setting-Up-To-Potentially-Reach-Escape-Velocity-Heres-Why"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On-chain analyst Willy Woo thinks Bitcoin (BTC) could be primed to surge in price. Woo tells his 1.1 million followers on the social media platform X that the top crypto asset is flashing a bullish divergence “with lots of room to run” on its volume-weighted average price (VWAP) oscillator...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It Too Late to Buy Bitcoin Cash? BCH Price Up 11% as GambleFi Project Reaches $700,000 Milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470713/Is-It-Too-Late-to-Buy-Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-Price-Up-11-as-GambleFi-Project-Reaches-700000-Milestone</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470713/Is-It-Too-Late-to-Buy-Bitcoin-Cash-BCH-Price-Up-11-as-GambleFi-Project-Reaches-700000-Milestone"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Cash’s ($BCH) price gains over the last seven days have outpaced market leaders Bitcoin and Ethereum. Since Wednesday May 1, Bitcoin Cash has risen 11% to change hands at a current price of $453. Over the same peiod, the token representing the original unforked Bitcoin ledger, $BTC, has...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for the Bull, Giant Whales Made Large Purchases in This Altcoin, The Price Increased by 40 Percent!]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470709/Preparing-for-the-Bull-Giant-Whales-Made-Large-Purchases-in-This-Altcoin-The-Price-Increased-by-40-Percent</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470709/Preparing-for-the-Bull-Giant-Whales-Made-Large-Purchases-in-This-Altcoin-The-Price-Increased-by-40-Percent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular artificial intelligence altcoin Render (RNDR) is experiencing a strong whale accumulation, its price increasing by 38 percent in the last week. Continue Reading: Preparing for the Bull, Giant Whales Made Large Purchases in This Altcoin, The Price Increased by 40 Percent!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Legal Blow for Cristiano Ronaldo as Judge Denies Dismissal Motion]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fef4ab0</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/legal-blow-for-cristiano-ronaldo-as-judge-denies-dismissal-motion/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a legal blow to Cristiano Ronaldo, the famed Portuguese  
soccer star, the judge overseeing the $1 billion class action lawsuit against  
him has rejected his motion to dismiss the case. The lawsuit, filed in Florida,  
accuses Ronaldo of endorsing Binance, which allegedly led investors into making costly and risky  
investments.
Ronaldo's Motion Denied in Binance NFT Lawsuit
Judge Roy Altman's ruling, issued on May 4, followed a  
request from the plaintiffs to stay proceedings until a ruling on a motion to  
compel arbitration. Simultaneously, the judge denied Ronaldo's motion to  
dismiss the case, stating: "We deny without prejudice the Defendant's 29 motion  
to dismiss."
The lawsuit revolves around Ronaldo's promotion of Binance,  
particularly in relation to a collection of non-f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert in losing money Su Zhu says you can afford to lose $10k]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470706/Expert-in-losing-money-Su-Zhu-says-you-can-afford-to-lose-10k</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19470706/Expert-in-losing-money-Su-Zhu-says-you-can-afford-to-lose-10k"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Arrows Capital (3AC) co-founder Su Zhu has claimed that “$10,000 is an amount you can definitely afford to lose if you’re in the Western world because you’ll earn that back in salary.” Zhu made the claim on the OX podcast when asked what he would do if he started in crypto today in search […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria Threatens Crypto Knockout: P2P Ban Looms In Fintech Feud]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fe98cd4</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/nigeria-threatens-to-ban-p2p-transactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigeria’s once-tepid stance on cryptocurrency has taken a sharp turn towards prohibition. The Nigerian government, citing concerns over Naira manipulation, is proposing a ban on P2P (Peer-to-Peer) trading platforms that utilize the local currency. This move, coupled with ongoing legal battles with major exchanges, throws the future of Nigerian crypto into uncertainty.
 
 
Naira Under Siege? The P2P Battleground
 
The Nigerian Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) alleges that crypto participants and exchanges are manipulating the Naira’s value through P2P transactions. Emomotimi Agama, the newly appointed Director-General, suggests delisting the Naira from all P2P platforms as a remedy.
 
Agama highlighted the government’s resolve to combat the perceived threat, saying:
 
 
“This is one…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Regulations Are Imminent, but Will the Regulators Align?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fd6178d</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/crypto-regulations-are-imminent-but-will-the-regulators-align/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regulatory change in the crypto realm has been a subject of heated debate for many years. The general ethos of cryptocurrency is one of anarchism or anarcho-capitalism. Proponents of the tech tend to be adamantly against any type of governmental intervention into markets or technology.
However, as digital assets and blockchain technology find themselves thrust into the mainstream, governments must respond. They must either incorporate these assets into existing regulations or create a new regulatory framework altogether.  
Lets look at how crypto regulations have evolved over the years, with a focus on US regulation.
Background: Crypto Regulation in the US
Much of the conversation surrounding cryptocurrency regulation in the US has been focused on something called the Howey Test. Having it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Nibley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thiel-Backed Cryptography Startup Lagrange Raises $13M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fd10c02</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/05/08/thiel-backed-cryptography-startup-lagrange-raises-13m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lagrange, which specializes in zero-knowledge cryptography, is the latest startup to ride EigenLayer's "restaking" wave.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Kessler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Not a Token Offering, It's a 'Node Sale': Sophon Blockchain Raises $60M]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fd10be3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/05/08/its-not-a-token-offering-its-a-node-sale-sophon-blockchain-raises-60m/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blockchain project's founders aren't even publicly named, but they've enjoyed remarkable success in fundraising, partly thanks to this increasingly popular fundraising method, where the longer you wait, the higher price you pay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bradley Keoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Injective, Underperforming in Crypto Markets, Now Plans Layer-3 Chain on Arbitrum]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fd10bd3</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2024/05/08/injective-underperforming-in-crypto-markets-now-plans-layer-3-chain-on-arbitrum/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Injective’s "inEVM," which connects the Ethereum, Cosmos, and Solana networks, will rely on Arbitrum's Orbit toolkit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Margaux Nijkerk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most FTX Creditors to Receive Over 100% Repayment, Court Document Shows]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fd20493</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/most-ftx-creditors-to-receive-over-100-repayment-court-document-shows/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX is poised to repay nearly all its account holders fully, according to a reorganization plan presented in court. The bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange has raised about $15 billion mainly by selling investments from itself and its affiliate, Alameda Research. This fund will ensure payments of 118 cents on the dollar for 98% of creditors with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bitcoin.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Principal Trader Arbelos Markets Raises $28M Led by Dragonfly Capital]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fdd4784</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/08/crypto-principal-trader-arbelos-markets-raises-28m-led-by-dragonfly-capital/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before starting Arbelos Markets last year, Tang served as chief investment officer at quantitative digital asset investment firm LedgerPrime while Lim was head of trading strategy at Galaxy and head of derivatives at now-defunct crypto lender Genesis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krisztian  Sandor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt Crypto Exchange FTX Lines Up $16 Billion To Repay Creditors]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fdd57c8</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/crypto-exchange-ftx-16-billion/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bankrupt cryptocurrency exchange, FTX has unveiled a new repayment plan aimed at reimbursing creditors and customers in full and offering billions in the form of compensation for the time value of their investment. 
 
FTX To Reimburse Customers In Full
 
In a press release on May 7, FTX disclosed that it would be repaying 98% of its customers at least 118% of allowed claims in cash. The insolvent crypto exchange had filed a new reorganization strategy with the United States Bankruptcy Court of Delaware.
 
Related Reading: Dogecoin Holders In Profit across 82%, What About Shiba Inu?
 
The reorganization plan, which involves the allocation of funds to customers affected by FTX’s fraud scheme, will involve a centralized distribution of all of the company’s assets during the time of its collap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Game 'MixMob: Racer 1' Reveals iOS and Android Launch Date]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229861</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229861/solana-game-mixmob-racer-1-ios-android-launch-date"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Race-to-earn” Solana game MixMob: Racer 1 is hitting the App Store and Play Store in less than a week, ahead of its next big competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Technical Analysis: BTC Faces Growing Uncertainty Amidst Market Fluctuations]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fda444a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-technical-analysis-btc-faces-growing-uncertainty-amidst-market-fluctuations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T12:31:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of May 8, 2024, bitcoin’s price is coasting along at $62,378, experiencing a 24-hour intraday range from $62,096 to $64,413, with a trading volume of $17.91 billion and a market capitalization of $1.22 trillion. Despite a decline of 2.1% over the past 24 hours, bitcoin has gained 9.3% over the last seven days. Bitcoin […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Mover Americas: Bitcoin Hovers Above $62K]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fdaeba4</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/08/first-mover-americas-bitcoin-hovers-above-62k/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T12:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest price moves in bitcoin (BTC) and crypto markets in context for May 8, 2024. First Mover is CoinDesk’s daily newsletter that contextualizes the latest actions in the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley, Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Minister Says Government Only Has Time to Implement Stablecoin, Staking Legislation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fc6ecf1</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/policy/2024/05/08/uk-minister-says-government-only-has-time-to-implement-stablecoin-staking-legislation/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T12:03:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economic Secretary Bim Afolami said that the government could put through stablecoin and staking legislation in the coming weeks but will outline was is coming later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camomile Shumba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Bitcoin Indicator Points to Period of Calm in Crypto Market]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fc1fa3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2024/05/08/key-bitcoin-indicator-points-to-period-of-calm-in-crypto-market/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC's volatility risk premium (VRP) has collapsed in a sign of a market trending towards stability, where future uncertainties are less of a concern.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omkar Godbole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyst Sticks To Guns: Bitcoin Still Headed For $150,000]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fc27291</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/analyst-bitcoin-still-headed-for-150000/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Lee, co-founder of research firm Fundstrat, has ignited fresh bullish sentiment in the cryptocurrency world with his prediction of a Bitcoin price surge to $150,000 by the year’s end. Lee, a prominent Bitcoin advocate, remains confident despite a recent price dip and ongoing inflation concerns.
 
 
Bitcoin: Early Days Of A Bullish Charge
 
He argues that the current crypto bull cycle is far from over. In a CNBC interview, he emphasized:
 
 
“The idea that it could get to $150,000 is still within our base case.” 
 
This optimism stems partly from the recent launch of several Bitcoin ETFs, which Lee sees as a “wonderful development” that simplifies cryptocurrency investment for mainstream audiences. These ETFs eliminate the need for individuals to manage private keys, a technical hurdle …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monero Exchange LocalMonero Is  'Winding Down' Its Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229844</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229844/monero-exchange-localmonero-is-winding-down-its-operations"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The peer-to-peer exchange for privacy coin Monero cited "a combination of internal and external factors" for its decision to close.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hut 8’s Bitcoin Mining Output Drops 36% to 148 BTC in April]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fcc5470</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/hut-8s-bitcoin-mining-output-drops-36-to-148-btc-in-april/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North American bitcoin miner, Hut 8, said it mined 148 bitcoins, or 36% coins less in April than it did in March. Hut 8 primarily attributes the decrease in the number of mined bitcoins to the relocation of its proprietary miners, which were previously hosted at the Kearney and Granbury sites. The Halving Effect Hut […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Crypto Exchange Coincheck Sees Nasdaq Listing Completion in Second, Third Quarters]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fcf84dd</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2024/05/08/japanese-crypto-exchange-coincheck-sees-nasdaq-listing-completion-in-second-third-quarters/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coincheck said the timing is subject to approval by Thunder Bridger IV's stockholders, the SEC and Nasdaq.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Crawley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoMining Secures Bitscale Capital Backing to Accelerate Its NFT-Based Bitcoin Mining Operation]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e742fcfec91</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/gomining-secures-bitscale-capital-backing-to-accelerate-its-nft-based-bitcoin-mining-operation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRESS RELEASE. British Virgin Islands / Wednesday / GoMining, the infrastructure company easing access to Bitcoin mining with its Liquid Bitcoin Hashrate protocol, has raised $3 million through a direct investment from Bitscale Capital, a top international VC fund. The agreement will see Bitscale Capital acquire equity worth $3 million, in the shape of GOMINING, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meme Coins DOGE and SHIB See Losses as Ethereum Drops 4%]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229845</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229845/meme-coins-doge-and-shib-see-losses-as-ethereum-drops-4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s favorite memes have taken the biggest hit today as the wider market sees a moderate drawback in comparison.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale Withdraws Ethereum Futures ETF Application to SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229830</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229830/ethereum-futures-etf-grayscale-etf-withdrawal"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T23:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firm appears to sidestep an “approve futures, deny spot” ETF strategy that could have landed in the courts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kawailani Ozawa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin 'Epic Sat' That Sold for $2 Million Used to Inscribe Ordinals Art—With Grimes' AI Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229804</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229804/bitcoin-epic-sat-sold-2-million-inscribed-ordinals-grimes-ai-voice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T23:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Ordinals inscription featuring Grimes' AI-generated voice has been created as part of a Bitcoin art project—on an "epic" satoshi that cost over $2 million.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Runes Haven't Lived Up to the Hype? It's Still Too Early to Say]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229809</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229809/bitcoin-runes-havent-lived-up-hype-still-early"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T22:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The immediate hype around Bitcoin Runes tokens has cooled off, but proponents believe this is a natural and expected lull.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neuralink Safety Concerns Drove Co-Founder to Break Up With Elon Musk]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229816</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229816/neuralink-safety-concerns-drove-co-founder-to-break-up-with-elon-musk"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Neuralink is already testing its brain implants in humans, a scientist who helped start the company says he left to develop a less intrusive technology.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michelle Obama and RFK Jr. Have Equal Odds of Becoming Next President on Polymarket]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229803</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229803/michelle-obama-rfk-jr-presidential-win-odds-polymarket"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The former first lady has no plans to run for U.S. President, but oddsmakers are backing her as enthusiastically as the actual, crypto-friendly candidate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[House Republicans Move To Crush SEC's Anti-Crypto Banking Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229786</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229786/us-house-resolution-sec-bank-bulletin-crypto-custodians"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress is mulling a resolution aimed at rescinding guidance that proponents say drives U.S. banks away from holding digital assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethereum Game 'Fantasy Top' Pays $1.25M to Twitter Influencers It Turned Into NFT Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229775</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229775/ethereum-game-fantasy-top-pays-1-25m-twitter-influencers-turned-nft-cards"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto influencers got a share of $1.25 million in ETH and potentially millions in Blast Gold for being tradable "heroes" in Fantasy Top.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Defeating Biden Would Be Good for Bitcoin: Standard Chartered]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229761</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229761/trump-defeating-biden-good-bitcoin-standard-chartered"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysts at British bank Standard Chartered today said that a second Donald Trump presidency could do Bitcoin good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fan Jack Dorsey Takes Kendrick Lamar’s Side in Drake Beef]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229729</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229729/bitcoin-fan-jack-dorsey-kendrick-lamar-drake"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s winning the Kendrick and Drake lyrical war? Dorsey says it’s no contest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Gensler Says It’s Our Fault the SEC Appears So Focused on Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229736</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229736/gary-gensler-our-fault-sec-focused-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s an “outsized ratio of journalist questions and crypto journalists to market cap,” SEC Chair Gary Gensler claims.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robinhood CEO Decries 'Regulatory Onslaught' on Crypto, Vows to Fight SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229728</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229728/robinhood-ceo-decries-regulatory-onslaught-crypto-fight-sec"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though Robinhood Crypto thought its "safety-first" approach was distinct, the SEC said that enforcement action is on its way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Take In $217 Million for Second Consecutive Day of Net Gains]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229727</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229727/bitcoin-etfs-take-in-217-million-for-second-consecutive-day-of-net-gains"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every single fund saw another day in the green with net inflows yesterday—including Grayscale Bitcoin Trust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEC Crypto Crackdown: Every Company That Is Being Investigated]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229723</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229723/sec-crypto-crackdown-every-company-wells-notice"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T15:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC is taking aim at crypto companies in the United States. Here's who has disclosed a Wells Notice or is reportedly under investigation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sander Lutz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[University Speaker Takes Ayahuasca, Shills Bitcoin, Gets Booed]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229687</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229687/osu-commencement-speaker-bitcoin-ayahuasca"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ohio State University commencement speech included Bitcoin shilling and some cringe-worthy karaoke—all fueled by psychedelics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Gladwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch 2 Preview: Everything You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=197793</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/197793/nintendo-switch-2-rumors-leaks-latest-news"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: It's official: Nintendo has announced a Switch "successor." Here's everything we've heard so far about the Switch 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play Social Games, Earn Crypto Rewards: Solana Gaming App 'Cupcake' Launches]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229618</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229618/play-social-games-earn-crypto-rewards-solana-cupcake"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cupcake uses a TikTok-like feed of social games to help bring players deeper into the crypto world—and serves up Solana-based rewards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Demands Release of Employee Detained in Nigeria]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229630</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229630/binance-ceo-demands-release-of-employee-detained-in-nigeria"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T11:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binance CEO Richard Teng alleged that Tigran Gambaryan is being held in "a dangerous prison in order to control Binance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Graves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Brady Ridiculed for FTX and Crypto Investments in Netflix Roast]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229627</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229627/tom-brady-ridiculed-for-ftx-and-crypto-investments-in-netflix-roast"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Star NFL quarterback Tom Brady was ridiculed for his Bitcoin affinity and ties to bankrupt crypto exchange FTX during a live roast on Netflix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacy Elliott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's AI Ambitions Emerge Ahead of iPad Event]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229615</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229615/apple-ai-strategy-siri-xcode-music"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T00:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between Tuesday's iPad event and WWDC, AI is expected to play a part in nearly every corner of the Apple ecosystem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Ethereum Game ‘Fantasy Top’ Is Taking Over Crypto Twitter]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229595</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229595/why-ethereum-game-fantasy-top-taking-over-crypto-twitter"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantasy Top is like fantasy football, but with crypto influencers. The Blast game is the hot new thing amid a cooling crypto market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Wallet Maker Exodus Jumping Up to New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229589</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229589/bitcoin-wallet-exodus-nyse-exod-listing"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exodus says it is the only U.S. company that will have its EXOD common stock tokenized on the blockchain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale's Ethereum Fund Discount Steadies as ETF Deadline Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229584</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229584/grayscale-ethereum-ethe-fund-discount"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grayscale hopes to convert its Ethereum Trust to a spot ETH ETF, and current investors see opportunity in the uncertainty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>André Beganski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Is Down, But These Analysts Still Think BTC Hits $150K This Year]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229582</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229582/bitcoin-150000-price-doubling-18-months-bernstein"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AllianceBernstein join Standard Chartered analysts in seeing the price of BTC more than doubling in the next 18 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long-Term Bitcoin Investors Have Returned To HODLing: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229577</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229577/bitcoin-long-term-btc-holders-grow"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin whales eagerly bought the latest dip, and long-term investors are now patiently awaiting the next leg up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Throuvalas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BTC Sinks Lower]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rUBpJmbc/btc-sinks-lower"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HK ETF volumes disappoint at $11M, crypto sinks. US ETFs see another $52M outflow, 4th straight day. EigenLayer FUD after 5% non-transferable airdrop. EigenLayer also geoblocks USA for claims. 5K+ withdrawals after EigenLayer announcement. Microstrategy bought another $8M BTC in April. Miner revenue drops to 2023 lows. Consensys vs SEC litigation will take years: Cowen. SEC had been investigating ETH for a year. Gensler may have misled Congress with ETH stance.KMNO hits $363M on launch. Decentralised Rune airdrop opens at $102M. Friend Tech airdrop delayed until Thursday. NFTfi airdrop claim today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Red Week For Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/XVGCQVOH/a-very-red-week-for-crypto"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Majors hit locals lows, break key support levels. Liquidations hit $420M, funding remains neutral. ETFs saw $344M withdrawals in April. CZ gets 4-month jail sentence. FTX sells $232M locked SOL at ‘around $100’. Final integration of SOL Firedancer ‘well underway’. SOL, DOGE, XRP open interest down 51% in a month. BlackRock BUIDL largest tokenised treasury fund. Uniswap integrates with Robinhood connect. Stablecoin bill may be coming very soon. Gensler lied to Congress: McHenry. KSI steps back from crypto trading. Coinbase supports Lightning network. BCH creator arrested in Spain. EigenLayer sees 12K queued withdrawals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Full Send]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/zCrCMabk/solana-full-send"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOL leads majors higher, DEX volume flips ETH. ETH burn rate hits yearly low. BTC needs to reach $67k for a ‘higher high’. Robinhood receives Wells Notice from SEC. Only 10% of stablecoin transactions are real: Visa. May 15th will see corporate filings of BTC purchases. Hayes continues to OTC buy PENDLE. Cartier arrested for USDT money laundering. ENA up 20% on rumours of integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memecoin Bounce]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/yw5MtFvY/memecoin-bounce"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto volatile but bounces after dovish Fed speech. ETFs see record $563m outflow. BlackRock ETF sees first outflow in 77 days. BlackRock expects more institutions to buy BTC. BNP bank buys BlackRock ETF. BTC continues to sit below STH average cost. Coinbase earnings today. Tether made $4.5bn profit in Q1. MicroStrategy building identity protocol on Ordinals. Dorsey’s Block Inc investigated in US. BlackRock leads investment in RWA firm. STX Nakamoto upgrade delayed by 8 weeks. LayerZero 1st snapshot taken ahead of airdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin ETFs Are Back? $378 Million In Gains Marks Best Day In Over a Month]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229553</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229553/bitcoin-spot-etf-inflows-across-the-board-gbtc-turns-green"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every fund flipped green on Friday, as more traditional investors hold on to their BTC-based shares.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana's Dogwifhat Pumps as Bonk, Dogecoin and Other Meme Coins Lose Ground]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229555</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229555/meme-coin-wif-bonk-doge-pepe"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T19:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WIF is the only meme coin in the top 100 posting gains amid a broader crypto dip. Other popular meme coins are struggling to maintain momentum.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Antonio Lanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Mixers Pull Out of the US Amid Regulatory Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229543</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229543/bitcoin-coin-mixers-shut-americans-out"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy preserving crypto services are shutting down or shutting out American users as U.S. agencies turn up the pressure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Moves $44 Million After a Decade—Here's How Much It Gained]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229534</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229534/bitcoin-whale-moves-44-million-after-decade-how-much-gained"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unidentified Bitcoin whale just moved 687 BTC after it sat for more than a decade. Here's how much the value increased during that span.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mathew Di Salvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Price Jumps Nearly 5% as Bitcoin, Ethereum Lag Behind]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/?p=229533</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/229533/solana-price-jumps-bitcoin-ethereum-lag-behind"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T16:13:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solana is the biggest gainer in the top 10 cryptocurrencies on an otherwise quiet Monday morning, as Bitcoin and Ethereum tick down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little With Mike Demarais]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Ajrh0oiK/we-do-a-little-with-mike-demarais"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike dropped knowledge bombs from years of building in the trenches alongside some deep cuts on the early Williamsburg crypto mafia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eth Rally Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Gj7TMrbP/eth-rally-fails"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto falls, ETH/BTC rally again marks mini sell-off. Yen carry-trade implosion linked to worries. ETH gas fees hit 6-month lows. 3rd straight week of institutional outflows. Slowing BTC ETF flows are just a pause: Bernstein. BTC now on track for 5 red weeks in a row. BTC may have topped, could hit $35k: Brandt. ETFs may become big sellers: Bianco. Consensys list 4 reasons ETH isn’t a security. Rumours continue to grow of EigenLayer airdrop. Perp DEX volumes continue fall, GMX underperforms. Wallets begin to block US users after Samourai case. WLD in reported partnership talks with OpenAI. Large unlocks this week for SUI, PYTH & MEME.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Sasha Stiles’ Experiential, AI-Infused NFT Drop with Bang & Olufsen]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/6Vi2IgYj/inside-sasha-stiles-experiential-ai-infused-nft-drop-with-bang-olufsen"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a launch party for the collection in New York’s SoHo neighborhood, the artist broke down her latest art experiment, “Four Core Texts,” with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview: How 'Notcoin' Will Evolve After the NOT Token Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PprnGP14/interview-how-notcoin-will-evolve-after-the-not-token-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open Builders founder Sasha Plotvinov speaks with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about how he envisions Notcoin's expansion and evolution after the token drop—into something akin to the "Netflix of social, viral games."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/IGWg0R64/magic-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BTC stables at $66k, liquidations in narrow range. BTC funding again turns negative in bullish sign. ETFs net inflow after Grayscale moves to lower fees. BTC demand 5x vs supply post-halving: Bitfinex. SOL congestion issue now largely solved. Two SEC lawyers resign after ‘gross abuse of power’. Ripple fights to lower $2bn SEC fine. SAFE trades at $2.8bn FDV after OKX lists. MANEKI hits $150m on first day, China memes pump. Memecoins are ‘black hole you can’t ignore’. DeGods up 20%, may switch back to SOL. Magic Eden launches Runes platform ahead of time.  Louis Vuitton gifts Pharrell jacket to NFT holders. Melania Trump launches necklace with SOL NFTs. Hoodie Punk trades for $620K.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury Watches, Designer Shoes Will Soon Trade Like NFTs: Arianee CEO]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CSNQG2md/luxury-watches-designer-shoes-will-soon-trade-like-nfts-arianee-ceo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T20:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel sat down with Rug Radio founder Farokh and Decrypt’s Sander Lutz at NFT Paris to discuss everything from the future of on-chain luxury to the secret hack to finding the best restaurants in France.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin's Co-Creator Explains the Game's Token Delay—And When to Expect NOT Now]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/7Zx33xo5/notcoins-co-creator-explains-the-games-token-delayand-when-to-expect-not-now"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notcoin co-creator Sasha Plotvinov spoke with Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai to discuss why the NOT token launch was pushed back from the original 4/20 target, when to expect the listing, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TON’s Justin Hyun Breaks Down The Importance of USDT Coming to Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/ODQI6ACA/tons-justin-hyun-breaks-down-the-importance-of-usdt-coming-to-telegram"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Token 2049 in Dubai, The Open Network’s director of investments sat down with Decrypt’s Sander Lutz to discuss what he sees as the game-changing integration of USDT onto TON, and his plans for getting Telegram’s 900 million users to start using crypto in the immediate future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Influencer Ansem Explains His Meme Coin Thesis and Why He’s Bullish on Bitcoin Runes]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/u9DHFoK0/crypto-influencer-ansem-explains-his-meme-coin-thesis-and-why-hes-bullish-on-bitcoin-runes"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T21:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ansem, the crypto trader who's amassed a sizable following on the back of meme coin Dogwifhat (WIF) and other calls, chats with Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz at Token 2049 Dubai about his meme coin thesis, why he's bullish on Bitcoin Runes, and what he sees ahead for the crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Sander Lutz Braves the Dubai Floods for a Crypto Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/mtjVHGa3/decrypts-sander-lutz-braves-the-dubai-floods-for-a-crypto-conference"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz reports from Dubai amid a historic storm that flooded the famed city, trudging through the streets to complete his essential task: Attending the Token 2049 crypto conference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold Beats Its All Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/6ULgUKVk/gold-beats-its-all-time-high"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T09:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) maintains its trend of reaching higher lows amidst choppy market conditions. Exchange-traded funds (ETFs) witness another influx of $125 million. There's anticipation of Hong Kong approving ETFs for both Bitcoin and Ethereum (ETH) come Monday. Notable institutional investor BlackRock shows interest in Bitcoin. Recent filings reveal increased Bitcoin purchases by banks. A Bitcoin-friendly political party secures victory in the South Korean election. Analyst Kang predicts Bitcoin could surge to $80-100k by May. Meanwhile, Ethereum sees accumulation by stablecoin whales on the rise. A new Ethereum Improvement Proposal (EIP) aims to streamline signing requests. Solana (SOL) experiences a resurgence in activity, reaching yearly highs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA’s Next Deep Space Mission Won’t Use Artificial Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/0WGP33Rp/nasas-next-deep-space-mission-wont-use-artificial-intelligence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T18:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thursday, Decrypt Media visited NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory in Pasadena, CA to meet with the Engineering team behind the Europa Clipper before its launch to Jupiter's Europa moon in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Do A Little with Weesh]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/LnaOT9bF/we-do-a-little-with-weesh"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T07:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s episode, we did a little something different. We took the man who is usually behind the camera and put him in front of it. We sat down with our producer Weesh to dive into how in fell in love with art and became a collector, how he met Andy and fun childhood memories together, his biggest wins in crypto, and so much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside VanEck’s Crypto Takeover of the New York Stock Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/9YAY4wGD/inside-vanecks-crypto-takeover-of-the-new-york-stock-exchange"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds collide as Decrypt reporter Sander Lutz heads to the floor of the NYSE to witness a special closing bell ceremony hosted by VanEck in honor of Web3. Featuring Choose Rich Nick, VanEck Head of Web3 Matt Bartlett, and more!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>