<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-12-22T11:12:43.407Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-12-22T11:12:43.407Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: Nigerian Currency Plunges to New Low Versus the US Dollar]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74837dceaf</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/report-nigerian-currency-plunges-to-new-low-versus-the-us-dollar/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T11:10:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The official exchange rate of the Nigerian currency versus the U.S. dollar recently plunged to a record low of 1,248 naira for every greenback. The governor of the Central Bank of Nigeria has told the country’s legislators that he sees the foreign exchange market stabilizing in 2024. 
 
Official Rate Nearly Matches the Parallel Market Rate
 
On Dec. 19, the Nigerian currency, the naira, briefly plunged to a record low of 1,248 naira for every U.S. dollar before recovering to close the day at 845 naira for every greenback. According to a Reuters report, the currency’s fall nearly matched the naira-to-dollar rates traders offer on the unofficial foreign exchange market.
 
When Nigerian President Bola Ahmed Tinubu assumed office in late May, the Central Bank of Nigeria (CBN) immediately aband…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto users to reach almost $1B in 2024, analysts predict]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126950/Crypto-users-to-reach-almost-1B-in-2024-analysts-predict</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126950/Crypto-users-to-reach-almost-1B-in-2024-analysts-predict"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T11:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitfinex analysts said the number of users could jump to between 850 and 950 million next year if bullish market conditions continue in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk anticipates mid-2024 launch for X’s in-app payment services]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126930/Elon-Musk-anticipates-mid-2024-launch-for-Xs-in-app-payment-services</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126930/Elon-Musk-anticipates-mid-2024-launch-for-Xs-in-app-payment-services"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Mogul Elon Musk’s latest venture, ‘X,’ is poised to roll out in-app payment services on its social media platform around mid-2024. However, the integration of cryptocurrencies, previously a subject of speculation and excitement among crypto enthusiasts, now appears to be a remote...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocket Lab Stock Up 17.3% After $515M Agreement with US Gov]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126943/Rocket-Lab-Stock-Up-173-After-515M-Agreement-with-US-Gov</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126943/Rocket-Lab-Stock-Up-173-After-515M-Agreement-with-US-Gov"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocket Lab's shares surged 17.2% in premarket trading on the reports that the company secured a $515 million contract a US government customer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Large Number of Options Expire Today in Bitcoin and Ethereum! What Does the Data Point to?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126938/A-Large-Number-of-Options-Expire-Today-in-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-What-Does-the-Data-Point-to</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126938/A-Large-Number-of-Options-Expire-Today-in-Bitcoin-and-Ethereum-What-Does-the-Data-Point-to"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:53:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, 25,000 Bitcoin (BTC) and 217,000 Ethereum (ETH) options will expire. What does it mean for prices? Continue Reading: A Large Number of Options Expire Today in Bitcoin and Ethereum! What Does the Data Point to?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert reveals key reasons behind Ripple’s (XRP) decline since 2017]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126929/Expert-reveals-key-reasons-behind-Ripples-XRP-decline-since-2017</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126929/Expert-reveals-key-reasons-behind-Ripples-XRP-decline-since-2017"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Due to its fluctuating fortunes, Ripple (XRP) has become a topic of keen interest. Once a promising contender in the digital currency market, Ripple has faced various challenges that have impacted its performance and market position. Historical performance and recent developments Since its...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memeinator puts meme tokens on their toes as investment potential drives presale]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126909/Memeinator-puts-meme-tokens-on-their-toes-as-investment-potential-drives-presale</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126909/Memeinator-puts-meme-tokens-on-their-toes-as-investment-potential-drives-presale"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memeinator aims to destroy weak and non-original meme tokens. Memeinator has utilities in gaming, NFTs, and staking. The project’s presale delivers 132% ROI with a bonus on token purchases during Christmas. Think of this: The meme sector rose to a peak of $36 billion this year from a market cap...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hong Kong says it’s ready to accept spot crypto ETF applications]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126915/Hong-Kong-says-its-ready-to-accept-spot-crypto-ETF-applications</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126915/Hong-Kong-says-its-ready-to-accept-spot-crypto-ETF-applications"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spain sees 56% surge in registered crypto firms in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126907/Spain-sees-56-surge-in-registered-crypto-firms-in-2023</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126907/Spain-sees-56-surge-in-registered-crypto-firms-in-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTBC Flying Oyster’s Ambitious Roster Reshuffling Rocks the PCS Esports Scene]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126911/CTBC-Flying-Oysters-Ambitious-Roster-Reshuffling-Rocks-the-PCS-Esports-Scene</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126911/CTBC-Flying-Oysters-Ambitious-Roster-Reshuffling-Rocks-the-PCS-Esports-Scene"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Skyrockets By 161,540%, Here’s What Behind It]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74837a59ce</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-skyrockets-by-161540/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu (SHIB), a popular Ethereum-based meme coin has sent the cryptocurrency community and investors into a frenzy as its burn initiative continues to see notable token burns over the past month. 
 
Shiba Inu Performs Another 8 Billion SHIB Burn
 
Data from Shibburn has revealed an impressive rise in the Shiba Inu token burn rate. The platform shows that the burn rate has increased by a whopping 161,540% over the past 24 hours.
 
The rise in the cryptocurrency’s burn rate was due to the massive token burn that was carried out by the Shiba Inu team. The team made yet another significant burn, which saw over 8 billion SHIB tokens being destroyed. 
 
 
According to the platform tracker, the team burnt approximately 8,533,564,693 SHIB valued at $90,711. The data indicates that the team sen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Godspower Owie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency scammers exploit MS Drainer to siphon $59 million: Details]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126885/Cryptocurrency-scammers-exploit-MS-Drainer-to-siphon-59-million-Details</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126885/Cryptocurrency-scammers-exploit-MS-Drainer-to-siphon-59-million-Details"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scammers have orchestrated a sophisticated operation using a cryptocurrency wallet-draining service known as “MS Drainer,” extracting a staggering $59 million from approximately 63,210 victims over the past nine months. The modus operandi involves leveraging Google and Twitter ads to lure...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NRG Head Coach Criticizes LCS Management’s Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126886/NRG-Head-Coach-Criticizes-LCS-Managements-Communication</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126886/NRG-Head-Coach-Criticizes-LCS-Managements-Communication"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin (BTC) Just Reached New All-Time High]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126894/Bitcoin-BTC-Just-Reached-New-All-Time-High</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126894/Bitcoin-BTC-Just-Reached-New-All-Time-High"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin's network is moving without any stops, reaching massive new threshold]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaiko Lists Factors Behind the 2023 Crypto Market Trends]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126896/Kaiko-Lists-Factors-Behind-the-2023-Crypto-Market-Trends</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126896/Kaiko-Lists-Factors-Behind-the-2023-Crypto-Market-Trends"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gold-Backed Token: How Does It Work?]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126897/Gold-Backed-Token-How-Does-It-Work</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126897/Gold-Backed-Token-How-Does-It-Work"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambitious Layer-3 Smart Clearing Protocol Yellow Network Launches Incentivized Testnet In Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126887/Ambitious-Layer-3-Smart-Clearing-Protocol-Yellow-Network-Launches-Incentivized-Testnet-In-Beta</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126887/Ambitious-Layer-3-Smart-Clearing-Protocol-Yellow-Network-Launches-Incentivized-Testnet-In-Beta"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The automated smart clearing protocol creator Yellow Network has announced the launch of its Layer-3 testnet in beta, along with an incentivized program that will reward participants who help to test the network’s capabilities and provide feedback.  Yellow Network is a cross-chain, peer-to-peer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[December sees Bitcoin whales selling off despite market rally]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126884/December-sees-Bitcoin-whales-selling-off-despite-market-rally</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126884/December-sees-Bitcoin-whales-selling-off-despite-market-rally"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Skyrockets By 161,540%, Here’s What Behind It]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126881/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Skyrockets-By-161540-Heres-What-Behind-It</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126881/Shiba-Inu-Burn-Rate-Skyrockets-By-161540-Heres-What-Behind-It"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating Crypto Flash Crashes: Strategies, Analysis, and Insights for Investors]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126875/Navigating-Crypto-Flash-Crashes-Strategies-Analysis-and-Insights-for-Investors</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126875/Navigating-Crypto-Flash-Crashes-Strategies-Analysis-and-Insights-for-Investors"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto flash crashes reflect a volatile landscape, innovation, and sometimes unexpected drop in prices. Just like their counterparts in financial markets, these are situations whereby there is a quick and massive fall in the price of a virtual currency over a shorter duration. Flash crashes are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do NOT Underestimate What Is ABOUT TO HAPPEN - HUGE Bitcoin Supply Shock Will Change The Market]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126917/Do-NOT-Underestimate-What-Is-ABOUT-TO-HAPPEN-HUGE-Bitcoin-Supply-Shock-Will-Change-The-Market</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126917/Do-NOT-Underestimate-What-Is-ABOUT-TO-HAPPEN-HUGE-Bitcoin-Supply-Shock-Will-Change-The-Market"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unfulfilled Promises of 2023: A Year of Missed Technological Milestones]]></title>
        <id>https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126859/The-Unfulfilled-Promises-of-2023-A-Year-of-Missed-Technological-Milestones</id>
        <link href="https://cryptopanic.com/news/19126859/The-Unfulfilled-Promises-of-2023-A-Year-of-Missed-Technological-Milestones"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As 2023 draws to a close, it is evident that the year has been marked by significant advancements in technology, particularly in AI and social media. However, amidst the flurry of breakthroughs and innovations, there have been notable omissions and unfulfilled promises that have left many...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget Announces Support and Development Plan for Bitcoin Ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748366d84c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/bitget-announces-support-and-development-plan-for-bitcoin-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bitget  
Wallet, a Web3 trading wallet, has unveiled a plan focusing on product  
research, development, and increased investments. This initiative aims to  
provide users with enhanced trading options and an improved overall asset  
management experience within the Bitcoin ecosystem.
Bitcoin  
Ecosystem Services: Bitget Wallet's Diverse Offerings.
Bitget  
Wallet's plan encompasses a broad range of services centered around the Bitcoin  
ecosystem. This includes support for BTC asset management, cross-chain swaps,  
on-ramping for EOA and MPC wallets, Taproot compatibility, and asset transfers  
for BRC-20 tokens and NFTs. The platform also facilitates users with insights  
into macro and micro market trends through Bitget Swap and offers interaction  
with popular projects via its DApp br…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Payment Provider Alchemy Partners Payment Processor Worldpay]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483624e15</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/crypto-payment-provider-alchemy-partners-payment-processor-worldpay/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T09:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fiat-crypto payment gateway Alchemy Pay recently revealed that it has partnered with Worldpay in a move that gives its users to access Worldpay’s Visa and Mastercard payment rails via its on and off-ramp service. Alchemy said its users will now experience better efficiency and customer experience when using their respective credit and debit cards to trade cryptocurrencies.
 
Worldpay to Support Alchemy’s NFT Checkout
 
Alchemy Pay, the fiat-crypto payment gateway, has joined forces with the payments processing firm Worldpay “to amplify its payment channels and elevate its payment capabilities.” According to Alchemy, this partnership allows its users to access Worldpay’s Visa and Mastercard payment rails via its on and off-ramp service.
 
In a statement released on Dec. 19, Alchemy said…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terence Zimwara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF’s Gem Shines Bright: Solana 20-Month High Makes It Crypto’s Next Big Thing]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74836d925a</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/solana-20-mo-high-makes-it-cryptos-next-big-thing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T09:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2022, the cryptocurrency realm encountered a major hurdle with the collapse of FTX, triggering industry-wide repercussions. This adversity posed challenges for Solana, one of its standout blockchains, disrupting its course.
 
Known for its innovation and tech strength, Solana had received a lot of praise, especially from important figures like the former FTX big boss Sam Bankman-Fried.
 
But when the crypto exchange unexpectedly fell, a platform closely linked to Solana, it brought a gloomy cloud over the blockchain’s previously positive future.
 
 
Solana Emerges Strong: 800% Recovery
 
Today, a lot of investors in digital assets are positioning SOL as the cryptocurrency industry’s success story. This is because of its incredible recovery from last year’s more than 90% loss.
 
The valu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solana Nears $100 as Meme Coin Frenzy Continues to Drive Rally]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483696c9a</id>
        <link href="https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2023/12/22/solana-nears-100-as-meme-coin-frenzy-continues-to-drive-rally/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=rss&amp;utm_campaign=headlines"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T08:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Value locked on the blockchain’s applications has more than doubled since November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaurya Malwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Javier Milei's Move: Argentina Legalizes Crypto amid Economic Challenges]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483567cc6</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/president-javier-mileis-move-argentina-legalizes-crypto-amid-economic-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T08:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To  
address economic challenges, Argentina's new government, led by President  
Javier Milei, has officially legalized the use of Bitcoin and other  
cryptocurrencies for contract settlements and payments. This announcement was  
made by Diana Mondino, the country's Minister of Foreign Affairs, International  
Trade and Worship, on December 21.
Strategic  
Response to Hyperinflation
This  
move is part of a broader economic reform and deregulation initiative by the  
Argentine government. While the decree does not explicitly mention  
cryptocurrencies, it includes provisions that grant individuals and businesses  
the freedom to choose their preferred mode of payment, even if it's not  
recognized as legal tender in Argentina.
The  
decision to embrace cryptocurrencies is seen as a strate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tareq Sikder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Offers New Virtual Currency Guidance]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748356865e</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/new-york-offers-new-virtual-currency-guidance/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T08:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Nov. 15, 2023, the New York Department of Financial Services (NYDFS) issued new standards for virtual currency (coin) listings and delistings. These new regulations apply to Bitlicensees and limited-purpose trust companies and include business model considerations for virtual currency entities (VCEs), updated risk assessment expectations for VCEs, new advance notification requirements, and updated definitions.
 
The following editorial was written by guest authors Wyatt Noble and Michael Handelsman for Kelman.Law
 
VCE Coin-Listing Policies
 
Under the latest guidance VCEs with prior approvals for coin-listing policies must receive NYDFS approval for both their coin-listing and coin-delisting policies before self-certifying any coins. Once NYDFS approves both policies, VCEs may self-cer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guest Author</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Connection: Coinbase Clinches Crypto License In Latest Global Push]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74835e7b92</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/coinbase-clinches-crypto-license-in-france/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T06:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase recently made a calculated strategic step to expand into European markets by acquiring a virtual asset service provider (VASP) license from the Financial Markets Authority (AMF) of France.
 
The acquisition of the VASP license from the French regulatory authority establishes Coinbase as an acknowledged and adherent participant in the French financial sector.
 
Based on trading volume, CoinGecko ranks Coinbase as the third-largest cryptocurrency exchange, with only Bybit and the similarly registered Binance surpassing it.
 
 
Coinbase Aims For Compliance Excellence
 
According to a statement released by the firm on Thursday, Coinbase will be able to provide custody of digital assets, purchase or sell digital assets using legal cash, trade digital assets against other digital assets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Encila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is France Becoming EU’s Crypto Hub? Coinbase’s VASP Registration Indicates So]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74835fb59c</id>
        <link href="https://www.financemagnates.com//cryptocurrency/is-france-becoming-eus-crypto-hub-coinbases-vasp-registration-indicates-so/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T06:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France is becoming a favorite for crypto firms as Coinbase becomes the latest to obtain a visual asset service provider (VASP) registration in the country. With this, the American exchange can offer its “full suite of retail, institutional, and ecosystem products and services to users in France.”
Crypto Demand in France Is High
The confirmation from Coinbase yesterday (Thursday) came on the same day Circle, a stablecoin issuer, announced its VASP registration in France. Coinbase is a stakeholder in Circle, known for its USD-pegged USDC stablecoin.
“Achieving VASP status in France allows us to continue to grow globally in the best possible way, onboarding the next 1 billion people into crypto while ensuring consumer’s assets are secure and that compliance is prioritized,” said Daniel Seifer…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnab Shome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘If You Want to Understand Bitcoin’s Value, Look at Politicians’ Hate Toward It,’ Says Sean Ono Lennon]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74835fcd0d</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/if-you-want-to-understand-bitcoins-value-look-at-politicians-hate-toward-it-says-sean-ono-lennon/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T06:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sean Ono Lennon, the acclaimed American-British musician and son of Beatles icon John Lennon, revisited the subject of bitcoin on social media platform X, formerly known as Twitter. He poignantly observed, “If you want to understand how valuable bitcoin truly is, look how much our politicians hate it.” Previously, Lennon has shared insights about the leading digital currency, highlighting that it offers him a sense of hope amidst an “ocean of destruction.”
 
Sean Ono Lennon Speaks Out on Bitcoin’s Value Amidst Political Pushback
 
A versatile artist, Lennon, who is also a part of The Claypool Lennon Delirium and the Plastic Ono Band, has previously expressed his views on bitcoin (BTC). In 2020, he described bitcoin as a tool that “empowers individuals,” and shared that it brought him “more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Redman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ministry of Information and Technology of China to Formulate New Web3 Strategy]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483414994</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/ministry-of-information-and-technology-of-china-to-formulate-new-web3-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T05:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ministry of Information and Technology of China has agreed to formulate a new strategy for the Web3 field to improve the state of the industry in China. The initiative comes as an answer to a proposal made at the 14th Chinese People’s Political Consultative Conference (CPPCC) National Committee, aiming to strengthen Web3’s condition in the country.
Ministry of Information and Technology of China Will Develop a New Web3 Strategy
The Chinese government plans to develop a new Web3 strategy for the country. In a recently released document, the Ministry of Industry and Information Technology answers a petition by Wu Jiezhuang, a member of the Chinese People’s Political Consultative Conference (CPPCC) National Committee, that seeks to promote the development of the Web3 industry in China.
Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive Ripple CTO Predictions: Five Catalysts That Could Shape 2024’s Crypto Landscape]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74834973bc</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/ripple-cto-drops-five-predictions-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T03:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post on X (formerly Twitter), David Schwartz, Ripple’s Chief Technology Officer (CTO), shared his predictions for the blockchain industry in 2024 and beyond. 
 
Interoperability As Catalysts For DeFi Growth On The XRPL
 
According to Schwartz, the convergence of artificial intelligence (AI) and blockchain will revolutionize cybersecurity and financial services. AI, according to Schwartz, will play a pivotal role in ensuring blockchain security, empowering accurate market insights and automated trading.
 
Additionally, AI chatbots, like those on the XRP Ledger (XRPL), will simplify development processes, fostering global innovation and financial inclusion.
 
Schwartz also anticipates that real-world asset (RWA) tokenization will drive the blockchain economy, with a particular fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ronaldo Marquez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bank of China Completes First Precious Metal Digital Yuan Settlement]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e748349ae6b</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bank-of-china-completes-first-precious-metal-digital-yuan-settlement/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T03:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shanghai branch of the Bank of China has completed the first settlement of precious metals using the digital yuan. The transaction, finalized on December 19, allowed the Shanghai Gold Exchange to close a $14 million precious metal trade after receiving the funds overseas, according to local media reports.
Bank of China Completes First Cross Borders Precious Gold Transaction With Digital Yuan
The Shanghai branch of the Bank of China announced that it has completed the first precious metal settlement using the digital yuan, the Chinese central bank digital currency (CBDC). The bank worked closely with the Shanghai Gold Exchange to transact the funds received overseas with the digital yuan. The transaction involved paying $14 million in exchange for undisclosed precious metals.
According …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Highlights Crypto’s Impact on Economic Freedom — Calls Crypto ‘the Future of Money’]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483324207</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/coinbase-ceo-highlights-cryptos-impact-on-economic-freedom-calls-crypto-the-future-of-money/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T02:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Brian Armstrong has highlighted that crypto isn’t just here to say but it’s the future of money. Emphasizing that cryptocurrency “gives people economic freedom, ensuring access to their own money and fair participation in the economy ungated by powerful legacy institutions,” he detailed: “The industry has turned the page on the unlawful behavior that distracted from its progress; compliant growth is in.”
 
‘Cryptocurrency Isn’t Just Here to Stay’
 
The CEO of cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase (Nasdaq: COIN), Brian Armstrong, published a blog post titled “The future of money is here — and it’s crypto” on the company’s website Tuesday.
 
He explained that after a “massive market correction,” crypto has witnessed a 90% increase in value this year, accompanied by a 60% surge in vol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Helms</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Liquidity Across Exchanges Remain Low, Will BTC ETF Providers Face Challenges?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483324054</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/bitcoin-liquidity-low-btc-etf-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T02:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CEO of Medici, Edward Boyle, has raised concerns about the low liquidity of Bitcoin (BTC) across leading spot cryptocurrency exchanges like Binance and Coinbase. 
 
Boyle believes this could pose challenges for Bitcoin exchange-traded funds (ETFs) providers, especially when they launch in the United States in the coming weeks, subject to the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) approval.
 
Bitcoin Liquidity On Spot Exchanges Low After FTX Collapse
 
In a post on December 12, Boyle cites Kaiko data that shows that there is generally only $200 million in Bitcoin trading volume within 1% of the spot price. Accordingly, this data means that if a large buyer or seller wants to execute a significant trade, they could impact Bitcoin prices. 
 
However, for those wishing to liquidate or bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dalmas Ngetich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital Seeking to Score Deals From Defunct Cryptocurrency Companies]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74833bcb39</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/galaxy-digital-seeking-to-score-deals-from-defunct-cryptocurrency-companies/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T00:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Galaxy Digital, a digital assets and blockchain financial services company, is seeking to score deals with defunct cryptocurrency companies to acquire their assets. According to reports, the company is eyeing FTX’s venture capital portfolio, which has a sizable stake in artificial intelligence (AI) disruptor Anthropic, among others.
Galaxy Digital Aiming to Complete Bankruptcy Sales for Disgraced Crypto Businesses
Galaxy Digital, a cryptocurrency and blockchain financial services company, is targeting the asset sales of crypto businesses to grow its capital. According to a recent FT report, the firm led by American billionaire Mike Novogratz would be eyeing other crypto-bankrupt companies to facilitate the sale of their assets.
The company, which was selected to sell FTX’s tokens, saw its …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Goschenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Historic Crypto Seizure: Silk Road’s 69,370 Bitcoin Now In US Government Hands]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e7483215945</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/historic-crypto-seizure-silk-road-69370-bitcoin-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T23:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crypto world witnessed a significant chapter close on December 20, 2023, as the United States Court of Appeals finalized the forfeiture of 69,370 Bitcoin. This decision, stemming from the notorious Silk Road case, marks one of the most substantial forfeitures in the annals of digital currency.
 
Final Chapter In Silk Road Saga
 
Silk Road, a now-defunct dark web marketplace, became synonymous with BTC in its early days. Since the shutdown of this notorious dark web marketplace, US authorities have been actively working to confiscate the crypto assets amassed during its operation
 
 
Their efforts have seen significant progress, leading to the recent development reported. On Wednesday, the Ninth Circuit US District Court of Appeals confirmed the transfer of the seized Bitcoin into feder…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samuel Edyme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Inscription Frenzy Hits EVM Blockchains]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74832c597a</id>
        <link href="https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-inscription-frenzy-hits-evm-blockchains/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T23:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of Bitcoin’s inscription phenomenon, Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM)-compatible chains are experiencing a surge in similar practices, leading to unexpected service outages and a little confusion over their use.
 
EVM Chains Face Surge in Token Inscriptions
 

 
Over the past year, Bitcoin inscriptions have surged in popularity due to the advent of Ordinals, significantly impacting the Bitcoin blockchain. This controversial method has led to a sharp increase in transaction costs and a congested mempool, reigniting debates reminiscent of 2017’s block size war.
 

 
The phenomenon has now extended to Ethereum and other EVM-compatible chains. Despite the initial skepticism about introducing inscriptions on smart contract-capable blockchains, the demand for EVM inscriptions has been …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Sencil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiba Inu Burn Rate Sees Another 420% Spike, What’s Driving It?]]></title>
        <id>http://www.inoreader.com/article/3a9c6e74832b45ff</id>
        <link href="https://bitcoinist.com/shiba-inu-burn-rate-420/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T22:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Shiba Inu community is on a roll with burning SHIB as the initiative continues to see spike after spike. The burn rate has seen a significant increase once again in the last 24 hours as millions of tokens were sent to the burn address.
 
SHIB Burn Rate Spike 420%
 
According to data from the Shibburn website, the SHIB burn rate saw another 421% increase in the last 24 hours. This spike comes as Shiba Inu community members change from their pattern from the previous day, which saw only a little over 1 million tokens burned.
 
 
This time around, there have been more than 5.3 million tokens incinerated, which brought about the 421% spike reported by the website. Interestingly, the total burns came from less than 10 addresses. As the burn tracking website shows, there have been only six b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Matherson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>